- Woo.
Oh.
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
- Yeah, it was good
to see you, man.
It's been about
a year and a half
since the Tokyo Olympics, man.
- No it hasn't.
It was like six months ago.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
We're in 2021, man.
- What?
Damn, you're right.
I don't know
what's wrong with me.
My short term memory.
- Short term memory?
You on that stuff, ain't you?
- What stuff?
- You what I'm talkin' about.
- Hey, man, we on TV.
- Okay.
- Three, two, one.
- 2021, what a year!
After spending 2020
in lockdown,
America was ready
to get down.
It was a 365 day
balls to the wall,
anything goes rager.
- This is absolutely insane!
- It was a year that
we flipped out and wigged out.
When some of us
drank too much beer,
others drank too much Kool-Aid.
According to the Chinese zodiac,
2021 was the year of the ox.
And boy, was it ever.
But it was also
the year of the goat,
the year the cat.
- I'm not a cat.
- Year of the squid,
the year of the seagull,
and definitely not
the year of the tiger.
In 2021,
the Bidens were welcomed in,
and the Cuomos were tossed out.
Facebook got Meta,
and this fool's ass got wetter.
Stadiums were packed,
some people got smacked,
Bennifer was back and
what this kid saw was wack.
It's the year Ted Cruz
fled to Cancun
and Captain Kirk
went to the goddamn moon.
- Oh, wow.
- Millions refused to get a job
and one desperately
tried to keep his job.
Some believed in Ted Lasso,
others believed Q,
and the world of social media
brought us these two.
- I'mma just island boy.
I'mma just island boy.
- Yeah, 2021 was poppin',
it was something to see.
Now, to make sense of it all
is Kevin Hart and Snoop D-o-gg.
- "Welcome to 2021 and Done",
I'm your homie,
Big Snoop D-o-gg,
The Dog Father, The Player,
The Coach, The Pimp,
The Liaison, The Executive,
The Money Maker,
The Producer of Algorithm,
and so on and so on.
- And I'm Kevin.
A.K.A., long, little feet,
uh, big nose, happy mouth.
Uh, long forehead,
little structure, uh,
big knuckles, small hands.
Um, that's all I got, Snoop.
- I like that.
You know, Kev, I'm just glad
we survived another brutal year.
I guess 2021 was better
than 2020,
but that's just like saying
the Jets are better
than the Lions.
[laughing]
- The Lions suck!
Yeah.
Now, uh, listen,
it's been a strange year,
and on this show,
we're gonna look back at
the stuff that you remember
and the shit that
you wish you could forget.
- Yeah, yeah.
Let's get into it.
It's time for
Shaking My Damn Headline.
- Oh, I like that.
Now, the year started off
with so much promise,
but less than a week in.
Well, it went off the rails
when a bunch of tourists
showed up for a field trip
in D.C.,
hoping to meet with
their congressmen
and hang with Mike Pence.
- Hang with Mike Pence?
Or hang Mike Pence?
- Oh my god.
- Let's take a look at
this white hot mess.
Oh, look at this.
This is when they
acted a fool.
January sixth, I remember
this like yesterday.
- Look at this.
- Just shit.
- Just madness.
- What are you doing?
- Taking over the Capitol.
- Look at this dumb ass.
Look at you.
What you gonna do?
He got a bongo in his arm.
He's got a bongo on him!
This really makes you
just think like--
- I want him to fall.
- -what the fuck
are you doing, man?
- I need somebody to fall, Kev.
This is not right.
- Look at this.
Look at this idiot.
Oh! Oh!
[laughing]
Oh, come on.
Come on.
- Now that was an Olympic
highlight for your ass.
- Don't you lose your grip.
God damn.
- There was one true hero
that day.
Capitol Police Officer
Eugene Goodman,
who led the mob away from
the Senate chamber.
Roll the clip.
- Don't you come up-
don't you come up, boy.
- Boy.
- You see this little stick?
- All right,
I'mma go over here.
- That motherfucker get bigger
every time it hits your head.
- Hey, don't you go further.
Hey, hey, hey!
Get your ass back, bitch.
- See, that was
the smartest move
he made right there,
'cause there was political
people in that room.
And he knew he had to deter 'em
to go this way.
That was the smartest move
right there.
See, that-- he from the streets,
because he knew
how to psych them out.
They didn't even pay attention
to that room.
They started following him.
That was a great,
great strategic move.
- Yeah, he better than me.
I would have got 'em
off my ass.
I was like,
"That's who you want.
"You want the people in there.
Go that way."
That's exactly
what I would have did.
Yeah, that man
trying to be a hero.
Sometimes you got to
worry about yourself, man.
- That's a fact.
I think that clip would be
way more gangster
if we reverse that.
Look at him now.
Get your bitch ass outta here.
- What would I say?
- Got the stick.
- Want me to crack
your head, cuz?
- Get your motherfucking ass
outta here right now.
Back up, boy.
- Back up, bitch.
Yeah.
- I got this.
Don't even worry about
what's going on out here.
Y'all just stay in there.
I got this shit.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, get on back,
and I'm gonna run
these motherfuckers outta here.
Matter of fact, I'mma back
that nigga get outta here.
[laughter]
- Oh! Oh!
Yeah, kiss my ass.
That's what y'all gonna do.
Everybody.
By the way,
that's one of those moments
where you really look around and
you got the feeling to go,
"Why did I take this job?"
Like, when all those people
standing there,
you look and realize
you're the only one.
He been the only one there
for years.
He been only one there
for years,
and it's been the best job ever
'cause nothing's ever happened.
- No.
- On that day, he was like,
"Ain't this about a bitch."
"Where Charles at?
Charles--
- He kept doing-
he kept doing this too.
Pushing that little thing.
Weren't nobody
on the other end.
- Nobody-nobody-
he kept doing this.
What I say--
"Hey, Charles.
"Hey, Charles."
- What, nigga?
I'm at McDonald's.
- Charles, I need you to act
like you in the other room.
- What you want, nigga,
number five or four?
I need you to get
your black ass back up here.
[laughter]
- Hey.
All right.
These insurrectionists
not only looted laptops,
but one dude try to walk out
with a podium.
Look at this right here.
- Nah, that's not a podium,
Kev, that's actually a lectern.
- Is it?
- Yeah, it's a lectern.
- How the fuck
do you know that, Snoop?
- Two things about me, Kev--
I smoke and I know things.
I just can't believe
that this guy would, like,
try to smash and grab America.
This is a country,
not a Louis Vuitton store,
asshole.
- I mean,
it's just ridiculous.
Where's he going put that?
The insurrections led to
Trump's second impeachment,
and Trump lawyered up.
The only lawyer missing
from the dream team
was the cat right here.
- We're trying to-we're trying
to- can you hear me, judge?
- I can hear you.
I think it's a filter--
- It is.
I don't know how to remove it.
- I don't know
how to remove it, judge,
but can you hear me?
It's some thing.
My kids put this damn emoji
on my face.
I don't know how to move,
but, uh--
- I'm not a cat.
- That-- if you're live,
I'm not a cat.
He said-he said,
"I'm not a cat, judge.
"I promise I'm not a cat."
"I don't know how to get this--"
- Who the hell does--
- I don't know how to get this
off the computer, judge.
- I'm not a cat.
- I'm not being an asshole,
but this is not a cat
talking to you.
Oh.
After the impeachment,
Joe Biden was sworn in
as president.
The inauguration was
a star-studded affair
with J.Lo in Chanel.
- Nice.
- Oh my god, look at this.
Lady Gaga, she was
in a Schiaparelli.
- Mm-hmm, fashion.
- And Bernie Sanders.
Bernie Sanders was in
whoever the fuck
made these mittens.
Look at this here.
Look at that.
Look at those mittens.
- Nigga's mask on wrong.
He got his mask
to the wrong side.
What's going on, buddy?
- But the real star of the show
is the young poet laureate
Amanda Gorman.
Play the clip.
- The successors of a country
in a time
where a skinny black girl
descended from slaves
and raised by a single mother
can dream of becoming president,
only to find herself
reciting for one.
- Very strong.
- Strong.
- Come on, man.
- I mean, listen,
that's what our young
Black girls need to see.
They need to see--
- Black girl power!
- ...in positions of power.
That's a moment
in history right there.
- Great work, baby girl.
- Absolutely.
- We commend you on the show.
In 2021, Mother Earth
stopped all of us in our tracks.
Fires, hurricanes,
record-setting temperatures.
But not even a historic flood
in New York
could stop fries
from getting delivered on time.
Roll the clip.
- That's right.
- Gotta love it.
- I'm not gonna fucking ing
get a bad rating.
You want me to get
fucking two stars?
- Oh, he gonna get
a bad rating, nigga,
'cause them fries is
in the water right now.
I don't give a fuck
what you talking about.
That nigga done drop
my whole bag of fries
in the water.
- I mean, but he
gettin' em to me.
You know, I know
what's going on outside.
- I don't want
no soggy fries, nigga.
Don't put my fries
in the water, Cuz.
You keep- you hold them
motherfuckers up top like this
when you walking
through the water, 'kay?
- What commitment.
You know, in the summer,
we thought the pandemic was over
and life resumed
back to normal.
People were finally
letting their hair down.
Let's take a look this.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, here we go.
- Her hair finna
get out of there.
Oh, it's going.
It's out.
Bye bye.
- Oh.
Time out.
She just turned
into The Exorcist.
Did you hear
what she just said?
- What'd she-what'd she say?
- Wig!
- My wig!
- My fuckin' wig.
- That ride needs
to be shut down.
Taking that girl
wig off like that.
That girl is a beautiful,
intelligent woman
that came to that park
to have a good time,
and she left without a wig.
That-- you should be ashamed
of yourself, park.
Shut it down.
- Yup.
- All right, Snoop,
let's keep it going.
- After a year of quarantine,
people seemed to forget
how to behave
out in the real world,
especially on airplanes.
Take a look.
- Sit down now.
- You can't hold us!
- Oh man.
- Down on the ground, sir.
- We're not on the ground.
- Yes, we are!
- Wow.
Yeah, see-see, this is
way too much patience.
It's way too much patience.
You gotta knock him
the fuck out right there,
right there.
- He already
knocking himself out.
- Look at this.
- Look at this sh-.
- Yeah, I see this.
He got to die.
You're not gonna
do this next to me.
- No.
What I'm gonna do is take
three, two people in the back
that I don't know and say,
"We finna come together
and kick his
motherfucking ass.
- We gonna beat his ass.
You're not going to look at me
and eat your mask.
No.
- Really? Really?
Oh, man, he calm now.
The police got him.
- Really?
What did I do?
Shut your stupid ass up.
You know what you did over here
growling at the goddamn
flight attendant.
- Why didn't they
cuff him, though,
that's that privilege again.
They didn't cuff him.
- By the way,
they shouldn't have trusted him
from the beginning.
He had on jean shorts.
I never met anybody
trustworthy in jean shorts.
Uh, in 2021,
the most boring thing
you could ever attend
finally got exciting.
I'm talking about
school board meetings.
Take a look at this clip
right here.
- The children and
your children's children
will be subjugated!
They will be asked,
"How many vaccines have you had?
"Have you been
a good little Nazi?
"Hail Fauci!?"
- I don't know who's next up
on that mic,
but that mic had a hot,
batch of COVID waiting for them.
- All variants included.
- That mic was a mess.
Jesus Christ.
Joining us now to make sense
of all this senselessness
and break down some of
the other big stories of 2021,
a man who never keeps it
on the DL.
Of course, I'm talking about
my brother, D.L. Hugley,
a.k.a. one of the kings
of comedy.
What up, D.L.?
- Hey now, what's up?
How y'all doing?
- Good, man.
- D.L., you didn't put
your Crocodile Dundee brim
on for this shit, huh?
- Fo sho, fo sho, fo sho.
You never know.
- I hope 2021
was better than 2020 for you
after you fainted on stage.
And I'm being
serious about you.
You are right physically,
mentally, you all right?
- Oh yeah, for sure.
Yeah, it took a while,
but you know,
2021 was challenging
for a lot of people.
But, uh, it was, uh,
it was an interesting
experience.
I learned a lot about myself
and I learned a lot
about the world.
But I never thought
I would see America
so frightened of a virus,
they let niggas
walk around with masks on.
[laughter]
- Yo, 2021, Juneteenth
finally became a holiday.
What's your feeling
about Juneteenth now?
- Well here's the thing.
It's interesting because
at a time when
they don't want to
teach slavery in school,
they want to commemorate
the end of it.
Like-- so good luck
explaining to kids
why they're off that day.
But I think we should
understand that Juneteenth
is the official--
is the commemoration of
the end of slavery.
Which is funny because
more white people will be off
on Juneteenth than us.
I think on Juneteenth, uh,
white people should have to
work all day for free.
- This motherfucker
got a great solution.
- Let's talk about
Joe Biden for a second.
You know, the black community
showed up for Joe Biden.
Do you feel like
he has delivered?
What's your take on that?
- I think that it's--
it would be like talking about
if the Atlanta Falcons
only had to play one quarter,
they would have been
Super Bowl champions.
But it's not.
It's four quarters.
Truth of the matter is,
our relationship with Joe Biden
was transactional.
If you have a transactional,
uh, relationship,
you gotta come through
with some transactions.
Like, you can't--
and they gotta be the ones
that the people
who voted for you find valuable.
So I think
the jury's still out.
I think he's done some things
I'm-- I've been pleased with
and some that I haven't been
very pleased with at all.
- D.L., you are--
you're the real deal.
I tell you all the time.
- Thanks, Man.
- Uh, and not only that.
You're a friend,
you're a brother,
and you're a legend.
So, man, please--
- I gotta say something
before we go.
First off, you-- this is like-
remember how nobody thought
stripes and-and polka dots
would to go together?
That's you and Snoop now.
You're seeing two men together
have so much fun, fucking up,
it's hilarious to me.
I can't believe-I can't believe
that they got you all
commentating on the world.
Thank, y'all, man.
Thank, y'all for having me on.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, man.
Thanks for coming on.
D.L., we appreciate you,
we love you.
- Likewise.
- Ladies gentlemen,
D.L. Hugley, king,
king of comedy, uh,
my brother.
I love you, man.
We'll talk soon.
- All right.
Thank you.
- Peace and love.
Love you, boy.
- Wow.
Hey, people will be right back
with more of
Welcome back.
Snoop, you know what?
It's time to talk about
that one thing
that gets us fired up
more than anything else.
- Antiquing?
- No, no.
Snoop, that's not
what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about sports!
In 2021 we said goodbye to
cardboard cutouts,
and welcome back
to real fans.
And sports got balls out.
- Yes.
- It was a great year for
the world champion,
Milwaukee Bucks.
And one enthusiastic fan
couldn't curb his enthusiasm.
Take a look.
Uh oh.
Oh, if he chugs it,
he gonna go ham.
He about to go ham.
No. No.
- Take that motherfucker off.
- Oh, don't rip it.
Yeah.
You know what?
That's always good
in the moment.
But then after they stopped
the music and they go "Mah!"
and they start
the game back up--
- And he like, "It's cold.
Where my shirt at?"
- You just gotta
sit back down.
You ain't got no shirt on
and you notice the people
looking at your stupid ass.
- I feel that.
Looking at you.
- They're like,
"You don't have another shirt?
- No.
Tore this motherfucker off
in the heat of the moment.
The Bucks won the NBA Finals
and at the victory celebration,
there was less than
winning speeches.
Let's take a look.
- Well, I came here they're
like, "Yo, you gotta, like,
"show, like,
you got to be the dog.
And I'm like --
- What?
- Man, we got dogs.
Like, they just ain't, like--
- What?
- We're-- like, I got here,
like, we-we already got dogs.
- What?
- They just don't know
how to be dogs,
and we gonna be dogs.
- What are you talking about
right now?
P.J. first and foremost,
you guys are Bucks.
- And they were, like, you know,
you got to be the dog.
So I'm like,
we already got dogs.
- What?
- Yeah, but we
the Bucks though.
- You just hear people
in the background going, what?
What, what?
What'd he say?
That's the part
that made me laugh.
That's why I'm like.
[laughing]
Don't even--
I'm like, what?
- Stop it.
- Uh, the Tampa Bay Bucs
celebrated their
Super Bowl victory
with a boat parade.
And even though he won
a seventh Lombardi,
Tom Brady partied like
it was his first championship.
- I'm open, Tom.
I'm wide open.
- Oh, wow!
- Hit me with it.
Look at this.
Come on, what?
Super Bowl?
What are you talking about?
Tom, why you got a knee brace?
- He had on a knee brace
at the after party?
- Tom, why got your--
Tom, don't ever
put your knee brace on
just to hang out, Tom.
- He was gone, man.
- That looked like that
Brett Favre commercial.
The copper--
What was it called?
- Coppertone.
- With him and Jerry Rice --
- Him and Jerry Rice
running them old ass routes.
He's out there playing
three on three with some bums.
- Hey.
- When I wear Coppertone,
I'm just as fast
as I was in 1987.
- Tom Brady,
don't you ever put
another goddamn
knee brace on
to go to a parade.
Sit your ass home if that's
what you gotta do, man.
- You sure you're in
a position to judge people
for getting to wild
after a Super Bowl, Kev?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I remember
this thing happening
to you a few years ago.
- Late in the game,
you guys didn't flinch, and--
- Sorry to interrupt, but I got
a special fan for you.
How's Kevin Hart for you?
- Oh, he need--
he need a ladder.
- Not one of!
The best!
- I like it.
- How'd you feel when Brady
had that ball and got sacked?
Lost the ball.
- Look at my eye.
- I'll say this.
- Look at my eyes.
- We're very lucky
to have this guy
a part of this team.
I've been drinking.
[laughter]
- I'm on cloud nine.
That's the best part.
- You were so fucked up.
- Yeah!
- Here you was trying
to be professional.
That's the part
I'm tripping on.
- Yeah.
- But you was like up here,
I-I am on TV, but,
look, let me tell you all.
Look--
- Hey!
I have never been more--
I have never been
more intoxicated in my life.
But guess what?
I'd do the same thing again.
Have you ever had that?
Have you ever been
so-so messed up,
like that you-you're
trying to keep it together,
but while you're trying
to keep it together,
in your mind, you're like,
"I look stupid as
fuck right now."
- I definitely did that
when the Lakers hit the, uh,
they hit
the Portland Trailblazers
in their game seven.
And me and the homies
just busted in the locker room
at the end of the game.
And they was doing
an interview with Jim Hill.
We was like, "We don't
give a fuck.
What's happening, nigga?
The Lakers rule, nigga.
Nigga, we just
won, nigga.
That nigga Jim Hill
was like,
"Uh, uh, back to you."
[laughter]
And I was like,
damn, we was acting a fool,
but fuck it,
we was excited,
you know what I'm sayin'?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Now, the Atlanta Braves
brought home
their first championship
in 26 years.
Over a million people
turned out for the parade.
And after waiting
three hours for it to start,
this is what they saw.
- Ah!
- They going fast
as a motherfucker.
- Oh, my God!
- Why they going so fast, cuz?
- Holy shit, man.
You know that-that may be
the funniest clip
that we've seen all day.
They going like 35.
They going--
- Motherfuckin'--
Do they know what a parade's
fucking supposed to be?
- What did they
tell the drivers?
No matter what,
under no conditions
do you slow
this bitch down?
But this is the parade,
we just wanna see the people.
I don't give
a fuck what it is.
You drive this bitch
through there
until we get to a place
where I feel like it's safe.
They-they did 35, 40.
- They was flying
through that bitch, man.
- Jesus Christ!
Do you see the people there?
What the fuck is going on?
- I'm crying laughing
'cause they was going so fast.
- Oh, my God, man.
That's probably one of
the worst parades ever.
That's gonna go down
in history.
While we're celebrating
championships,
how about Candace Parker,
who came back
to her hometown
and brought the Chicago Sky
their first WNBA title?
Go ahead, Candace,
roll the clip.
- Nope.
- Candace, haul ass.
Go to your family. Go!
Go to your family,
Candace.
- Where they at?
- Hug 'em! Hug 'em!
- Find 'em!
- Come on,
- Come on, give me
a hug, my people.
- That's what I'm
talking about.
- I love it, I love it.
- Go back to my people.
Good for her, man.
- So happy for CP3.
- All jokes aside.
- Yeah, she did
that in, uh, L.A.
She was a great player
for the L.A. Sparks.
She-she did
great things for us,
but for her to go back
to her hometown
and get that
championship game,
I know that means
the world to her.
Shout out to CP3.
- I mean, I don't think
there's a better taste,
a better taste of success
for us athletes.
I, I know because of,
uh, my success in
the church league.
I told you, we won
a championship.
We played against--
- I would love to have
played against y'all
in the church league
championship games.
- I don't know why, Snoop.
We were quite--
we were-we were
the real deal, okay?
The real deal.
- Okay.
- I'll never forget
the championship game.
I had seven points,
eighteen assists,
36 rebounds, 15 blocks.
Uh, and I believe--
if I think--
what was it,
what was the other one?
Uh, I forced
a lot of turnover.
Either way, it was one
the best games ever played, man,
and they still talk about it.
- And I wish they had
a VHS back in the day
to see that.
- Well, brother, all you
gotta do is go to,
uh, SaintChristian.com
ZionBaptistedu.,
uh, BasketballForGod,
and you'll see all
of my success, brother.
That's all you gotta do.
- In other news...
- Hoopin' for the Lord.
- Yes, praise God.
In 2021, boxing
made a big comeback.
But some of the biggest fights
didn't feature real boxers
like this match between
Lamar Odom and Aaron Carter?
- Oh, Jesus.
Look at this shit.
Jesus Christ, man.
- Look how big he is
to the dude he's fighting.
That isn't-- that's--
- Aaron was catching him though
in some of the rounds.
I actually-- here's what's bad,
I watched the fight.
[laughter]
I paid for it
and everything.
I was like, oh, this
is gonna be good.
I'm a firm believer.
I'm a supporter of
all these fights.
- So you spent that
$5.99 for that fight?
- Yeah, I remember
that now.
So that was like Lamar Odom
versus Aaron Carter.
I was like,
I gotta see this shit.
- Fighting live for $5.99.
- I thought,
this is gonna to be good.
This here is gonna
to be real good.
- Over in the UFC,
Conor McGregor broke his leg
during a fight
and it was nasty.
- Oh, my God, are you sure
you wanna see that photo?
I don't wanna look at it.
- Oh!
- God damn it, man.
Look at that.
- But I love
his-his-his tenacity
and his fierce way
of fighting.
He was talking shit
after he broke his leg.
He was, "I fuck him up,
there's nothing
he can do to me."
And his leg was
fucked up.
I'm like,
cuz still talking shit?
- Snoop just pulled
that accent out his ass.
It was great!
Oh, my God.
- He said that he believes
that one of the kicks
that he checked
is what broke your leg.
- Only Conor, man.
Only Conor.
- While his shit is broke,
in pain,
sitting on the ground
and Joe Rogan got
to sit down next to him,
'cause the nigga
can't stand up.
Who does the interview
sitting next to the nigga?
- I don't know.
But if his shit was broke,
he was extremely calm.
Tell you what, you wouldn't
had got a word out of me.
Jesus...
How you feel?
Fucked up, man.
Get me outta here!
Oh, my God.
My foot's in my ass, man.
Get me outta here.
Uh, you know, Snoop, man,
I think the best
sporting event of 2021
was actually
the 2020 Olympics.
- Hey, hey, you know,
what my favorite part
of the Olympics was?
- Oh, Snoop man, come on.
Don't say it.
You ain't gotta make me blush.
I already know.
- No, it's not you.
It's the horse.
Roll that clip.
- Oh! Oh!
- Hey! Yeah.
Oh, look at this, cuz.
- Oh, come on, man.
- This horse is off the chain.
I got to get this
motherfucker in the video.
- You made that horse famous.
That horse probably got
a lot of ass after that.
- He probably got
a lot of jealousy, too.
I know when he
went back in the barn,
all the other horses
was mad and shit.
Oh, you think you
something, huh?
You think you-you think
you hot 'cause you was on TV
and Snoop was talking
about you, huh?
Fuck you
and your fake ass hair.
[laughter]
- Our next guest gets in
a lot of passionate debates
every single morning.
You may know him
as an analyst,
but I know him
as my alarm clock.
Here to give us the last take
on sports in 2021,
please welcome
Stephen A. Smith.
- What up? What up?
How you y'all doing?
- We all good, baby.
Good to see you, man.
I see you lookin' good.
Got the fireplace
in the background.
I like that.
I can put somethin'
on that fire
if you want me to.
- Hey, I don't mind.
Here's the only problem,
obviously I got
the fireplace on,
that means
it's cold outside.
- So, uh, we'd like
to welcome you to the show.
How was your 2021
and did you happen to get into
any disagreements this year?
- No, 15 segments a day,
75 a week,
over 3,000 a year,
I'd say I got into
my share of disagreements
pretty much every day,
every minute of every day.
Except I haven't lost
any of those disagreements,
and that's
the most important.
- 75,000 and 0.
- Stephen A. Smith,
two naked women just walked by
in the background,
explain it.
[laughter]
- That is a lie.
- Why you didn't turn around
and see if he was lying?
- He just sat up.
Oh!
Was 2021 a good year
for sports to you, Stephen?
- Well, for me personally,
I-I was shocked
to see that Tom Brady was
gonna smack down Kansas City
the way that they did.
I didn't think that
they'd be able to do that.
Uh, but to see
a brother in his 40s
go out on that football field
against young lines,
against a stud
like Patrick Mahomes,
Travis Kelce's big time,
Tyreek Hill's big time.
And to see Tom Brady do it,
but not just what he did,
it was how he did it.
Remember, you saw him
going at the Honey Badger,
- Right.
- Tyrann Mathieu.
And we all got mad respect
for the honey badger,
we know what a big time
player he is.
But it's one thing
to-to-to go at him,
it's another thing
to talk smack to him,
to get this face
during the Super Bowl,
to let him know
I'm coming for you,
and went for him
and got him,
'cause it made
this upcoming season
that much more beautiful.
We all thought that Kansas City
was relatively invincible
until we saw them
get smacked down like that.
- Uh, Stephen A. Smith,
we talkin' about 2021.
Let me tell you, um, one of
my least favorite moments.
And I-I think we got a clip.
Do we have the clip
of Stephen A. Smith
hitting the heavy bag
when he was
working out boxing?
Uh, just roll the clip
of Stephen A. Smith
throwing some of
the most aggressive uppercuts
that I've ever seen
in my life.
Uh, dressed like he has
never went to the gym.
Uh, Stephen A. Smith,
as you can see,
has on a pair of
the loosest gray sweatpants,
and a, uh, black tank top
that definitely doesn't fit.
It looks like it's been
through seven family reunions
and, uh, and two barbecues.
But boy, when I tell you,
this did not do good
for our race as well.
- I know that was rehab
for your rotator cuff.
- Yeah.
- I know that, so that was--
that was good work to show
that it was coming back to you.
Didn't nobody understand
the whole story
behind the video.
- Yeah.
- That was progress
on your rehabilitation.
- I'll tell you what
I do understand: bullsh-.
The trainer kept saying--
the trainer kept
telling Stephen A.
good, good, good.
Good. That's--
And it shows
how easy it is for us
to get caught up
in the moment.
He got caught up
in the goods.
Uh, okay, let's get back to
some serious stuff right now.
- Steven A., I wanna speak to
the wisdom and the knowledge
that you speak to
when you on television.
I really appreciate you
for giving
the young homies
in the industry
and the young homies
in the-in the sports world
understanding of
what they can and can't do,
and you try
to keep them straight.
And even though
they get mad at you,
I appreciate you and I do
know that behind your back,
they be thanking you.
They just ain't man enough
to say it to your face,
so I'mma say it for 'em.
Thank you.
- Nice.
- I love y'all as brothers.
I'm proud of y'all,
and I'm always, always, always
here for the both of y'all.
And that's just
real love as a brother.
- Damn, look at that.
- That's heavy, right?
- Kicked it off
with a bang, man.
Stephen A. Smith,
thank you so much, Stephen.
We love you, man.
Wow.
- Peace.
- We'll be right back.
We got more highlights
and low lights in 2021
when we come back.
- Put chestnuts roasting on
a fire in the background.
- Stephen A. Smith, huh?
- That's nice.
- Welcome back to
"2021 and Done".
- 2021 was a jam-packed year
in entertainment.
The best limited series on
Netflix was "True Story".
- And that is a fact.
And the best album of the year
was "Algorithm".
- That is also a fact.
The best talk show of
the year was "Hart To Heart".
- And you do know that.
And the best entertainment
sports show of the year
was "Olympic Highlights".
- Man, if you don't
talk your talk,
I'mma walk my walk.
As a matter of fact, Snoop,
you already know I'm in a doop,
and I'mma tell you
something else,
I'll throw you for a loop.
Get the car, and I'mma
drive it around the hoop.
Who wanna get with me?
They better ask 2003,
because I now know
I'm where I'm supposed to be.
- Mmm!
- Wrapping up the charts
and being the... walk.
All right.
Okay, I'm sorry.
It's getting ridiculous.
Let's just move on.
In one of the most watched
television events of the year,
Prince Harry
and Meghan Markle,
sat down with Oprah
to talk about leaving
the royal family.
And after hearing this shit,
well, it isn't hard to see why.
Watch this.
- Check it out.
- Hold up, stop right now.
- There are several--
there are several
conversations about it.
- There's a conversation
with you-
- With Harry.
---about how dark
your baby is going to be?
- Huh?
- Potentially, and what that
would mean or look like.
- Ooh.
- Oh, God, don't freeze frame
Oprah like that.
Come on, man.
- Don't do her like that
with her mouth like that.
- Don't do freeze frame
Oprah like that.
Uh, I mean,
look, that was tough.
But you know what?
- That was tough.
- We gotta stand
by Harry, man.
Harry did the right thing.
That man sided with
his woman and said--
- And said, you know what?
fuck that, I'm out.
- I'm out, I'm out.
- You all gonna question
what color my baby gonna be
and all that?
That ain't got nothing
to do with nothing.
I love this woman right here.
- That's right.
- And if I love this woman,
love has no color on it.
- Mmm, said and shouldn't
be said any more.
- Mmm...
- God damn it, Snoop.
Sometimes you just get
so profound with it, man.
You know what you
made me wanna do?
- What?
- Sing another song.
* At the end of the day
I'mma flow my way *
* Ask me where I'mma be
and it's another day *
* Don't matter what the
color is cause I do *
* What the fuck
you wanna see *
* It's me and Snoop *
Oh! That was an accident.
It came together
at the end, though.
- It really did.
- Came together at the end.
Uh, 2021, brought the end
of the Kardashians on E!
and the end of
Kim and Kanye in real life.
Uh, in the divorce,
Kim got the house
and Kanye got the stadium.
That's right.
When they separated,
Kanye moved into
Atlanta's
Mercedes-Benz Stadium.
This is actually Kanye's room.
Let's take a look.
- The motherfucker
really did move in.
- Yeah, yeah.
It looks like the women's gym
at the NCAA tournament.
Look at this shit.
Remember, they only
had three weights?
- It looked like
the Olympic dressing room--
- The box beds!
---with the beds. Exactly!
- Only Kanye.
Look at this shit, man.
- Then he went to a game
later that night
that was on top of the stadium
that he was sleeping up under.
- Yeah, well,
when they said, Kanye,
what you about
to do after this?
I'm about to go downstairs
and go to bed.
[laughter]
What?
Wh-What?
Yeah, I'm about to go
right to sleep.
I ain't gonna do
too much after this.
I ain't trying
to be up all night.
I'm gonna go right downstairs
and go to bed.
Tell 'em they gotta wrap
this basketball shit up.
I got a big day tomorrow.
- While he was living there,
Kanye was spotted
making an appearance
at one of those games
we talking about.
Let's check it out.
- Hey, Kanye!
- Jesus Christ, Jesus Christ.
Kanye got pantyhose
on his face.
[coughing from laughter]
Kanye-Kanye walked--
Kanye walked in
that bitch looking like
a bank robber
from the '80s.
Put the money in
the bag, bitch!
Luther?
You know, they could always
see who was robbing them
in the pantyhose?
- Say, you jive-ass nigga.
Put the money in the bag.
[laughter]
- I don't wanna hear
shit you got to say
if there ain't
the money in the bag.
- Hey, man, I know you.
You don't know me.
Stop looking at me, man.
Just put the money
in the fucking bag.
- Yo, roll the clip again.
Let me see what he had on
walking to the gym again.
Look at this shit here.
God damn it.
God damn it, Kanye.
- Nigga had on the
Eddie Murphy "Delirious" outfit
with a stocking cap.
[laughter]
I can't make
this shit up, man.
- You gotta-you gotta-- I mean,
there's only one Kanye, man.
You know, Kanye was trying
to hide from the paparazzi,
but the pantyhose
weren't enough.
So he took it
to the next level,
as seen in this photo.
Look at this right here.
- Oh, shit.
- Yup, there it is right there.
Yeah, yeah.
By the way,
perfectly normal.
I don't know who that is.
Who's that?
Who's this?
Who's this regular guy
at the bank?
This isn't suspicious
at all.
I'm not scared.
I'm not scared at all.
Who is this man monster
that looks perfectly normal?
He doesn't eat people.
Who the fuck is this?
Oh, he's got black eyes.
Look at this fucking--
look at the mask
and then look at the eyes.
- This shit is amazing, man,
that he would do some--
- What is Kanye
trying to do, man?
- I don't know.
This year, the people
started a movement
to #FreeBritney,
and it worked.
- Fans are important.
That right there,
that should not be
just looked past.
That's love.
That's people standing by
who they've supported
over the years.
That's dope as hell, man.
- Yeah.
No justice, no peace.
Get Britney
on these streets.
[laughter]
- I don't-I don't know
how he does it,
he just does it.
Shit just comes
to him so fast.
My last rap, it thought--
I literally took about
ten minutes thinking of
that shit before I did it.
It was an incredible year in
entertainment and pop culture,
so we thought,
who better to check in with
than the only guy
who's on TV more than us?
You know him from
"Good Morning America"
and "Fox Football Sunday",
please welcome the man,
the myth, the legend,
Michael Strahan.
- What's up, fellas?
- There he is.
- What's up?
- Where you at, Mike?
In the closet?
Wh-where they got you?
In a closet doing
an interview?
- Hey, you know what,
Snoop, you-you know,
when you do all right
for yourself,
this is what you call
a bookshelf, buddy.
This is, like,
an office, baby.
Look how expansive it is.
- Hey, I haven't read
in a long time, Mike.
Reading is fundamental.
I may have to come over
and borrow a book or something.
- Nah, nah, nah.
I never open 'em,
they just look good.
I buy these big thick books,
they'll look good.
- They just look good.
- I was watching
the NFL, man,
and I love how they
gave you your flowers, man
on the air, man.
How does that feel?
Getting that appreciation
from your coworkers, man,
those Hall of Famers that was
giving you that love that day?
- You know what, man?
It's-it's amazing.
I-I-I mean, to have
your-your teammates,
the guys you played with
to show love by showing up,
man, meant the world to me.
And the Giants
retired my jersey,
I never thought
that was gonna happen.
You know, I'm out there
just trying to survive,
just trying to keep a job
so I had to move back
in with my parents.
Next thing you know,
my jersey's gonna hang
in the rafters forever.
So that was a big--
that was incredible.
That was incredible.
- Well, Mike, listen, you know
nobody likes the trash you
more than I do,
but in this moment,
I'm going to take
the high road.
And I gotta honestly say,
it's well deserved.
I talk trash to your face.
I-I try my best to get you
off your rocker.
But I can say, man,
that-that jersey,
it belongs
in the-in the rafters.
That's the last time that
you're gonna hear me say
anything nice to you.
Don't you ever
expect it again.
I'm doing it because
you deserve it.
This is the end of the year,
we're-we're wrapping it up,
so I felt like I should throw
something nice to you in it.
All right? So don't
ever expect it again.
That's the only time.
- All right, Kev--
Kevin, if you do that again,
I know something's wrong.
- Yeah.
- Something's wrong.
- Let's get into
the year, man.
What do you feel,
in your opinion,
was the biggest entertainment
story of the year?
- Oh, man!
Dave Chappelle is one
of the biggest, I think.
- Ahh.
- You know?
- Yeah.
- I think that was one of
the biggest
because comedy has always been
that one place
where people can go when--
if you're a great comic
at what you-you do,
you can do it and kind of
not say have free reign,
but you're able to kind of,
you know, balance it.
- Um-hmm.
- And I do--
I think that
the Dave Chappelle story
and the cancel culture with him
was one of the biggest--
biggest stories.
- It actually was.
- So, yeah.
- And this year we saw
the last James Bond movie
with Daniel Craig.
Is it true that you're playing
the next James Bond?
- Ah, man.
Hey, first of all, I--
they called me,
but I can't--
I can't do the accent, Snoop,
so, I pulled myself out.
- You pulled yourself out.
Uh, did you agree with
People Magazine'sdecision
to name Paul Rudd
the sexiest man alive?
- Hey, Paul's my guy, man.
Laughing is sexy.
- Which is why
I don't understand
why I keep getting robbed!
Why do I keep getting robbed?
Every year I'm overlooked.
Year after year, man.
- So, Mike, you're one of
the best game show hosts
I've ever seen.
Why weren't you named
the new host of "Jeopardy"
this year?
I thought that was going to be
you to fill in
for Alex Trebek, man.
- Hey, Snoop,
I ain't smart enough for
that show, man.
I sat on the couch with my mama
watching that show last week.
I'm like, Mama, get it.
Because, you know, your mom--
my mom thinks
she can win everything.
And then after about
five wrong answers,
she go, I'll stick to
"Wheel of Fortune".
I said, yes, Mama,
stick with the wheel.
Hey, your son ain't smart enough
for it either.
I'm messin'--
I'm not smart enough for that.
I'll stick with
"Pyramid", man.
I'm good with it.
- I love the honesty.
I mean, I think it takes
a smart man to realize
that he's a dumb man
that puts him in a position
to be a better smart man.
I love it.
T-That's brilliant!
- Hey, Mike,
what gives you hope for 2022?
- Oh, man, what gives me hope
for 2022?
Every year we go to
a military instillation.
And we do a-a show.
And then you go, you sit around
these young soldiers
and you realize
that we all right.
So, when we go to do things
with the military
and the people
who really protect our freedom
here in this country
and really are behind us
or in front of us in most ways,
it gives me hope, brother.
Every time I see that
it kind of rejuvenates me
about where we're at.
- That sounds dope, Mike.
- That's dope.
- And I just want to give you
a shout-out
for joining us on the show.
We love you;
we appreciate you.
- Man, I appreciate you.
- Peace and love, Mike.
**
- Welcome back to
"2021 and Done".
Social media had
a lot of likes
and some really big dislikes
this year.
We're going to talk about
some of them
in a segment that we're calling
"Viral Overload".
- This past summer,
Kevin and I
covered the Olympics on Peacock.
And some of our clips
went viral.
But shortly after the Olympics,
a new trend popped up
on social media.
The hood Olympics.
Check this shit out.
[chatter]
- One, two, three,
four, five, six...
- Do you know
this was started by
some crackheads, right?
- Of course.
- This was a-this was a move
that the crackheads
told the dope dealers,
if I do this,
you give me a 20 rock.
And then everybody
around the world
started doing crackhead shit
and didn't even know it.
- All to go viral.
- Yep.
Just to be seen and break
your motherfucking neck.
- Bunch of people with
fucked up spines out there
because of this dumbass thing.
- Bang!
- Necks and spines
rearranged all over.
- Um-hmm.
- Uh, that's a lot
of fail videos.
But one guy successfully
took home the crate gold.
Check him out.
- Mike said he going up there
rolling up a blunt.
- Oh, he's rolling up a blunt.
Homeboy, if he pull this off,
he gonna get it.
He rollin' up?
Lookin' like DJ drama and
Drake and motherfucking--
Every light-skinned nigga
I know.
- It's all good!
- Oh, he caught one, too.
Them George is on point.
Look at his George.
Oh, he licked it down.
No spinnin' and lip it.
That's the spin lip technique
right there.
You do that good,
I'm gonna roll--
when you rollin' a blunt,
that's the technique
that you use
when you on the run.
Like a lot of times we runnin'
and tryin' to get
outta there fast rollin' up.
He's--
[applause]
- Give that nigga a lighter.
Give that nigga a lighter.
- This nigga-this nigga right
here gets the standing
motherfucking ov--
look at his homie on his side.
- Oh, my god. Look.
Oh, yeah.
The hype up from everybody else
is what makes it even better.
Yeah! Yeah!
Go get him a light!
- Get that nigga light and
light that bleezie
cause that was too easy.
- If you're an aspiring artist,
social media is an amazing tool
to help you
promote your talent.
Roll the clip.
* Cause I'm an island boy *
* and I been trying to amaze *
* Oh, I'm an island boy *
* I'ma just island boy *
* I'm a good cute white boy *
* Let me just keep that gun *
* Let me just
staring at the sun *
* I'ma fool gazing *
* I'm like in the pool I stand *
* I'm an island boy *
* I put my vest on, yeah, *
* like a wild woman
tryin' to make it to the tall *
* But I'm an island boy
I been tryin' to make it *
* I ain't singin' with
a gang gang slang *
- Gang, gang.
There they got
to use that word.
I'm speechless.
- I'm not.
- Two goofballs in the pool.
- You know why
I'm not speechless?
- Why?
- Because I'm an island boy.
[laughter]
* I'm an island boy *
What is happening, man?
- I don't know and
ain't tryin' to understand it.
- Dammit!
- What's understood
don't need to be explained
and I don't want to
understand it.
- Tell you what does.
Tell you what does
need to be explained.
- What?
- How I became an island boy.
- Knock it off, man!
* Cool and gay *
- All right,
all right, all right.
We been making fun of
social media
and we know that it can be
a very dark place.
But it also brought
some joy in 2021.
Here to show us the lighter side
of social media
is our good friend,
comedian Lonnie Love.
- Oh, Lonnie!
- Lonnie, don't show out
like that,
got all your little awards
and shit behind you.
You just showin' out.
Look at you!
Just awards everywhere.
Go, girl!
Look at her!
You go, girl!
- What-- wait!
- Hi, fellas!
- What an asshole!
What an asshole!
[laughter]
- I love you, too, Kevin.
Now, look.
I want to--
before I give you
my-my video clips
that I selected for you fellas;
I want to talk about
how great of a year
this was for women.
Yes, I know you're excited
to hear about this, fellas,
so just hang in there.
We had Adele; she's going to
have a residency in 2022.
Jennifer let go of that
cheatin' ass fianc
and got a new one,
her old thang.
And I'm like Bennifer 2.0,
I'm all for that.
Tina Turner got inducted in
the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame
on her own.
- Yes! Yes!
- Without that
beatin' ass Ike.
- Oh, my god!
- Yay for women!
And we had the first female
vice president
inducted this year.
It was a great year.
Britney Spears was freed;
Meghan got the hell
up out of Britain
and came on over here
and lived next to Kev.
That's what I heard.
- No.
[laughter]
There goes the neighborhood.
- Yeah, that's what I heard.
No, it was an amazing year
for women, Lonnie.
You-you couldn't have
said it better.
And me and Snoop,
we support the women
that are thriving
in today's entertainment world
and just in life in general.
I'm definitely a supporter
of you and all your success.
You left yourself out of it.
I mean, look at the awards
and stuff in the back.
I mean, look at
your progression,
look at your growth.
- You're doing the same, wow!
- You should have
been on your own list.
- Well, you know,
we've come a long way
since "Soul Plane",
Kev and Snoop.
- Yes, we have.
Yes, we have.
That's right!
- Right.
- So, I almost
forgot about that!
- Ain't that a reunion, huh?
- Ain't that about a bitch!
Yeah, Lonnie.
- That's a hell of
a reunion right here.
Talk about it, Lonnie.
- God damn, I forgot about it!
- God is good.
Look at us!
Look at us now!
- Kev was the star.
Snoop was the costar;
he was the pilot.
And we made $17
at the box office.
But look!
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Look what happened.
We are back together.
So, this is an inspiration.
You guys have always been
an inspiration to me.
And I want to show you
a couple of viral videos
this year that I promise
that will warm your hearts.
So, roll it, Leslie!
Roll the clip!
- Aww.
- Oh, it's a little
chicken asleep.
- There we go.
That's good.
- Is that what it is?
A baby chicken?
- It's a duckling.
- A duckling.
- Okay.
- Is that the ugly duckling?
- He's asleep.
- Yeah.
- Didn't that warm your heart?
I could feel it.
I could feel the look.
I could feel the warmth
in y'all heart.
- Yeah.
- Just wanna double check,
Lonnie,
you went and found that
yourself, right?
You searched for that.
- Yes, I did.
- Okay.
- I said what--
what would encourage Kevin
and put a--
a smile on his face?
And I said a duckling.
Something smaller than him.
I was like that is great.
- Okay, all right.
- Now, I have something else.
I have something else
that maybe you guys would like
because you guys are fathers
and you work a lot.
- Yes.
- So, you're gonna love
this next viral video.
I dare you not to cry.
This is a good one.
Okay, let's watch.
- Okay. I've got a tear
ready to fall now.
Oh, oh, wow!
See?
This is a dad's dream
right here, man.
You see how
he threw that hat off?
- Yep.
- He threw that hat off
and was like,
"Hey, that's my daddy
out there!
"I don't give a damn about
nothing else but my daddy!"
- That's right.
- Yeah, I just want to
make sure--
I just want to make sure
I'm looking at the same videos.
You talking about the baby
that just ran to his dad, right?
- Yeah.
- Was he supposed to
run to somebody else?
I don't understand.
There was no--
there was nobody else out there.
It's not like-it's not like
somebody else
got out of the truck
and he made a decision.
It was one man
that stepped out the truck.
And the man probably said,
"Son, come here."
I mean, I-- okay.
Yeah, Lonnie, that's, uh,
my eyes are watering.
Just right now I'm--
I'm a mess if you look at me.
That's an adorable
little boy, Lonnie.
Thank you for that.
That's cool.
- Okay, okay, I got one more.
- Oh.
- Okay?
I got another one that'll
make you feel better
about the state of the world
in 2021.
- Okay.
- Now, we've seen so many people
using the social media
to show off their clothes and
their cars and their houses.
You know?
But this lady used
social media to give back.
- Okay.
- Let's roll that clip.
- Let's see it.
Man, take
the motherfucking money!
- I'm gonna tell you something.
Let them give that to--
to Jamal.
I know a dude named Jamal
that drive an Uber.
"Hey, Jamal,
I want to give you--"
he gonna snatch that shit
out your hand.
You won't even finish--
you won't even
finish the sentence.
- No, don't give-- no, no.
- No.
- This is a lot.
- That's a lot.
- You better not.
No, you're lying.
You're lying.
No, I'm serious,
I'll give it to you.
- Well, have a happy--
have a Happy New Year, fellas.
- Yes, Lonnie.
- We're gonna make 2022 great.
Thank you so much.
- And, Lonnie Love,
you lookin' good over there.
I don't know
what he doing to you,
but he doing something to you
cause he got you over there
smilin', gleamin',
and glossin'.
So, I want to give a shout-out
to the man behind the scenes.
I don't know where he at,
but he doin' somethin'
cause he got you smilin'!
- I heard-I heard...
- It's the ring light.
It's the ring light.
- No. No, I heard he was
a island boy.
[laughter]
- Get outta here!
- All right, Lonnie.
Love you!
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
Lonnie Love,
always great!
Thank you for uplifting us.
Hopefully we see more of that
in 2022.
We'll be right back
with more after this.
Welcome back to
"2021 and Done".
This year, some people
struggled to get by on stimmies,
but some people
made so much money
they flew their asses to space.
"This is All Up
in Your Business".
- Yeah, we nosey.
Now, for rich people,
space is the new St. Bart's.
Elon Musk, Richard Branson,
and Jeff Bezos all are competing
to dominate
the final frontier.
Bezos sent four civilians
into space,
including Captain Kirk!
Let's take a look at this.
- Ready to go.
- Let's listen in and
watch this launch.
Blue Origin.
- Is that space?
- No. Shit!
- That look like
the desert, cuz!
- Looks like Utah.
- God, then done flew to
the hills of Utah or something.
Like they went to space.
That's some bullshit!
- It is so moving, commander.
This experience is
something unbelievable.
- Beaming into our studios,
please welcome
William Shatner!
- Whoo!
- Captain Kirk,
what's up, baby?
- There he is!
- There I am!
I knew I was there.
That's called
a minor event.
There are four people
there to greet you.
Oh, I'm so happy
you're alive.
Four people.
After a lifetime.
[laughter]
- William Shatner,
we just saw a video
of you getting shot into space
and coming down.
You seem to be emotional.
Could you describe
the moment for me?
- I had the most, uh,
unexpected reaction.
We got up there
and we hit weightlessness.
And then we were allowed
out of this 5-point harness
that kept us in the chairs.
And suddenly we're
floating around.
And I had seen footage
of Jeff Bezos,
who had done
a previous trip,
in weightlessness
with his back to camera
and his feet spread
and his little--
his little tushie exposed.
And one of the other people
in the spaceship
was throwing candies
at his little tushie.
- Oh, no!
- Oh, yeah.
- Is he saying they was puttin'
candy in Jeff Bezos ass?
I just want to make sure
I heard you correctly.
- Yeah, I-I didn't know
how far you guys went
with ass and asshole.
- Yeah.
- Okay, either/or.
- I didn't know where to go.
- Yeah.
- But look,
what's the difference
between Bezos rocket ship
and the Starship Enterprise?
- His asshole.
[laughter]
So, I looked
out the window,
and I was looking
down to my left
and I could see the way
the spaceship cut through
the blue air.
And suddenly,
we were through it
and I looked up into
the right-hand side.
Oh, wow.
And I saw black,
black, ominous space.
And it was
so shocking to me.
I thought
I'd see moon, stars.
Nothing! It was--
what I was looking at
looked to me like death.
- Wow!
William, man, we were
honestly in awe of the fact
that you did it.
We think it's dope
as hell.
- Thank you for taking us
to space, Kirk!
- Yes, sir.
- It's a pleasure
to talk to you guys.
- Thank you so much.
- T.J. Hooker!
Hello!
From Bitcoin to Ethereum,
to Dogecoin,
cryptocurrency
blew up in 2021.
- Oh, my god!
Indeed, it did!
Snoop, what do you know
about cryptocurrency?
- Well, I'm a Crip, cuz,
so you know I know about
everything that got
crip in it.
- Well, Snoop, gotta be
honest with you.
I'm not sure if
that's how it works.
But some people made a shitload
investing in this stuff.
Like this guy.
Take a look.
- On February 5, Dogecoin
dipped back down to 4.5 cents
and Glauber went all in
and invested $250,000.
- That's when I sell
all my stocks,
max out my credit cards,
call my mom,
my aunt, my uncle to borrow--
let me borrow some money
and I go all in on
Dogecoin at 4.5 cents.
- On April 15 at 6 p.m.,
Glauber Contessoto
became a crypto millionaire.
- I just became a millionaire
by spending all my money
on Dogecoin.
- That's really
not a millionaire
'cause Uncle Sam will
take half of that shit.
- Once Uncle Sam
swipes at that, buddy,
you're gonna get a harsh
dose of what the fuck!
- He gonna get an understanding.
- Yeah.
- You 100,000-aire,
you can say that.
- Yeah. Yeah.
There you go.
People took crypto to
the new level this year.
I mean, look, they use
blockchain to trade NFTs.
Snoop, do you got NFTs?
You got some, don't you?
- I got a whole--
yeah, I got some NFTs.
I got my mind
on my money
and my money on NFTs.
I built a whole metaverse
called, uh,
you know what I'm saying,
the sandbox.
Flexin' on them.
Check this out.
**
Hey! Get 'em, Dogg!
Get 'em Dogg.
I don't know shit about it,
but I'm getting' this money.
[laughter]
Get 'em, Dogg!
Look at that nigga's party.
Look at this fake nigga's party
in the fake world.
- It's a metaverse.
- I know!
- God damn it!
- And it's goin' down.
- It's goin' down.
Look like it's goin' up.
Look like you
crushin' over there.
- I'm getting' it in, Kev.
I got some property.
You wanna buy
a little space over there?
I got a little neighborhood.
- So, wait.
Just can you break it
down a little bit to me?
Just what the world
of your metaverse is?
- Yeah, so the metaverse
is like, you know,
it's real but it ain't real,
but then again it is real.
- Okay.
- And it's--
it's a place
where you live with avatars.
You got all kinds
of things goin' down.
Like whatever I do
in my real life
is happening
in this world.
And then we sellin' property,
we sellin' avatars,
and we sellin' space,
and we sellin' all of the above
with the NFTs in that world
to create a whole
other metaverse
outside the universe.
Now, I know you don't
understand nothin'
about what I'm sayin',
but just listen to me.
Like most people get
like this much space,
I got this much property.
Hold on, let me lay
my shit out.
[mumbling]
- All this is yours?
- Yeah, I got this one--
- This is all your metaverse?
- Yeah.
And everybody else
got like a corner.
- Ain't this a bitch.
- So, people tryin' to be
my neighbors right now.
They tryin' to move
next to my community.
But I'm tryin' to put
a neighborhood watch together
'cause I don't need
no ignorant shit around me
in my neighborhood.
- Now, last question.
How often
are you checkin' in
on your-on your metaverse?
Is it like a daily thing?
- Oh, I'm the landlord.
I'm the landlord.
You know, they break bread
or fake dead,
I'm gonna give you
them numbers.
When I give you
the number, Kev,
let me give you
the numbers on the low.
- You a goddamn--
hey, let me tell you
something about Kevin Hart.
Kevin Hart just got himself
a metaverse, too.
Uh, yeah.
Y'all gonna get to see
when my world is goin' in
and what's goin' down, man.
Break bread or get dead
unless you wanna be fed.
Uh... Come in,
that's my Mini Cooper
right there.
Snoop got a Cadillac.
That's my Mini Cooper.
Think of the homies
right there.
I'm-I'm about to have
the same shit
or I'm gonna come
live with Snoop.
Something' got to happen.
- Oh, shit!
- If those numbers
is real, brother,
me and you are roomies.
- I'm tellin' you, man.
Let me get back
to the script.
Crypto isn't the only place
where people
made money this year.
Some, uh, Reddit users
took it upon themselves
to disrupt Wall Street.
- Yes, they did.
People that never
invested before
decided to get
a piece of the action.
Take a look at this little
investor right here.
- She gave him
ten shares of GameStop
for Kwanzaa back in 2019.
- Wow.
- At the time,
it was worth
about 6-bucks a share.
- I know this kid
loves videogames.
And at the time,
I was teaching him,
you know,
financial literacy.
- She was saying that
I basically owned
a small portion
of the company.
- Jaiden made
the call to cash out,
making more than $3,000.
- What are you going
to do with the money
that you've made
on GameStop?
- Come on, mama, you made him
cash out at 3 Gs?
- I-I think-I think we supposed
to make this positive.
[laughter]
- Man, that some bullshit.
- Well, I'll tell you what,
what a-what a time, right?
Just to-to breakdown of
life level of understanding
to our youth
and pretty much just
make sure they understand
the world of stocks
and investing
and that's what's
important today.
Um, man!
All right, you know what?
Here to drop more knowledge
on the world of business
and our economy is the owner
of the Dallas Mavericks
and the best-looking
shark since "Jaws".
Y'all show some love
for my guy Mark Cuban.
- What up, Kev?
What up, Snoop?
- Mark, what's happening
with it, baby?
- Uh, just crackin',
havin' fun.
- Let's talk about
the highlights of 2021.
Give me your biggest
highlight of 2021, Mark.
- Oh, the vaccine.
Getting that vaccine
in my arm
and getting into family.
That-that was
my highlight for 2021.
And, you know, with all-all
the stress everybody has had
and all the battles over it,
just being able to-to have
a little bit of confidence
that, at least for, you know,
some period of time,
my-myself and my family
were protected.
- Mark, uh,
you're a billionaire.
I know it.
The world knows it.
Do you plan on launching
yourself into space soon?
- Hell no!
I'm afraid of heights,
guys, no lie.
Like I won't even go on
a rollercoaster,
let alone a spaceship.
No.
- Oh, my God, with all
these supply chain issues,
are you finding it
hard to import,
you know, more white players
from overseas?
- Oh, damn!
Oh!
And see, I even put
my Steelers jersey
back there for you, Snoop.
I mean, right back there
I got my Steelers jersey.
And here you are
killing me!
- Come on, MC, you know
it's love, baby.
You know it's love.
- I know it is.
I don't care if they're
from the moon.
If J-Jeff Bezos goes up
and grabs me one from Mars
and he can come back
and play, I got him.
- So, Mark, when you
become president in 2024,
what will you do to make sure
the economy runs smoother?
- First, I'm not
running for president.
Two, what I would do,
we've just got to get
people more comfortable
with each other.
That's the key
to it, right?
The economy is not
doing bad.
I mean, we're getting over
as much as we can,
but there's just
too much divisiveness
and there's just
too much conflict.
And somebody's gotta go
out there and be a leader
and really just start to
bring people together.
And I think it's possible,
but it's just gotta be
the right person.
- What I want to know is
how did you get people excited
about going back to work?
- You know, people want
to deal with people, you know?
The cool thing about
the pandemic, if there is one,
people really got
to find out
more about themselves
and experiment.
And that led to some people
going back to work,
some people working
from home,
but a lot of people
starting businesses,
a lot of people being
really creative
and, you know, selling NFTs,
learning about crypto
and new opportunities there.
We saw an explosion
of entrepreneurship.
- What was the dumbest
pitch you heard
on "Shark Tank" this year?
- Goddammit!
- Oh, my God!
There were so many.
We've had like
fart candles come on,
wakin' bacon where you
wake up to the smell
of bacon in a toaster
that catches on fire.
I mean, it was just crazy.
So, this is
their life, right?
- Yeah.
- They put everything
that they own.
Lots of times it's
their life savings,
their family's life savings,
they mortgage their house.
And they come in and say
I-I believe in this so much.
And they've mortgaged
their house.
And, you know,
like, oh, my God!
And you feel horrible
for them.
But you've gotta respect
the grind, right?
- Yeah.
- You gotta respect
that they went for it.
And so, that's why I always
try to give them advice
and always
wish them the best,
even if I think
it's awful.
But there's been
some good ones, too.
And Kev will tell you.
He's got some good ones that
we put-- we-we did together.
- That's dope.
So, I'm coming on
"Shark Tank" 2022.
Let's go ahead and sign off
on that right now.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's do it!
- Let's make it official like
a referee with a whistle.
- Lock it in.
You gotta do it.
- You better know.
- Hey, if we get
you both on at
the same time,
that-that's fire
right there.
- Done deal.
I like it.
- Until Snoop cusses
one of them people out.
Hey, get your stupid
ass outta here!
Your dumbass invention
you got.
Get your dumbass
outta here, man!
I said no, cuz!
I ain't giving you
none of my money.
- 2021 left so many people
searching for answers.
So, before you go, Mark,
I got a question for you.
Who's gonna play in
the 2022 NBA finals?
- Dallas Mavericks
versus I don't care!
- I like that answer.
I like it.
Peace and love.
Let's go Mavericks!
- Yes, sir!
- Yeah, that's what
I'm talkin' about.
- Welcome back to
"2021 and Done".
- For the final word on
the year that has been
both challenging
and inspiring,
we turn to a man who can
put it all into perspective
with his unfiltered take
on everything
from politics
to pop culture.
Please welcome to
the show Killer Mike!
- Hey, what's up, fellas?
How y'all doin', man?
- There he is?
What's goin' on tonight?
- Killer Mike,
what's happenin'?
- Welcome!
- Oh, man,
I'm glad to be in
the presence of kings, man.
Glad to be here.
- Let's not pull
any punches here, man.
2021 was a mixed bag
for the Black community.
Do you see things
improving in 2022?
- Yeah, absolutely.
Things are constantly
improving for Black people
because Black people
don't give up.
Dick Gregory talked about
that, at our ability
to, within
one to two generations,
change the whole dynamic
of our families.
So, he was someone
I knew and loved
his last three years
in life
and he helped me to refuse
to look at the world cynically.
So, Black people,
we always improving.
We always beatin' the odds.
- Uh, Killer Mike, um,
what-what was the highlight
of 2021 for you, man?
- Aw, man,
on a personal level,
my baby girl made
the JV team.
- Here you go!
Congrats!
- But I tell you something.
We got a call from
a brother named JB
who's a rapper
in Oklahoma.
And he said, man,
there's a brother named
Julius Jones here,
and he may be executed.
You know? And he's-he's
probably not guilty,
based on what
other men have said
about another guy
said that he did it.
And right up until literally
the day before his execution,
like day of, the governor
of Oklahoma, Governor Stitt,
was being petitioned
by smaller groups
to say, hey, we need help.
Me and Tip jumped
onboard the last minute
but it really was spearheaded
by people locally on the ground
and in the rap scene
by my guy JB.
And the fact that
that brother got clemency,
that was
a highlight for me.
- Huge.
- And the other highlight
was right here in Georgia,
I-I got to see three men,
who deservedly so,
get convicted
on various forms of murder
on Ahmad Arbery.
And I'm hoping that
as we get forward,
we will stop letting these
be the premier cases
and we can hear
more cases of justice
gone right from the start
and not wrong
and we have to make
a fuss about it.
- Mmm...
- So, Mike,
you spent a lot of time
with Bernie Sanders this year.
Did you burn one
with him?
- Man, you know what?
He won't burn with me, man!
- Goddammit!
- He'll eat fried chicken,
but he won't burn
the dope with me, man.
But-but listen,
it's my goal to get the OG
to burn one with me.
It is my goal to burn it down
with Willie Nelson.
So, I know you know Willie.
- Yeah, I love it.
- I'm gonna make
the Willie Nelson play
happen for you.
Say less.
- Say less.
- That's-that's a done deal.
- What do you feel
we have to do in 2022
to bring more justice,
more hope, more opportunity,
and more laughs to the year?
- I want to say, man, take care
of your coin Black people.
If we, as a community,
build our tax base
and take care of our money
and take care of our own small
and medium businesses,
then you become
financial donors
to these local politicians
that want your vote.
And then they forget
about you
and they have to respond
to you differently.
If we, as a community,
are shopping with one another,
taking care of one another,
we starting to
create an economy
that takes care
of ourselves.
Because ain't nobody
coming to save us,
don't nobody
love us like us,
and if we cheap labor,
they gonna always use us cheap.
- Well equipped, man!
Well equipped with
a plethora
of knowledge
and information, man.
- So, why are you
gonna use plethora?
You don't even know
how to spell that shit.
- Pleth-- I can spell
plethora right now.
- Spell it right now, man.
- You want me to
spell it right now?
- Spell it.
- I can spell it right now.
- It's the spelling bee.
- Right now.
- Spell plethora.
- Me spelling plethora,
that takes the light
off of Killer Mike.
And that's not
what I want to do.
- No, no, it don't.
- Yes, it does.
- Mike wanna know
you smart.
- No. It's not about me
right now, Snoop.
- Okay.
- So, after we're done
with Killer Mike,
all right, then I'll go
and I'll spell it for you.
- All right.
- But right now, I want to
continue to shine a light
on this brother
and the-and the amount
of positivity
that he's doing for us
and our community.
Mike, an amazing
conversation.
We appreciate you coming on
and showing us some love, man.
We love you.
Thank you so much, man.
- Love you.
Love and respect, brother.
- Killer Mike for president!
- Yes, sir.
Take it easy, Mike.
Now, Snoop, before
we take a break, man,
I just wanna--
I want to take a moment.
This is all kidding aside.
I just want to take a moment
just to-to have the opportunity
to give you
my sincere condolences
for the loss of
your mother this year.
You know, I now how much
you adored your mom, Beverly.
And I know how much
she meant to you.
So, I feel like
we should take a moment
to reflect on
the memory of your mom
and also some
of the other people
that we lost this year.
- Thank you, Kevin,
I appreciate that.
* Yeah 'til we meet again
meet again *
* I'm been tryin'
to hold it in *
* Tryin' to be strong man *
* Every now and then
I gotta break *
* Wishing you could wipe
my tears away *
* Until we meet again
meet again *
* I'm happy you don't
feel no pain *
* but I can't pretend like *
* since you been gone
it's rainy days *
* I try to let it go
let it go let it go *
* Thank you *
* for the days
I see you smilin' *
* when you were here *
* I really do *
* I said I thank you *
* for all the game
that you told never sold *
* always clear *
* oh yeah *
* I'm tryin' to be
who you said I would be *
* life is good but
it's hard without you *
* and I'm not gonna lie *
* keep weighin' me down
I need a higher me *
* when I get home
and I'm layin' in my bed *
* who can I call on who's
the last of the mohicans *
* that knew real love *
* now I'm walkin' around this
gettin' real rough *
* I hope that we
can be together yeah *
* til we meet again
meet again *
* I been tryin'
to hold it in *
* tryin' to be strong *
* every now and then
I gotta break *
* wishin' you can wipe
my tears away *
* thank you for the days
I see you smilin' *
* when you were here *
* I really do *
* thank you
I'm so grateful *
* I said I thank you
for all the game *
* that you told never sold *
* always clear *
* oh yeah *
* I'm tryin' to be
who you said I would be *
* life is good but
it's hard without you *
* And I'm not gonna lie *
* keep weighin' me down
I need a higher me *
* when I get home
and I'm layin' in my bed *
* who can I call on who's
the last of the mohicans *
* that knew real love *
* now I'm walkin' around this
by gettin' real rough *
* said I hope that
we can be together *
* til we meet again
meet again *
* I've been tryin'
to hold it in *
* tryin' to be strong *
* every now and then
I gotta break *
* wishing you could
wipe my tears away *
* until we meet again
meet again *
* I'm happy you
don't feel no pain *
* but I can't pretend like *
* since you been gone
it's rainy days *
* I try to let it go
let it go let it go *
- Welcome back to
"2021 and Done".
- Now, you may not know this,
but celebrities get
all kinds of things
sent to them ahead of time.
- That's true.
I've already got
the iPhone 27
and I got an invite
to Oprah's inauguration.
Very true.
- They also send us all
of next year's stories
so we already know what's
gonna happen in 2022.
- Yeah, You know, Snoop,
let's give 'em a little peek,
just a little sneak peek
at what we're talking about.
- A sneak peek?
- Yeah, guys, give us
those envelopes, please.
- The man in all black.
- Mm-hmm, thank you, man.
Appreciate it.
Okay. First thing.
Cardi B.
Cardi B's gonna hit menopause
and she's gonna release
a new song called
"Dry Ass Pussy". Yeah.
- Megan Thee Stallion
will give birth
to a beautiful baby boy
and name him Tony the Pony.
- Oh, man!
Not the pony!
Not Tony the Pony!
Kyle Rittenhouse
is gonna debut
his new stand
your ground beef tacos.
So good, they'll make you cry
without tears. That's good.
- In an effort to put
the controversy behind them,
"Jeopardy" announces
its new host,
Dave Chappelle.
- Oh, shit!
By the way,
it would be great.
- It would be.
- That'll be fucking strong.
I can see it.
- I'd like it.
- Colin Kaepernick
will turn down an offer
from the Jets, saying,
"I don't want to play
football that bad."
You say Lions.
You should have said Lions.
- A Black person will
finally watch "Yellowstone".
[laughing]
- I been watching that
show for a very long time.
[laughing]
Very good show.
- It's okay, Kev.
- It's a good show.
I'm really into it, too.
Uh, I'm out.
You got any more?
- Okay, what about this one?
Elon Musk will
announce the new Tesla
that can suck your dick.
- Oh, wait a minute!
[laughter]
I mean, technically...
I mean, what's wrong
with that if that happens?
[laughing]
Like, I ain't in the wrong,
the car doin' it.
I ain't doin' it!
[laughing]
Don't be mad a me,
be mad at Tesla. Right?
Why you keep driving back
and forth to the store?
- Ask Tesla.
[laughter]
And that was
Storylines of 2022.
- Oh, shit. I thought--
that's what I wanted to do.
- We all been through a lot
this past year and half.
But one of the brightest spots
of this strange time
has been our friend, D-Nice.
His Club Quarantine
kept us positive while apart
during the pandemic.
- We got 100,000
people in here
rocking with us
right now.
This is absolutely insane!
- Say hello to
the one and only D-Nice!
- What's up, Snoop?
What's up, Kev?
- What it do? What up?
- What's goin' on
with ya, champ?
- Aw, man, I'm so happy
to be here with you guys.
- It's an honor and a treat.
It's a treat when players meet.
- Well, let's get
right to it.
Was the highlight
of 2021 getting out
of the Club Quarantine
and performing live
in front of people?
- Man, my highlight was
playing the Hollywood Bowl.
You know?
I sold out the Hollywood
Bowl in two days.
It was awesome.
- Where did the idea for
Club Quarantine come from?
Like how did you--
how did you come about?
- I was having a cigar
with one of my buddies
who used to play in the NBA,
Jimmy Jackson.
And we were just
trying to figure out
what we were going to do
for like the two weeks
that they said we were
going to be quarantined.
And he talked about working
on his commentating skills,
and I was like, hey,
they got this feature
on Instagram called Live.
They weren't really using
it that much at the time.
I was like, yeah,
I just think I'll go on there
and just play some songs
and share stories.
And then it took off.
- Huge.
And you DJ'd Obama's
60th birthday party.
You gotta give me
the details man.
- Yes.
- What was it like?
- His birthday
party was just fun.
And his thing is,
if we make the kids dance,
then we'll have
a good party.
So, Barack is never really about
playing just Stevie Wonder.
Like he wants
the [indistinct], you know?
He wants all of that.
You know?
He wants his kids to be able
to have a good time, as well.
- Super dope.
- So, D-Nice, you are--
you also DJ'd Snoop Dogg's
50th birthday party.
How was that?
- I did.
I had a blast
at your party, bro.
One, you looked amazing,
and your wife looked beautiful.
And there was nothing
but love in there.
- Hey, man, thank you
for doing that for me
on Grandma's birthday,
on Grandma's day.
You know what I'm
talking about?
- Yes, sir.
- I'm not a shit starter,
I'm all about
positivity and peace,
but you did-- you did Snoop
and Barack Obama's party.
Um, whose was better?
Whose party was better?
- Damn! That's a tough one.
Snoop's party was better.
- That's politically correct.
- Let me get
Barack on, please?
[chuckling]
If I can. Just let me get
Barack on the line, please.
Yeah, DJ-- DJ Nice said
your party was ass.
Well, listen, D-Nice,
we can't talk about what you do
and not allow you to-to put
what you do on display, man.
That is our show.
And listen,
we're going to wrap
things up here.
It's been real, honestly,
way too real, Snoop.
- Come on, man. It don't get
no realer than this.
And you ain't
gotta go home 2021,
but you gotta get
your ass up outta here!
- D-Nice, listen,
we love your positivity.
Will you play us off as we
head into the better new year?
- Please do.
- Let's do it.
- That's what I'm
talking about.
- Okay.
- Get the hell outta here, 2021.
Oh, that's your track, Snoop.
- You better know it.
- This your track.
You know what, man?
We gotta--
you better be lucky
I ain't put on my Chux.
If I didn't have
on these little pants,
I woulda
showed you something.
I don't have a lot of wiggle
room in these, Snoop.