I can't go with you tomorrow.
What?
Why not?
I'm grounded indefinitely.
How did you get grounded?
My mom found the books
and then lost her mind.
She made me return them.
I think she'd rather find pot
in my room
than a book on Ashland Falls.
That's messed up.
Well, what did you do?
I returned them.
She drove me to the library
and watched me do it.
And she was mad -- like, mad.
Well, listen.
I think my theory was right.
You have a new theory
on this house every day.
We are looking
in the wrong places.
The town borders
not only changed, they shrunk.
How'd you know?
It all goes back
to the power gr--
Uh, just a minute!
Come in!
I said come in.
Ashley.
I thought you said your parents
were taking your brother
to college.
Ash.
Jesus, Ash.
Stop freaking me out, okay?
It's probably Jesse
just messing with me.
Are you sure?
Do you want me to call someone?
No. No.
It's...
It's fine.
There's...nobody here.
Want to come over?
No.
It's fine.
Natalie?
It's nice.
It's definitely better than
the last place Bonnie showed us.
Uh, I only showed you
that last place
to get it out of your system
because I knew you would
keep asking me about it.
You know us well.
Now, this place is about the
same price, but twice the space.
How can that be?
- Sounds like a red flag, right?
- Mm. Could be a red flag.
But it's been on the market
for about three years,
and the sellers are
very motivated.
Where is Isabel?
I think she's still in the car.
Stop worrying about your sister.
Any place is better
than a freshman dorm room.
And this place definitely has
enough room for Isabel.
Uh -- Oh. She is still
going to live with you?
- Isn't that still the plan?
- Yeah.
At least for her first semester.
Well, I guess I can finally get
my piano.
Hey, Izzy.
What do you think?
Oh, and, uh, congratulations
on your scholarship.
Thanks, Bonnie.
I'm sure your mother would be
very proud.
She would.
And this place has tons of space
for your art.
You still do that, right?
Art?
It's what she got
the scholarship for.
Uh, so...
There's at least two leaks
in the master bedroom.
It even got to the first floor.
I'm looking at the living room
right now.
The living room?
How bad is it?
It's a mess, Bonnie.
I can send someone out
this afternoon and take a look.
Are you sure it's not
a plumbing problem?
Old pipes can leak,
too, you know.
Yeah, I-I'm pretty sure.
But the roof was listed as new,
right?
It was.
Have you checked Maria's studio?
No, I have not checked
Maria's studio yet.
Let me call you back.
I'm gonna show you
how to make these two ends meet
using an easy trick.
But first, my husband has to do
his regular interruption.
Sorry, everyone.
I'm just looking for leaks.
- Forgot you were recording.
- It's okay.
We've been dealing with a lot
of bad leaks
from the storm last night.
Uh, I think my studio
was spared.
I thought you retired
Martha the Mannequin.
Oh, I love Martha.
She's all I have left
of my first studio in New York.
Sure, she's seen better days.
She's about as well maintained
as our roof.
I get it. I get it.
You don't like Martha.
Now get out of here.
Hello there.
Hey.
Are you my neighbor?
I am.
I thought this house was gonna
sit on the market forever.
- My name's Larry.
- I'm Chuck.
I thought this place was
a ghost town.
Haven't really met anybody yet.
Been dealing with
some housewarming issues
since moving in.
Yeah?
What kind?
That rain we got last night.
Roof leaked
in almost every room.
Yeah.
That willhappen
in these old homes.
Hopefully I'll have
some recourse
against your old neighbor.
Said the roof was new.
Definitely not new.
Oh.
Sorry to hear that.
Pain in the ass.
But I doubt there's any recourse
to be had.
Why is that?
'Cause the previous owner
killed himself, Chuck.
They didn't mention that?
You were right about the roof.
The seller listed it as replaced
three years ago.
- You sent in all the pictures?
- Yeah.
I got up there.
That roof is not new.
Not sure how my inspector
could have missed that.
But don't worry.
I'll figure it all out.
- Thanks.
- And don't forget.
Next week you owe me
a testimonial
saying how great
Bonnie Davis Realty is.
Chuck? You there?
Yeah. Yeah. Sounds good.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Okay.
Bye, now.
Hey. Hon?
Maria.
What time is it?
It's early.
Just...Just look outside.
My God.
It's not here!
How the hell did it get outside?
Did you put it out there?
Do you think I would do that?
No, but it didn't
walk out there on its own.
What's going on?
What are you doing out here,
Martha?
Hey.
What's going on out here?
Hey, Larry.
I'm beginning to think it has
a mind of its own.
You don't know
how this got out here?
My best guess is that
my little sister is taking on
a dark sense of humor.
How is she?
Isabel.
Her, uh, mental well-being,
I should say.
Why are you asking me that?
I know what happened
to your mother.
With the car accident?
Maria sort of filled me in
on your story.
I'm very sorry.
This -- This town has had
a lot of...suicide.
People struggling
with depression seem...
the most vulnerable.
To her.
Sorry.
"Her"?
Keep an eye out on Isabel
is all I'm saying.
She knows how to mess
with people.
Isabel.
Wait.
That's it?
That's all you're gonna say?
We have a wonderful library.
You should read up
on the town's history a bit.
Friends of Gardening
are welcome.
Gardening?
Don't...do it.
I'm sorry?
Are you okay?
What's your name?
Ashley.
Can I call someone for you,
Ashley?
No.
Trust me.
Just put the books back
and leave.
Don't...do it.
Listen.
It's real.
It's -- It's all real.
Just don't look for it.
Just...
Just get out of this town.
You looking for Forest Road?
What's that?
People who, uh, take out
these old archival books
are always thinking
they're gonna find Forest Road.
It can't be found.
Uh, I've --
I've never heard of it.
Oh, by the way,
there's a young girl back there
that seems really upset.
Also, I think somebody left
a stack of books
in the middle of the aisle
in the arts section.
I'm on it.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Olivia.
- Hi, Mr. Wilson.
- Come on in.
You're my first student
at the new house.
Uh, let me take your coat.
Have a seat.
What should I do?
Let's start with some scales.
How about a C major?
So we're starting
with the basics, I see.
Not to worry.
I teach all skill levels.
- Can I get you some water?
- Water would be great.
You got it.
It's honestly refreshing
to teach someone like you
instead of the kids in my class
who think they know everything
there is about music already.
So I think this will work out
well.
So you do have some skills
after all.
Why were you...
There...
There's a woman at the piano.
A woman?
I-I th-- I think I should go.
Wait.
Olivia, what happened?
She just started playing.
I didn't see her face.
I didn't want to see her face.
...on the Internet.
If any record existed, I'm sure
the town got rid of it long ago.
Right.
But what happened in 1980?
Hey.
Chuck.
You found us.
Maria is out of town,
so I thought I might check out
Friends of Gardening.
You hiding your gardens
from the Gestapo?
Subject matter
of these meetings...
is something
a lot of the townspeople
would rather
never get discussed.
Have you seen her?
Seen who?
Come on.
Have a seat.
Thanks to those of you
who made it out tonight.
I see some more empty seats
this time.
I get that.
It's not easy to talk about.
I sometimes wish we had
an addiction of some kind.
But we've got her.
You know why the other ones
are not showing up, right?
They're scared.
I'm telling you.
One youth suicide.
Everyone is hiding again.
It's starting to feel like
1980 all over again.
You weren't here in 1980.
It's not that bad.
Yet.
I don't know.
The library books
started showing up again.
Something's going on.
We haven't had a suicide
in years.
And now that young girl, Ashley.
It really does feel like
we're starting another bad wave.
Let's not hit the panic button
yet, okay?
Anyway, Chuck here is new
to town.
I'm sorry.
Hey, everyone.
You must be wondering
what we do in these meetings.
Everyone here has been affected
by her in some way.
Lost a loved one to suicide
or...
just being terrorized by her
in some way.
Could be through
a lost loved one
or even a sentimental object.
Sometimes through their dreams.
The dreams are the worst.
They won't stop.
I have my home on the market,
but truthfully, I'm...
thinking about just walking away
from the mortgage.
Screw it.
From what I heard,
Ashley's parents
put their place on the market
once it started for her.
They should've just left.
I mean, I don't care
what kind of financial situation
you're in.
You have to go
if you're high risk.
And she was clearly high risk.
I honestly don't think
it would have mattered.
It's like an infection.
She stays with you
once she's in.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I don't know much about this.
Who are you talking about?
You keep saying "her."
I-I don't know who that is.
Helen Foster.
Who's that?
She's the one that's been
inflicting pain on this town
for decades.
It's the reason why we keep
these meetings secret.
The town discourages
active dialogue about Helen.
They say it's because they don't
want to perpetuate myths, but --
Which is just bullshit.
It's bullshit.
They know she exists.
They're just scared.
They don't know how to stop it.
It's because
it can't be stopped.
It canbe stopped
if we find Forest Road.
Forest Road.
825 Forest Road.
It's where Helen is said
to have lived in the '40s,
when she killed herself.
It's like no one knows
where it's at.
- It doesn't exist.
- No. Wait.
Listen.
I'm sure it existed once, right?
But it's gone now.
It has to be.
It's why nobody can find it.
And I know you've all tried.
Don't forget I...
I see what books you check out.
No.
Nobody can find it
because they're not looking
in the right place.
How do you know
there's a right place to look?
I mean, there's not one bit
of evidence that proves
the house can still be found.
Hey. Every abandoned structure
in town's been checked.
I don't know where to look.
Then stop looking.
You ever thought about that?
Finding that house is
the only way to get rid of her.
Don't you get that?
Hmm?
Destroy the house,
destroy Helen.
If that's where she died,
that has to be where her power
over this town comes from.
It's obvious it's outside
the town borders
as they're drawn today.
Has to be out there somewhere.
I'm sorry, everyone,
but I think it's, uh,
time to cut this meeting short,
get going.
Is it her?
We're just being careful.
Shit.
I'm out of here.
You know, sometimes
she ends our meetings abruptly.
It's happened once or twice.
You just have to keep an eye out
for the signs.
Art?
It's what she got
the scholarship for.
Uh, so...what do you think?
Well, I'm amazed at the price.
I-I feel like we're gonna find
dead bodies in the basement.
Mm. No mention of dead bodies
in the disclosure.
Listen.
This town just has really old
homes but with very good bones,
which is what you want.
Lease is up in the city
next month.
I don't think we can wait.
Yeah.
It's -- It's got good bones.
So...should we put an offer in
today?
Isabel, what do you think?
I'm not sure moving
to this tiny town
with Chuck and Maria
was a good idea.
Chuck's in his own world,
teaching, giving piano lessons.
Maria's super distracted
with the store opening
and her live stream.
The strangest thing is
that since I moved here,
I've been having these dreams
about my mother.
And every time,
it feels so real.
I know what Dr. Lewis would say.
I just miss her so much,
and it's causing me to feel
these things.
Hey.
Sorry to interrupt.
Who were you talking to?
Oh, it's just something
Dr. Lewis suggested
until I find someone
more local --
keep a daily journal of my...
you know, thoughts and feelings.
Stupid stuff.
Um...
...do you think therapy
is helping?
Yes, Chuck.
What do you care?
It's not costing you anything.
I'm your brother.
I just want to make sure
it's actually helping you.
Wow.
Izzy, these are good.
When did you draw this?
Kind of looks like
our new house.
I don't really remember.
Two, three years ago, maybe.
What's this one?
Is that you?
Whose hand is that?
Mom's?
I can't remember
why I drew that.
Just remember I drew it
right after you left us.
I didn't leave you.
I...
Maybe you can help unpack some
of the kitchen stuff tomorrow.
Take your mind off things.
Just stack it all up
like Mom did?
Remember that?
Stacking all the bowls
and dishes in a pyramid
and leaving a note that said...
They won't put themselves away.
Yeah.
Get some sleep.
Mom?
Maria.
What time is it?
It's early.
Just...Just look outside.
It's not here!
How the hell did it get outside?
Did you put it out there?
Do you think I would do that?
No, but it didn't
walk out there on its own.
What's going on?
- My dressing mannequin.
- What about it?
It's outside in the yard.
The yard?
How'd it get there?
Damn it, Isabel.
Somebody put it out there.
You don't think it was me,
do you?
I don't know.
I'm not worried
about my mannequin.
But that dress could have been
ruined if it had rained.
Sorry.
"Her"?
Keep an eye out on Isabel
is all I'm saying.
She knows how to mess
with people.
Isabel.
Wait.
That's it?
That's all you're gonna say?
You should read up
on the town's history a bit.
We have a wonderful library.
Friends of Gardening
are welcome.
What the hell were you thinking?
You really think I'd do that
to Maria?
Chuck.
It wasn't me.
Where'd you go?
Maria's out of town,
and you haven't answered
your phone all night.
Where'd you go, Chuck?
Just out.
Larry and I went for a drink
after their, uh,
gardening meeting.
Why?
Is, uh, something wrong?
I don't know.
It's...just been weird
around here.
I can't explain it.
And there's this girl
at my school.
Uh, her name's Ashley.
Last night, she killed herself.
Are you okay?
Uh...
...I don't think so.
Some things are happening
that...
I really can't tell
if they're just in my head
or if they're real.
I have a friend from school.
His name's Luke.
He said something
about this town having an...
effect on people.
Have you heard that?
No.
Have you ever...
ever had suicidal thoughts
yourself?
My heart...
My heart hurts every day.
Like...physical pain.
I hate this feeling.
Has your therapist
prescribed you anything?
I'm sure there's a pill
out there that can help you.
I don't understand why you
think I'd want to be medicated.
Okay.
No pills?
Then stick with the therapy.
But stop blaming yourself
for what happened to Mom.
That is a hole
you do not want to go down.
Mom would never blame you.
Hell, even the police said
it was nobody's fault.
It was a car accident.
A random tragedy.
Happens all the time.
And the shitty thing is that
this time it happened to us.
It didn't happen to us.
It happened to me.
I lost her, too.
You lost her a long time ago.
I realize I didn't do
a good job keeping in touch
- when I left --
- "A good job."
Your wife didn't even know
you had a sister.
Hi.
Um, is Isabel home?
I'm here.
It's nice to meet you,
Mr. Wilson.
This is my brother, Chuck.
Chuck, this is Luke from school.
Oh. Okay.
It-- It's nice to meet you.
Uh, I'm starting there
next semester.
Right.
Music history.
You signing up?
Um, maybe.
Let's go.
We'll be upstairs.
Oh.
Uh, okay.
Just...Just leave the door...
Sorry.
Let me clear some things.
You made these?
Yeah.
So, you never answered
my question the other day.
What question?
Have you seen something?
Is there something to see?
In this town?
Yeah.
And people who start
to ask questions
usually have seen something.
Chuck went to some meeting.
Gardening people?
Friends of Gardening.
Yeah.
Uh, they try to fly
under the radar
so they can talk about it
openly.
But everybody knows they're
not talking about gardening.
What are they talking about?
This town has been rumored
to be haunted forever.
Did I tell you about
the library thing?
Okay.
Well, some guy hung himself
years ago in the library.
He used a stack of books
to climb up on a rope.
The creepy part
is that the same stack of books
have been seen by people walking
in that aisle since then.
They got rid of those books,
and still they would turn up
stacked in that aisle.
Hey.
Uh, I'm sorry to interrupt.
Uh, were you just in my studio?
No.
Why?
Um, nothing.
It's -- It's nothing.
Um, I'm -- I'm sorry to bother.
It's nice to meet you.
Your sister?
In-law.
- So what's behind it all?
- Right.
So, it's all tied to a woman
who lived here
like a half-century ago --
Helen Foster.
Her daughter was bullied
at the school -- like, bad.
Really bad.
And nobody did a thing about it.
Helen wrote the school.
She even wrote the family
of the bully dozens of letters,
and still it never stopped.
Her daughter committed suicide.
Helen went down a spiral.
She lost her job,
was about to lose her house
when she killed the parents
of the bully andthe bully, too.
And then she killed herself.
Put a shotgun in her mouth.
Boom.
What house was hers?
Nobody knows.
Just an address --
825 Forest Road,
which doesn't exist
on any current map.
Has anyone ever tried to find
the house?
Oh, yeah.
But the only existing maps
from the time
have been under a court-ordered
seal since the '50s.
A while back, the town council
was supposed to vote
on unsealing the documents --
You know, throw open everything
on the location
of Helen's home --
but they never got the chance.
The 1980 town council meeting.
Yep.
Nobody really knows
what happened that day.
Uh, when the meeting
was supposed to start,
the room was locked.
People could see
the town-council members
and just one lone woman
in the audience.
Helen Foster.
I don't think this is working
the way I hoped it would.
It's the dreams.
I've never experienced anything
like this in my life
until I moved here.
They're so real.
They usually involve my mother.
I had a dream I went downstairs
and she was in the kitchen,
just standing there.
I called out to her.
She wouldn't answer me.
She would just...stare.
Then she just...
started screaming.
It was this...
bloodcurdling scream.
I'd only heard that scream once.
It was right before she died.
Thanks for inviting me out
tonight.
I didn't want to go
to this place alone.
No. It -- It could be fun.
You want to check it out?
Anything here catch your eye?
So much good stuff here.
I love when a painting
has something hidden within it,
something you might never notice
unless you stare at it
for hours.
What?
I don't know.
Maybe it's just, um...
It's exactly what Chuck says
about music.
There's something locked inside
that you won't find
unless you hear it over
and over.
Um, you want something
to drink?
Sure.
Sparkling water if you have it.
- Two.
- You got it.
Thank you.
Was this whole night
Chuck's idea?
No.
It was mine, actually.
Thanks.
You know,
I thought you didn't like me.
Why would you think that?
Come on.
You guys were fine
with your life in the city,
your apartment.
And here I come out of the blue
to mess everything up
and send you running
for the 'burbs.
Um...
Listen.
So, I have a sister.
She lives on the other side
of the country,
and the only time I ever see her
is on my sewing vlog.
You know, she sees me.
Um, but we are distant.
She just...
She never understood
the stuff that I went through
when I was younger.
What do you mean?
Um...
Well, I have, um,
bipolar disorder.
I have medication.
It keeps it mostly in check
for me.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
It's not something Chuck
and I even talk about...ever.
Um, I've had two episodes
since we've known each other.
One time he found me
in the middle of the night,
um...just swollen eyes
and bloody nose.
I was just standing
in the hallway of our building
like I had no idea where I was.
Were you okay?
Eventually, yeah.
And -- And don't get me wrong.
Chuck, he's very supportive.
But he just doesn't get it.
He just doesn't get anything
that he can't physically fix
himself.
Um...
what I'm trying to say is,
um, just I get it...
what you're going through.
God.
Come on. Let's go.
Attention, everyone.
The gallery is closing.
Please leave
in an orderly fashion.
Hey.
Uh, let's go.
It's getting worse every night.
I think I need to leave.
Okay. So a move to campus
would be great, right?
What?
It's Chuck.
He moved out when I was young,
and I hated him for it.
Now I feel like I'd be doing
the same thing,
just when we finally had
the chance to be a family again.
Okay.
So what do you want to do?
Honestly?
I want to find Forest Road.
You're not the first.
Chuck has stacks of books
from the library,
- looking for any kind of clue.
- That's already been tried.
- Maybe you can help.
- No.
- No?
I'm not getting involved
in that.
- Why not?
- Look.
Some people think Ashley
and her friend
were looking for
Forest Road, too.
So?
And they might have found it.
One of her friends told me
that...
...strange things
started happening to her
before she took her life.
It might be because she found
Forest Road.
Is that true?
I don't know!
Nobody knows. That's the point.
I'm not taking that risk.
I don't walk under ladders,
I won't open umbrellas indoors,
and I won't look for
Forest Road.
No way.
Maybe you could just find out
how Ashley did it.
- Like what she was up to.
- You're not listening.
Chuck.
What's up?
Hey, can you make it back
to the house?
Yeah, I can be there.
Is everything okay?
There's nothing to worry about.
I just need someone
to stay with Maria.
- And she's okay?
- She's fine.
Just had a little scare.
Can you make it?
Yeah.
I'm just 10 minutes away.
I'll come home now.
- What's up?
- I have to go.
I'll call you later.
What's going on?
Are you okay, Maria?
Everything's fine.
You start packing.
I'll be back in a little while.
Looking for Helen Foster's
home?
Who is Helen Foster?
Hey.
Can I come in?
Yep.
You leaving?
Tomorrow.
Moving to campus.
Chuck wants me out
after what happened to Maria.
Just like that.
Out of his life again.
How's she doing?
Not good.
Probably gonna leave
in a couple days, too.
Where will they go?
I don't know.
Chuck's just stalling.
He thinks he can find it.
Well, that's what I wanted to
talk about.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh.
I...I met your mom.
She looks a little different
here.
Nice woman.
What did you just say?
Your mom?
This is her, right?
She let me in.
That's not funny.
What's not funny?
My mom's dead, Luke.
She died in a car crash
a few months ago.
You mean you saw Maria?
I, uh...
W-Who is this?
That's my mother.
That's not who you saw.
Are you fucking with me?
Luke...
...what did you see?
Well, w-when I knocked
on the door, a-a woman answered.
She said she was your mother.
I-I said, "Nice to meet you."
She said you were up
in your room and --
and she'd be up
to check on you later.
Hey. Uh, I'm sorry.
I...
Maybe I was wrong.
Maybe...I was wrong.
I-I have to go.
Isabel.
Maria?
Isabel...it's Mommy.
These dishes
won't put themselves away.
Where are you, honey?
Don't you want to see
what you did to me?
Isabel!
Where are you going?!
And this place has
tons of space for your art.
You still do that, right?
Art?
It's what she got
the scholarship for.
Uh, so...what do you think?
Well, I'm amazed at the price.
I-I feel like we're gonna find
dead bodies in the basement.
Mm. No mention of dead bodies
in the disclosure.
Listen.
This town just has really old
homes but with very good bones,
which is what you want.
Lease is up in the city
next month.
I don't think we can wait.
Yeah.
It's -- It's got good bones.
So...should we put an offer in
today?
Yeah. I'll be in the city
tomorrow morning.
- We can talk about it then.
- Yeah. No problem.
But you'll have the floral
pattern samples for them?
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- Great.
We'll see you when you get
to the city.
- Okay. I got to go.
- Safe drive.
Bye.
Any particular reason
you're all of a sudden
so interested
in Ashland Falls history?
It'll sound stupid
if I say it out loud.
When have you ever filtered
yourself for sounding stupid?
Oh.
Uh, want to get some pizza?
Sure.
Let Isabel know.
Right.
Hey.
How do you feel about pizza?
Okay.
What?
She just said, "Okay,"
and hung up.
First few months of therapy
are gonna be rough.
They were for me
when I was her age.
What happened to you
was different.
How so?
Yours was an illness,
easily corrected by medicine.
There's nothing easy about it.
You know that.
I just think that therapy is --
A scam. Yes.
I know how you feel.
That is your opinion,
so keep it to yourself.
She was the one driving.
You have to understand the
impact that must have on her.
This place is definitely
different than the city.
But I'm fine.
I know that tone, Maria.
You're not fine.
You're a city girl.
Life in the country
isn't your style --
especially with a teenager.
How's that going
with the sister?
I don't know, Allie.
I just -- I mean, of course I'm
happy that we could help her.
I just...
I don't know if I can last
out here.
That's what I mean.
Chuck is asking you for a lot.
Yeah.
I mean, we'll just wait and see
how Chuck likes the school.
If he loves it,
we might be stuck here.
- Well, better get going.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Um, tell Mom I said hi.
- Will do.
- Love you.
Allie says hi.
Tell her hi back.
Anything interesting?
- Strange, actually.
- Mm? Like what?
Well, it's all normal
town-history stuff.
Stuff started as a coal town,
blah, blah, blah.
But then, in 1953,
the town randomly changed
all street names
and redrew its borders.
- Why would they do that?
- I don't know.
Oh.
And, uh, get this.
This house used to be...
15 Rose Lane.
Rose Lane. I love that.
Can we switch it back?
Put a rose on the mailbox
or something.
Did you find any --
Did I find any what?
"They won't put themselves
away."
What are you doing?
Cleaning up the dish exhibit
here.
Hey.
Uh, could you tell Isabel to put
things away in the kitchen?
It's not a college dorm room.
Uh, okay.
I'm off.
Wish me luck.
You have to leave already?
Uh-huh. I still have a business
I need to get back to sometimes.
Just keep your phone on
and be safe.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Love you.
Family and friends and an
entire school are in grief today
about the tragic death
of Ashley Stork
of the Ashland Falls area,
whose body was found today
in what appears to be a suicide.
Yeah.
It's just an awful tragedy.
Another one for Ashland Falls.
That town cannot seem to catch
a break.
Yeah, but Ashland has a problem
that nobody wants to --
- Hello?
- Hey, Maria. You there?
Hey, Ron. Yeah.
What's up?
Did you get on the road yet?
Because they're really
hassling us
about our booth placement again.
Of course they are.
Uh, I will be in the city
in two hours.
- Do not let them move us.
- Okay.
I'll try.
This has been going on
for decades in Ashland.
Remember, the entire town
council was found dead in 1980
because they dared to throw open
the books on the town's history.
Now, explain that.
Hello, everyone.
Uh, thank you for being
so understanding
about the late start.
It was a long drive back
from the city,
but the convention went well
despite some early
administrative hiccups.
But the good news is that we
sold out of almost everything,
including the evening gown
you all made with me last month.
Ooh.
And look at this.
I haven't even taken it all
out of the car yet.
Um, Allie, as you can see,
more than enough material
for the bridesmaids' dresses.
Um, so the conventions
are really good
for finding materials that
you won't find at a local chain,
um, whether that be special
imported fabric or just --
Um...
Uh, excuse me, um, one minute.
Oh, hey.
Um, sorry to interrupt.
Were you just in my studio?
Uh, no.
Why?
Um, nothing.
It's -- It's nothing.
Um, I'm -- I'm sorry to bother.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm...so sorry about that.
Um...
Okay.
Where were we?
- Hey. We're home.
- Hey.
How was the gallery?
Oh.
It was, uh, interesting.
Well, it's hard to compete
with the city stuff.
No.
The artists are all talented.
I'm not being an art snob.
It's just...
the weirdest thing happened.
What's that?
I don't really know
how to explain it.
Uh, one minute,
we're standing there
looking at this collection
of paintings.
The next, we're being rushed out
the door like there was a bomb.
Any idea why?
They covered up some painting
and told everybody to leave.
That was the end of our night
out on the town.
Not much else to do around here,
so we came home.
I get it.
Not in the hub of culture
anymore.
I didn't say that.
It's just hard to find something
to do with Isabel.
I mean, I was shocked there was
even one art gallery here,
but then thatclosed.
It's like...
I don't know.
How was she?
I can't tell.
But, you know, I'm just
the random sister-in-law
that didn't even know she
existed until three months ago,
so...I wouldn't begin to know
what normal was like for her.
You know, we lived under the
same roof for almost 10 years.
Yeah.
I just feel more like a stranger
to her than a brother.
That's why she's here, right?
Hello, everybody.
I, um...
Um...
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's -- It's been a hectic
few days.
Um, it's cold in this house,
um, even though the temperatures
are still warm
here in Ashland Falls.
Uh, but that reminds me.
Fall is definitely here,
and we are going to be making
sweaters from scratch,
which I think you'll have
a lot of fun with.
Uh, knitting sweaters
is a little bit more difficult
than making a dress.
But for me,
it's so much more fun
because of all the different
designs you can make.
Uh, think holidays --
um, ugly Christmas sweaters,
Halloween sweaters.
You can really go to town
and be funny and crazy.
Um, like last year,
I made Chuck a "Die Hard"
Christmas sweater
because "Die Hard" is
his favorite Christmas --
Huh.
My sister, Allison,
is calling me.
Um, Allison is a regular watcher
of the vlog,
so I don't know
why she's calling me
when she knows that I'm live.
Um, Allie,
if you're watching this,
can't it wait three minutes?
Thanks.
Um, anyways, uh,
leave it to Chuck to think
that a movie about terrorists
is a Christmas movie.
Um, but what I'm trying to say
is that you can really make
anything
once you know the basics
of the sweater.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why people are
picking right now to bother me.
Allie, if you are calling
about the bridesmaids' dresses,
don't worry.
I have it all taken care of.
See?
You just worry
about the food, okay?
What now?
Hey. Claire.
What's going on?
"Get out of the house now."
Um...
Okay. Uh, Claire, uh,
give me a ring after the show,
I guess.
Um, so the basics
of the sweater are the sa--
I -- someone's playing a joke?
I think I can get us
into some campus housing
for the short term.
We're gonna have trouble
selling this place.
Are you taking your pills?
Yes.
Okay.
It's just, the last time
something like this happened --
A thousand people saw it,
Chuck.
I know. But maybe they saw...
I can get us out of here
by tomorrow if you want.
Hell, even tonight.
I just need a little time.
This was a mistake.
I mean, I knew we never
should have left the city.
Isabel would have been fine
on her own in a dorm room.
- No, she needed to --
- You needed!
You needed absolution.
This was your way
of trying to fix everything,
but you didn't need to do
any of it!
We didn't need to do this!
Maria...
I can fix this.
What's going on?
Are you okay, Maria?
Everything's fine.
You start packing.
I'll be back in a little while.
Looking for Helen Foster's
home?
Who is Helen Foster?
Chuck wants me out
after what happened to Maria.
Just like that.
Not on his life.
How's she doing?
Not good.
Probably gonna leave
in a couple days, too.
Isabel.
Come on down here
and talk to your mother.
I know you're there, Maria.
Hey, I'm sorry. I --
Maybe I was wrong.
I-I have to go.
Isabel.
Maria?
These dishes won't put
themselves away.
Where are you, honey?
Don't you want to see
what you did to me?
Where are you going?!
Isabel? Isabel!
Isabel. Are you okay?
Where is she?
- I don't know.
- Where is she?
I don't know. Are you okay?
Are you hurt? Are you okay?
It's okay.
You're okay.
What happened to your face?
What are you talking about?
You're bleeding.
What?
Here.
I did it.
You did it?
What's going on?
We need to talk.
Everybody's obsessed
with street maps,
either in books or the records
the county has under seal.
Nobody ever thought
to look at the infrastructure,
but Ashley did.
How do you mean?
It's actually quite brilliant.
She figured out
that, by the early 1900s,
this tiny coal town
was mostly electrified.
So instead of following roads,
she figured out what we really
should be looking for.
The power grid.
Exactly.
It's the one thing the town
never thought to conceal.
The library is full of books
on the county infrastructure,
but one book in particular
actually has a specified map
of the grid layout from 1923.
Where am I looking?
Put it side by side
with any current map,
you can clearly see
the border shrunk.
Right here.
There's power lines leading
out that way,
but today it's not part
of the town.
Where are they going?
That's where Forest Road is.
I'm taking this with me.
Wait. You're going there now?
- I'm coming with you.
- Is--
Hey, Chuck,
ready for your close-up?
Don't tell me you forgot.
We're filming
your testimonial today.
I told you a week ago.
Now is really
not a good time.
Maria isn't feeling well and...
Listen...
I understand that you guys
have been
going through some problems.
This guy cost me a lot of money.
And to rebook him
would set me back.
Just give me 30 minutes.
I can do it.
Hey, hon. How you feeling?
Never better.
You go do what you have to do.
We all know I'm better
on camera anyway.
Are you sure
you're feeling okay?
Yeah.
You go look for Forest Road.
We'll be fine.
Hey. One last favor?
Can you stay here with Maria
until we get back?
I thought you were gonna ask me
to go with you.
Thank you for everything.
If you find it,
then you can thank me.
Uh, can you zoom in a little
closer on her?
Tighter.
Get in tighter.
No, I don't like that.
I don't like that at all.
Bring it out. Keep coming.
Okay, let's see
what that looks like.
How about something like this?
Eh. Yeah, okay.
All right.
Zoom in. A little further.
All right. That looks great.
All right, so, Maria,
please introduce yourself
to the camera.
My name is Maria.
And last name?
Okay, uh, fine.
Um, tell the camera
how you found out about me
and Bonnie Davis Realty.
What do we do if this
is the house?
We burn it.
Down to the goddamn ground.
Maybe we should have
called someone first.
Look, Izzy...
I'm gonna find this house.
If you want to stay behind,
it's okay.
I understand.
Go ahead, Maria.
I noticed the first
sign that something was wrong
when my daughter came home
from school crying.
Uh, I-I'm sorry.
Maria, are you talking about
how you found out about us?
You want to know how I...
How you found out
about Bonnie Davis Realty.
Oh, I see.
And daughter -- you mean
your sister-in-law, right?
What did I say?
You said daughter.
I guess she kind of feels
that way between you and Chuck.
Let me start again.
After the crying came the blood.
I began to notice drops of blood
in the bathroom sink.
This is her house.
It has to be.
Sad.
What happened to her, I mean.
She's gotten her revenge
100 times over.
Where do we start?
Look for anything that confirms
that this is the house.
I had to do something.
I had to let them know what
they were allowing to happen
was an abomination.
I was civil with
the Clarke family at first.
So, so civil.
I didn't want to hurt anyone.
I wrote letters
detailing every abuse
my daughter was experiencing.
That should have been
an end of it.
It should have been.
But it only got worse.
The school promised to do
something...
...and they never did.
I went to the town council.
They wouldn't even see me.
I wrote...so...many...letters.
They went unanswered.
I showed up at their house.
Nothing.
Nothing!
- This house used to be
15 Rose Lane.
Izzy!
Izzy. Izzy.
We have to go right now.
Izzy.
Maria?
I noticed...
the first sign
that something was wrong
when my daughter came home
from school...
crying.
Who is your daughter?
Mary.
And where is Mary?
Dead!
Izzy?
So sorry.
I saw thing.
Chuck.
Izzy!