Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
Hey, Mr. Schiller.
Merry Christmas!
Hey, Lou,
How are you?
I'm good.
Are you ready
for the big winner?
Just a few more customers.
I haven't seen
your brother yet, though.
Uh, yeah, he should be here
any minute.
Hey, what's this I hear
about you leaving Pine Grove?
I'm headed to New York
to write.
Well, isn't that
what you're doing
for the newspaper?
Yes,
but I'm going there to finish
a novel that I started.
A novel?
Mm-hmm.
Um, I love Pine Grove,
but it's time for a change.
Well, you will be missed.
but I wish you
all the luck in the world.
Hey, there he is.
Hey, sorry,
-I didn't miss it, did I?
-No.
Jeralyn thought
she was going into labor,
but it was a false alarm.
This is it, this is it.
Attention everyone!
Attention!
Everyone, attention!
The Schiller Family
Christmas Tree Farm
is happy to announce
that we just hit a milestone.
This tree marks number 50,000!
-Oh!
-Wow.
And the lucky winners are...
Aaron and Beth Taylor.
Aaron and Beth Taylor!
You two are going home
with a check
for $5,000...
-What?
...and, of course,
a free Christmas tree!
Are you kidding?
Wow!
We've never won anything before.
Thank you so much!
What a wonderful
Christmas gift!
Can I interview you two
for The Pine Grove Register?
Sure! You know...
we've never been interviewed
before, either.
Brice, get a few more pictures
real quick.
Yep, that's the one.
Okay, you guys,
Merry Christmas!
-Congratulations!
-Thank you!
Henry's a great one,
isn't he?
Hi.
How'd it go
at the Christmas tree farm?
It was great.
They had no idea
that it was gonna happen.
-You'll have it by tomorrow.
-Oh, great.
I'm uploading the photos now.
Oh, wonderful.
Oh, Brice, these are great.
Which one do you want to use?
Uh, let's go with
the surprise shot.
Yeah, I agree with Mom.
Brice, you absolutely
captured the moment.
That's great.
Merry Christmas.
The Pine Grove Candy Emporium
wants a half-page Christmas ad.
Honey, that's wonderful!
I'll go let the team know
that we need to adjust
the layout.
Hi, nephew!
Aunt Marcy!
You look great.
Same as you did
last time I saw you.
What was it, two years ago?
Well, thank you,
I'll take that compliment,
and you actually missed
the last two Christmases,
but who's counting?
Well, I didn't want
to make it three in a row.
Tell that to your parents.
Oh, they send their love
from Cancun.
They wished
they could have rescheduled.
I've heard that one before.
Come on inside.
All right.
Is that fruitcake?
Did you add chocolate
to it this time?
Ah-hah, anything else?
Triple sec?
It's going to be good
having you here.
How about
a cup of peppermint tea?
Yeah, sure.
Sure you don't mind
having me around
for the next two weeks?
Oh, as far as I can tell,
I'm getting the better
of this deal.
And you sure you don't mind
helping me at the restaurant?
I can't think of a better way
to spend Christmas.
So, how is
the job search going?
Oh, it's going.
I got a few things
I need to figure out.
There's not a lot of people
looking to hire a chef
around Christmas,
but...
I've got some feelers out there.
I was surprised to hear
the restaurant even closed.
Yeah, me too,
but times change,
and you've got to change
with them.
And you know the Tavern's
not as fancy
as what you're used to.
It'll be a nice
change of pace.
Great job
on the Christmas Tree story.
Thank you.
I am really glad
that my final piece
was about Christmas.
It doesn't need to be
your last piece.
You could cover
the Time Capsule ceremony.
It would be a great angle
to have
the fourth-generation Webbs
cover the first generation.
I am dying to see
what's inside that capsule,
but I want to have fun with it
instead of it
turning into work.
Well, you can't blame me
for trying.
I just want to keep you
around the office
for as long as possible.
I know...
but if I'm gonna finish
this book,
I actually need the time
to dedicate to it.
We're gonna miss you.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
Hey, I found these photos
from the 1921 ceremony.
That's your
great-grandfather, Louis,
holding the time capsule.
This is incredible.
It's really been 100 years.
This is going to be
a really interesting story.
You sure
you don't want to write it?
Bah! No...
I still have to pack,
I'm on the Christmas show
planning committee,
and I still have
Christmas shopping to do.
I'm booked.
Well, I thought I'd ask
one more time.
What's with all the cookbooks?
You changing your menu up?
No,
I'm looking for a new recipe
for the "Taste of Christmas."
What's that?
A local charity event,
where all the restaurants,
diners, bakeries
from the tri-county,
we set up booths,
and then at the end of the day,
the judges come around
and pick their favorite dishes.
That sounds fun.
How come I've never heard of it?
Well, because you haven't
been here early enough.
It's happens the last week
before Christmas.
Well, I'm here now,
you want some help?
You bet I do.
Especially since I lost my title
to The Fairfield Cookery
three years in a row.
Then let's go win it back.
Ah!
I know it's a few weeks late,
but here's to turning 30!
Thank you, you guys,
you really
didn't have to do this.
Of course we did!
I'm just sorry it took so long
to coordinate our schedules.
Well, that's what I get
for being best friends
with the deputy mayor
and a busy attorney
who is about to become a mom!
Which means you're about
to become an aunt.
Oh, I can't wait.
You know,
it wasn't that long ago
when all we thought about
were boys, clothes,
and really bad hair days.
Well, the only boy
I thought about was Brice.
A little sappy, but sweet.
I owe it all to you guys.
Really?
Yeah, it was the first day
at a new school,
I didn't know anyone,
and you two invited me
to have lunch.
Oh, and we went over
to Lou's house afterwards
to bake brownies.
And we ate all of them!
That afternoon
was the first time I saw Brice.
Then it took him three years
to notice me.
Yeah, he's always been
a little slow
with those kind of things.
Promise you'll be back
for the baby's first birthday?
Of course...
and Thanksgiving and Christmas.
You know, if you're gonna be
coming back that often,
maybe you should just...
stay.
I've always just stayed.
You guys have
gone after your dreams.
It's time I went after mine.
Then here's to New York...
And old friends,
and lots of video chats!
Don't you know it.
You know,
after all these years,
I still can't tell
what the secret ingredient is
in this sauce.
And I don't plan
on telling you anytime soon.
Maybe when I retire...
I've never heard you talk
about retiring before.
Well, I mean, not right now,
but someday.
But I mean, right now,
I've gotta get these orders out.
Oh, I got it.
Thank you.
No problem.
They're for table seven.
Table seven, coming up.
I know that
New York is expensive,
so I'll probably be eating
on the cheaper side.
-Yes.
-Three lunch specials.
Here you go.
Here you are.
What are we celebrating?
Years of friendship
and adventures to come.
Sounds fun.
Can I get you guys
anything else?
How about some silverware?
That would be helpful.
And maybe some salt and pepper?
Salt and pepper?
I don't think you'll need it.
This meatloaf is perfect.
I know the chef.
She uses a secret ingredient,
won't tell me what it is.
Oh, I'm putting pepper
on everything these days.
Just a pinch of salt for me.
Sure.
I'll take the salt
and pepper, please.
Okay.
Just kidding.
I've been eating
Marcy's meatloaf for years,
I know it doesn't need anything.
Because it's made with love.
Lots of it.
Yeah.
Okay, uh, bon appetit.
He is... unusual.
He's definitely different.
He's certainly the cutest
waiter she's ever had.
Thank you all for being here
on this very special evening.
We're here tonight
to witness a historic moment.
Our town's founders
buried this Time Capsule,
and to carry on what they began,
we will bury our own
Christmas Time Capsule
on December 24th
at our annual Christmas Show.
You're all invited
to bring any items
you'd like to submit
to the newspaper office,
and the committee
will then choose those items
that best represent
Pine Grove today.
Now, I'd like
to turn things over
to Eli Webb.
Thank you, Mayor Townsend.
On behalf of my family,
it is an honor to carry on
what my grandfather,
Louis Webb, began,
and I think it only fitting
that my daughter,
and his namesake, Lou,
join me in opening
this treasured box.
-We love you, Lou!
Let's see what mementos
the citizens of 1921
have left for us.
We've got a...
We have a hymn book.
-Hmm, that's nice.
-Yeah.
We have this beautiful
hand-crafted tree ornament.
Ooh...
We have a menu
from the Pine Grove Tavern...
-Oh!
It's my grandfather's journal.
Isn't that special?
May I?
Of course.
Oh...
Here we go.
We have the Christmas edition
of The Register!
With a very interesting
headline,
"Santa Claus Makes Unexpected
Visit to Pine Grove."
Who would have thought.
What have you got there, Lou?
I don't know.
Yeah, okay.
Interesting.
Sure looks good to me.
Shouldn't you taste it first?
Ha...
Okay, I deserve that.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'm sorry
if I offended you yesterday.
I can get pretty opinionated
when I get talking about food.
Well, I get that way
when it comes to bad grammar,
so...
Makes sense
since you work
for the paper, right?
How do you know
that I write for the paper?
I...
I may have asked Marcy
about you.
Hmm...
and what else did Marcy say?
She mentioned
that you were a Webb.
Just one in a long line.
Hmm,
not every day you meet somebody
with a library named after them.
Not me,
my great-grandfather.
Well, that's an impressive
family history.
Thank you.
I suppose the Webbs have made
their mark on Pine Grove.
What about you?
You're heading to New York
to make a name for yourself?
That's what I'm hoping for.
Maybe I'll see you around.
Hey, Lou.
Did you happen to ask Marcy
about me ?
No.
"He wished me
a Merry Christmas,
and before he departed,
he left me a beacon,
instructing that it be placed
in a window
a hundred years from now,
and then,
in the blink of an eye,
he was gone.
There was only the sound
of distant sleigh bells
and an infectious laugh,
until both were lost
in the night,
and whether or not
anyone believes this story,
it's Christmas,
and that's
when the magic happens."
That's a sweet story.
Mm-hmm.
It's almost like Santa
actually visited Pine Grove.
Grandpa always could
spin a good yarn.
I wonder what inspired him
to write it.
Probably just wanted
to bring some Christmas cheer
to the town.
Times were tough back then.
It was just after
the First World War,
and the way I heard it,
Louis almost packed it all in
and went to San Francisco
to try his luck as a reporter,
but he stayed
and started The Register.
Any idea
what changed his mind?
You know, I never heard
that part of the story.
Look at this,
it's a Christmas recipe
from the Tavern.
Well, Marcy's gonna love this.
At least now we know
why this was in there.
Yeah, and by putting it
in the time capsule,
it shows that Louis had
quite the sense of humor.
Mm-hmm.
Maybe it wasn't just a joke.
Okay, maybe it was.
Now, I know most of these items
are going to go on display
at City Hall,
but why don't we keep
this one here?
Just in case Santa comes back.
And the journal.
So I was thinking
about the
"Taste of Christmas" contest.
Yeah?
What about ham?
Well, I've already done
two hams,
a Christmas goose,
I've even done
a Christmas steak.
This one's perfect.
I'll take this one, thank you.
All right, I'll keep thinking.
"Gingerbread house
decorating contest"?
Is there a Christmas event
this town doesn't have?
I don't think so.
While I'm here,
I need to order some desserts.
Would you mind
opening up the restaurant?
I'll meet you back there.
Yeah, I can handle that.
All right.
There you are.
Thank you.
You need some help?
Hey...
Uh, yeah,
it might look like that way,
but I think I've got it.
You sure?
I got it.
That lock has always
been tricky.
It's all yours.
Let me show you.
Okay.
Wow.
Thanks.
I'll have to remember that.
Oh, hey, I see
you've met my nephew.
Nephew?
Yeah, I'm in town
for a couple of weeks,
helping out for the holidays.
Come on, let's get inside
out of the cold.
Yeah.
Thanks for bringing
these menus and recipes.
I just can't get over
this menu.
I have never seen
anything this old.
I've never heard of
a Christmas Caroler's Stew
before.
It must have been pretty good
if it was in the paper.
It's got an interesting
blend of spices.
Reminds me of a dish
I used to make.
Oh, you like to cook?
You could say that.
I'm a chef.
Then I'm confused.
Oh, up until recently
Kyle was head chef
at one of Chicago's
best restaurants.
Yeah, I'm only here
for Christmas.
I brought you something else.
I found the arrangement we did
for my first solo.
It's still really lovely,
and I think it could work
for the Christmas Show.
Lou was the soloist,
and the best singer
in the choir.
I just don't have the time
this year.
Lou's family
sponsors everything
from the food pantry
to the Christmas Toy Drive.
How do you find time to write?
That's exactly why
I'm stepping down
from my usual commitments,
but, Marcy,
you put on a great show
every year, no matter what.
I'm just glad I'm here
this year to see it.
'Bout time.
You know, this might be
just right for Jeralyn,
and I've got another idea.
I have a submission
for the time capsule.
So, you're a chef.
I'm in between jobs right now,
but...
it's a long story.
So, you are a writer
and a singer.
I'm trying
a different kind of writing,
a novel,
but that's also a long story.
Well,
seems like we're both
at a fork in the road,
metaphorically speaking.
Mine was a choice
I've been thinking about
for years.
Unfortunately,
mine is by circumstance,
but it's given me
the opportunity to come here
and spend more time
for Christmas.
Christmas is the best time
of year in Pine Grove.
Yeah, I might have to
agree with you on that,
based on what I've seen.
Hey, Brice!
Whoa...
These are just
today's submissions.
Wow.
Okay, well, here's another one
for the pile,
a menu from the Tavern.
I don't know how
you're going to narrow it down
to just 12.
Good thing
it's a committee decision.
Ooh...
Ooh, Mom bought these cookies
for the staff,
and since you don't
work here anymore...
Rude.
But since
I'm such a good brother.
Thank you.
I will be at City Hall
if anyone needs me.
Hey, what's there?
Anything I should know about?
No.
Just Naomi and I
setting up
the time capsule display.
Hey!
For Naomi.
Prepping for dinner already?
No, I thought we'd test a dish
for the "Taste of Christmas."
Pork loin?
Bacon-wrapped pork loin
with cherries.
I can smell Christmas already.
So? How is it?
Try it out.
It's not bad.
Mm, not bad,
but it's nothing special,
and I need this to be special
if I'm going to beat
The Fairfield Cookery.
Maybe we need to think
outside the box.
My box, but not yours.
What do you mean?
I mean, maybe
I should step it up
and let my talented nephew
teach me a thing or two
about nouvelle cuisine,
I mean, it's your specialty
after all.
All right.
Thank you.
Ooh.
Thinking about
entering the contest?
No, I was just
picking up some pastries,
and thought I'd stick around
and check it out.
Hmm, it's not too
old-fashioned for you?
Oh, I haven't had
a good old-fashioned Christmas
in years.
Usually, when I am in town,
it's just for a quick visit.
Well, you seem to have
a lot of time now.
Why not enter?
Is that a challenge?
Well, I've been known to make
a mean gingerbread house
in my day,
but you, sir,
are a professional chef, so...
Well, yes,
a chef, not a baker.
That's two different things.
I guess that does
level the playing field
a little bit.
Mm, I'd say.
All right, you're on.
Let's see what you got,
Mr. Chef.
Set it up.
That's what you call
giving it a shot?
Well, it's not
without its flaws,
but I'm happy
with the way it turned out
given the time constraints.
I used to decorate cakes
in culinary school.
I guess it paid off.
Well, you are certainly
full of surprises.
Wait till you really
get to know me.
Do you think
that's likely to happen?
I'd say the odds
are in our favor.
What are you going to do
with yours?
I don't know.
Maybe--
Well, I guess that answers
that question.
Come in!
I was on my way to the paper,
but I thought I'd swing by
and drop these off for you.
I figured you might need
all this.
Thanks, Mom.
That's really thoughtful.
Did I interrupt your writing?
I hadn't even
really started yet.
Well, it doesn't look like
you're making much progress
with the packing.
I know,
but it's just so hard
to decide what to take
and what to leave behind.
The apartment is small,
and even though
Stacy is giving me
half of the bookshelves,
it's not nearly enough space
for all my books.
You can store whatever you need
at the house.
Thanks, Mom.
Hey, Henry!
Hey, Lou.
Hey, do you need some help?
I thought I had it,
but I guess not.
-Kyle?
-Is that you?
Didn't I tell you
the odds were in our favor?
How are you handling
this tree?
Yeah, Marcy asked me to get
the biggest tree I could find,
but I think this one's too big.
Well, I think you got it now.
Henry?
We'll hold
these two trees, please?
This one and... that one.
You got it, Lou!
-I'll take that for you.
-Hey, thanks.
Yeah.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Oh, yes! Kelly's is open.
What's that?
What?
You haven't had Kelly's famous
Christmas treats before?
Can't say I have.
Ah! Okay.
So Kelly's is only here
in Pine Grove,
and their peppermint bark
is one of a kind.
You can only get it
in the weeks
leading up to Christmas.
Hey, I've had
Christmas treats before.
Yeah, but not like these
you haven't.
Come on.
Are you ready to admit
I was right?
That's pretty good.
Oh, come on!
This is like peppermint
and chocolate from heaven.
Kelly grows the peppermint
himself,
and he actually
makes the chocolate by hand.
I did an article about him
for the paper.
This is the perfect spot
for a shop.
I could even see
opening up a restaurant here.
Is that the fork in the road
you were talking about
the other day?
Mm-hmm.
The question is...
do I take the chance
to go out on my own,
open my own place,
or do I just continue on
down the path that I've been on?
Which is what?
Working for other people.
I've had some good bosses,
but at my last place,
just mismanaged the place.
He didn't have...
He didn't really care
about the food
that came in and out
of that kitchen.
It was an investment for him,
but for me,
being a chef and cooking,
it's a passion...
You know, it's like...
being in love.
I'd like to feel that way
about my writing again,
finish the novel I started.
Is that why you're moving?
I want to make my own mark
as a Webb.
And the only way to do that
is to move?
For me it is.
Why is that?
I come from a long line
of incredibly
accomplished people,
and in New York,
I won't have anyone
or anything to prove
except to myself.
But why New York?
I have a few friends there,
and since it is the publishing
capital of the world,
I thought it might be inspiring.
Okay.
That makes sense.
I promised myself
that I would get
at least two chapters done
before I go.
Well, sounds like
you've got it all figured out.
Eight years in the making.
Don't get me wrong,
but it seems like
you're falling in love
with the romance
of a new beginning
in a new place.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing.
Inspiration comes to people
in all different kinds of ways.
Hmm.
You did good, Kyle.
Oh, thank you, Lou, for helping.
This is definitely
the biggest tree we've ever had.
I'll get some refreshments.
She's great, isn't she?
Marcy? Yeah.
She's always been generous
with her time.
You know,
it's because of her
that I started writing
for myself.
How did that happen?
I was always a really big reader
as a kid,
and once, in choir,
she was trying
to get my attention,
and she couldn't
because I was so into
the book that I was reading.
Marcy suggested
that if I loved
reading fiction so much,
why not write it?
You never
considered it before?
No.
It took a little bit
for the idea to sink in.
Yeah, she's always had a knack
for bringing out
people's passion.
She's the reason I'm a chef.
We really owe her a lot,
don't we?
Yeah, I guess we do.
This tree needs more lights.
Right.
That is the best tree
the Tavern's ever had.
Thank you.
You want to stay
for dinner?
On the house.
Oh, your food
is always so tempting,
but I really should get going.
You got big plans
or something?
No, I'm just
rehearsing with Jeralyn
for the Christmas Show.
Rain check then.
-Oh, excuse me.
Oh, I need to take this.
Seems we've got a problem
with our linen delivery.
Hey, thanks again
for your help.
There's no way
this tree looks this good
without your expertise.
Hmm, I'll toast to that,
and you're right, it wouldn't.
But if writing doesn't pan out,
I can always get a job
decorating Christmas windows
on Fifth Ave.
I don't think you're
gonna have that problem.
What makes you say that?
Call it a hunch.
Hey, what's your book
about anyway?
It's a love story
set back
in the Spanish Civil War.
I was a history minor
in college.
Hemingway fan?
You've read
"The Sun Also Rises"?
Mm-hmm.
After culinary school,
I spent a year in Spain,
traveling all over.
That sounds amazing.
Yeah, it was.
Incredible.
I learned 19 different ways
to make tapas.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
You'll have to tell me
about that later.
Sorry to leave you
with a mess, but I gotta go.
No, I got it.
It's fine.
Bye.
Tapas.
Jeralyn, I love this ornament.
Thank you.
You're welcome,
but I thought you weren't
going to get a tree this year.
I wasn't, I know,
but it's just not Christmas
without one.
Or without you singing
the Christmas solo.
I don't know
what I was thinking
when I said
I'd take over for you.
Jeralyn, you have
a beautiful voice.
But I've never sung a solo
in front of
the whole town before,
and making my debut
at the Christmas Show is...
...it's a bit overwhelming.
I totally get that,
but Marcy
wouldn't have chosen you
if she didn't think
you could do it.
Maybe...
but I've got big shoes to fill.
Oh, yeah, you do.
Um, size 11!
Okay, but you are practically
a legend in Pine Grove.
Hardly.
Great-grandpa Louis--
he's a real legend.
I started reading through
his journal,
and even though his name
is all over this town,
it's amazing
how much self-doubt he had
at such a young age.
Speaking of self-doubt,
we better start rehearsing.
I need all the help I can get.
Whoo, hold on, I gotcha girl.
Come on, Mama.
Come on.
-Thank you.
Of course.
At least I've got
a great coach.
You are talking
about me, right?
Okay, okay, don't answer that.
You ready to start?
As ready as I'll ever be.
Okay, let's do it
like Marcy taught us,
and warm up.
Okay?
I don't even know
why you're worried, girl.
Come on, you sound amazing!
No such thing
as too many lights,
huh, Dad?
Now, who in the world
taught you that?
Oh, I don't know.
It's only something
I've heard you say
every Christmas
since I can remember.
Mm-hmm.
I'll be in the garage
if you need me.
All right.
Hi.
Oh, hey, Dad.
How's it going?
Finding enough room?
I actually found
a bunch of Great-grandpa Louis's
letters and stuff.
You find anything interesting?
Not especially.
Um, oh, the journal
that we pulled
from the Time Capsule
is turning out to be
a real page-turner.
Really?
Mm-hmm, seems that
the stories you heard were true.
He really did turn down a job
writing for
The San Francisco Ledger.
Did he say why?
Not so far,
but he did mention
the time capsule a lot,
and no mention of why he put
the beacon in there.
Which proves
it was just a joke.
Maybe.
Did he say anything else
about the time capsule?
Turns out
that he was frustrated
with his fellow
committee members
because they couldn't decide
what to put in it.
Well, let's hope
history doesn't repeat itself.
Yeah.
Are you sure
I can't fix you something
before you leave?
Thanks,
but your tea and cookies
were good enough, Mom.
Well, thanks for
stopping by, sweetie.
-Love you.
-Love you, too.
Uh.... Dad,
there's been something
I've been wondering for a while,
and after going through
Grandpa Louis's letters
and stuff in the trunk,
it just felt like
the right time to bring it up.
You know you can always
talk to me about anything.
Are you disappointed
that I don't want to stay
with the paper?
I know sometimes
it can be hard
to live up
to the family legacy,
but I understand your decision.
My dad was Mayor of Pine Grove,
I didn't follow
in his footsteps.
But I mean,
you stayed with the paper,
and you became publisher
after him.
Because it's what I wanted,
and what I loved.
It's not
that I don't love the paper.
I do, all of it.
I know, I know...
and all your mother and I want
is for you to find
what makes you happy.
I think I'm on the right path.
Then there's your answer.
I know moving to New York
has been a big goal of yours
for a long time...
but I think I'm the one
who's had trouble letting go.
How many fathers get to work
with their daughters
so closely, for so long.
I'll miss that.
Now it's your time,
and seeing the determination
in you every day,
I know you'll do well
in New York.
This is for you.
Dad, I can't...
It's just a little something
to help you out along the way.
Thank you.
I could never be disappointed
in you, Lou.
Now, go find yourself.
That's important
for us Webbs to do.
-Bye, Dad.
-Bye.
Now, the main difference
between nouvelle cuisine
and traditional cooking
is presentation,
and the combination of flavors
all in one dish.
So I came up with
a Lobster Ravioli
with ivory-white chestnuts,
scented with butter and thyme,
over a bed of purple carrots,
radishes, and beets.
What do you think?
I like it.
Not too far out of the box,
but just far enough.
Yeah, that's what
I was going for.
-Let's get to it!
-All right.
Where's the rest of it?
Nouvelle is also about
small plates.
Small plates I get,
but this portion
is awfully small.
Go ahead and try it.
The presentation
is just so pretty, I...
Ah, okay.
Excellent.
But?
There are just
a lot of flavors going on.
That's the whole point
of nouvelle cuisine.
That may be,
but what I'm not tasting
is Christmas.
We have two more days.
And more cookbooks
to go through.
Hear me out.
It won the drama award
for this year.
-The year that the--
-No offense, Mayor,
but I don't think
your nephew's Christmas play
should go in the time capsule!
But it's a wonderful depiction
of Pine Grove in 2021.
It's the next "Our Town".
With all due respect,
I saw the play,
and your nephew
is no Thornton Wilder.
How about we put a pin in this?
We're still getting submissions
every day,
and we have a week
until Christmas Eve,
so there's still
plenty of time to debate.
Let's talk about the ceremony.
Lou, you want to fill us in?
Yes.
So, Santa will be making
an appearance,
and passing out toys
for the toy drive,
and then Jeralyn will be
singing a solo.
I think that covers our agenda.
We'll meet again on Saturday
to go over our final choices.
Want to grab dinner?
I would, but I have to go
back to the office
and clean out my desk.
I could come along and help.
Oh, I would love that,
but then
we'd be talking all night,
and I have eight years
of memories to go through.
I don't mind going down
memory lane.
I know, but...
you know that we'd get
all sentimental and weepy,
and I wouldn't get
anything done.
Good point.
Hey, does your dad
still have that thing
from the time capsule
in the window at the newspaper?
Hmm, the beacon, yeah.
He put it there
just in case Santa
ever needs to find his way
back to Pine Grove.
Or maybe he put it there
for someone to find
her way back.
Trust me,
I don't need a beacon.
Marcy?
Hey, Marcy!
You guys open for take-out?
Hey.
Marcy already left.
We closed a bit early tonight.
Oh, okay.
Well, have a good night.
No... you don't have to leave.
What were you going to order?
I'll make it for you.
I don't know,
maybe a sandwich?
A sandwich...
Come on in, sit down.
I'll cook you something
better than a sandwich.
What's wrong
with a sandwich?
I hope you like lobster.
Wow...
I was not expecting
something so fancy.
You look nice.
Thank you. You too.
That is so delicious.
Mm.
Good.
Marcy and I made that today.
We were working on some recipes
for "The Taste of Christmas".
This one didn't make the cut.
Not Christmassy enough?
That's exactly what she said.
You don't agree?
Well, she also mentioned
there were too many flavors
going on.
I'm no food critic,
and it is so good.
It does seem
a little bit elaborate
compared to
what Marcy's known for.
That was kind of
what we were going for.
We thought maybe if we went
more nouvelle cuisine,
it would increase
her chances of winning.
We all know
how much she wants that.
If I can help her get it,
it would mean so much.
I mean, she taught me to cook.
No wonder
you're so comfortable here
in the restaurant.
Yeah, this kitchen is
the first place I ever cooked.
I was 11 years old.
I thought you didn't grow up
here in Pine Grove.
No, I didn't,
but my parents and I,
we'd try to come back
every year for Christmas,
and back when
my grandparents were here,
on one visit,
Marcy offered to watch me
for a few hours,
so she brought me
to the kitchen,
and put me to work,
and even though
I was just peeling potatoes,
I remember watching her
and thinking,
"I want to be a chef
when I grow up."
That's beautiful.
I'm sure Marcy is thrilled
to have someone follow
in her footsteps.
Yeah, she is,
but I'm sure you can tell,
our cooking styles
are different.
I feel like
I can appreciate her style
more than she appreciates mine.
Well, if this ravioli
is any indication
of what you can do,
I'm sure you'll have
your own spot one day.
Yeah, maybe.
I'm still
at that fork in the road,
but I'll deal with that
after the holidays.
You know...
I bet Marcy wins this year
with you on her team.
You think so?
Mm-hmm.
I'll get us more wine.
This is it.
I think...
I just found
the winning recipe.
That's a great idea.
My great-grandmother's
old Christmas recipe?
You don't think
that's too old-fashioned?
Not if it's done right,
maybe with a contemporary
twist or two.
No, something's
not working with this one.
Maybe too much coriander.
I'd say too much cumin.
Mine's not much better.
Should we start over again,
and use a pinch of saffron
instead of cumin?
I say we take a step back,
clear our heads.
How about a walk,
get some fresh air?
No, you go on.
I'm going to clean up here.
That was a long walk.
I stopped to help
some neighborhood kids
build a snowman.
You're still at it?
I had an idea,
I wanted to see
if it would work.
And did it?
You tell me.
Oh, now that
tastes like Christmas!
Mm... but I can't tell
what you've added.
That's my secret.
Oh, you're not
going to tell me?
I'll tell you,
when you tell me the secret
to your meatloaf.
Thank you. Please enjoy.
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
Kyle, when you take
those samples out,
make sure you go all around.
All right, I'm gonna
check out the competition
while I'm at it.
Smart.
Who do we have next?
The Fairfield Cookery.
Fairfield Cookery...
Wow, look at this spread.
It's delicious,
I can tell,
but I'll give you a...
I heard that
I need to taste your stew.
It's getting rave reviews.
Well, let's hope
the judges think so, too.
Mm... Mm.
Tastes like a winner to me.
This stew is amazing.
Absolutely fantastic!
Thank you.
Thank you. Please enjoy.
Please enjoy.
Mm! Hey!
I was just at your booth.
And what do you think?
The stew is phenomenal.
You and Marcy came up
with an inspired choice.
Okay, good.
Marcy's really anxious
about winning,
so I'm going to check out
the competition.
Want to join?
Mm...
Now I see why Marcy's worried.
This Fairfield Cookery
is gonna be tough to beat,
There's a lot
of great chefs here.
Well, it's not Chicago,
but we hold our own.
I just wish I was here
more often for Christmas.
Is there a reason
why you weren't?
Yeah, I missed
the last two Christmases
because I was with my ex
and her family.
I can't imagine not spending
Christmas in Pine Grove.
Christmas in New York
is phenomenal.
You're gonna love it.
But everyone I love is here.
So you're not leaving
a boyfriend
or anybody special behind?
Mm-mm. Totally single.
I find that surprising.
Thank you,
and if I do find a guy,
he's gonna
have to love Christmas.
Is that a dealbreaker?
Absolutely.
What's yours?
Uh, well, she would
have to love my cooking.
That's too easy.
You're right.
Thank you,
I'll take the compliment.
All right, how about this,
she's gotta have
a great sense of humor,
and laugh at my corny jokes.
What if she doesn't?
I never thought about that.
That might be too hard.
You're laughing.
I'm gonna go find my friends.
Okay.
I should get back to the booth.
I'll be rooting
for you and Marcy.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Hope you enjoy!
Hey, tell your friends
to get on over
before it's all gone.
Marcy? Kyle?
Why don't you take a break
for a second?
Okay.
Your booth is doing great.
Thank you,
but we're almost finished up,
so you'd better get some.
Oh, we tried your stew, Marcy.
Believe me, we all did.
So, what's going on?
It's our honor
to award the Pine Grove Tavern
first place for Best Entree
in this year's
"Taste of Christmas" contest.
Hey, congrats, Marcy!
This is so exciting!
I can't believe it!
Thank you.
You did it, Auntie.
No, we did it.
Yes, we did, didn't we?
One more time
for the Pine Grove Tavern!
Whoo!
Yeah!
"I knew
this would be my last Christmas
in Pine Grove,
as I'd accepted
the newspaper job
in San Francisco..."
"...And it took
every ounce of my courage
to ask my beloved Mae
to be my wife
and come with me.
It shattered my soul
when she turned me down.
She couldn't bring herself
to leave her family,
or her new community.
She had more faith in it
than I did."
Hey, Auntie.
Hey, Kyle!
What are you doing here?
I thought you were
back at the house.
Getting some last-minute
Christmas shopping done.
What about you?
Same.
Looking for something
for the Webbs.
I saw these adorable
earrings for Lou.
I'm just not sure
if they're her style.
You've been hanging out
with her lately,
you got any ideas?
I didn't even know
she had her ears pierced.
Really?
These are nice, though.
Thank you.
Oh, one second.
Hello?
Yeah.
No, yeah, I'm definitely
still available.
Sure.
Okay.
What kind of restaurant is it?
Okay, great.
Yeah, no, I'd love
to come in for an interview.
I did it.
They're perfect!
Okay, all right.
Yeah, I'll see you then.
Bye-bye.
Hey. Hi there.
What can I get you?
Two dozen Christmas Buns,
and a large coffee, please.
Coming right up.
Hey, Lou.
How you doing?
Hey.
It was a late night.
-Here you go.
-That explains the coffee.
So, what kept you up?
Writing...
or attempting to.
Ah-hah.
I've heard about this,
the proverbial writer's block.
I know you said
inspiration is personal.
How personal does it have to get
before it kicks in?
Well, it's different
for everybody.
When you know, you know.
What brings you out so early?
I've got to finish
my Christmas shopping.
I still have to get
a gift for my aunt.
Hey, you think you can
help me out with that?
I could,
but I'm actually headed
to a committee meeting.
I could meet you
in about an hour.
All right, it's a date.
Thank you.
Wait, are these
the Christmas Buns
everybody's talking about?
Yes, they are,
and you need to try some,
but not these ones.
Uh, excuse me,
can I get another one
for my friend, please?
-Thank you.
Let me know what you think
of them later, okay?
I will.
Thank you.
Yeah, I've never been
the greatest
Christmas gift giver.
You just need to know
what people like.
You know, you've got
to pay attention sometimes.
Right, okay.
Let's try this table.
You really think
I should get jewelry
for my aunt for Christmas?
Well, haven't you noticed
she always wears a brooch?
Uh...
Well, I mean, there's so many.
I don't which one to choose.
Think about
what Marcy likes to do.
She likes to cook...
uh... sing,
boss me around.
Oh, right there.
I think she's gonna like
that one.
Oh, yeah, that's the one.
He'd like to see
that one, please.
Thank you.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Can you warp this up for me?
Thank you.
Looking for a Christmas gift
for someone?
No.
I've always loved lockets.
There's just something
so special
about putting a picture
of someone you love in there,
and wearing it
close to your heart.
I know that sounds cheesy.
No, that's not too cheesy.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Merry Christmas.
Well, uh... thanks again.
All right, I'm gonna...
let you enjoy
the rest of your day.
Okay.
Kyle?
Yeah.
In case you're interested,
a few of us are going
to the town square tonight.
It should be a clear night
to look at stars,
sit by the fire pit.
Yeah, I--
Oh.
Sorry.
I'm expecting
an important message.
Good news?
Yeah.
I've got an interview tomorrow
at one of the top restaurants
in Chicago.
That's great!
Congratulations.
Thanks,
but I don't have the job yet.
I have to cook something
for the owner.
So the question is...
what do I make?
Why not show him who you are.
Cook what you love.
That's good advice.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Hey, Lou.
What time tonight?
I'm planning
to get there at 8:00.
I'll see what I can do.
Looking for something?
Oh! Naomi...
No, I mentioned to somebody
that I might be here,
but I don't think he's coming.
He?
It's not a big deal.
Okay, well, you're wearing
your new coat,
so I'm guessing it is.
You know I'm gonna find out
sooner or later,
so you might as well tell me.
Two ciders, please.
Remember the waiter
from The Tavern?
The cute one?
Yes.
Um, he's actually
Marcy's nephew from Chicago,
and he's actually
an amazing chef.
-Are you two dating?
-No.
No, we just ran into each other
a few times, that's all.
Thank you.
Well, maybe you two are running
into each other for a reason.
No.
He's from Chicago, and hello,
I'll be in New York.
Okay, you have five more days
till you leave,
you never know
what could happen.
In this case, I do.
-Okay, maybe the two--
-Not gonna happen.
Hmm.
Good luck!
You're going to love
everything about New York,
but nothing beats, nothing beats
a Chicago deep-dish pizza.
What?
Everybody knows
that New York pizza is the best.
Everybody's wrong.
I knew there was a catch.
I knew
there was a catch.
Hey, you never forget
your first meal
in the Big Apple, never.
It sticks with you forever.
It's like something
you're really passionate--
Like, do you remember
the first book that you wrote?
I was six
when I wrote my first book.
You were six?
When you wrote your first book?
Yes, but, okay,
there was exactly one copy,
and it was printed on cardstock
from my dad's office.
And did the author
sign the book?
Oh, with crayon.
What was it about?
A little girl
that goes to the North Pole
to make sure Santa is
giving gifts to the elves.
And you wrote it yourself?
Yeah.
My Dad helped me
with the pictures.
He took it to the paper
and got it professionally
printed, bound, everything...
and, um...
he got it wrapped,
and I opened it
on Christmas morning,
and I saw,
"Written by Louise Webb."
I never forgot that.
Won't be long
before you see your name
like that again.
It's frustrating, you know?
Nothing that I've been
writing lately
has been sticking.
I write the words,
and they just
slide off the page.
Well, keep going.
Sooner or later,
something's gonna stick.
Your passion
has taken you this far.
You'll get it.
Thank you.
Hey, you know
what I think is gonna help
with your writer's block?
S'mores.
You chefs think chocolate
solves everything.
It does.
This is the last batch.
We get better at this
every single year.
We sure do.
For me, it's the highlight
of the season.
Me, too.
Despite all of the work.
So much of it.
I was thinking
that I would wear my red dress.
Oh.
Would you mind if I borrow
your charm bracelet again?
Of course not,
but I think you should keep it.
Why?
I was going to give it to you
eventually,
so it might as well be now,
and it would be nice knowing
that you'd be taking
a little piece of me with you
to New York.
Oh, Mom...
I love you.
I love you, too.
Hey, Del,
it's great to finally see
your restaurant.
Well, I've heard a lot
about you
from our mutual friend, Michael,
He's been singing your praises.
Well, hopefully,
I can live up to it.
I've prepared
two of my favorite dishes.
Great.
Let's give them a go.
Mm.
This Kanpachi Tartare
is outstanding.
The flavors are just right.
This is very nice.
Thank you.
Now, what's this?
This is
"Christmas Caroler's Stew."
It's an old family recipe.
Also very nice,
but a little too
meat and potatoes
if you know what I mean.
Well, since it's Christmas,
I thought it might be fun
to have a seasonal dish.
Fair enough.
Both of these dishes
certainly showcase your talents.
Why don't you give me
a couple of days
to get back to you?
My chef is leaving
right after New Year's,
and I need to fill
that spot soon.
Are you available then?
Yes, absolutely.
That's good to know.
Sorry we're late.
Kyle just got back from Chicago.
I had to stay late
at the restaurant to clean up.
Oh, no worries.
I'm just really happy
you both could make it.
That is a lovely pin, Marcy.
Oh, you know me
and my brooches.
Who doesn't?
I see your father,
I'm gonna go say hello.
Excuse me.
So, how did things go
in Chicago?
Pretty good.
I took your advice.
Which advice was that?
I made something I love,
and I think the owner
liked it, too.
but I won't know for sure
until he actually
offers me the job.
I'll bet he does.
Yeah?
What makes you say that?
Call it a hunch.
Lou, come and say hello
to the Marshalls!
Mrs. Webb,
this is quite the spread.
Thank you.
We go all out every year.
You mean this party
is a long-lasting tradition?
It started with
Eli's grandfather, Louis,
in 1925
when he built this house.
He didn't have
much family of his own,
so he invited anyone
who didn't have somewhere to go.
That way,
no one was on their own.
Wow.
That's a lot
of Christmas parties.
Well, this town
loves its traditions.
Yeah, I noticed.
You really do have
a beautiful home.
Thank you.
It is, isn't it?
Care for a tour?
Yeah, I'd love one.
-Excuse us.
-Mm-hmm.
This is
one of my favorite places.
I used to come out here,
snuggle up
with a cup of hot cocoa,
watch the snow fall,
and become inspired.
I thought you said
Hemingway inspired you.
Yeah, well, he came after.
After reading him,
and Fitzgerald,
and Dorothy Parker,
the plan was to go to New York
and become a novelist.
So, what stopped you?
My parents offered me a job
at the paper,
and I thought
it would be good experience
before New York.
Was it?
Yeah,
but I didn't think I'd stay
as long as I did,
and I never could
quite find the time
to finish my book.
That sounds like
an excuse to me.
Hmm...
I suppose it is.
I had a big birthday this year,
and seeing all that my friends
had accomplished,
and I was still
stuck in Pine Grove
at the same job,
I... suddenly became terrified
that I would never
achieve my dreams,
so I thought, to do that,
I had to leave.
Yeah, I get that.
It's too bad, though,
It would have been nice
to spend some more Christmases
here with Aunt Marcy.
What makes you say that?
'I might have met you
a whole lot sooner.
Lou, I've been looking for you.
We need you at the piano.
Oh, right.
Coming.
Good evening, everyone.
I'd like to thank you all
for coming tonight.
I know we all
look forward to this
year after year.
Lou...
take it away.
How come no one ever
asks me to sing?
Because you sound
like a foghorn.
Shh...
Bravo.
"Pine Grove
had made me feel
part of something
for the first time in my life,
and I was deeply in love
with Mae,
so it was with a heavy heart
that I contemplated leaving.
I wrestled with this decision
for days,
but it wasn't until I realized
exactly what
I'd be leaving behind
that I had a change of heart.
My community
had become my family,
and it dawned on me that--"
"--everyone I loved was here."
"Every town
is filled with memories,
especially at Christmas.
No one could have imagined
that something found inside
a 100-year-old time capsule
would have
such a profound effect
on a young woman
at a crossroads,
or that she would utter
the same words
as her great-grandfather
whom she had never met--"
"'Everyone I love is here.'
It was enough to stop her
in her tracks."
I was thinking
about today's special.
The Quiche Lorraine?
Yeah. How do you feel about
changing it up a bit?
What would you have in mind?
How about a cranberry tart
with pancetta and thyme?
It's more or less
still a quiche.
It sounds delicious.
Let's do it.
"Her great-grandfather insisted
that he'd only printed the story
to sell more newspapers,
telling her,
'People want to believe
in miracles at Christmas,
because that's
when the magic happens.'
But she wondered
if there was more to the story
than he let on.
For instance,
why was the beacon
placed in the time capsule?
And then it dawned on her.
It wasn't the whimsy
of the Christmas season,
it was his way of telling them
that he had found
his way home."
Hey, it's Lou Webb.
Yeah, I'd like to place
a lunch order to go.
Special of the day,
cranberry tart
with pancetta and thyme.
Thank you.
You didn't have to do this.
Well, it's a special delivery.
Let me know how you like it.
You have not failed me yet.
Come inside, come in.
I hope I'm not
interrupting anything.
No, actually,
I have been writing
all morning.
How is
the Spanish Civil War going?
I... I put that aside.
I actually started
writing something new,
something I really love,
and everything
just fell into place,
and I wouldn't have even
stopped writing,
except I, uh... got hungry.
Well, that's great.
Now you don't have to move.
Are you kidding?
I'm even more excited
to get to New York.
Well then, I'm happy
you had a breakthrough.
I'm pretty happy
about it myself.
We should celebrate.
This is my celebration.
We can do better than that.
Like what?
Go out with me.
That is an interesting
proposition.
It hadn't crossed your mind?
It might have.
You know,
for two people who met
fighting over pepper
and salt shakers,
we're way ahead of the game.
We have done a lot
in a short amount of time.
So...
let's keep the momentum going?
What did you have in mind?
I heard there's
a sleigh ride tonight.
I can pick you up around 6:00?
Unless you have other plans.
I'm really behind on packing,
and the movers
are going to be here
in a couple of days.
Yeah, I guess the move
is pretty close, huh?
It'll be here
before we know it.
So, what are we saying?
That maybe
we shouldn't start something
we can't finish.
Would've been nice.
All right, I'm gonna...
I'll see you around.
Sorry I'm late.
Where have you been?
I started writing
and I lost track of time.
But we already printed
your last story.
It's not for the paper.
I started writing a new book,
and the pages
just poured out of me.
That's awesome!
I know.
And since
you're in such a good mood,
there's one thing
I want to ask you...
Yeah, what's up?
Are you taking
your desk chair with you?
Because if not,
can I have it?
What is your problem?
It's just
so much better than mine.
It, like, really goes.
Okay, it's all yours.
Thanks, sis.
You know, this place
is not going to be the same
without you.
I know.
But at least you'll always
have my chair
to remember me by.
Mm-hmm.
Let's get you a drink.
Yes. Pour it on up.
Here's to having you on board.
Thanks.
I'm very excited.
Now, you mentioned on the phone
that you had some ideas
about the menu.
Yeah.
I've spent the last
two weeks in a small town
working at my aunt's restaurant.
Mainly comfort food,
but well-prepared, high-quality.
It's the type of cooking
that reminded me
why I wanted to become a chef
in the first place,
and the type of food
that first inspired me.
Now, now, don't get me wrong,
I love nouvelle cuisine,
I love it,
but I was thinking
maybe we could
combine the two.
Comfort and nouvelle.
I understand
where you're coming from,
and it's a unique approach.
It's just not the right one
for my vision.
Now, come on,
I'd like to introduce you
to the staff.
Okay, everybody.
Time to open up
the Secret Santa gifts.
I think, this year,
Lou should go first.
Okay.
Are you my Secret Santa?
I'm not telling.
It's a going-away gift
from the entire staff.
I can't believe you managed
to keep a secret!
It took restraint.
Thank you.
This is the perfect gift,
and I'm going to miss
all of you so much.
We're just so proud of you,
and wish you all the best
on your journey.
Here's to Lou.
-To Lou!
-To Lou.
To Lou.
I'm gonna miss you, sis.
I love you guys.
Hey, you made it!
Of course.
Here, let me help you with that.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas Eve Eve,
everyone!
Just wanted to say
thank you so much
for another wonderful year
at the Tavern,
and winning back
the "Taste of Christmas" title
was just the perfect gift.
Yeah.
And I also want to pay
a special thank you
to my nephew, Kyle,
who's also just invaluable
in preparing tonight's
celebration,
and he's also done
a greater service for me.
He has decided, finally,
after so many years away,
to spend Christmas
with his aunt.
Kyle, it means so much to me
to see how far you've come
in your life,
in your career,
and that you'd take the time
to share it.
Well, maybe
in the spirit of Christmas,
you can share
the secret ingredient
in your meatloaf?
I could...
if you're willing to share
the secret ingredient
for the Caroler's stew.
Maybe after dinner.
All right, everyone, dig in,
and thank you all again, really.
Hey, what's with the long face?
What are you talking about?
Well, for a guy who just
landed the perfect job,
you don't seem too excited.
Well, that's because
I didn't take it.
I turned it down.
Why? What changed your mind?
On the drive back,
I had time to think about it,
and I guess you could say
Pine Grove.
You've wanted a job like that
forever, Kyle.
Yeah, I know,
but I had a rediscovery
over the last couple of weeks.
Cooking with you,
and the contest,
it brought out something
I haven't felt in a long time.
I want to bring my own ideas
to my work,
and not just
implement someone else's,
you know what I mean?
So, what are you going to do?
I don't know,
I haven't thought that far yet.
Well, this might be
a happy coincidence then.
What do you mean?
What about working here?
As chef, here?
Not, not just as chef,
a partner.
A partner?
I'm going to retire
eventually, Kyle.
Not soon, but someday.
And I want someone I can trust
to take care of the business
after I leave.
Now, you don't
have to decide now,
just think about it.
You okay?
Yeah.
Just feeling
a little bit nostalgic.
Do you want to come over
and sit around
the Christmas tree?
Or we could watch
a Christmas movie.
I think I'm gonna take a walk,
clear my head.
Well, whatever you got
on your mind,
I know you'll figure it out.
Yeah.
Thanks, Mom.
Good night, Dad.
Good night.
Hey.
Hi.
Mind if I ask
what you're doing
sitting alone
in the middle of town?
Just thinking.
About?
Too many things.
That's the problem.
You mind if I join you?
I've got a few things
I need to think about, too.
Sure.
You want to talk about it?
Not really.
You?
Nah...
I'm good just sitting here.
If you listen hard enough,
you can hear
the sounds of Christmas.
You can?
Shh... listen.
I can't hear anything.
I hear...
a fireplace crackling,
carolers singing...
and even the bells
from the sleigh ride
we didn't take.
Hey, you know, that would have
been a lot of fun.
Maybe next year.
I'll be back for Christmas.
Yeah, so will I.
You want to get that?
Sorry.
Brice, hi...
Yes.
Tell Jeralyn
that I'll be right there.
I'm gonna be an aunt.
I've gotta go.
Hang on, I'll drive you.
Thank you.
I can't believe
our first grandchild was born
just after midnight.
He is so cute.
We think so.
Where did Brice go?
I don't know.
He just said
he had something to do.
It's going to be a lot of fun
having a little one
around again.
Mm-hmm, and babysitting,
and watching him growing up.
I am going to love
being a grandmother.
You guys are going to be
the best grandparents.
And I like the part
about the babysitting.
So do I.
I'll just have to catch up
when I come back on visits.
We'll be here...
and you'll always be his aunt,
no matter where you are.
I don't think
that's good enough.
I just heard
that we've got
the first Christmas Eve baby
born today,
and I've got some photos of him
already printed out.
-Oh!
Can I have one of those?
Sure. Why?
Well, since he is
the first Christmas baby
born in Pine Grove,
and he is
a fifth-generation Webb,
it's only fitting
to put this picture
into the time capsule.
And that way,
in 100 years from now,
when the town opens it,
there will, hopefully,
still be some Webbs here
to find out
what Christmas was like for us.
If you want to get
that picture
in the time capsule,
shouldn't you all
be getting over there?
The ceremony is starting soon,
and someone
has to take my place.
You sure went to great lengths
to get out of your solo...
...but I do have to say,
he's so worth it.
It's my pleasure to now
introduce Louise Webb
to sing "This Christmas".
Thank you, Lou.
That was beautiful!
Thank you.
And next up,
it's time to load
the Christmas time capsule!
As you all know,
everyone was invited
to submit items
for the new time capsule.
Your submissions
were overwhelming,
but we narrowed it down
to 12 items
we felt would best represent
to future generations
what Christmas in Pine Grove
was like in 2021.
So, once again
I'm delighted
to turn things over
to Eli and Lou Webb.
Thank you, Mayor Townsend.
In no particular order,
these are the items...
a Christmas Edition
of The Pine Grove Register...
A not-so-lovely
Christmas sweater,
which I hope they don't
judge us too harshly for.
We have
a picture of Main Street
as it looks today.
We have a menu,
and an award-winning
"Taste of Christmas" recipe
from our beloved
Pine Grove Tavern.
Did you submit the recipe?
And before we continue,
we're including a photo
of Pine Grove's newest resident,
Christopher Webb,
the youngest descendant
of one of our town's founders,
Louis Webb.
Aw...
This is what Christmas
is all about.
Family.
Actually, uh...
there are a few things
that are going to take
some getting used to,
which is what I was trying
to tell you about last night.
Hmm...
What things?
Well, I decided not to take
that job in Chicago.
Really?
Yeah.
To be honest,
I haven't had
this much fun cooking since...
I don't even know when,
so I decided to stay here
and partner with my aunt.
Well, you are
an award-winning team.
You know, you had
something to do with it.
I did?
Mm-hmm.
I don't know,
maybe we could make it work.
I'm willing to go to New York
as often as I need to,
because, uh...
I'm falling for you.
I also had a change of plans.
Oh, really?
I'm not moving to New York.
What?
Why?
I can write from anywhere,
and when the time is right,
I can find a publisher,
but this...
is right now.
I'm falling for you, too.
Seeing as Christmas
is right around the corner...
Go ahead.
It's not too corny, is it?
-No!
-Okay.
Just corny enough.
I love it.
You may not have noticed
Marcy's pins,
but you do pay attention.
Did you see that?
The beacon just lit up.
I don't know
if it was the beacon,
but, yeah,
I thought I saw a light.
Probably a power surge,
energy surge,
something like that.
Maybe,
but it is Christmas,
and that's when
the magic happens.