Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
- How's it looking,
Mayor Givens?
- Hey, Cassie, everything is
coming together perfectly.
- Oh, my.
This time tomorrow,
Dickens, Ohio becomes
Victorian London.
- It's gonna
be a wonderful week.
- Oh, it depends on your
grand finale, doesn't it?
Now, how are things looking
over at the theater?
- I'm gonna say it,
this is going to
be the best version
of "A Christmas Carol"
this town has ever seen.
- It's
the 100th anniversary
of our town's production
of the play, Cassie.
It has to be better
than the best.
- Well, technically
better than the best
still makes it the best,
am I right?
It will be.
- Well, when you have
a seasoned veteran
like Ray Muller playing Scrooge,
it pretty well
directs itself, right?
- Well, not really.
I mean, okay,
so this one time
when I was at NYU,
I was-
- oh, Harry!
I'll just be over
here if you need me.
Some of these flats
are older than I am.
I wonder if we should
touch up the edges a bit?
- Hey, guys.
- Ah, Matt, you read my mind.
Thank you. You guys, your paint.
You're great.
- You got it, Cassie.
- Andy Fitzgerald,
"Dickens Gazette."
- Ah, Andy.
I know who you are.
You, uh, you've been
my parents' neighbor
for like 30 years.
- I got a part-time job
as a reporter with the paper.
It's a bucket list thing.
Just go with it.
- Is this for that Arts
and Entertainment section?
- Mayor's got us doing a
special Dickens Day edition.
He wants this year's production
to get as much
press as possible.
- Oh, that's good,
because people are
going to love it.
At least I hope they love it.
It's just, the cast has
been working so hard, right?
And I know how much this play
means to people
during the holiday.
- I wonder though, isn't
directing local theater
kind of a step
down from Broadway?
- Um, well,
I wasn't ever actually
on Broadway per se.
- Well, that's not
what your mom says.
- Well, see, I directed
a couple of shows off Broadway-
- And how far off?
- Off, off. Like,
you needed a car.
Okay, listen, the
mayor brought me on
because I know this play
backwards and forwards.
I grew up with it.
My first role was in this play.
- Ebenezer's lost love, Belle.
- Uh, no. Cratchit
daughter number three.
- Hmm.
- No lines, but, well,
I created a complex
backstory for her, okay?
- Hmm.
- And I was only six.
- Maybe I should get
a quote from Ray,
the Sir Patrick Stewart
of Central Ohio.
Is Ray here?
- Uh-
Where's our Scrooge?
- You know, he should've
been here a few minutes ago.
- Give me a call when
the star of the show
gets here, okay?
- Okay.
Okay, so, so remember Tiny Tim
doesn't feel sorry for himself.
He has a really positive spirit,
which is ultimately what
gets Scrooge to change.
- So I shouldn't act sick?
- Just let his sickness
show only on the outside.
On the inside, Tiny Tim
is like any other
happy-go-lucky kid.
- What about the crutch,
can I still use that?
- Yes, just try not
to wave it around
like a lightsaber on show night.
Deal?
- Deal.
- Okay.
- I'd better get going.
My mom's over there.
- Okay, I'll walk you.
- My mom said you were
like the best actor
in Dickens growing up.
- Aw, that's nice.
I, uh, I wasn't bad.
Okay, bye.
- Bye, Cassie.
- Hey, Brandon!
- Hi, Marilyn.
- Hi!
- Hi, Mom.
- Hey, you. getting in
some extra rehearsal time?
- Yeah, yeah.
Brandon is just so committed
to doing a great
job as Tiny Tim.
- A director's
job is never done.
- No, not until everyone
takes a bow.
Um, did you tell Andy
I was on Broadway?
- Oh, I might've
said something. Why?
- Well, because
apparently everyone thinks
I'm some big director
that's got this in the bag.
- Don't you?
- I hope so.
But I haven't worked as a
director in five years, right?
I'm not exactly brimming
with confidence.
- I blame David.
I mean, you took time off
to help him start his business.
And what did he do in return?
- Well, he amicably agreed
to a divorce and
fair settlement,
which is the whole reason
I get to have this time
to figure out my next steps.
- Well, would it be good to know
that the Palmer's are hiring
someone in accounts payable
and I can put in a good word?
- Uh,
I will keep that in mind.
Oh, oh, that's the mayor.
Uh, I gotta go.
- Okay. Bye, sweetie.
- Bye.
- Cassie, I'm sorry
for taking you
away from everything,
but, um, this is something
we should discuss
away from the rest of the cast.
- I had a feeling this
was gonna be an issue.
Ray, I can only
imagine how weird
this must be for you to
have your former student
now be your director,
but if something's wrong,
you can talk to me.
- That is the issue, Cassie.
He can't talk at all.
Raymond has laryngitis.
- Oh. Oh, okay.
Uh, Ray, I'm sure
you're gonna be fine.
I mean, you know,
all of your blocking
and your lines, right?
And I'm sure your
famous lemon-ginger tea
is gonna clear up your
throat lickety-split,
right before the show
on Christmas Eve.
- It's not that's
simple, Cassie.
Raymond has a
large vocal nodule.
- Oh.
- 40 years of performing
and teaching have finally
caught up with him.
And he is on strict vocal rest.
Not a peep for a month if
he wants to avoid surgery.
- Oh no, no Ray, I'm sorry.
I can only imagine how
hard this is for you.
- I know Ray is irreplaceable,
but I'm gonna have to find
someone else to play Scrooge.
Who's his understudy?
- Daniel Gary.
- And he's what, not good?
- Daniel won a trip to Jamaica,
and because Ray has
never missed a show,
I told him to go.
- I hate to say this,
but we may need to
cancel the play.
- What?
This is the longest running
production in the country.
We just need to find
another Scrooge.
- Who could possibly
fill Ray's shoes?
His Scrooge is iconic!
- Okay, I completely agree,
but I can just call some
of my theater friends
in New York, right?
I'm sure one of them
is gonna know a name
that we can hire to come
out and do the show.
- We don't have the budget
to hire a big actor.
Besides, this is
community theater,
it has to be someone
from Dickens.
Jake Dorsey.
I like it. I like it a lot.
- No, it's not good.
I don't like it.
- Why not?
Jake is the biggest name
that's ever come
out of this town.
- Yep.
- I can't think of a better way
to promote Dickens Days.
And he'd definitely
draws a big crowd.
- Mayor Givens,
he's an action star.
Okay? The guy's a super cheese.
There's no way he could handle
a complex role like Scrooge.
- He's a professional
actor, Cassie.
I'm sure he could
learn the part,
especially with your help.
- And his nephew is
playing Tiny Tim.
I bet he'd love to do it.
- I'm sure he's busy.
- Only one way to
find out, call him.
- Oh, you
think Jake Dorsey
is gonna take my call?
- Why not?
You were both in
Ray's theater class
together, weren't you?
- Yeah, but, you know,
we really weren't close.
You know, he was more
behind the scenes
and I was, you know.
- Cassie.
- What?
- Please get his number from
his brother and call him.
It's either that
or we'll have to
cancel the play.
- Do the right thing,
or it's the last
thing you'll do.
- Cut, cut. Cut, cut.
- Are we good? You got that?
- That was excellent.
All right, yeah. Are we good?
- Uh, let's take it again, Jake.
- Do we need to take it again,
or do you just
wanna take it again?
- No, you were great.
Let's just, one more.
We had a technical.
- All right, everybody.
Let's go back to one.
- Let's reset.
- Oh, Denise.
Everybody, my agents here. Hey.
Hey, Dee Dee, what did they say?
Did they make me an offer?
- N- oh, oh, we'll talk.
- What is that face?
It doesn't look good.
- Reset!
Hey, you.
- Oh.
- And action!
- Oh, hey, Brandon.
Hi, Allison.
- Hey.
- Whatcha watching?
- My Uncle Jake.
He's doing a huge action scene.
- Oh.
- Do the right thing,
or it's the last
thing you'll do.
Do the right thing,
or it's the last
thing you'll do.
- He is so cool.
- Sure is. Yep.
Wait, is he shooting
a movie right now?
- Actually, it says
tomorrow's the last day.
- Oh, great.
- Maybe he can come
home for Christmas.
- Ha ha, don't
count on it, buddy.
- Hi. Hi, Craig.
- Hi, Cassie.
- Dad, can I have some
more fries, please?
- Oh, only because
watching you play Tiny Tim
makes me feel compelled
to overfeed you.
Cassie-
- Yeah?
- Brandon has been talking about
how much you've
been helping him.
- Mm, he's a natural.
- Well, I hope
he's not too good,
or he might leave
us like Jake did.
- He had a dream,
honey. He followed it.
- That he did.
- I don't know if you heard,
but Ray Muller lost his voice.
So-
- Yeah, what a bummer.
- Yeah.
- Isn't that what an
understudy is for?
- Well, yes, but,
okay, so the mayor
wanted me to ask Jake
to come home and play Scrooge,
and I need a way of
getting ahold of him.
- Really? That would be amazing.
- Well,
good luck with that.
I mean, he hasn't
been home in years.
- Well, I have to try, you know?
Otherwise, um,
there won't
be a play at all.
- Here, here's his number.
I would call him for you,
but I don't think it
would help your chances.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- Did you tell them how
important this role is to me?
- You are literally
shooting the third movie
of your own franchise.
You have a catch phrase.
What more do you want?
- Okay, it is the
"Dunes of Eastlynn,"
it is my mother's favorite book.
She'd be very proud if she knew
that I was playing
the role of Travis.
I mean, I'm perfect for it.
- I get it, I do.
- I've made you a
lot of money, Denise.
All I'm asking is for you
to get me in the room.
- I will do everything
I can, all right?
But, please, don't
get your hopes up.
You know how these things go.
- Aren't, aren't
you supposed to be
my biggest cheerleader?
- I am. You are amazing.
I just, I have to take
this call, all right?
We'll talk. I promise.
Hello.
- Here you go, with all
the usual accoutrements.
That is French for
high-maintenance actor.
- I'm okay. Thanks, Ben.
- All right, then.
Well, you'll be happy to know
I finished the
Christmas shopping
for your brother, his
wife, and Brandon.
- What'd I get them?
- Oh, you were very generous.
Craig got a new
set of golf clubs,
Allison got a personalized
charcuterie board,
and Brandon got a
top-of-the-line gaming headset.
- You're the best.
- I know,
which is why you got me
a VIP weekend in Vegas.
- You know what?
You should have made it a week.
- Oh, I did.
- Good.
- So we still need
two more overcoats
and a hat for Bob Cratchit.
- Yeah.
- Cassie, just make the call.
What's the worst
that's gonna happen?
- Oh, I don't know.
Uh, maybe Jake hangs up on me
and I don't get
to direct the play
because there is no play?
- Is this about you shooting
him down for the prom?
- Well, uh, I did
not shoot him down.
I told him very nicely
that I was waiting
for Mike Van Camp to ask me.
And in my defense,
he hadn't spoken
more than two words
to me before that day.
- Yeah, I'm sure
he's totally over it.
- I just know he's
probably too famous
to even take my call.
- Well, let's find out.
- You hit video.
- Oh no.
- Hey boss?
- Yeah?
- Got a 614 number here.
- 614, that's Ohio.
You don't, you don't
need to answer that.
- Oh, shoot, uh-
- Um.
- It's a video call.
- Jake! Hi.
- Cassie Pruitt?
- Yes, hi.
- He remembers you!
- Howdy.
- Howdy?
- Yeah.
- Wow. I, um, I just didn't
think you would pick up.
- Well, I didn't.
My assistant did. Say hi to Ben.
- Oh, hi!
- Hi. You haven't
changed this high school.
- Ah, thanks.
- Okay, so the last
I heard about you,
you were taking
Broadway by storm.
Are you still crushing
the Great White Way?
- Oh, you bet. You bet.
Yeah, but listen, so I'm
back in Ohio right now.
I'm directing "A
Christmas Carol"
for Dickens Days this year.
- You're directing. You're
not gonna act in it?
- Oh, well, I actually
studied directing at school.
I just, I just thought
it was more challenging.
- More challenging than acting?
That's a weird thing to say.
Um, well, it's cool that
you're back in Dickens.
I'm sure they're happy to have
the on-and-only Cassie Pruitt.
That's a big deal.
- It is a big deal, yeah.
- Yeah, no, I know.
I just said that.
- I don't, what?
- Let me ask you a question.
Whenever I get a call from Ohio,
people want something,
like an autographed picture-
- I'm good.
- Or a lot of times they want me
to sing "Happy
Birthday" to their mom
and send it via video.
So what do you want?
- Okay. So this is the
100th Dickens Days,
which, of course, means
all eyes are gonna be
on the festival, right?
Especially the play.
- Right, I mean, the play
was the most important event.
- Exactly. And, okay, so
we've run into a little snag.
Ray Muller, who plays
Scrooge, he lost his voice.
So we don't have a Scrooge
and the play is only a
week away on Christmas Eve.
- Well, Ray is irreplaceable.
- Not necessarily.
Okay, so hear me out,
the mayor was
wondering if maybe you
would come home and
take over the role.
- The mayor is wondering?
- I know
it's ridiculous.
It's so silly. I
wasn't even gonna ask.
- Why is it ridiculous?
You think it's ridiculous
because you think
I can't play Ebenezer Scrooge?
- No, it's more that I,
well, I didn't think you would.
- As it turns out,
I'm preparing for a
career-defining role.
Yeah, I'm, I'm not
gonna be available-
- Okay, but hold on, hold on,
it's just that if, if
I don't find a Scrooge,
there won't be a play at all.
- Well, why don't
you play Scrooge?
Or is it, is it not
challenging enough for you?
- Ooh, good. Okay.
Well, I just thought
I'd give it a try.
So good luck with your movie.
- Yeah, congrats
on the play. Bye.
- That was so weird.
- Yeah, that took a turn.
- Jake! How's my handsome guy?
I bring cupcakes, your favorite.
- You're bringing cupcakes.
Did they make me an offer?
- Ah, look,
I'm sorry, Jake.
They just don't think
you have the chops
for a dramatic part.
- That hurts.
- Oh, Jakey.
- Listen, is there nothing
that I can do to prove myself?
- Look, what
do you want me to say?
No one's just gonna hand you
a meaty, dramatic
role.
Look around. Come on.
You got a good thing going here.
Don't fight it.
- So, as much as it breaks
my heart to say this,
without Ray, there's
no Ebenezer Scrooge.
And without Ebenezer Scrooge,
there's no play.
I know, I'm so sorry.
Trust me, nobody wanted
this more than me.
And I just wanted to say
thank you all so much.
You've been great, and
this is such an honor.
- Bah, humbug!
- Excuse me, this is a
closed meeting for cast.
- Bah, humbug!
- Jake?
-
- Hi. Hey, what's up?
Hi, hi, hi.
- Yeah, hi.
Can you guys just
excuse me for one sec?
Yeah, sorry. Just a minute.
- Mm, hey, guys.
- What are you doing here?
- Well, you said you
needed an Ebenezer Scrooge.
Well, guess what?
Here I am.
- Uh, yeah, what
happened to this whole
career-defining role?
- Well, I turned it down
because I want a chance
to work with a bonafide
Broadway director.
So what, you gonna make me
audition for the role now, hmm?
- Okay, guys, great news,
uh, you have a Scrooge.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Whoo!
You're gonna be great.
- I am gonna be great.
- Yeah, I know, I just,
I just said that.
- My agent, hang on. Hello?
- Look at you directing
an A-list celebrity.
This is a huge deal.
- Or a huge mistake.
I'm coming to you live from
Dickens, Ohio, my hometown.
And look at this,
this is my new cast
of "A Christmas Carol."
- Do the right thing,
or it's the last
thing you'll do.
- Did you hear that, America-
- Uncle Jake!
- Oh! Oh!
It's my nephew! It's Brandon.
Look at this kid.
Oh, my gosh.
Ah! What's up?
Hi, good to see you.
- Welcome home.
- Hi, Craig.
- Hey.
Man, I cannot believe
how big you've gotten.
You're huge.
- That's because
you haven't seen him
since he was six.
- Hey, I was hoping
that you guys
would accept my invitation
to come out to LA.
- Yeah, well, it's kind
of hard to get away.
You know, with the restaurant.
- Jake, why don't I get
your bags in the car
and get you settled
in at the house?
- Allison, that's
so sweet of you,
but I'm actually
staying at the, the B&B.
- What? You're not
staying with us?
- Sorry, Brandon.
I didn't want to
impose, you know?
It's such short notice.
Plus, I'm gonna be
spending most of my time
trying to learn my lines.
- I can help you. I
know everyone's lines.
- Yeah, the
trick is getting him
not to mouth every single one.
- Does he? Does he do it?
- But I'll see you tomorrow
at Dickens Days, right?
- Let's see. Yeah, we'll see.
- Yeah, we should
probably get going.
- Yeah.
- Okay, night!
- Welcome home, Jake.
- Bye, Allison.
- Ah, all
right. Awesome.
Great rehearsal today, guys.
I'll see you tomorrow.
- Here is your script.
- Thank you, boss.
Uh, I'm gonna head back
to the B&B and get settled in.
- Where all your bags?
- My assistant went
ahead with them.
- You brought an entourage?
- It's one guy.
- Hmm, can you walk to the B&B,
or do you need a limo?
- I can walk, as
long as somebody
rolls out a red carpet for me.
- Oh. Well, see, it's winter.
So the best I can do is
carpet of pine needles.
- Yeah? That would work.
- Yeah?
- You could do that.
- Great.
- Well, which way
are you heading?
- Towards the inn.
- Would you to walk with me?
- Sure.
So how does it feel to be back?
- Weird.
- Yeah, it was weird coming home
from New York, too.
Everything always seems so-
- Small.
- I was gonna say quiet.
- Ah, no, Malibu is quiet.
- Right.
- So I know this really
great cocoa stand
if you wanna, can I buy you one?
- Cocoa with you?
- Yeah.
- I will not say no to that.
Here you go.
- Ooh, thank you.
- This looks good.
Merry Christmas, thank you!
Wow, I mean the town
has gone all out
for Dickens Days,
this is elaborate.
- Yeah, the mayor decided
to really kick it up a notch-
- Here you go.
- For the 100th anniversary.
- Huh.
- We're even doing a
horse and carriage ride.
- Ooh, you know, the last time
I was on a horse and
carriage, I had to,
I had to jump off
of a helicopter
in land mines for
an action sequence.
- Well, I think
that is out of our budget,
but technically, so is
a movie star like you.
- All right, tell
you what, while I'm here,
let's, let's pretend
like I'm not famous.
- Oh, well, you're the
one that brought it up
with the whole
helicopter thing, right?
So, yeah.
- okay, fair point.
- True fair point.
However, I have to say
that it feels weird
being back home.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Everywhere I look, I just,
I remember all of these people
who didn't think I would
be successful at all.
- Is that why you
don't come home much?
- No, but it's why I
work so hard to make it.
Well, what about you?
How did they convince the
one-and-only Cassie Pruitt
to come home and direct
community theater?
- Well, I came back
about three months ago
to help out after
my mom's surgery,
and they needed a director.
So I just decided to
stay through Christmas.
- And then it's, is
it back to Broadway?
- Back, truth is,
I never really got there.
- Well, what does,
what does that mean?
- Well, it's a,
it's a long story and
a pretty short walk.
So maybe, maybe some other time.
- Okay.
- So what about you?
What ultimately made you decide
to come home and do the play?
- You're surprised, aren't you?
- Considering you hung up on me?
I'd say
yeah, a little bit.
- Okay, what
exactly did you say?
Directing, it's more
what than acting?
- Challenging, but that
is not what I meant.
- There it is.
- You took it wrong.
- Listen, Cassie, you
shot up the bat signal.
I answered your call.
If Dickens, Ohio
needs Jake Dorsey,
well then, guess what?
I'm gonna come
home, save the day.
Oh, my gosh.
Look where we are.
This is the best
job I've ever had.
I mean, aside from the
whole movie star thing.
- You worked here?
- What?
- You know, I
remember you worked
at your mom's restaurant, but I-
- Cassie, you used to come in
and you'd buy things
for your parents
and I was the guy
behind the register.
- Yes. Okay.
Yeah, it's all coming back.
- No.
- I remember that you were
the best set
builder we ever had.
And I remember that
you were really quiet,
like really quiet.
- I was shy.
- Aw, you were shy?
Is that why you never
auditioned for any parts?
- No, I auditioned
for every single play.
I never got cast because
all they saw me as
was the guy who
could build the set
and point the spotlight at you.
- Or, maybe you
weren't good enough.
Oh! Oh!
- Ooh!
- You don't think
I'm good enough
to play Ebenezer
Scrooge, do you?
- Well, hopefully, you
are gonna prove me wrong.
- Yeah, I am.
- Let's do this.
So this is by far the
best B&B in Dickens.
- Yeah, it's beautiful.
- Hey, boss.
Bad news, the linens
aren't Egyptian cotton.
I've overnighted some,
but it looks like
you'll have to suffer
through some low thread
count percale tonight.
- Ben, I,
I don't care about these things.
- Since when?
Hi, uh, Ben.
I'm Jake's personal assistant.
- Cassie.
- I was just joking about
the low thread count thing.
- Yeah, I feel like
you weren't though.
- No, I wasn't.
- Hey, whose team are you on?
- Yours, of course.
Here is your key.
Everything is unpacked.
Text me if you need anything.
- All right. Thank you, Ben.
- So Been seems-
- Great, yeah.
Yeah. He's great.
- So is it okay if I
run everything by you
or do I have to go through Ben?
- No. Cassie, it's me.
You just talk to me.
- Perfect. So I'm going to
text you a rehearsal schedule.
You have a fitting
in the morning,
and the festival kickoff
is tomorrow at 11:00 a.m.
- Yeah, um, I'm probably
not gonna make that,
sleeping in with
the West Coast time
and lines to learn.
- Right, except for
the rest of the cast
will be there to
promote the show.
- Okay.
- And the mayor is gonna be
there to promote that
you are now in said show.
- I'm gonna try to make it.
- Right, which is
code for, "Meh."
- I'll tell you what,
you tell the mayor
that I'm getting into character
and he's gonna understand that.
- Oh, well you do look
pretty annoyed right now.
So maybe he'll buy it.
Hey listen, Brandon
will be there.
You don't wanna
disappoint him, do you?
- Really? You're going to
bring my nephew into this?
- Mm, I just did.
- All right, Cassie Pruitt.
- See you tomorrow, Scrooge.
- Yeah. Wait a minute.
Are you calling me
Scrooge as my character,
or as a general sort
of personality trait?
- Mm, yes. Night.
- Bah, humbug.
- Good morning,
and happy holidays
from the town of Dickens, Ohio.
As mayor, I'd like to
officially welcome everyone
to the 100th anniversary
of Dickens Days.
As you know, every year,
in the week leading
up to Christmas,
our town is transformed
into Victorian London
and we are transported back
to the time of our namesake,
the great writer and
chronicler of his age,
Charles Dickens.
And for our Centennial
celebration,
we've pulled out all the stops.
Today, we'll have a visit
from Father Christmas.
And tomorrow is the
gingerbread house contest.
Then, candlelight
caroling on Main Street,
Dickens Day of Giving,
and finally, our
Christmas Eve production
of "A Christmas Carol."
This year, it's a
special privilege
to welcome home Dickens'
most famous actor
to play the starring
role of Ebenezer Scrooge,
our very own Jake Dorsey.
- Jake! Uh, you missed your
wardrobe fitting this morning.
And the mayor was on stage
hoping to introduce you.
- Right, but for what?
He was going to have
me come up on stage
and scream, "Bah,
humbug" at people.
I'm not gonna do that.
- Well, didn't have a
problem screaming it
last night at the theater,
twice.
- Because I was making
a grand entrance.
It was, it was very different.
- Are you getting cold feet?
Do you not wanna do this?
- I wanna do it, but I
signed up to do the play.
I didn't come here to
do all this other stuff.
- Okay, well, all
this other stuff,
it's part of promoting the play.
- Speaking of
promoting the play,
is that Ray Muller over there?
- What?
Ray! He'd love to see you.
Come over, come.
Ah, hi!
Oh, this is so you, Ray.
You can't even
talk and you still
find a way to help
out, thank you.
- Mr. Muller, I don't know
if you remember me or not.
I'm Jake Dorsey from your
high school theater class,
20 years ago almost.
- Yeah, that's right.
"Throttle Run."
I'm sorry for the circumstances
that have brought me here.
It's awful to hear about,
but I hope I do you proud.
Sir, they're big shoes to fill.
- Hi, Mr. Mayor.
W- hold on. Hold on, wait.
What? What do you
mean he's not coming?
Okay, calm down.
I'll be right there. Okay, bye.
- What's wrong?
- Father Christmas can't make it
and there's a line
of kids already.
What?
- Ho-ho-ho-ho, Merry
Christmas, Dawntae.
That's for you, my dear.
Merry Christmas. Pretty hair.
All right. Well, Oh!
Well, hello there, young man.
How are you? Merry Christmas.
- Hi.
- So I know I'm a
little too old for this-
- Oh, nonsense,
you're never too old
to talk to Father Christmas.
Question, would
you like, perhaps,
a pair of headphones
for your video games?
- Nah, I already have some.
- Oh.
- So I don't know
if you know this,
but my Uncle Jake is home.
He's Jake Dorsey,
the famous actor.
- Oh, I know who he is Yes.
- Well, the only thing I want
is for my Uncle Jake
and my dad to get along.
Maybe my Uncle Jake
would come home more.
I really miss seeing him.
- Well, I, I bet that I can
make that happen, Brandon.
- How do you know my name?
- Because I'm,
I'm Father Christmas.
I know everything!
Here, lad, a little
extra candy for you,
my boy, Merry Christmas.
Don't tell anybody.
- Merry Christmas.
- Brandon!
- Oh!
- I'm just wondering
if I could give you
a really important job.
- Yeah, sure.
- Could I put you in charge
of helping your Uncle Jake
learn all of his lines?
- Yeah, I can do that.
- Maybe you two could
work together tomorrow
while you build gingerbread
houses at the inn?
- Awesome. I'll be there.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- And I suppose you'll
want want a day off.
- If it's quite convenient, sir.
If I-
- If, if, if
I were to hold back
half a shilling wages.
- It's crown.
- Crown.
- Half a crown.
- Crown, right.
- Pay up.
- You're just messing up
to see how many I'll eat.
- Maybe, just maybe.
- Uncle Jake! Say
the line, please.
Do the right thing,
or it's the last
thing you'll do.
- It must be awesome
being famous.
- Maybe not. It's okay,
it's got its perks.
But sometimes,
sometimes you just
wanna be a guy
who can shove
marshmallows in his face.
You know, without
everybody paying attention,
and not be bothered
by anybody, capisce?
- Hey, we gotta get going.
- Okay, let me just wash
my hands, they're sticky
from all the candy.
- Okay.
- He's a good kid.
- Yeah.
Look do me a favor,
just try to keep in mind
that it's going to crush
him when you leave.
And you're a big deal to him.
- Well, he's a big
deal to me, Craig.
- Come on, Jake.
You haven't seen
him in like years.
- Craig, can we
talk while I'm here?
Can we have a conversation?
- You mean more than
what we just did?
I'm good. Ready?
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye, buddy.
- Yeah, I
actually remember that.
- I'm so sorry I'm late.
- It's okay.
- Hi. I'm Millie.
- Hi, Millie. I'm Jake.
I play Belle, your lost love.
I mean Scrooge's
lost love, whatever.
I'm Millie. Did I
say that already?
- Yeah, you did.
- I am so excited
for the Christmas Eve
ball flashback scene.
We get to dance together.
- Oh, Millie, honey, Jake
doesn't play Young Ebenezer.
Jake is old.
- Ah.
That's, thank you.
- Okay, she has no idea
that he is in love with her.
- Are you kidding?
Girls always know when
a guy's into them.
Okay, let's get
to work, shall we?
- Not always.
All right, so we'll just, what?
We're taking it from the top?
We'll do that-
- Yeah, yeah.
I will call action, okay.
- Okay.
- Action.
- Merry Christmas, Uncle.
- Bah, humbug.
- Christmas, a humbug?
Uncle, you don't
mean that, I'm sure.
- You're poor.
Nope. That's not right.
- No.
- I skipped something.
- Yep.
- Merry Christmas?
What right do you, what?
Merry Chris-
Nope. That's not it.
Uh, Merry, uh.
Well, Merry Christmas.
I think I'm gonna have to
find a different voice,
'cause that one...
Can we just take
it back to the top?
- Yeah, yeah, for sure.
Just please remember
this is not a movie.
There's no going
back on show night.
- I
know that, Cassie.
- I just gotta make sure.
- Um, you know what,
don't worry about it.
Bah, Humbug.
- What right have
you to be dismal?
You're rich enough.
Don't be cross.
- Do you, do you
need back again?
- No.
- Oh, guys, please do
not record rehearsals.
Actors need to feel safe
to find their characters, okay?
Thank you.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- All right, let's pick
it up from Fred's line.
- What right have
you to be dismal?
You're rich enough.
Don't be cross.
- What else can I be
when I live in such a world
of fools as this?
What?
- Nothing, it's just,
it's a lot different
from how Ray did it.
- Ray's not here, bro. I am.
- Can, can I make a suggestion?
- Most directors give the
actors a couple of times
to run through it
before they jump in
with the performance notes.
- Cool, okay.
Uh, let's just keep going.
- Hey.
- You okay?
- Yeah, no, I'm fine.
- Listen, it's
just the first day.
It'll all come together once
you get your lines down.
- It's not
my lines, Cassie.
I'm good at
remembering my lines.
I just, I have to
be in character
in order to trigger them,
and I don't know who
Scrooge is on the inside.
So I just, I don't,
I don't know.
- Okay. So listen,
I know you have a lot
more experience than I do,
but can I make a suggestion?
- Uh, yeah. Please, yes.
- Okay so when I sat
and I had problems
getting into character,
I would think about her
from the outside in.
- What do you mean?
- Okay, so I would
think about her walk
and her hair and
her posture, yeah.
Remember, Scrooge is
an old man, right?
He's cold and he's stiff
because he's too cheap
to have a fire burning.
He has a constant
scowl on his face
because he doesn't even
love his own family,
or doesn't realize
that he actually
does love them, yeah.
Does that makes sense?
- Yeah, that's, that's
really helpful, actually.
- Good.
- I'm sorry about
being uncool in there.
- Yeah, it was a little
uncool, but all good.
So some of us are gonna go
to the Three Ghost Pub
after the candlelight walk.
You wanna join?
- I would love that.
- Okay. Meet you
at the inn at 8:00?
- Great.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Thank you, Cassie.
- No problem.
- Hey, boss.
- Hey, where you been?
What is that?
- I went to Cleveland to get
some more of your moisturizer.
- Nah, you didn't
have to do that.
The hotel stuff is fine.
- I don't even know
who you are anymore.
- You know what, in fact,
I want you to keep this.
Merry Christmas, it's a
little present for you.
- Thanks. You going somewhere?
- Yeah, I am gonna do
the candlelight walk
down Main Street, and then,
I'm gonna hang out with
the cast afterwards.
What?
- I don't know. It's just,
you seem happier than usual.
- Well, I don't know,
it's kind of nice
being back home.
- You want some tasty news?
- Yes. What?
- My celebrity
assistant text group
has some chatter about
the "Dunes of Eastlynn."
And, FYI, they still haven't
cast their Travis yet.
- Huh. Does Denise know this?
- I already took care of it.
- Ben, my man, I'm starting
to lose count on my IOUs.
- Eh, don't worry. I'm not.
- All right. I'll see you later.
Noel, noel, noel, noel
- Merry Christmas!
- That was fun.
I haven't sung Christmas
carols since I was a kid.
- I know, right?
One question though,
were you lip syncing?
- Oh, busted!
Okay, A, I don't know the
words to any of those songs,
and, B, you are the one
with the beautiful voice.
- Okay, now, that
is exaggeration.
- Holiday Christmas
program senior year,
"Let It Snow."
You brought down the house.
- There he is, our
town's celebrity!
- Jake, you remember
my mom, right?
- Yeah, I remember your mom.
Come here.
You look good!
- Oh, thank you.
Everyone is so excited you
came home to do the play.
- I'm happy to help out,
but you must be very
proud of your daughter.
- Oh, I couldn't be prouder.
- Thanks, Mom.
- Oh, Cassie, look,
there's Glynnis Palmer. Go.
Go talk to her about that job.
- Mom, it's
not a good time.
- What job?
- No job.
- Okay, I'll go talk
to her. Glynnis!
- Um, so listen,
we're all meeting
at the Three Ghost Pub.
So we should probably-
- Is that where we should go?
- Yeah, we should go right now.
- Okay, get you
out of this moment
of awkwardness.
- Yeah, it was really weird.
Are you ready for Christmas
- This is an nice place.
Are you breaking my heart
Oh, look at this.
Are you ready for Christmas
- Oh, look who that is.
- Scrooge!
- Bah, humbug.
- Hi.
- Do you want a drink?
- Yes, could I get a Bob's
Buttered Rum, please.
- And I'm gonna try the
Marley's Mead. Thanks bro.
- I think you better
get out there,
otherwise you're gonna
disappoint all your fans.
- Oh, I'm not a big dancer.
I'm not a small one either.
- Just come with me.
- Where are we going?
- We're going to dance.
- No, I don't know how to dance.
- Well, look, I am
going to show you,
okay?
- Okay.
- Yes. One hand here.
- This hand goes here.
- Okay.
- And then we sway.
- We just sway?
- Yeah.
See, it's not that hard.
Um, what was that conversation
that you were having
with your mother?
What was that about?
I don't think you wanna know.
- No, I do wanna know.
Absolutely. You can talk to me.
- So it's been a long time
since I've worked as a director.
And it's just because
I put my career on hold
to help my
ex-husband's business.
And now that we're divorced,
I'm just trying to figure out
what my next steps are.
But I need to prove to myself
that I can still do this, right?
Before I just give up.
That's why I want this play
to be really successful.
- I guess that means I gotta be
the best Ebenezer Scrooge
this town has ever seen,
even though some people
say that I can't.
- I think you can.
- Ah, you were skeptical.
You were skeptical
on the first conversation
on the phone.
- I, um, that's
because I was jealous.
- Jealous? Of what?
- It's embarrassing.
I was the one that
was voted most likely
to become a household name.
Don't laugh!
- That is embarrassing.
- Do you wanna know something
that's even crazier?
- What?
- I was voted the guy
who was least likely
to leave Dickens.
- Well, I guess the
voters were wrong, right?
- They were wrong.
You know, I don't
blame you for doubting
whether or not I
could play this role,
because even after
all this time,
I'm not sure that I
have what it takes to,
to do something more serious.
- I know you have what it takes.
I'm gonna help you see it.
- Oh, okay, can...
It's close, but can
I make a suggestion?
- Uh, yeah. Yep, of course,
you are the director.
What do you got?
- So I think
the key here is Scrooge's shock
at feeling afraid for
someone else's future
rather than just his own.
- Huh, okay.
- I want you to
think about Brandon.
He is your actual nephew.
This is all here for
you. Get into it.
- Okay. All right, all right.
- Yeah, be great.
- Um, okay.
- Merry Christmas
to us all, my dears.
- God bless us, every one.
- Spirit, tell me that
Tiny Tim will live.
Oh, kind Spirit, say
he will be spared.
- If he be like to die,
he had better do it
and decrease the
surplus population.
- Yes!
- Yeah?
Yeah, yeah?
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- So much better.
- Possibly.
- Right? You're good.
- Okay, just a
reminder for everyone
who is delivering pies for
Dickens Days of Giving,
we are meeting at the
Country Grill at noon.
I'll see you there.
- Hey, I would like to
join you. Is that okay?
- I'd like that.
- Good.
- Okay.
- Nice work today. Thank you.
- I put the figgy
puddings in the back,
the mince meat and the
rum cakes on the counter.
- Hey, hey.
Ah, it smells good in here.
- Yeah, that'd be the pies.
- Yeah. This place
looks amazing.
- Hey.
- Same old vibe.
- Yeah, that's 'cause
it's the same old place.
- Hey, wait a minute.
What happened to the
second dining room?
Why is it walled off?
- A few years ago, I
had to sell the space
to the shop next door.
- Well, why didn't you tell me?
- Well, I didn't think
you wanted to know.
- Of course I wanna know.
Hey, if you needed money, Craig-
- No, I didn't need
money. I needed the help.
- Cool, I mean, can I help
with the cost of some
of these pies at least?
- Jake, we make the
pies every year.
I'm happy to do it.
- Hey, I wanna help.
- Yeah, well, Mom passed
away about five years ago
and we haven't
heard from you much,
so that's news to me.
- Just because I didn't stay
and help you run this restaurant
doesn't mean I don't care.
- I didn't ask you to stay,
and I didn't expect you to.
- You know, what
is your problem?
- My problem is, Jake,
is that you say you care
about Brandon and
the rest of us,
but we hear from you
once a year at Christmas
when a bunch of presents show up
that nobody really wants.
- Hey, I'm trying
to be generous.
I don't, I don't
know what else to do.
- It's not complicate, Jake.
Just check in once
in awhile, okay?
Come home for a birthday,
be part of your family,
not some celebrity
who occasionally
remembers he has one.
- Thanks
for the pie, honey.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Brr, all right, how
about when we're done
delivering the pies,
we go get some dinner?
- Hmm. Yeah, I'd like that.
- Yeah?
Maybe, uh, maybe Craig's?
- I don't know about that.
I saw him earlier, and
things were a little tense.
- Well, you're gonna be
with me this time, yeah?
And Craig and I are buds.
- Ha ha, what, so you're
gonna vouch for my character?
- I don't know.
I think I gotta get to know
you a little better first.
- I look forward to that.
- Holy cow.
Wow.
You look amazing.
- Thank you.
Oh, full service. I like it.
Thank you.
- Hi.
Have you seen Craig yet?
- I have not, no.
So I don't think
that sibling rivalry
will be on the menu tonight.
- There he is. Craig, hi!
- Oh, hi.
- There he is.
- Do you need some menus?
There you go.
The specials are on the back.
- So what were your
favorites growing up?
- Uh, well, chicken pot pie.
- The chicken pot pie.
- And do you still serve it?
- Every night.
- Do you remember when we
would just eat the crust,
how mad Mom would get?
- You know, I made a couple
of tweaks to that crust.
And I think it's even better,
but you should try it.
- I would, I would love that.
- Yeah, sounds good.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay, what just happened?
- I just helped my actress
change the motivation.
- First you get people
to stop filming me
and then you give me that advice
about getting into
Scrooge's body,
and now this.
- I'm just, you know.
- You're just doing your
job extremely well, Cassie.
Don't ever let anybody tell you
that you can't be a director,
because you are an
amazing director, Cassie.
You were meant to do this.
- Thank you.
It's, uh, it's really
nice of you to say.
- I'm just being honest.
- Well?
- Mm, Craig, my gosh,
this was fantastic.
This was like all
of our childhood
just wrapped up on a plate.
- And that's
why I love what I do.
- Mom would be really proud.
She knew that she was
leaving the family legacy
in the right hands.
- Well, thanks for coming in.
Jake, that means a lot.
- Well, look at that.
Well, I would offer
to walk you home, but-
- You've got to be kidding me.
Did you plan this?
- I had nothing to do
with this, I promise.
But, I mean, we can't let a
perfectly good carriage ride
go to waste, can we?
Jump in.
Can we jump in?
We're jumping in.
- All right.
- It really does feel like
Victorian London, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
- Okay, smile.
- Ah. You know, I bet Scrooge
would have hated selfies.
- Oh, I'm sorry. We
don't have to take one.
- No. Tonight, I am
not Ebenezer Scrooge.
I'm Jake Dorsey.
- What, who?
Ha ha, ha ha, yeah.
- Ha ha, zing.
- And I have, I don't know,
it's been a long time
since I've wanted
to take a selfie with somebody.
So, ready?
- Okay, yeah.
- One, two, three.
- Look cute.
- Got it. All right.
- Aw!
- There.
Are you cold?
- I am, actually.
- Here, let me get a blanket.
Oh, my gosh.
- What?
- This is so weird.
Wow, it's so wild.
It's like, of all the books
this guy could be
reading right now.
This is the book that they're
turning into the movie.
This is the role that
I wanted so badly.
This was my mother's
favorite book.
That's, that's why I
wanted to do it, you know?
'Cause I just, I just
wanted to make her proud.
- Why didn't you tell me that?
- I don't know, I mean,
I have to pace myself
about how much I
overshare today.
- I had a great time today.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Me too.
It kind of makes me wish I'd
asked you out in high school.
- You did.
Yeah, you asked me to
the prom, remember?
- You remember, you
remember the one thing
that I wish you would have
forgotten from high school.
It's amazing.
- I regret something
too, though.
- What?
- I should've said yes.
- Yeah, it's 'cause
I'm famous now.
- No, because I know you now.
- Good morning, Ben.
- Good morning, boss.
You enjoy you're
carriage ride last night?
- Ooh, I did.
In fact, you wouldn't
happen to know
who arranged that, would you?
- Santa's little helper.
So don't forget,
before rehearsal,
we've got the crew
from Cleveland today
coming to interview you
at the ice rink.
- Hmm. Okay, but
why the ice rink?
- Because it's
fun. And Christmas.
You played hockey.
- I don't, I don't want
this play to be about me, Ben.
- Isn't that
why you came here?
This is about you.
- Not anymore.
I mean, I kind of
feel like Uncle Jed
from "Beverly Hillbillies."
- You look cute.
- Cute. Cute on Scrooge.
Isn't that an oxymoron?
- It's a different
direction, I'll say that.
But, on show night
when your makeup is on
and you're onstage,
no one will think you're cute
or even remotely
attractive whatsoever.
- Okay, now you're just
hurting my feelings.
Uh, "Cleveland Today" is
coming to interview me
at the ice skating rink.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah, do you
wanna come with me?
- No, do you have any
idea how hard we worked
to get them to come here
and do a piece on the play?
But they just kept saying,
"You're too far away."
Hmm, I guess that's what
they mean by star power.
- Wanna know what they
mean by star power?
- Yeah.
- Boom, right here.
This is what they
mean by star power.
Feel it. Feel it!
- You are such a dork.
- Uncle Jake!
- Whoa!
Hey buddy. What's up?
My parents wanna know
if you and Cassie
can come to dinner
tomorrow night.
- Can we?
- We can.
- Yes!
- There you go. It's a date.
All right, you two
work out the details.
I am gonna go change.
- Your uncle is nuts.
- I know.
- Welcome back to
"Cleveland Today."
And as promised, we
are live in Dickens
with hometown
megastar, Jake Dorsey.
Jake, welcome back to Dickens.
- Well, I'm happy
to be here, yeah.
- Now, I have it
on good authority
that you didn't come home
just to do some skating.
You're here to do
community theater,
is that right?
- That's right, yeah.
I am going to play
Ebenezer Scrooge
in a Dickens production
of "A Christmas Carol."
- What made you
decide to do that?
- Well, I'm from Dickens, Ohio.
Dickens Days is
close to my heart.
And of course, Ray Muller,
who happens to be the
best actor out of Dickens
and was also my
coach in high school,
he got a little sick
so I stepped in.
- Well, that's
very heroic of you.
- Yeah.
Also, it's given me a chance
to work with a really
incredible director.
- Oh, is it somebody you've
made movies with before?
- No, actually,
somebody that I've known
for a very long time,
somebody I have a
lot of respect for.
In fact, do you mind
if we call her over?
- Absolutely!
- Cassie, come on over here.
This is Cassie
Pruitt, everybody.
-
Isn't she great?
- There she is.
Well, I was hoping we would get
to see you on the
ice as well, Jake.
Didn't you use to play hockey?
- I did.
- Oh no, no, no, no.
Sorry, I do not need to lose
my lead actor to a broken arm.
He is just fine in
this dirty chair.
- Can you imagine Ebenezer
Scrooge on crutches?
You'd be like, "Wait,
is it Tiny Tim?
Is it Scrooge? (grumbles)"
- Okay, well, Cassie, tell me?
- Yeah?
What is it like
directing such a mega star?
I can imagine it's
a little daunting.
- Ah, no, no.
Jake's a total pro.
We're lucky to have him.
- And between you
and I, tell me,
what is your favorite
Jake Dorsey movie?
- Ooh, good question.
I actually would like to know
the answer to this too, Cassie.
- Okay, well it's, um,
it's the one where he is,
he is like (imitates whooshing),
like, right onto the car.
- They all have that in them.
- Yeah, right?
That's the joke.
- Yeah.
- Just want to let you
viewers know that the festival
runs all the way
through Christmas Eve.
It's gonna be a step back
into Victorian London.
- That's right. It's
gonna be a lot of fun.
So come on down
to Dickens, Ohio,
and come see a play.
- Well, I think
you just convinced
a few thousand people
to do just that,
Jake Dorsey.
- I hope so.
I'm Carrie Lee Gaffney
for "Cleveland Today."
Now I'm going to
throw it on back
to you in the studio.
- I can't believe
that you haven't seen
any of my movies.
We're doing a marathon.
- Hey, is it cool with you
if I take the rest
of the night off?
- Ben.
- I wanna visit a couple
of friends in Cleveland.
- Oh, Ben, why don't you
take the holidays off?
I'll see you next year.
- Hey, I wanna see
you nail this part.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll see you later.
- It must be nice knowing
someone's got your
back like that.
- Yeah. I mean,
well, I pay him, so.
So there's that.
- Well, right.
No, but I think
he actually cares, though.
- He does. He does.
Actually, more than
my agent, sadly.
- Well, thanks.
Thanks again for including
me in the interview.
- Of course, Cassie.
Hey, what are you doing
for the rest of the afternoon?
- I was
actually debating
getting a Christmas tree,
but I'm not sure
if I'm up for it.
- Wait, wait a minute.
Hold on, you don't have
a Christmas tree yet?
I mean, you know
that's like a felony
in this town, right?
- I know. Yeah, it kind of is.
But you know, I just,
I've been so busy and...
Okay, the truth is
Christmas kind of reminds me
of my ex-husband,
and I just didn't
wanna do it alone.
- Well, guess what?
You're not alone.
When I was a kid,
my favorite thing
was decorating a
huge Christmas tree.
- Yeah?
And when I worked here,
I had this knack for
finding the perfect tree
for every customer.
- Hmm, what's the secret?
- The secret was
finding the tree
that's right for you.
- Oh, so I should look for one
going through a rough patch?
- Well,
it's funny, you know,
if a tree has gone
through a rough patch,
it makes it the strongest
tree on the lot.
- I like the way you think.
I think this is it.
- Yeah? That's the one?
- Yeah.
- Jake?
- Matt!
Ah, what's up brother?
Oh, look at this guy.
Oh, look at you.
- You wanna work here again?
- It's
tempting, actually.
- You're great at
drawing in crowds.
- Ah, it's probably
just the popcorn.
- It could be.
- It's good to see you, man.
- Have fun, guys.
- Bye.
- That's amazing.
Well, this is, this
is a lot better
than what I would
be doing in LA.
- Yeah? What would you be doing?
- Um, well, I'd probably
be watching old movies
in my pajamas, and then be
sulking about being alone.
And then I would be
spying on my brother,
Craig, and his family
via social media.
- Is there a reason you wouldn't
just come home for the holidays?
- Ever since
my mother passed away,
I have found it very
hard to come back here,
especially at Christmastime,
which I guess makes Craig
feel like I don't care.
He doesn't understand it,
which makes my feelings get hurt
and I don't understand him.
And then, we sort
of just drift apart,
which I guess is how
that happens, so.
- Your home now, right?
- Yeah.
- So maybe it's
time for new start?
- Yeah. And it's
going pretty good.
- Good.
- All right.
Should we do the magic three?
- Yes.
- Remember that?
- I do.
- Okay.
- Okay. Here we go.
- One, two, three.
- Oh!
- It never gets old.
- It works though.
It's beautiful.
You know the only
thing that's missing
is a bunch of presents
under the tree.
- No, I'm good.
I'm, I'm very content
with what I have.
- Okay, I have a
confession to make.
- You're married?
- No.
- Okay.
- When we were in high school,
I made a present for you,
and I didn't have a
courage to give it to you.
- Why?
- Well, because I
asked you to the prom
and that took me two weeks
to muster up the
courage for that
and then you turned me down.
So, you know, I could
only imagine how,
how the gift was just gonna
Right?
- Okay. So what was it?
Do you remember?
- Yeah, of course
I remember what it was.
- And?
- No, I'm not gonna tell you.
- Jake!
not the man I was.m not, m
I am not the man I.
I am not the man I was.
- Okay.
So this whole,
this whole story
is about changing your life
before it's too late.
Now, I know you've had success,
but so has Scrooge, right?
And it's, it's the other things,
the important things,
the things that matter
to us at Christmastime
that he still has
the power to change.
And I just see that you
are so busy up in here.
I need you to get
out of your head
and into your body.
- Yeah.
- Spirit! Hear me.
I am not the man I was.
I will not be that
man that I have been
for so many years.
Why show me all this
if I am past all hope?
Assure me that I yet
may change the shadows
that you have shown me.
Let the boy live!
I will honor Christmas
in my heart and keep it,
try to keep it all the year,
in the past and the
present and the future.
The spirits of all three
shall strive within me.
I will not shut out the
lessons that they teach,
the lessons that they teach.
- Brilliant.
Ah, it was so good.
Mm.
Now this is mulled wine.
It's a English
Christmas tradition.
- Ooh, it smell spicy.
- One of the vendors
made it in his garage.
- Ooh, garage wine. Risky!
- Craig actually
tried to make eggnog
a couple of years ago.
It didn't go his way.
- Can I try?
- Sure, son.
No, just kidding.
- Uh, maybe in a few years.
- Mm, I got something
for you to try. Hang on.
Here you go, buddy.
- Oh, Christmas 'crackers.
- Uh, you got my
child explosives?
- I did. Yeah,
apologies in advance.
Although Craig and I,
we used to blow those
things up every Christmas.
Good times, good memories.
- Blew the place up.
- Speaking of, do you
happen to have the stuff
that I left at Mom's?
- Well, as a matter
of fact, yes.
It's been collecting
dust in the shed.
Walk this way.
- Cheers.
- Good thing. Cheers.
- Oh, Dickens League champs,
peewee division.
I remember that.
Do you remember the summer
you taught me how to
throw a curve ball?
- You mean I tried
to teach you how to
throw a curve ball?
- No, no, you taught me.
- No no, it didn't curve much.
- No, it curved!
- That's what big
brothers are for.
- Oh, wow.
I'm sorry, I, I have been gone
for the past few years.
And I'm sorry.
- You missed a lot.
But I'm sorry too.
- Why? Why are you sorry?
- You know, when mom got sick
and you were already
in LA working,
my life here was,
you know, trying to
keep the restaurant open
and taking care of her.
It was hard.
So when she died
and you came home
for the funeral, I was angry,
and I said a bunch of
things I shouldn't have.
So I'm sorry.
- Yeah. Yeah, I remember.
And I also said a lot
of stuff that I regret.
That was rough patch.
- You know, the truth
is, I like it here.
I love Dickens, and I
love the restaurant.
And I'm happy for you.
Mom would be proud of you.
I'm proud of you.
- I just miss her, man.
- And I know that she
would be proud of you.
She really would be.
She would also be
really jealous of you,
because the crust, man,
on her chicken pot pie.
'Cause it's, it was
better.
Hey, I'm coming home a
lot from here on out.
So you're gonna wish that
I would leave, actually.
- Love you, man.
- So before we get ready
for our dress rehearsal,
I just wanna say
that this has been
one of the best
weeks of my life.
Thanks to all of you.
Thank you.
- And here's the
Cassie for bringing out
the best in all of us.
Oh! Now, before I forget,
all right, here they are.
Okay, a little birdie
told me that Ray
used to get you all a
present before the show.
- It was me. I'm the bird.
- That's right, he is.
So I know this is
just dress rehearsal,
but I wanted to thank you
for your patience with me
and just for making me feel
like part of the family.
- Aw, thanks, Jake.
- Merry Christmas.
- A pocket watch!
Thanks, Jake.
Thank you!
- Thanks, Jake.
- And you, come here.
All right.
- You didn't have
to get me something.
- Technically I didn't.
I couldn't believe it,
but when I was going through
all my stuff at Craig's,
I found this.
This is the gift that I made you
all those years ago
that I never gave you.
- What?
Is this an actual mixed tape?
- It is, yeah,
it's the collection
of all my favorite songs.
Old things.
- How am I supposed to play it?
- I don't know.
- Thank you, Jake.
- Thank you, Cassie,
for everything.
- And I got something
for you too.
- You did?
- I did.
- Ah!
- Look here. Aw, man.
This is awesome.
"To my all-time
favorite Scrooge.
It's all right, it's all true,
it all happened, Cassie."
Is this the line from the play?
- Have I taught you nothing?
- Thank you.
This is an amazing gift.
- I'm so glad you like it.
- I love it.
I love it.
- Jake!
- Yes.
- I've been trying
to get ahold of you.
- Uh, yeah, 60,000 texts later.
What's going on?
- So don't kill me,
but I may have recorded
some of your rehearsals.
- Why?
- Before you get upset,
I may have sent some
of the best parts
to some people who
may have sent it
to their bosses at the studio
making "Dunes of Eastlynn."
And the producers are
considering you for the role.
- The role?
- The role.
- Jake, that's amazing!
- Okay, hold on a second.
Why, why hasn't
Denise called me yet?
- Oh, I think your
agent is still trying
to figure out how to
take credit for it.
- Well, we know who
the credit belongs to.
It belongs to you,
and it belongs to you.
- There is one thing you
have to do first though.
- What?
- The producer, Jeff MacQuarrie,
he has this holiday
party every year.
- Yeah, okay.
So this party in
Hollywood, it's like,
it's infamous.
You have to be in his inner
circle to get invited.
- You're invited, Jake.
- Ah, are you kidding me?
- That's amazing.
- He wants to meet you first
before he makes
his big decision.
- Of course he does, absolutely.
When is it?
- Tomorrow night.
Christmas Eve.
- Gosh darn it.
Well, that's a no-brainer.
I made a commitment to
Cassie, to the play.
I'm not going.
- Jake, I'm sorry,
but you have to
play the game here.
If you want a shot at this part,
you have to be there.
- Yeah, well, I'm
not gonna be, so.
- Jake, I think you should go.
- Ben, give me
just five minutes.
Yeah? Five minutes.
What are you talking about?
- The whole reason you're here
is for this exact
career-defining role,
and now you have a shot.
I am not gonna be the one
to stand in the way
of your dream part.
- Okay, with all due respect,
I understand that.
But what about the play?
- We'll figure it out.
- Cassie, you needed
this to be a success.
- No, what I needed
was to remember
why I love directing.
It's not about success,
it's about the whole production,
the whole experience with
the cast and the crew
and watching the whole
play come together,
helping you find
that inner Scrooge.
Yeah, that's the whole thing.
And it all made me
realize that, directing,
that is what I am meant to do,
and that's not gonna change.
- You know what else
is not gonna change?
Your Scrooge.
I'm staying.
- Then I'm kicking
you off the show.
- What are you talking about?
You can't do that.
- I just did.
Jake, you've wanted
this for so long,
and you're ready.
You're ready.
- But what about us?
- I, um, I have to figure out
my own future,
you know, before I can
have one with someone else.
- Hey.
I am sorry that I have to go.
I hope you're not
too disappointed.
- It's okay.
Dad said the movie is about
grandma's favorite book.
- How did you know
what role it was?
- Cassie.
That's when I understood
why you had to leave again.
And if she didn't make
you go, I would have.
- when will I see you
again, Uncle Jake?
- Soon, I promise.
I got a lot to come back for.
I got you, I've got
your mom, your dad.
- Isn't there
another reason, Jake?
- I can't believe
he's just gonna leave.
Well, he didn't
have a choice, Mom.
- Why?
- Because I kicked
him off the show.
Well, I'm not talking
about the show, honey.
I'm talking about your heart.
- Right, well, I also-
- If there's one thing
the last few weeks
have proven to me,
it's that you are a
fabulous director.
And I know you'll figure out
how to put on a great play.
And I'm sorry for
ever doubting you.
- Thank you. That means a lot.
- I've also never
seen you so happy,
until today, that is.
You know, I understand why you
kicked him out of the play.
I doubt he would've
left if you hadn't.
But, did you tell him you
wanted him to come back?
- No.
- Do you?
- Yes.
- Then he
deserves to know.
- Mom, I told him it
wasn't the right time.
- And is that the truth?
- No.
- You're just scared.
Plus, the heart doesn't
care about timing,
it only knows who
makes it beat faster.
- Thank you.
- You okay?
- Ben, you've had my
back for a long time.
You're the only person I trust.
Do you think I'm
doing the right thing?
- Do you want me to answer
that as your assistant
or as your friend?
- How about as my manager?
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
I mean, I don't know
what took me so long.
- Yeah.
- I mean, you've been
in that role for years.
It's about time
you get recognized,
and paid for it.
- Well, now I am really
glad I came with you
to Dickens instead of Vegas.
Thank you, Jake.
- You guys, he
didn't want to leave.
I told him to go.
- What? Why?
- Because this is a role
of a lifetime for him,
and we are still gonna
put on a great show.
This is community theater.
It's not about any one of us,
it's about all of us.
- So we're not
canceling the show?
- Of course not.
You guys have worked
way too hard for that.
- So what are we
supposed to do now?
We're right back where
we were last week.
- We're gonna be fine, trust me.
- Are we?
Because there's a
bunch of new stations
coming from Cleveland,
all here to see Jake Dorsey.
- That's true.
- What are they going to say
when they find out
he's not even here?
- I don't know, but
they're gonna see
a great performance.
- Well, who's
gonna play Scrooge?
- Me.
- I mean, with
the right costume,
I think we could pull it off.
It could be great.
- You guys, we're doing this.
The show must go on.
Get into it. Let's go!
- Whoo!
- All right!
Let's go!
Okay, this is it.
Break a leg, everyone.
And I'm gonna need
a compound fracture.
- Are you sure
you wanna do this?
- Well, I would rather
be down here with you,
but I don't really
have a choice.
Okay, I gotta get to the stage.
- Okay. Oh, your headset.
- Oh, sorry. Okay.
- Hi!
- What is happening?
Um, hold lights. Hold lights.
- Hey. Sorry, guys.
- What are you doing here?
As much as I would actually love
to see you play Scrooge,
and I really would,
I have grown fond of the role,
and of you.
I meant it when I said
you could count on me.
-
They showed up.
- It's Jake!
_ Hey, look, it's Jake!
- All right.
- You see? He's back.
- Yeah, we've got a show to do.
All right, let me go, uh-
- Get ready, okay.
We wish you a
Merry Christmas
And a happy New Year
Good tidings we bring
To you and your kin
- Bah, humbug!
Merry Christmas, indeed.
Spirit, say that the
boy will be spared.
- If he be like to die,
he had better do it
and decrease the
surplus population.
- No.
- And so I release you with
a full heart, Ebenezer.
- Turn around, you fool.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, Spirit, oh, oh.
Spirit!
Merry Christmas, all!
Happy New Year to all the world!
Ah, hello!
There, the window
through which I saw all
the wandering spirits!
It's all right.
It's all true.
It all happened.
- Merry Christmas, indeed.
- That's all you
need to say, Bob.
Hop up, boy!
Oh! Hey!
- God bless us every one!
- Ray Muller, everybody!
This play would not be possible
without our amazing
and brilliant director.
Let's hear it for Cassie Pruitt.
Cassie, come on out.
Good job.
- Thank you.
- Uncle Jake, say the line.
- You want me to say it?
- Yeah.
- Hey, do the right thing.
- Or it's the
last thing you'll do!
- That's right.
Congratulations.
- And a cheers to you.
- I'm so proud of you.
You guys just nailed it.
There wasn't a dry
eye in the house.
- Thank you, Craig.
- Come here.
I love you, buddy.
- Ah, I love you
too, little brother.
- And this one
is gonna take Broadway by storm.
Hey. You look happy.
- Yeah, I'm happier than I've
been in a really long time.
- Me too.
- You have no idea
how relieved I was
to see you standing
on that stage.
- It's the easiest, best
decision of my life.
- But you miss the party in LA.
Now you're not gonna
get the role you wanted.
- Maybe, maybe not.
It's Christmas,
and I need to be with
the people that I love.
- How do you feel about
long distance relationships?
- Cassie, wherever you are,
that's where I wanna be.
- Mm, good line.
Or was it the delivery?
- It wasn't a line,
and I'm not acting.