Long ago,
a prophecy foretold
the rise of a chosen one,
a woman with fiery hair,
who would reshape the world.
But the gods, fearing her power,
whispered into
the hearts of men,
urging them to burn
any child who fit the prophecy.
And so, innocence was lost,
as the innocent
were consumed
by the flames of fear.
No.
Have mercy, she's only a child.
This child is a gift
from the light,
she's your daughter,
your seed, I swear it.
Don't damn your soul!
Avalon, take my hand.
No, you don't have to do this.
She is your daughter,
I am your faithful wife.
No!
No! No!
Something dark
has happened here.
Tell me, do you dream of her?
You do, don't you?
I saw nothing,
because there was no dream.
Then why did you wake
with such a fright?
Because I felt the eyes
of a little man watching me
while I slept.
And I haven't eaten.
How about I give you a taste
if you tell me your dream?
Food first.
Dream first.
All right.
I dreamt I was with three women,
and they all wanted me
at the same time,
but I couldn't decide
which one to please first.
I don't believe you.
And now you know
why I was so angry
when you woke me.
I was very disappointed to
see your face.
If that was your dream,
you would have awoken
holding a different sword.
Hmm. Perhaps.
Father, they've come.
Go find the men and tell them
what you have seen.
The prophecy is true.
Your men, they will not come.
They will not believe the boy.
Let us all go.
Tell them what you
have seen yourself.
Whatever they're preparing,
it happens tonight.
Our lives are in your hand.
I'm not worried, father.
I know.
Be safe.
You be safe, my nephew.
I will see you again, Uncle.
Here, in the glory of the light.
Again, nephew.
Not in glory.
Not yet.
You may have sent him
to his death.
When they hear the prophecy
is true, they will come.
You blindly believe in people.
And you don't believe
in them at all.
Air flows from above.
Yes.
But where does it lead?
Did your dream not tell you?
Did yours?
I would like to hear
more about this dream
with the three women.
Take me back there now.
I wonder, though.
Were you just changing
the details
from when you used
to sleep with the pigs?
-What?
-Bhodie, the pig pleaser.
You know, it's a shame Father
didn't have room
in his castle
for one more bastard.
Yes, Father's seed was sown
far and wide.
Luckily for you,
you were born
with Father's gift of sight.
Hmm. But not his name.
After this, Bhodie,
you won't need his name.
That's because only the living
have need of a name.
It's begun.
It's the Brother of Caius.
They're sacrificing
themselves for the gods.
You mean demons.
They are killing themselves
for demons.
One man's gods,
another man's demon.
The longer we wait,
the less there'll be to fight.
There's the torch.
We must find a way in.
If you still want to leave--
What are they doing?
They're preparing her body.
For what?
To free the fallen.
They are opening
a gateway to hell.
Whatever happens,
we cannot let a demon
through that gate.
You've seen this before,
haven't you?
I promise you, brother.
We will walk out of here
alive today.
Bhodie!
Help me!
Why did they stop?
Demon.
No!
Bhodie, do you remember
your pledge?
We have failed.
No, we haven't.
Not yet.
Did you mean it, those words?
She cannot be saved.
What if she could?
How far would you go?
Would you go to the ends
of the earth?
She's gone, brother!
Swear it and mean it
or say nothing at all.
I would do all that is required
to fulfill the prophecy,
including giving my life.
I know.
But this is your destiny.
You will fight for her
when others will not.
You will protect her
when others fail.
You will be the shield
while the storm rages on.
That is your destiny.
Remember,
no matter how dark it gets,
light will make a way.
Come with me.
Poor, poor knight.
Betrayed by his brother.
Abandoned by his father.
Chasing the promise of glory.
But will any be found?
Who are you?
I am the lonely Keeper
of this realm.
And what is this place?
You failed to protect her.
Now you've traveled through
the Forbidden Gate
to the land of the gods.
Do you want my help?
Can I afford the help
of a demon?
My kindness is not enough.
Speak plainly, demon.
What is your wage?
I can help you
save the chosen one.
And why was she?
The girl with the fire for hair.
I made a bargain.
I gave her this.
This will allow you to die
a hundred deaths.
I offer it to you.
A hundred deaths?
More or less.
Hopefully less.
And what of your bargain?
The bargain?
Yes.
All I ask
is that when the gate opens,
you will suffer me
passage with you to your realm.
That is the price
of a hundred deaths.
More or less.
And how do I return
to my brother?
Three lords hold three stones.
And has the chosen one
gone to fight these lords?
She has.
And you are wasting time.
Why don't I just kill you,
demon?
You may try, I suppose.
But the power of the talisman
only works
as long as I still have breath.
Fine, Keeper.
If I succeed,
I'll allow you passage through
the gate with us.
A fine bargain.
But it must be sealed in blood.
Just a drop.
When I cover your wound,
I may not be able to
help myself.
Betray me, demon.
And I will hunt you through
the ages.
Yes, very worth.
As long as there is light
in this talisman,
you will be able to die
and be reborn.
If the light dies,
you die with it.
Having second thoughts?
Name your purpose.
You are outmatched.
So be it, little mouse.
I demand that you
cut me down now.
You've made a grave mistake.
It would be wise for you
to release me right now.
Looks like you're the one
that's trapped now,
little mouse.
A knight of the light,
here in the realm of the fallen.
One would wonder
what crime he committed
to be sent here.
Or does he hunt the witch?
You're not the witch, are you?
If so, no, I'm not hunting
the witch.
Who sent you?
I'm here because
of the prophecy.
Which one do you speak of?
Prophecy of a woman,
who couldn't be burned with
flames for hair.
She would dispel the darkness
and unite all men against
the return of the gods.
And where did you hear
of this great prophecy?
My father and brother dreamt it
and it was confirmed in
the ancient text of the light.
And would you have me believe
that you are here in the land
of the gods,
risking your life, because
a dream and an old book
told you so?
Well, you are here, aren't you?
And you think I am
the woman from the prophecy,
the one who will unite
and save man?
I would hope so.
Or have I followed
the wrong woman through
the forbidden gate?
You are gravely mistaken.
Would you care to elaborate?
You are mistaken,
because of my hatred for man.
Why would I want to save them?
I think mankind
refers to women as well.
Surely, there is someone at home
worth saving.
Let me be clear, Knight.
I want nothing to do
with your prophecy.
Mankind has done nothing
for me, but cause me pain.
And if I had the power,
I would destroy them myself.
How's that for your prophecy?
I will admit,
I like my version more.
Also, if you can't even best me,
how do you think
you can help me?
I tend to think well on my feet.
Then you'd better stand.
Because tonight, we are
going to kill a witch.
And just like that,
you'll trust me?
You're wearing
the Keeper's talisman,
which means you made
the same barter as I.
I'm Bhodie, son of Azra.
Usually, this is the part
where you introduce yourself.
How long has it been
since you saw me in the chamber?
Not even an hour has passed.
For me, it was a lifetime ago.
Listen carefully, Knight.
I have fought the witch for
as long as I can remember.
Each night, no matter what I do,
it captures me,
peels back my skin,
drinking my blood.
It is a pain like you have
never felt in your life.
You will be forced
to relive the darkest
moments of your existence
over and over again.
Then you will die,
and be reborn,
and have to muster the courage
to do it all over again.
So how does one avoid
living the darkest moments
over and over again?
Your blood is fresh.
The witch will be
drawn to you.
As it pursues, I will circle
from behind
and then we will kill it
together.
So you intend to set a trap
and use me for the bait.
Do you want the stone?
Also, you ruined my trap,
so now you are the new one.
You still haven't told me
your name.
Avalon.
Well, Avalon, you tell me,
how does this
Keeper's necklace--
-No, don't!
-Even work?
Who is this--
Ah, Bhodie.
Son of Azrael.
How have you crossed
through the Forbidden Gate?
Surrender yourself
and receive my judgment.
Have you succumbed?
What happened to me?
Succumbed to what?
What did you see?
What did they say?
He told me to call
out to him.
Did you?
No.
Never keep your talisman off.
It shrouds you from his sight.
Now he has found you
and knows that we are coming.
Who has found me?
You're out of your depth,
Knight.
The Invoker.
His gaze has set upon you
and now you have doomed
our quest.
At another time,
I would appreciate your
offer to comfort me,
but given
our current situation--
I'm not trying to lie with you.
Oh.
We have lost most of the day.
We must move quickly.
The night comes and with it,
the witch.
Yes, and with the witch
comes our glory.
There will be no glory today.
Only pain.
Why are you removing
my armour then?
You'll be able to run faster
without it.
Run?
You think of me a coward.
I need you to run.
That's the trap.
So there's the stone.
But where's the witch?
Why do you cry?
Oh.
I cry tears of happiness.
A demon.
Yes.
And who is this?
He's the helper.
Come out of the shadows
and face me.
He has come to sustain us.
I can taste his blood
in the air.
Come.
Help us.
Worship us.
Let us each have a turn
and partake.
I come for the stone.
Give it freely and you will
not be harmed.
He comes for the stone.
Should we give it to him?
Oh, the stone.
Yes.
Many come for its power.
What do you offer?
What do you require?
Blood.
Suffering.
Pain.
Then pain and suffering
you will have.
But it will be your own.
Here is my last offer.
Give me the stone.
We will start with pain.
Come out of the shadows
and face me.
Beside you. Over here.
More.
Hello. Did you miss?
Oh. Don't run, little knight.
You wouldn't want to spoil.
I can hear your heartbeat.
Hang on. Hang on.
Oh, little knight.
Come play with sisters divine,
he came far,
but all he will
receive is suffering.
Do you know now who we are?
We are the promise.
The promise of pain.
The past,
future,
the present.
Scream for me.
Don't go anywhere.
There's a matter we have
to attend to.
Tend the other guest.
The lord of the stone
must be overcome.
Welcome back.
How?
I warned you,
the witch's power is great.
I felt them drinking my pain.
My agony.
And then you died,
yet you are here.
How is this possible?
A hundred deaths.
And you, you betrayed me.
And I had the stone.
You lied to me.
You've already lied to me.
How have I lied?
When you told me why
you were here.
The prophecy.
How is that a lie?
I am here for you.
You don't even know who I am.
No, obviously not.
You're here to help yourself.
But now you know what
this place is.
Now you'll forget your prophecy,
your promise,
and you'll do whatever
you can to escape this hell.
You'll even sacrifice me
and your prophecy to do it.
That is the truth.
Listen here,
you betray me again--
And what?
You'll kill me?
Hurry up then.
Add to the scars.
Make it interesting.
I didn't think so.
It doesn't matter anyway.
It's all an evil trick.
How so?
I had the stone.
We had won.
And it turned to dust
in my hand.
We must overcome
the lord of each stone.
Maybe that means
we need to kill them
instead of trying to
sneak around.
The witches cannot be killed.
I have tried more
than a hundred times.
You've tried
a hundred times alone.
You've never tried with me.
Let us work together.
What say you?
Doesn't matter what I say.
Darkness comes and with it,
our death.
Or maybe our life.
What do we do now?
We wait.
Oh, Bhodie,
you should have stayed
at home with the pigs.
So how did you get captured
by the brothers of Caius?
I wasn't captured.
I found them and came
here by my choosing.
You willingly went to the Caius?
Why?
They said they could help me.
So you didn't need to be
saved after all.
I never said I did.
Of course not.
The next time I see a woman
bound by savages,
I'll just assume she's there
of her own free accord.
I have come for the stone.
I claim the boy.
I like the way he screams.
How does glory taste?
I will not fail again.
The light shall prevail.
What were you hoping for?
That they would just stand there
and let you chop them down?
The only screams
will be yours tonight.
Oh, and charging them
like a boar.
Why didn't I think of that?
You were late.
You went early.
Who's early now?
Was it worth it?
Yes, it was.
-For fearing God.
-Look at me.
Do you see how mine is dimmed?
Each death has a cost
and it's one step closer to us
being trapped here forever.
This is only the first lord
and we have two more after this.
You came here to save me.
Start acting like it.
The light shall prevail.
You swing like a brute.
Are you even trying to hit them?
Know this, you foul creature.
When I awake, I will make
your life a living hell.
So you do bleed.
What happens to one
happens to both.
Don't you see?
Their strength is
their weakness.
We only need one strike.
What have you been trying
to do this whole time?
Dance with them?
Of course, we need to strike.
No, we need one strike.
I'm listening.
Last time.
Your blood grows cold.
But the boy, still so fresh.
What's wrong boy, you afraid?
No words from the brave knight?
Don't be shy.
Say something!
You cannot see me.
They're blind.
They are blind.
- Please, I need to rest.
- No, wait, please.
What was that you were
saying earlier?
The witches cannot see us.
So?
Even when we are quiet,
they can hear our breath.
Then we will mask
the sound of our breath.
And how does one mask
their breath?
We will hide the sound
of our breath behind these.
The knight thinks
he's so clever.
He thinks because we are blind,
we cannot see.
I can hear you.
I can hear your heartbeat.
You can't hide from me.
I wasn't trying to.
You did it.
You defeated the first lord,
my king.
But you are troubled, my lord.
Your brother sees her
as the savior of mankind.
But you've seen what
she becomes.
She's already betrayed you.
Welcome back
to the land of the dead.
One lord is slain.
Two more remain.
You have done what many have
failed to do before you
Before me?
How many others have
there been?
All those who pass
through the gate
suffer a similar fate.
Where's Avalon?
She is soaking her wounds
from battle.
She waits for you
in the bathhouse.
Avalon tells me that you
removed your talisman
and saw one of the lords.
Which one did you see?
I saw the Horned Demon.
And what did he say to you?
He asked how I came
to this place.
Is that it?
Yes.
She waits for you.
We did it, Knight.
We defeated the first lord.
I would back away.
This isn't water.
You don't look at me,
but you desire to.
You aren't mine.
And who is supposed
to give me away?
You are.
These are the tears
of the tormented.
One day, they will fuel
hell forever.
A light's promise.
Still holding on
to your prophecy,
do not be mistaken.
I may not burn,
but I am not the woman
from your prophecy.
You said you're here
for your revenge.
What revenge can be gained
from here?
It is not revenge, but the means
to do so that I seek.
Well, do tell.
I seek a weapon of great power
that would force even the light
to bend its knee.
And where is this weapon?
It is guarded by the final lord.
The Invoker.
What does the sword do?
It gives you the power
of the gods.
And what will you do
with this power?
Revenge.
And you must be on your way.
The Invoker holds
the second stone.
The gods will be afraid now
that two humans killed,
but couldn't be killed.
You are mistaken.
Those who failed to kill
the witch before you
will now come.
Your enemies have multiplied.
And what does it matter?
If we die, then we are reborn.
One of us has died
more than the other.
Avalon is right.
She can no longer risk death.
Her soul cannot handle it.
How do we reach the Invoker?
There are two paths
to the Invoker.
The first climbs
over icy mountains.
The second is much faster.
But it's plagued by demons.
And the Invoker's eye is on it.
Those who take that path
usually overcome.
And what of the third stone?
Where do we find it?
Lilith.
She will find you.
And bring her bargain.
And one may wonder
if we should have taken
the bargain from you, demon.
One may wonder
how many times my bargain
has saved you, Knight.
Let us finish this.
Open the gate, Keeper.
Do you trust this demon?
He has been with me
for as long as I can remember.
Which way shall we take?
I would rather face the
mountain
than fight more demons.
Then it is the narrow path.
The Keeper says
we are going to be followed.
The stone's not safe.
We should stay close
to the shoreline.
There's no cover out here.
They're swearing
as he was following us.
We're to die out here,
aren't we?
I would rather fight
another demon
than face any more
of this mountain.
You may get your chance.
We are forced at hand.
What does he want?
Revenge.
What for?
For sending him here.
I expected more
from the slayer of the witch.
You will find today
is full of disappointment.
Here is my offer.
Let us share the stones
together.
We will kill the last lord
and we'll share the girl.
And we will leave this hell.
You will have neither.
Give me the stone
and I will end this swiftly.
Do you mind if we skip
to the fighting part?
I'm quite cold.
So be it.
Come on, Bhodie.
Your brother isn't here
to save you this time.
I will take care of him
and the girl.
And...
Are you going to beg
for your life?
Are you?
Hey.
What?
No!
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm just resting
on this comfortable ice I found.
You should try it.
Can we stick
to the shoreline now?
Stick to the shoreline?
Yes.
But you go first.
Avalon?
You are troubled, my lord.
Your brother sees her
as the savior of mankind.
You've seen what she becomes.
She's already betrayed you.
What will stop her
from doing it again?
You have betrayed yourself,
Knight of Light.
What trinket do you wear
around your neck?
Remove it and reveal
yourself to me.
You dream of me?
Oh, you flatter yourself.
You cry out my name.
At first, I thought it was
for pleasure.
But you are sweating blood.
I wonder, what kind of dream
causes a man
to bleed in his sleep.
The only thing I dream of
is leaving this hell.
And you still think
you don't lie.
So you don't believe
in the light?
I never said I don't
believe in the light.
Do you think all things
were created by the light?
In the beginning,
it was the light.
And the light was with God
and the light was God.
All things were made by Him.
And without Him was not
anything made that was made.
In Him was life.
And life was the light of men.
And the light shineth
in darkness.
And darkness
comprehended it not.
I know the ancient words.
Yet you don't believe it.
Tell me.
Where was the light through
all my suffering?
Where was the light when
your father left you a bastard?
The light never made me
a bastard.
And the light never brought you
your suffering.
That was the choice of free men.
Then you see.
The light is no more powerful
than a common man's will.
Why would I worship
such a weak being?
The light is just another
demon pretending to be a god.
Another monster that
needs to be chopped down.
Maybe the light values
free will more than
the absence of evil.
Instead of making us
mindless slaves.
He offers us free choice.
Choices bring pain.
They can also bring joy.
If your master is so great.
Then why are you wearing
another master's
trinket around your neck?
Your words are empty.
Nephew.
How are you here?
This is glory, uncle.
Bhodie.
Have you passed over?
There's nothing there.
We must take the faster path.
What you saw isn't real.
You don't know what I saw.
You are being deceived.
It could be what's happening.
It could be the future.
Or it could be a trap.
Move.
No.
I will not let you sabotage
my quest.
You mean your revenge.
I cannot live with myself
if I do not do
all in my power to save
my nephew.
And what if he's already dead?
And what if he isn't?
We must take the faster path.
Who's the boy?
If we are going to die,
I would like to know
who the boy is.
I already said he's my nephew.
And why is he so dear to you?
Because he's my blood.
And why do you laugh?
Aren't we all family
somewhere down the line?
Related in one way or another.
We and our enemy share
a great-grandfather.
Yet we still do horrific things
to each other.
Family.
The Keeper told me about
your brother.
I know you didn't choose
to come here.
You were forced and betrayed
by your own family.
Say too much.
Family means nothing.
Family always keeps
the greatest horse.
Is that who's responsible
for burning your friend
at the stake?
An angry family member?
Be careful what you say next,
bastard knight.
Who was it?
A brother?
A jealous uncle?
An angry sister?
No, not your sister.
So much hatred for men.
Maybe it was your father.
Now what had your mother done?
I'm guessing I'm not
the only bastard here, am I?
Son of Azrael.
You have entered through
the Forbidden Gate.
Stand before me
and receive my judgment.
I see you, Knight.
How did you pass through
the Forbidden Gate?
And why have you come?
There is another with you.
Avalon.
Daughter of Hope.
How have you been
hidden from my sight?
Wake up, Knight.
I see.
You are but a pawn
in a greater game.
You reek of hate.
Receive my judgment.
Her heart is dark.
Her fate sealed.
The wound will consume her.
Be gone, Knight.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I should never have strayed
from the path.
Knight, thank you.
For what?
For being here.
Come.
Let Avalon heal.
The wound will consume her
if I don't intervene.
This will slow the wound.
The wound will consume her
if I don't intervene.
This will slow the wound.
I am a friend.
You're cold, son of Azrael.
Warm yourself for your journey.
Are you a demon?
I am a friend.
Like you, I was betrayed by
someone I loved.
I would watch your words.
If the prophecy is true,
why did your brother
not come himself?
Well, what is it that you want?
How many times
have you died for her?
And all she sees is a bastard.
She doesn't even call you
by your name.
Is that your bargain?
You'll offer me comfort.
No, Bhodie.
No bargain.
I offer you love.
I don't desire your love.
Then whose love do you desire?
I want you.
Not as the knight.
Not as the bastard.
But you, Bhodie.
I will not bargain with you.
Are those the words
of the Keeper?
Or yours?
Tell me, what do you know
of the Keeper?
Do you know
why he wants to return?
What his unfinished business is?
Does one need a reason
to escape this hell?
The bargain you made with him,
you know,
only two can enter the gate.
Oh, you didn't know.
Once you collect all the stones,
you are bound
to take the Keeper.
And if she, Avalon,
collects the stones,
she is bound to take him.
Bound by blood.
She didn't tell you, did she?
That you labor in vain.
That's why she can't say
your name.
She's already betrayed you.
And how do I know
it is not you who lies?
You need my stone
to open the gate.
I've been here a long time.
And it has taken me an eternity
to find just one stone.
I want you to know that
it is you who I desire.
And even though you refuse me,
I freely give myself to you.
No bargain, no tricks.
All I ask is that you consider
what I'm about to tell you.
The Invoker doesn't just have
the last stone,
but also a weapon.
I know this already.
A weapon powerful enough
to reshape the world.
With it, you would be
the most powerful man
in all of history.
With it, you would be a god.
And I, your queen.
And together, we could reshape
and save the world of man.
We could fix everything
the light
and the gods have done.
And why wouldn't I just let
Avalon take the sword?
So she can take revenge.
You've seen what happens
when she does.
Take the sword.
Deny the light.
And kill the gods.
Deny the light?
To take the weapon,
you must deny the Light.
The light allowed the gods
to bring evil into this world.
The light allows evil to exist
and therefore, is as evil
as its creation.
This is my sign of love to you.
My commitment to you.
All I desire is your love
in return.
I said
I will not bargain with you.
Have it your way.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, I am.
How?
When?
Does it matter?
How did you defeat
the second lord?
I don't think I did.
May I see it?
We now have two of the stones.
All we need is one more.
And then we get to leave
here together.
Yes.
Yes, together.
Maybe I should go alone
for the rest of the journey.
Alone?
Why would we do that?
I still have light
in my talisman.
Let me finish this.
You can't stand against
the Invoker alone, Knight.
I know why you call me,
"Knight".
You know nothing.
I know what haunts you.
Get to the point.
I've seen you holding
the corpse of a person
you dearly love.
I know that this is why
you seek revenge.
I'm losing interest
in this conversation.
Let me be clear then.
Even if we defeat the Invoker,
you will be offered
a great power.
A power that could reshape
this world.
A power that could be
used for vengeance.
Yes.
And I will take that power.
You'll damn your soul.
In my dream--
Oh, we're listening
to your dreams now?
I saw you take the sword.
I like this dream so far.
And you were lost.
You were consumed with darkness.
Void of light.
Is that it?
You'll damn your soul.
And with it, the prophecy dies.
My father, he never heard
of your damn prophecy.
"Witch.
Whore.
Burn her.
Burn her!"
I held my mother's hand
and listened to her scream
as her fingers melted
between mine.
I wait for the fire
to consume me.
But I don't burn.
I wish I did.
I hold my mother's hand
until it turns to ash.
When I return,
I will kill my father
and burn his kingdom to ash.
I am here for revenge.
Not your prophecy.
And I don't care if I lose
myself in doing so.
We can bring your father's sin
to justice another way.
But can your brother
and nephew wait?
Men storm the gates.
Your brother's life hangs
in the balance.
He knew the risk.
That is why he stayed.
That is his part.
And what is my part?
What will history
remember me for?
For rising above hate
and choosing a better way.
Not for your father
or your mother.
But for yourself.
So you're asking me to wait here
while you retrieve
the final stone?
Yes, I would.
And if you can't beat
the Invoker,
he will take your stone
and we will both be stuck here.
What then?
I will give you the stone
from the First Lady.
That way it will be safe.
You've been faithful
to your words so far.
I will stay.
I wish we would have
met sooner, Knight.
No! Wait!
William, you were wrong!
You were wrong!
I know not how to save you,
brother.
Brother!
Avenge me.
There is no light here.
There is only darkness.
Even in the darkest moment,
there is hope.
Son of Azrael,
I have seen the deception
that has befallen you.
Leave this place and return
to your brother's aid.
I show you mercy.
Take it before I change
my mind.
Invoker, you will let me leave?
I am not the Invoker.
I am the keeper of this gate,
the guardian of this realm.
I keep demons
and those who confer with demons
from leaving this place.
You are not the Invoker.
No, and you're not a demon,
so you may leave.
Tell me, where's Avalon?
She is receiving her judgment.
Bhodie, I--
She conspired with demons
to free the fallen
into your world.
But I am bound to her.
You need to leave.
You are bound to a lie.
Yet I am still bound.
I took an oath, an oath
that I cannot break.
Gatekeeper, I ask that you
allow her passage with me.
She stays.
Then so do I.
So be it.
Bhodie, behind you!
I want you to know,
I take no joy
in your destruction.
Did you really think you
could defeat me by yourself?
What makes you think I'm alone?
I want you to know,
your destruction brings me
no joy.
You, you're the final lord.
Apologies for not introducing
myself properly.
And how far back
does this lie go?
Did you know I would follow you
through the Forbidden Gate?
It wasn't meant for the bastard.
Your brother, William,
was meant to follow.
I underestimated his cowardice.
You're lying.
I fed your brother
and your father stories
of the prophecy.
The chosen one,
their blind faith was
so easily manipulated.
Like I said, Knight,
you are out of your depth.
There is no prophecy,
there never was.
Now you will do whatever you can
to escape this hell.
Take the sword
and strike him down.
A prophecy isn't a lie,
it's a choice.
The choice of who you will be.
A choice everyone must make.
If you take that sword,
your father wins,
you'll become just like him.
What is her other option?
To be like her mother,
helpless,
and burned at the stake?
Avalon.
I don't want to.
Then don't.
You don't need it.
If only two may pass,
then I will stay behind.
No.
No, you will not.
You look at me and see
something that isn't there.
I see you.
I see your hurt, your pain,
your anger.
Yet I know you will rise
above it.
I know only two may pass,
let me stay behind.
Then it's settled.
The boy will stay.
Take the sword and let us leave.
Take the sword.
No.
What do you mean no?
I said, no.
After all I've--
after all I've done,
I will not be denied.
I am choosing a different path.
A different path.
I don't think so.
I underestimated you, Knight.
You found the last bit of
humanity left in Avalon.
After I'm done with you,
there will be none left.
Avalon?
Mother.
Take my hand, Avalon.
Don't you remember your promise?
Avenge me, Avalon.
Avalon, avenge me.
Burn.
Avenge me, Avalon!
-Burn the witch.
-Avenge me, Avalon!
Burn!
Avenge.
We are bound, you and I
by a hundred deaths.
Bound by blood.
Each death brought us
closer together.
Each death made us one.
Through each passing,
we draw closer.
Our spirits will merge as one.
I can endure.
But can she?
You didn't really think
you were the chosen one,
did you?
There's nothing special
about you.
Do you intend to strike me down?
No!
One of you will take the sword.
Take the sword.
If not for you, for her.
You promised
you would protect me.
- Take the sword.
Without the sword, you are
forever a bastard,
forever a prisoner.
You will pass
from this world unknown,
unheard of, and unloved.
But with the sword,
you could conquer all.
A god among men.
You said you would protect me,
Uncle.
Take the sword.
All honor will be yours,
even your brother will bow
to you.
Avalon will be yours.
Take the sword.
Take the sword, Uncle.
I am the Great Invoker.
I weave and shape humanity
to suit my desires.
The mere whisper of my voice
commands the masses.
I will be yours.
Come, be with me, Bhodie.
Take the sword.
It was I.
I who commanded her father
to burn her.
"Witch!
Burn!"
These are my words!
You are my puppet.
I am the puppet master.
You are nothing!
Deny the light.
Love me.
Worship me.
Deny the light.
I own you!
Take the sword.
No.
But do you burn?
Are you all right?
He took everything from me.
After so long,
walking down that path,
I don't know where to go.
Where do I go?
Through the gate.
And after that?
Whatever it is,
we'll do it together.
Together.
Yes, together.
Come, brother.
Let us fulfill the prophecy.