Downloaded from
YTS.MX
- Ho, ho, ho!
[festive music]
♪
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
- ♪ Light the tree
and deck the halls ♪
♪ Snow stuffed
down your overalls ♪
♪ Trying to wrap
the presents on time ♪
♪
♪ The mistletoe's
a special place ♪
♪ To spill hot chocolate
on your face ♪
♪ Shaking every gift
to see which one is mine ♪
- ♪ Loud Christmas,
Loud Christmas ♪
- ♪ The more of us
the merrier ♪
♪ To Santa Claus
it's scarier ♪
♪ One boy, ten girls
♪ Wouldn't trade it
for the world ♪
♪
- They're gonna see
this house from space.
- Hun, where are you?
- Hut-hut-hike!
- I'm okay!
[electric guitar riff]
- Get ready for
the 12 Pranks Of Christmas.
- [screams]
My life is over.
- Get ready.
It's almost game time!
- Christmas is
only 2 days away,
and I can't wait.
[upbeat music]
When you've got 10 sisters,
Christmas can get pretty epic.
[phone chirps]
Your driver, Bill,
is en route with your package.
This year, I ordered
an extra special gift
for my family.
♪
Luan, what gives?
- I decided to up my game
from the 12 Puns Of Christmas
to the 12 Pranks
Of Christmas.
- Well, if it's
a Christmas prank,
then I'm all-in.
- That was number nine.
Three more to go.
[chuckles]
- Now that Luan is gone,
I'll be safe for a while.
- Hey, Stinkoln!
[screams]
- [screams]
[grunts]
Oh, spoke too soon.
- Just getting ready
for a Christmas afternoon
football game.
Can I try that tackle
one more time?
- No.
- Ugh!
- Christmas at the Loud house
is full of traditions.
Each one of us contributes
something important
to our special day.
[explosion]
How is
the Permasnow coming, Lisa?
- It's the trace amount
of ammonia needed to sustain
the creation of snow
that is the constant variable.
- Or as I like to call it,
Thursday.
You're our only chance
at a white Christmas.
- Science will prevail.
- Hi, Lincoln.
- Lucy, you scared me.
- You're welcome.
I've collected
all the dead pine needles
from our Christmas tree.
- I'm sorry for your loss.
[spooky music]
♪
- Yeah!
[upbeat rock music]
♪ It's Christmas time,
and our hearts are free ♪
♪ Presents tucked
underneath the tree now ♪
♪ It's the best day
of the best time of our lives ♪
- Great Christmas tunes, Luna.
- Thanks, little bro!
♪
- Tell me honestly, Lincoln.
Does my concept design
for my custom-made
Christmas pajamas
have too much sparkle?
Tanya thinks
it's bordering on too much.
Don't you, Tanya?
[soft dramatic music]
- Leni, there can never be
too much Christmas sparkle.
- Thanks, Lincoln.
See?
Sparkle equals happiness.
- Move.
I need to put my tiara on.
- I need to get
Hops' outfit on.
- I don't care.
- Lola, Lana, merry Christmas.
- Come on, Hops.
- It looks like
Rudolph himself.
[frog croaks]
- Right on, bro.
- How is the Christmas pageant
coming, Lola?
- If you must know, Lincoln,
it's literally taken years
from my life.
- Okay.
I need my beauty time.
♪
- Light tree.
- Lily!
Tomorrow night,
Lily gets to turn on the lights
for the Royal Woods
Christmas tree.
- This is Katherine Mulligan
coming to you live
from the scene
of tomorrow's...
- Katherine Mulligan.
- Magical Royal Woods
Christmas tree lighting.
- Light tree, Lincoln.
Light tree.
- Yes, Lily.
- No chance of snow.
- Hi.
- Stop doing that.
[spooky music]
- [scatting melody]
Figgy pudding.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey, Lincmeister.
Want to give the old
figgy pudding a test drive
before the big day?
- [chuckles]
That's so nice, Dad,
but I'll save it for Christmas.
- Huh.
- Yuck.
- Hey, Linc, you feeling
the Christmas spirit?
- I sure am.
- Me, too, bud.
Me, too.
- Whoa!
- Your mom is swinging from
the lights again, isn't she?
- Yeah.
- I'm okay!
- Okay.
- The toast is burning!
- I know, hon.
I know.
- Everything is fine.
I've got this.
- I'm sure you do.
[phone chirps]
- Yes!
My super special Christmas
package is being delivered now.
- Super special package, huh?
- It'll be the best
Christmas gift ever.
- ♪ Figgy, figgy,
figgy, figgy, pudding ♪
[imitates record scratching]
♪ Figgy
- Oh, whoa.
What a rush.
[upbeat music]
- The decorations
look great, Mom!
- Oh, thanks, honey.
It's a labor of love.
- Lincoln Loud?
- You betcha.
♪
Five stars for you, Bill.
- Merry Christmas.
♪
- I've worked
awkward and annoying jobs
all year to save for this.
♪
- ♪ Dangerous
- You tell Mom
I did all my chores.
[cash register rings]
- ♪ Dangerous
♪ Dah, dah,
dah, dah, dah, dah ♪
♪ Work hard,
play harder, got it ♪
♪ Put money in my pocket
- Here you go, Lincoln.
- Thanks, Mom.
- Here you go.
[cash register rings]
- I just had a mani.
Thanks, Linc.
♪
- ♪ With money in my pocket,
oh, yeah ♪
♪
- "What's in the box?"
You might be wondering.
A 13-person toboggan
so that my entire family
can ride down the hill
on one sled.
♪
That's the greatest thing
about Christmas.
No matter what happens,
it's the one day of the year
we'll always be together
no matter what, guaranteed.
- Kids, breakfast is ready!
- Out of my way!
- Food, food, food!
- I'm coming!
- Lincoln, watch it!
- Food, food, food, food, food!
- I'm coming.
- Take it easy out there.
- Up, Lucy.
[loud flatulence]
- I heard that!
- Ew!
- I got you, Leni.
- Ha ha, good one.
- Prank number ten.
Only two more to go.
- Toast coming up.
Here you go, kiddo.
- I want toast.
- The darkness suits me.
- Hey, I got your back.
[both hiss]
[laughs]
Okay, I think we're good.
Hey, Linc, you better
watch where you're...
Going.
[phone ringing]
Does anyone else
hear that ringing?
- Oh, it's Lori.
- Hi, Mom.
- Lori.
- Lori?
I want to talk to Lori.
- Lori!
- I miss you so much!
- Hi, Lori!
- Lori!
Lori!
What time are you
coming home today?
- That's actually
why I'm calling.
I've given it a lot of thought,
and I don't think
I can come home
for Christmas this year.
- What?
- Exams are coming up,
and I have
a winter golf tournament
two days after Christmas.
It just feels like too much
to go all the way home
just to turn around
and come all the way back.
- Oh, well,
Christmas just wouldn't
be the same without you.
- Yeah,
it sure wouldn't, kiddo.
- I think it'd be easier
just to go to Bobby's house.
- Okay, hon.
We understand.
- We support you, sweetie.
- What?
- Incoming.
- Duck!
- Lincoln.
- No, don't do that!
Don't support her.
This is totally unacceptable!
Am I right, everyone?
- Well, actually,
it makes more sense.
It does.
- I mean,
Bobby does live closer,
and, you know,
we live so far away.
- Thanks, Mom and Dad,
for being so understanding.
Dad, are you crying?
- Lori, please.
You have to come home.
You'll miss everything.
- I know, Lincoln.
This wasn't an easy decision.
- But what about Lily lighting
the Royal Woods Christmas tree?
- Light tree.
all: Aww.
- And what about
Christmas morning?
I bought us
the best Christmas gift ever.
But if you're not here,
it won't be the same.
It can't be the same.
Oh, Lincoln.
You're so sweet.
I will see your Christmas gift
when I come home
for the summer.
- Yeah.
- Summer?
- Perhaps now would
be the best time to tell you.
Sam invited me to go skiing
with her and her family
on Christmas Day,
and I really want to go.
Can I?
- No, you can't go.
- That is very kind
of Sam's family to invite you.
- All right, Luna.
Yeah, of course, you can go.
- Yes.
- So fun.
- Uh, well, I've been asked
to bring merriment and cheer
to the Sunset Canyon
Retirement Home.
Luan and Mr. Coconuts
coming at you Christmas Day.
Pretty, uh, sweet deal.
- Tell Pop Pop I said,
"Merry Christmas."
- Absolutely not.
- Luan, I think that's
a very kind thing you're doing
at the old folks home.
- It sure is, kiddo.
- What is going on?
This is Christmas.
- Okay, Lori,
I think we're gonna say
so long for now.
- Bye, everyone.
I love you.
I will call on Christmas Day.
- Lori, no!
- Slice it!
- Okay, everyone.
Family meeting.
Living room.
Now, listen, we know
this isn't the Christmas
we were expecting
with Lori, Luan, and Luna gone.
- We just have to make
the best of the situation.
- Tell them, Mom.
We need to fix the situation.
- Wouldn't it be fun
to take a trip?
- A trip?
- On Christmas?
- With three of the kids
gone already,
maybe we could be our crazy,
old spontaneous selves.
Get up super early
Christmas morning,
jump in Vanzilla, and take
the remaining kids on a trip
somewhere exotic.
- Go on.
- Somewhere like Miami.
[together]
Yay!
- No!
- I have always wanted
to vacation in Miami.
- Dad, no.
- Bikinis!
- Miami is where
the Little Miss Citrus
Pageant takes place.
- We could go
to a Miami Dolphins game.
- The moisture will do wonders
for Hops' scales.
- We could witness
a shark attack.
- Huh?
- [sighs]
- Miami.
- Yay!
- Whoo!
- Yeah, Miami.
- But what about all of
our Loud family traditions?
All those special things
that we do together
as a family on Christmas Day?
If we're all split up,
it won't feel like Christmas.
- I get why
you're disappointed, honey,
but sometimes plans,
they change.
- Yeah, you have to adapt.
Roll with the punches, right?
Besides, we'll start
new family traditions.
- And Lily can still light
the Royal Woods Mall tree
on Christmas Eve.
- Light tree.
- Aw.
- But I don't want to make
new family traditions.
I want
our old family traditions
that I know and love.
- I promise we'll make sure we
have a great family Christmas
even if some of us are apart.
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
- Fine.
I didn't want
to have to do this,
but it's the only way.
- What's he doing?
- What?
- What's that?
- My super special
Christmas gift
is going to change
all your minds.
- What is that?
- What have you got there, bro?
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- Uh, what is that?
- Firewood?
- Mulch?
- Ah, man, that's broken.
- Or a coffin?
- What?
No.
It's a 13-person sled
for us all to be on
when we go down the hill
at Tall Timbers Park...
- Aw.
- Together.
♪
- Next year, little bro.
- Yeah.
- Totes, Lincoln.
- Yeah, it'll be colder then.
- It just would be better
for all of us--
- Don't even worry about it.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and we
can get some glue.
- Besides, Lincoln,
there's no snow anyway,
so it's not like we can
even use your thingy-thing.
- Sled, Leni.
It's a sled.
- Oh.
- It's settled.
We're going to Miami
for Christmas!
- Yay!
- I'm so excited!
[indistinct excited chatter]
- Oh, my god.
I'm so excited.
- Ho, ho, ho.
Who's next?
- Straight ahead.
- Are you sure?
- I absolutely love
the blue cashmere scarf
for nana.
- Oh, Harold, I don't know.
Maybe we should have gotten
the foot massager
or the back scratcher.
- Dads, we're so close.
I can see Santa's red coat,
white beard,
and the promise
of baking equipment.
- How did we get so lucky to
call you our little sugarplum?
Come here.
- Ho, ho, ho, who's next?
- Did you remember your list?
- That's like asking
did I remember to breathe.
I've been working
on the perfect gift list
all year long.
I can barely contain
my excitement.
- Reindeer Clyde, come in.
This is Christmas Humbug,
and I've got a code elf-red.
- Hold my spot, Dads.
Christmas Humbug,
this is Reindeer Clyde.
- Christmas is ruined
all thanks
to my selfish family.
- What happened?
- Lori isn't coming home
from college,
Luna is going skiing with Sam,
Luan has a gig
at Sunset Canyon,
and Mom and Dad are taking
the rest of us to Miami.
- What?
What about me?
What would I do?
Coming to your house
on Christmas Day
is an essential part
of my holiday experience.
- Finally someone who gets it.
- This is the worst news ever.
- I have to save
Christmas, Clyde.
I don't know how,
but I've got 24 hours to do it.
- I've got your back,
Christmas Humbug.
I'll be right there.
- Thanks, Reindeer Clyde.
I knew I could count on you.
- We'll see you Christmas Eve.
- Ho, ho.
- Sorry, Santa.
Come on.
I've got to get
to Lincoln's house.
- But, honey,
don't you want to tell Santa
about your non-stick pans?
- And the silicone baking set?
- There's no time!
- Ho, ho.
Come on down, young lady.
- Okay, Lincoln.
What's the plan?
- We need to make Lori
want to come home
even though it makes more sense
for her to stay at college.
We need to make her homesick.
- Great.
How do we do that?
- We send Lori the one thing
that will remind her
of a Loud family Christmas
more than anything else.
- I have no clue
what you're talking about.
- It says here they can deliver
anything overnight
and keep it hot.
- "Operation
Make Lori Homesick"
is officially in effect.
- 1 Loud down, 11 to go.
- Sweet.
- Let's consult the mattress.
- Oh, Lincoln.
Impressive.
- I call it,
"Operation Work Our Way
Through My Sisters and Mess up
All Their Christmas Day Plans
So We Can All
Stay Home Together
and Have
the Best Christmas Ever
and Also Think of
a Shorter Name
for This Operation."
- I like it.
I like it.
- Now, we need to stop Luna,
stop Luan, and stop Miami.
Step one is in motion.
- Is that poop?
- It's Dad's figgy pudding.
- Oh, right.
- Now on
to the Luna Swagger Surprise.
- Because what's life
without a little swagger?
- Okay, the coast is clear,
but we've got to work fast.
- It's a good thing
I perform well under pressure.
- Hit it.
- Hello, there.
- Stop.
Go to minute 15
and 3 seconds.
- Lu.
- Stop.
- Go to minute four
and three seconds.
- Na.
- Stop.
- Now go to one minute
and eight seconds.
- Hello there, Luna Loud.
Mick Swagger here.
[both scream]
- Just giving you a ring
to say I'll be in Royal Woods
on Christmas Day.
I'd love to get together
and jam.
Hope it's not
too late notice, love.
See you spoon.
- Yeah!
- Did he just say, "spoon"?
- This is the greatest day
of my life.
- But then you
can't come skiing?
- Jamming with Mick
is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity, Sam.
- I know, but this is gonna be
such a special trip for us.
- We'll take a different trip
some other time.
♪
- We've got a big day
of sabotage ahead of us,
so be sure to get
a good night's sleep
and eat a balanced breakfast.
Good work today,
Reindeer Clyde.
- Thanks, Christmas Humbug.
♪
- Rise and shine.
- Good morning, Louds.
- Lori is getting
my special delivery
this morning.
♪
[phone chirps]
Oh, look at that.
Arriving in three, two, one.
♪
- Aw, that's so sweet,
you guys.
Oh, it's Dad's figgy pudding.
[ominous music]
[gags]
I've never missed
dad's figgy pudding
on Christmas ever.
It's just so awful...
and yet I love it!
Oh, I've got to get home.
I can't be away from my family
at Christmas.
What was I thinking?
Okay, I can figure this out.
I'm strong.
I'm independent.
I don't need anybody's help.
[festive Latin music]
[phone plays voice recording]
Boo Boo Bear, Boo Boo Bear.
Boo Boo Bear,
I need your help.
- Hey, Lori.
- Can you drive me home?
- Oh, babe,
I really want to help,
but the mercado van
is out of commission.
♪
- Is that the mercado moped?
- Sure is.
I'm making a delivery
of Christmas tamales
for my abuela's hairdresser.
♪
- Lori, I totally understand.
I couldn't live without
Dad's figgy pudding either.
[laughter]
No, of course I won't tell Mom
or Dad you're coming home.
It'll be a surprise.
Right.
Be safe and see you spoon.
I mean, see you soon.
Lori is officially
on her way home.
- Sweet.
- I love
your dads' theater stuff.
- Wait for it.
One shark head
compliments of the McBrides'
very own production,
"Jaws: The Musical."
- Clyde, that's huge
and perfect!
- What do you want it
for anyway?
- We're gonna shoot
a fake video of a giant shark
attacking someone on the warm,
sandy beaches of Miami?
- Come again?
- My family won't want to go
to Miami if it's shark season.
- Couldn't your family
still want to sit
by the hotel pool
and take in the rays?
Ow.
- You're right.
We have to think up something
more than a giant shark.
What is this?
- Oh, that's Crockie
from "Lake Placid: The Musical"
last summer.
- What if there was a creature
that was half-shark,
half-crocodile?
My family wouldn't be safe
on land or water.
- A crockyshark.
- I was thinking sharkodile.
- That's better.
Go with that one.
- We'll get the crocodile body,
put the tail on it,
attach the shark head.
Sharkodile.
- A venture
of this magnitude requires...
an arc welder.
Don't worry.
I'll ask my dads
for permission first.
- Once the sharkodile
is all put together,
we can mount it on your dads'
tandem bike so we can move it.
- I don't like it.
[dramatic music]
I love it.
- We just need a victim
for the sharkodile to attack.
- Whoa, Lincoln,
I really want your family
to stay for Christmas,
but I'm not willing
to kill someone over it.
- We're not gonna use
a real person.
- Well, then,
who are we going to use?
- ♪ I heard those bells
always ringing ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- [gasps]
Tanya, we are going to have
so much fun in Miami.
- Could you help me?
I need a sweater.
- Mm, Christmas sweaters
are totes in right now.
Here, let me show you.
- Thanks.
- Well, Santa,
let me start by saying
I have been really, really,
really good this year.
Actually, I have
testimonials from my dads.
- Reindeer Clyde, come in.
I have found our victim.
I repeat,
Come back ASAP.
We need to grab her.
Clyde?
- I'm just gonna leave now.
[soft dramatic music]
- Okay, yes,
it is lamb's wool,
which technically needs
to be dry cleaned,
but lambs take showers, right?
So I think
you're fine to wash it.
Owie.
- Thanks for nothing.
- Just a foot.
[sighs]
Another satisfied customer.
- Nothing to see here.
- She's slipping.
- We so need this vacay, Tanya.
[jazz music]
Tanya?
♪
Tanya!
[upbeat music]
♪
- [gasps]
Act normal.
♪
- [laughs]
- We have everything
we need for the Miami video.
- Yeah.
- Now "Operation
Lose Luan's Laughfest."
- That's a lot of Ls.
♪
- Hey.
- Okay, put him in.
- What if he can't breathe?
- Clyde, he's a puppet.
- You're right.
My dads always say
I'm too empathetic,
and it drains me,
but some people
are born
with extra mirror neurons.
- Clyde.
- [sighs]
So he can breathe.
- Good idea.
- Clyde, let's go visit
my Pop Pop and your Nana.
It's time to get old.
- My daughter
is coming to visit today.
- Oh, that's lovely.
- Hey.
- Hello.
[loud flatulence]
- Lay off the broccoli.
- I agree.
- What in the dang heck?
- That there is Luan Loud.
Pulling pranks on us
to advertise her
Christmas Day show?
What a sin.
- Do I know you?
- Uh, nope, nope.
- Oh, what
a pretty little flower.
- Look at that.
Luan Loud using the tricks
of her trade to sell tickets.
It just ain't right.
- Do I know you?
- Nope.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- Oh.
- Now Luan Loud is messing
with the pudding machines
all to promote her
Christmas Day show.
It's a real shame.
- No one messes
with my pudding.
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
- It's true.
Nobody messes
with Scoots' pudding.
- Might be best to go
with a different act
for Christmas Day.
- I agree, a far less devious
and messy entertainer.
[murmurs of agreement]
- Are you sure
I don't know you?
- I feel like I know him too.
- Ah, no, no, no.
You don't know us.
I have
a very common-looking face.
- Yep, very common and bland.
Common and bland.
- Let's get back
to the matter at hand,
what to do about Luan Loud.
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
- As the head of the board
of Sunset Canyon,
I hereby fire the kid.
[together]
Yeah!
- Hold on there, Scoots.
Luan is my granddaughter,
and clearly she has made some
catastrophic miscalculations
when it comes
to her marketing platform,
but can't we just
give her another chance?
- [gasps]
- Oh!
- Oh.
- Oh, dear.
- My word.
- Well, Al?
- Oh.
- Fire her.
- Yeah!
- Yes!
- Yes.
[all cheering]
- We did it.
- "Lose Luan's Laughfest"
accomplished.
Lily's baby powder
really did the trick.
- This is all
working out perfectly.
Luna and Luan are staying.
Lori is on her way home.
And now,
for the pièce de résistance,
a sharkodile attacks
the beaches of Miami.
- Color me impressed.
- I can't wait
for Christmas all together.
- Honey, are you sure
this is necessary?
We're leaving tomorrow.
- Lynn, I can't have
a lopsided Santa.
Are you crazy?
- Am I crazy?
You're the one up on the roof.
- I heard that.
- Just don't fall off the roof.
Again.
- [screams]
- Oh, oh, oh.
- Ooh, ooh.
Thank you, Santa.
- Santa.
[chuckles]
I would have caught her.
- I heard that too.
- What?
[upbeat music]
♪
- Only 60 miles to go.
- You're my hero, Boo Boo Bear.
- I've got to get home
in time to watch Lily
light that tree tonight.
- Well, we're going
turbo mode, babe.
[engine chugging]
- Ooh, it's getting
a little cold.
- Hug me tighter, babe.
That'll keep you warm.
- I love you, Boo Boo Bear.
- Well, I love you more.
- Nuh-uh.
- Uh-huh.
- Well, I love you more.
- Nuh-uh.
- We're gonna need
a bigger bike.
[dramatic music]
- It's more megalodon
than "Jaws,"
but that only adds
to the terror.
[phone beeps]
- It's already 3:05 p.m.,
and this video has to be ready
for the 5:00 p.m. local news.
- Once we're done shooting,
I'll spruce it up
with some special effects
on my computer, then send it
to Katherine's personal e-mail.
- How'd you get
Katherine Mulligan's
personal e-mail?
- She auditioned
for my dads' reimagining
of "Wonder Woman:
The Musical."
She should keep her day job.
Let's just leave it at that.
- Hm.
- Could you please ask our star
to come out of her trailer?
- Oh, Tanya?
[upbeat music]
♪
Clyde.
- One second.
- Clyde, we're ready.
Come on.
Let's do this.
Perfect.
Clyde, let's get ready to croc.
- Yeah.
♪
- Ready?
- Ready.
- Let's make some news.
- I hope this thing
is waterproof.
- This is Katherine Mulligan
coming to you live
with breaking news.
I have just
personally been delivered
footage of
a graphic, horrific attack
by a creature that some
may call prehistoric,
but all will
certainly call deadly.
The attack took place
on the sandy beaches
of Miami, Florida.
The following images
are disturbing,
so if there are
little ones about,
you might want
to shield their eyes.
- Cover up, everybody.
- Dad, your hand!
- I shan't, I shan't.
- I want to observe.
- Sharky.
- Oh, oh, no.
- She looks familiar.
- A shark?
- Oh, no, oh.
- [screams]
[all gasp]
- Oh!
- Dad, can I see?
- Terrifying.
- And now I would like
to bring in the leading expert
in wilderness survival, Mr...
- Rip Hardcore!
- Thank you, Katherine.
I was signing my book,
"Ripping Through The Jungle,"
in a nearby bookstore
when I decided my presence
was far more needed here.
- Well, thank you,
Mr. Hardcore.
- Now, listen.
What we have here
is a full-grown,
genetically-enlarged
mutated crossbreed of species,
aka a sharkodile.
- Oh, a sharkodile.
- Hungry monster
is incredibly dangerous
and not to be messed with.
I once encountered another
such crossbreed of creature,
the piranhagator,
off the shores of Australia,
and I have this
and this to show for it.
They always attack in pairs.
But in my book,
I lay out a very detailed plan
on how to trap and disable
such a formidable beast.
Order now and I'll throw in
one of my sweat-stained
bandanas for free.
- Already ordered.
Thank you, overnight delivery.
Ooh, my.
Oh, Mr. Hardcore,
could you tell us, please,
what you might do
if you encounter such a beast?
- Better than tell you.
I'll show you.
I would grab the beast
by its tail.
- Whoa.
- Whoa!
- And once I had
the sharkodile
under my complete control...
- It doesn't bend that way!
- Capture the beast.
- Why me?
No.
I'm not a sharkodile!
- While Fred and Rip
continue this demonstration,
this is Katherine Mulligan
advising anyone who is planning
a Christmas getaway to Miami,
it's time
to cancel those plans.
- [screams]
- Aw.
- But I planned
my whole vacay wardrobe.
- Big disappointment.
- A sharkodile?
Terrifying.
How could a shark
and a crocodile even--
- How could a shark
and a crocodile even do what?
- [clears throat]
- Never mind.
I'm sorry, but I think
we better cancel
our trip to Miami.
- No.
- Aww.
- Bummer!
- Aw, man.
- And just when
I was coming around
to the idea of having
Christmas somewhere else.
- Eaten by a shark
and a crocodile
at the same time?
- Thanks, Luna.
I wasn't picturing it,
and now I'm picturing it.
- It's all so scary.
- Well, listen, everybody.
I mean, I'm sure
that woman got some help
and is feeling much better.
- I don't think she did.
- As for us, listen,
we're going to be great, okay?
Don't worry, gang.
We're gonna have
a great Christmas, huh?
I'll whip up a Lynn-tastic
Christmas Eve dinner,
and then we have
the lighting of the Royal Woods
Christmas tree
to look forward to tonight.
Huh?
Lily?
- Ready!
- See, "weddy"!
So let's all put on
our Christmas finest
and get all dressed up
to honor Lily.
Huh?
It'll be fun.
[indistinct
disappointed chatter]
- But bikinis!
- What about my tan?
- I want to go to Miami!
- Hey, cheer up, everyone.
Christmas here won't be so bad.
- Worst Christmas ever.
- Right?
- Right you are, Mom.
I'm going to go get dressed up
for the Christmas tree lighting
right now.
Great idea, Dad.
[whistling melody]
- [laughs]
- Oh.
- [continues whistling]
- How cool was Rip Hardcore?
- The absolute coolest.
- We're, like, one sharkodile
degree of separation
from the master
of wilderness himself.
- It's almost
too much to comprehend.
- Was your family upset
that they got
their Christmas plans canceled?
- Once my family
is all together
tomorrow for Christmas,
they won't even remember what
they were disappointed about.
Christmas is officially saved.
♪
- [shivering]
Twenty miles, babe.
[engine sputtering]
- What--what's wrong?
- Uh-oh, no more gas.
- Bobby.
- Hey, mini Louds!
Dinner is almost ready.
- Down in a second!
- Pull yourself together,
Mr. Sprinkles.
There will be other pageants.
- Hey, Lola.
You getting ready
for the tree lighting?
- I'm not going.
The Little Miss Citrus Pageant
was going to be
a career highlight for me.
Now I'll probably
never get to wear
that beautiful orange sash.
- Well, at least you can
still have a Christmas pageant
right here at home.
- Don't patronize me, Lincoln.
- Hey, Lynn,
want to try that tackle again?
I'm heading into the end zone.
- Now that I'm not gonna see
the Dolphins,
I don't feel like
playing football anymore.
[rock music]
- ♪ No presents
tucked under the tree ♪
- Luna?
- Oh.
Hey, little bro.
- Are you crying?
- Sam broke up with me
because I picked jamming
with Mick Swagger
over going skiing with her.
- What?
That wasn't supposed to happen.
I mean, I'm so sorry
that that happened.
- ♪ Christmas time
is when our hearts are free ♪
♪ But if I ain't with you,
I'm in misery ♪
♪ My heart is dead
[sobbing]
- Leni, are you okay?
- No!
- Why aren't you dressed
in your super special
Christmas outfit?
- I'm not really
in the Christmas mood anymore.
I don't know what's worse,
that I miss Tanya
or that I got fired
for losing her.
- You got fired?
- The boss said I should have
caught whoever stole her.
I really let Tanya down.
Wherever she is,
I hope she has her cover-up.
[sobbing]
- Hops!
It's your favorite sink.
Snap out of it, buddy.
- What's wrong, Lana?
- Ever since I broke the news
that we weren't going to Miami,
Hops fell into a frog slump.
[frog croaks]
I can't even get him
to swim in the sink.
It's not gonna be
a merry Christmas now.
- [loudly blowing nose]
- Luan, are you okay?
- Pop Pop just called
to cancel my Christmas Day gig.
Who hires you
to bring merriment and cheer
and then fires you
for no good reason at all?
- I don't know.
Who?
- It's not a joke,
Mr. Coconuts.
- I'm sure
you'll go some other time.
- No, I won't.
Because I'm never speaking
to Pop Pop again.
I might as well
quit comedy too.
I clearly lost my touch.
- But hey, what about me?
What will I --
- It's not all about you,
Mr. Coconuts!
- I'm canceling Christmas.
- I want to be in Miami.
- My life is ruined!
- Tanya!
- Worst Christmas ever.
[soft dramatic music]
- I was just really looking
forward to our trip to Miami.
We work so hard all year.
- I know, hon.
I know.
A break
sure would have been nice.
- Mm-hmm.
- Some other time, maybe, huh?
- I sure hope so.
- Maybe when we retire.
- [chuckles]
- Hello, Lincoln.
- Ah, you scared me!
- You're welcome.
Everyone is so sad.
- Everybody, please!
Downstairs family meeting!
- I thought we were the only
ones allowed to do that.
- Hm.
- Lisa.
- What is it, Lisa?
- What's wrong?
- What is it now?
- Lisa.
- What is it, Lisa?
- Come on, Lisa.
- Lisa, what's wrong?
- On the contrary, Mother.
Everything is very right
because of this.
- Everything is right
because of hairspray?
- No, Leni.
what I hold here
is the potential
for us to still go to Miami.
- What?
- Miami?
- Miami!
- It's a carefully calibrated
mixture of immobilizing agents!
Street name--
Sharkodile tranquilizing spray.
- Ooh!
- That sounds very fancy.
- Sharkodile
tranquilizing spray?
That sounds
incredibly dangerous.
Am I right?
- Here, let me see it.
- No, I want to see it!
- No, I have it!
- Come on!
- Guys, stop!
- I want the hairspray!
- Give it back!
- How does it work exactly?
- Miami, here we come.
- Dad, does that even work?
[spray hisses]
- Whoa.
- Oh!
- [coughs]
- [screams]
- Oh.
- Dad?
- What's going on?
- Dad, I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
- Uh-oh.
- Dad, Dad?
- Yeah, yeah.
I think I am buddy.
[all sigh]
- It doesn't work.
- Sorry, Lis.
Looks like
your invention didn't work.
Such a bummer.
I really wanted
to go to Bababi.
- Huh?
- Is he all right?
- Bababi.
[clears throat]
That was meird.
[chuckles]
- Honey, are you okay?
- Beh, I'm bine.
Bine.
Buh.
I'm buh-ine.
[laughs]
Babine.
- Okay, Dad?
- There's something wrong
with my bips.
There's something--
what's wrong with my bips?
'Cause I don't think
I can beh-beh my bips.
I can't--
Baht's wrong with my body?
My bibe.
What's wrong with my bibe, bib.
What's wrong with my bibe, bib?
[speaking gibberish]
[gasps]
My baps!
I can't feel my baps.
- Dad, that's not normal.
- They're like bib old bippers.
I can't feel
my baps or my baba
or my bips.
I can't--
[screams]
[all scream]
I can't--ooh, that feels bood.
[laughs]
Boo, hey, baby.
Boo, boo, ba-boo, boo.
Boop.
[laughs]
- Lisa, help him.
- I can't.
It just has to wear off.
- Well, how long is that?
- [screams]
[all gasp and scream]
- Bime all might!
[laughs]
- It's in beta test.
- That was a good pratfall.
[phone ringing]
- I can't beb up.
- Dad, are you okay?
- Lori.
- Hi, Mom!
- Where are you?
And why do you look so cold?
- Don't freak out,
but Bobby and I
are kind of stranded
on the side of Route 23.
- What?
- I was coming home
to surprise you all,
but Bobby's moped
ran out of gas.
- Hi, Mrs. L!
Feliz Nochebuena!
My bad about the gas.
- Will you please
come pick us up?
[both shivering]
Is there something
wrong with dad?
- Bi, Bobby!
- Hey, Mr. L!
- Dad will be fine.
- I'll be bine.
- Stay where you are.
I am on my way.
- I love your mom.
- [singing gibberish]
- I am going
to pick up Lori and Bobby.
Please watch your father.
- [laughs]
Bye!
I'm gonna go mape binner!
[together]
No!
- Ah, my kitchen!
[laughs]
- Kitchen!
- [laughing]
No.
- Oh, no.
- No.
- Whoa, whoa, Dad.
Pots and pans
don't belong on the floor.
- Clyde?
- Uh, Lincoln,
you better turn on
the local news right now!
[dramatic music]
♪
- What you are
about to witness
is footage
taken just hours ago.
- The hybrid animal is here?
[dramatic music]
Oh, no.
- Is that the sharkodile?
- He's here?
- That's a her.
- It's here now?
- Sharkodile in the woods.
- I should have
listened to Clyde.
- You sure it's okay
to hide this thing
in the woods until later?
- What could possibly happen?
- Okay.
♪
- I'm here with a woman
identifying herself as Scoots.
Ms. Scoots.
- I sold her a sweater today.
- Can you tell us
please what happened?
- Sure, I was out
on a pudding run
when I saw this sucker
going through the park,
probably looking for someone
to chomp on.
- Ah!
- Ugh!
- Rip, Do you have any
expert advice for our viewers?
- My main points of advice...
- [speaking gibberish]
- One, do not leave any form
of meat hanging outside.
Two, do not wear perfume
that smells like meat.
- Meak?
- Be aware.
- Sound, solid advice, Rip.
- Thank you, Katherine.
- Well, you heard it
here first, people.
The sharkodile
has come to town, our town.
An emergency curfew
has been put into place
for everyone's safety.
Sadly this means
this Christmas tree lighting
at the Royal Woods Mall
has been canceled.
[melancholic music]
- No light tree.
♪
- Oh, it's so not fair.
- No, worst Christmas ever.
- I can't believe
this is happening.
- In the meantime, if you
should see the sharkodile,
please call our tip hotline
at 555-0HNO.
That's 555-0-H-N-O.
This is Katherine Mulligan
reporting that Christmas
is officially ruined.
Stay safe, Royal Woods.
- Ruined is right.
- Aw, man.
- Mr. Coconuts.
- Worst Christmas ever.
- I can't believe I'm missing
my pageant over this.
- This is such
a bummer, you guys.
- Come in, Clyde.
We have to save Christmas.
Didn't we do that already?
- I have to call
Katherine Mulligan's tip line
and tell her the truth that
the sharkodile is not real.
- Everyone,
and I mean everyone,
will hate you on Christmas.
- Clyde, Lily needs
to light that tree tonight.
- Oh, hold on.
Hello?
Have you seen the angry beast?
- Hi, yes, um,
I have seen the sharkodile...
- Ooh, get it.
Get it out.
Tell me.
-- Because it's me.
The sharkodile isn't real.
- Ugh, listen, kid,
this is a serious situation.
We don't have time
to play games
when people's lives
are at stake.
Ugh.
It was just some kid
playing a prank.
Load her up!
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- Okay, Sharkodile.
It's you and me.
- And me.
- Clyde?
What are you doing here?
- I had a hunch Katherine
wouldn't believe you.
I mean, you're just a kid.
- I'm gonna have
to ride the sharkodile
down to the Royal Woods Mall
to show Katherine Mulligan
that it's not real.
- You're not gonna do it alone.
- Really?
- What else would I
be doing on Christmas Eve?
- You could tell Santa
your Christmas list.
- No way.
Friends are way more important
than some silly gifts.
- You're my best friend,
Reindeer Clyde.
- And you're mine,
Christmas Humbug.
- Let's go right some wrongs.
- Yeah!
- I don't know how much longer
I can take this cold.
I'm so hungry, so weak.
♪
[gasps]
Vanzilla!
Mom!
- Thank goodness
you two are okay.
- Mom, you literally have
no idea what I've been through.
- Come get in the van
to warm up.
- Um, Mrs. L, can I ask you,
like, a really big favor?
- Okay.
- I still need
to make my abuela's
Christmas tamale delivery
for her hairdresser,
or she'll kill me.
- You had food
in that thing all along?
- Uh...
- What do you need?
- A gas station?
- Katherine and her news team
are at the Royal Woods Mall.
We've got to get to them.
- Let's do it.
♪
- Oh, you're mine, sharkodile.
You're mine.
♪
[phone rings]
- Hello.
This is Katherine Mulligan.
- Katherine!
I found the sharkodile.
Whoo-hoo!
I sent you the link
to my drone.
I need you to start
streaming the footage.
I'm hot on the beast's tale.
- Be careful, Rip!
Get the feed up!
It's go time!
[dramatic music]
♪
- We'll save time if we cut
through the neighborhood.
- Okay.
Turn here.
- [laughs]
I've got you cornered!
♪
- Oh, you can run,
but you can't hide.
Got you now.
[laughs]
- Oh, it's Rip Hardcore.
- Awesome!
- Here, I come, baby!
- Wait a second.
Is Rip hunting us?
[both scream]
- This is Katherine Mulligan
reporting live
from outside
the Royal Woods Mall
with real-time drone footage
of the sharkodile.
- What?
- It has left the woods
and is headed towards town.
He's in a residential
neighborhood, oh!
- Go right.
♪
- I've never seen
anything like this.
He's turned north.
- Ah!
Look out!
- I think that's my house!
- I think that's our house.
[both screaming]
[together]
That is our house!
♪
[all scream]
- Mom is gonna kill me.
- Best Christmas ever.
- In the name of science!
- Lisa, what are you doing?
- I filled this
with my sharkodile
tranquilizing spray.
I'm going
to capture the sharkodile
to study it for science!
- Lisa.
- I have just received word
that the sharkodile is headed
directly towards
the Royal Woods Mall.
- Not the mall!
- And it's dragging a very
unhappy Santa behind it.
- It's go time.
- Lisa, wait!
- Lisa!
- Sharkodile!
- I'm, like,
so not okay with any of this!
- We have to go after Lisa.
- Huddle up!
♪
Three, two, one!
[together]
Save Lisa!
- Save Lisa.
- Let's go.
We have to get
to the Royal Woods Mall.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Where's Dad?
- [snoring]
Miami!
- Ew.
- Dad!
The sharkodile ripped down
all of our
Christmas decorations.
- And Lisa ran after it.
- And it's headed
to the Royal Woods Mall.
- Who did this to my kitchen?
There's pancakes
on the ceiling.
- [screams]
- We're coming, Lisa!
- Lisa!
- I don't understand
what's happening!
- All right, Dad,
but why are you crying?
- I don't know.
- Okay.
- I don't know why I'm crying.
♪
- This adventure
has gotten way out of hand.
- Way out of hand!
- Katherine,
it's coming right at you.
Get to high ground for safety.
- I'm going up on the roof.
No, you two stay down here.
You'll get better footage.
Listen up, people.
This is Katherine Mulligan.
I'm advising
a calm and orderly
evacuation of the mall.
The sharkodile is coming.
I repeat,
the sharkodile is coming!
[people screaming]
- Oh, I can't believe this.
- Believe it.
- We'll be home soon, honey.
- Thanks, Mom.
- [humming melody]
- Whoa!
- Oh!
- Are those
my Christmas lights?
And my Santa?
[knocks]
[both scream]
Lisa!
- I am commandeering
this vehicle, Mother.
♪
- Lisa, what's happening?
- Follow that sharkodile!
Greetings, older sibling.
- Uh, hi, Lisa.
- I don't think
it's a good idea
to follow a sharkodile.
- Mother!
It stole all of
your Christmas decorations
and your Santa!
- Let's get the sucker.
- Go, go!
- It is moving fast.
This is Katherine Mulligan,
and we are still here live.
I see it, the sharkodile!
It's coming right towards us!
- Go, sharkodile!
[laughs]
- We're so close!
- Run away, people!
Run away!
- Hey, no, come on.
- What are you doing?
- Seriously?
- Keep filming!
♪
- I see Katherine Mulligan!
- Let's punch it,
Christmas Humbug!
- Katherine,
I'm the sharkodile!
♪
- Got you!
[both scream]
[tires squeal]
- [grunts]
- Go get him!
It looks like it's heading
straight into the mall.
all: Ooh!
- Ah, yeah.
[laughs]
[both screaming]
- Lincoln, what do we do?
- Pedal!
Pedal like your life
depends on it.
I can't see very well.
- Look out!
[both scream]
We're hitting everything!
Where are we going?
- I don't know!
- Ah!
Hang tight, mate.
I've been a good boy this year.
[laughs]
- Come on!
- Come on, hurry!
- Go!
- Go, go, go!
- Come on!
- I have to save
the sharkodile!
- Lori, hurry!
[together]
Lori and Mom!
- No time for hellos!
Lisa ran inside
after the sharkodile!
- [gasps]
- What?
- Let's go get Lis!
- Why are we running
towards the sharky thingy?
[tranquil festive music]
♪
[both screaming]
[dramatic music]
♪
- It's the end of the line
for you, Reindeer Clyde.
You've earned it.
[tires screech]
- Santa!
Nonstick pans,
a silicone baking set,
a bread maker, an air fryer,
a 6-speed tilt-head food mixer,
Rip Hardcore's new book,
an Ace Savvy comforter set.
Oh, no.
- What am I doing?
[upbeat music]
♪
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
♪
No!
- Lincoln!
- [grunts]
Oh, no!
Oh, reindeer!
Oh!
[grunts]
- [laughs]
I'm just gonna go now.
- Oh, it's like
Armageddon in here.
Come on.
Okay, we've got this.
- This sharkodile
belongs to science!
- Lisa, get back here
right this instant.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[together]
Clyde!
- We've been searching
everywhere for you!
- I think I have
some explaining to do.
Oh, this is Santa.
- Oh, hello, Santa, thank you.
- Good to meet you.
- Come on, you sharkodile.
I'm ready for you.
- Get the shot.
Go.
[dramatic music]
♪
[together]
Lincoln?
- Lincoln?
- Geez, Al.
What's up
with all your grandkids?
- Al.
- Oh.
- [laughs]
I told you I had
some explaining to do.
- Lincoln?
Well, there goes
my Nobel Prize for science.
[water gun hisses]
Whoops.
- You're not a ferocious
cross-breed creature.
[together]
Three, two, one.
- You're a boy--babbily,
bibbily, babatha, batha,
bibbily bip, bibbily bip.
[laughs]
Bibbily bip baha.
I hit the bump.
[body thuds]
- Well, if I ever act
like that...
[chuckles]
Just, you know--
- Lori, you're home!
- Of course.
I couldn't miss
Christmas with my family.
- Lincoln, what happened?
Why are you the sharkodile?
- Yes.
I think that is the question
on everyone's mind.
- Lincoln, I think it's time
for you to start explaining.
- I made up this entire thing.
The sharkodile in Florida,
all of it.
That's not all.
And I lied to all of you.
Leni, I stole Tanya.
Lori, I tricked you
into coming home.
- What?
- Luna, Mick Swagger
isn't visiting.
Luan, I sabotaged
your gig at Sunset Canyon.
- Lincoln, why would you do
all of these horrible things?
- Wait!
Does that mean Tanya is okay?
- Yes.
- It's all so dark, Lincoln.
- You made me question
my comedic calling!
- But why, little bro?
Why would you mess
with your own fam like that?
[soft dramatic music]
- Because I wanted us all
to be together on Christmas.
It's the one time of the year
that I can count on
all of us being together.
I love my family.
I don't want us to break apart.
I got scared
that we were all growing up
and going our separate ways,
and if I could
take it all back, I would.
♪
- I understand.
- You do?
- I do too, bud.
- Growing up is hard.
Change is hard, but family--
family is forever, Lincoln.
[tender music]
- That's right.
We're always tied together
by our hearts,
no matter where we are.
- So you're not mad?
[decorations crash]
- Oh, oh, I would say
we're really angry...
- Well, there's a few things
to figure out.
- But I think we can
breathe through it.
- But no,
we're not mad
at where your heart was
to make you do all this.
♪
- I'm so sorry, everyone.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make things right.
- Bring it in.
Come on.
♪
- Oh.
- [laughs]
- Ooh.
- Aw.
- Ahem, on behalf
of all of Royal Woods,
I would like to know one thing.
[dramatic music]
Would anyone like
to light a Christmas tree?
[tender music]
- Tree!
[all cheer]
[festive music]
[cheers and applause]
- It's sparkly!
- Merry Christmas!
- Wow.
♪
[upbeat rock music]
- Let's rock!
♪
♪ It's Christmas time,
and our hearts are free ♪
♪ Presents tucked
underneath the tree now ♪
♪ It's the best day
of the best time of our lives ♪
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
- ♪ We're gonna celebrate
for all that we've got ♪
♪ Our hearts are tied
in one big Loud knot ♪
♪ We're spreading joy
all around the house ♪
♪ Tonight
♪
♪ Yeah, we're uniting
with love and good cheer ♪
♪ Opening doors,
so glad this day is here ♪
♪ All right
♪
[together]
♪ Rock the halls
♪ So bells will ring
♪ It's Christmas time,
and we're together forever ♪
♪ Left this time
for the world to sing ♪
♪ It's Christmas time,
and we're together forever ♪
♪ Sometimes you gotta scatter
to learn somehow ♪
- [singing gibberish]
- ♪ What matters is
we're gathered together now ♪
♪ Yeah, we're all
one Loud family ♪
[together]
♪ We know
♪ We're together forever
- [screams]
♪ Together
- ♪ Together
- ♪ Forever
- ♪ Hearts will
forever be tied ♪
- ♪ Together
- ♪ Forever
- ♪ Yeah, we're gonna party
all night ♪
♪ Together
- ♪ Together
- ♪ Forever
♪ Merry Christmas
♪ Oh
- There you have it, folks.
A little boy's wish
to spend Christmas together
with his family.
This is Katherine Mulligan
saying it may
not be a white Christmas,
but it certainly will be
a merry one after all.
- One more time!
♪ Together
- ♪ Together
- ♪ Forever
♪ Merry Christmas
♪ Oh
- Tree time.
[indistinct chatter]
[together]
It's yours.
[indistinct chatter]
[loud flatulence]
- [laughs]
I got you.
Prank 11 and prank 12.
"The 12 pranks of Christmas."
- [laughs]
- That's my granddaughter.
I'm so proud of you, honey.
- Rip's book!
- Rip's headband!
- Rip bros!
[indistinct chatter]
- Thanks for the pajamas, Leni.
- Tanya and I worked
supes hard on them.
The hat was Tanya's idea.
- More figgy pudding,
anyone, huh?
- Oh, honey.
- I'm good.
- All right, all right.
Later, okay.
[chuckles]
- As you can see,
things turned out for the best.
I have 300 hours
of community service,
but we got to spend
Christmas morning together.
And, in a few hours,
Luna is going skiing with Sam.
Luan has a double gig
at Sunset Canyon.
We're going to take Lori
back to college,
and then the rest of us
are going to--
- Miami!
[all cheer]
- Miami, here we come.
- Oh, Lincoln, sweetie.
We have one more gift for you.
- What?
Where is it?
- Check it out.
- What could it possibly be?
- Come on, Lincoln.
[upbeat music]
- [laughs]
- It's our sled!
- It was so kind
and so thoughtful for you
to come up with such
a special gift for the family.
- So we all chipped in
and fixed it
while you were asleep.
- You can't even tell it
was broken at all!
Thank you.
Too bad there's no snow.
- Oh, I wouldn't be so sure
of that, big brother.
Never underestimate
the power of science.
[explosion]
♪
- No way.
- Is this possible?
- It's so sparkly.
- Way to go, Lisa.
- Awesome.
- This is epic, Lisa.
♪
- Let's ride!
- Let us partake
in a freezy game!
- ♪ Oh, the presents
tucked under the tree ♪
♪ Oh, can you feel
that holiday energy? ♪
♪ It's the perfect time
of year ♪
♪ To me
when our noses are cold ♪
♪ But our hearts are free
♪ It's Christmas,
together forever ♪
♪ It'll be the best ever
♪ We're gonna bring it
this Christmas ♪
♪ Bring on the weather
♪ In your ugly sweaters
♪ Everybody sing, sing, sing
♪ Oh, oh
♪ It's Christmas time,
and it's gonna be wild ♪
♪ Oh, oh
♪ We're gonna have
the time of our lives ♪
♪ We'll be dancing
in the falling snow ♪
♪ When we're all aglow
♪ There's
a little bit of magic ♪
♪ All the bells
will do the jingling ♪
♪ And we're staying in
♪ While Santa Claus
is sleighing ♪
♪ It's Christmas
- Family is connected
by their hearts.
Even when we're apart,
we're not really apart.
I will miss
how things used to be,
but I'm really enjoying
how they are.
- ♪ Everybody
sing, sing, sing ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh,
it's Christmas time ♪
- Let's hit Tall Timber Hill!
[all cheer]
- ♪ It's Christmas time,
and it's gonna get loud ♪
- Ready?
[together]
Ready!
[explosion]
- Science!
[all screaming]
- ♪ Whoa, whoa
♪ It's Christmas time,
so gather around ♪
♪ Oh, whoa
♪ It's Christmas time
♪ And it's gonna get loud
♪
- ♪ Hey, hey, it's Christmas
- ♪ Wake up,
it's Christmas morning ♪
♪ Snowflakes
just keep on falling ♪
♪ Put on
those matching jammies now ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey
- ♪ The tree
is glowing bright ♪
♪ I could
barely sleep at night ♪
♪ This holiday
is rocking out ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
- ♪ There's no present
like the present ♪
♪ When we're all here
♪ Christmas
is so much better ♪
♪ When we are all together
♪ So put your hands up
and shout ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey, it's Christmas
- ♪ Can't help
but feel so jolly ♪
♪ When you are next to me
♪ Christmas
is so much better ♪
♪ When we are all together
- ♪ Hey, hey, it's Christmas
- ♪ Yeah
♪ Christmas together