Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
- How 'bout some
black-and-whites,
Mrs. Rodriguez?
Zoe just baked them.
- Yes, please.
- Hey, Mrs. R!
- Hey, Zo.
And a dozen macaroons.
- Comin' right up.
- How's my granddaughter
doing at choir practice?
- Oh. With a voice like that?
Ava is gonna be the star
of The Little Queens
Carolers fundraiser.
- Oh, Dee Dee,
you're so good with those kids.
My daughter tells me
Ava comes home
after every practice raving.
- Thanks, Mrs. R.
- How's your Nonna's new hip?
- Titanium.
She power-walks
two miles a day now.
- You're an angel, Dee Dee.
You know, my son
is single again.
- Oh. Tempting. Um...
But I've got my hands full
between the Christmas pageant
and helping Ma,
and helping Zo,
and the dogs ...
- I'll tell him to stop by.
Bye-bye!
- Great.
- You know,
the son's single again.
- No way!
- Hey! I made those!
Get outta here!
- Stop it!
- Take over, Freddy.
Duty calls.
Oh! Can't forget my lucky charm!
Sorry for running late, Whitbey.
You know I get lost
in the moment.
Do you at least like my playing?
- It was excellent, Sire.
- Great.
Rock and roll, sir.
- I will.
- I love my job. I love my job.
- Hello. Thank you.
Good to see you. My pleasure.
Good to see you.
Oh, Mother.
You look absolutely beautiful.
And Father, positively regal.
- And you look slightly flushed.
- And barely on time.
- But I am on time.
- Members of the Privy Council,
we welcome you and your families
for our yearly
holiday gathering.
- Thank you.
- Prince Colin,
if you will do the honor.
Lovely, lovely.
- And how was the last-minute
Christmas shopping?
- Oh, it went quite well.
- Clearly.
- Well, it's quite hard
to hide from the paparazzi
in a place this small.
- There are considerably
more paparazzi in New York.
- You will have to do better
when you're there.
- New York?
- Thank you.
As you know,
Queen Alexandra and I
are honorary chairs
of the International
Children of the World
Charity Christmas Ball,
a cause dear to our hearts.
Which makes us so pleased
to announce
that Prince Colin
will journey to New York
in advance of our arrival
to introduce himself
to the international community
as a future head of state.
- Hi, General.
How's your day going?
Oh, seems like
it's going pretty well.
- Hey, sweetie.
- Hey, Ma.
- So, your father's out on a job
and Nonna Sophie's at...
Canasta.
- Of course.
I brought you some antipasto.
- Thanks.
- If that's not enough, I can
scrape up some cioppino for you.
- No, Ma, this is fine.
- Are you sure?
- Thank you. Yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
You know, your cousin Zoe?
She's awfully good at baking.
I mean, if you were interested,
she could probably show you
some things around the bakery.
I'm sure if you asked--
- I see your wheels turning.
- What did I say?
- I know what you're thinking.
- What?
- "When is my darling daughter
going to figure out
her path in life?"
- Oh, please!
I never said such a thing!
Come on.
- Trust me. I think about it
enough for both of us.
- Okay. Listen,
my darling daughter.
You just came back
from spending a lot of years
in service to your country.
You take all the time you need
to figure out what you wanna do.
And when you do, us Parettis
got your back. Capischi ?
- Capischi.
- Yeah.
- Love you, Ma.
- Eat your food.
- Hey, Dee!
Can you answer that, please?
- Yeah.
Hello, Rossi's Bakery.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey, Eddie.
Zo, it's your fiancé.
- Hey, baby!
- Uh, actually, I'm calling
to talk to the both of you.
Uh, two of our bakers
got poached by another hotel
and I kinda need your help.
Uh, people from all over
the world are here
for this international
children's charity thing,
and, uh, I told Chef Pierre
that my fiancé
is the best baker in the world.
- Aw, babe!
- I mean, it's true.
And you've been saying
you wanted to grow your business
and maybe open up another
location after we tie the knot.
- Yeah, when's that happening,
by the way?
- What do you need from me,
Eddie?
- Uh, your fanciest delights
and whatever you can
throw together fast. All right?
Pastry approval's today.
Goodbye.
Zo! This is... This is huge!
- What day is today?
Tuesday? It's Tuesday.
I gotta get the Martinez
wedding cake done by 5:00.
- You can do it!
- No. No, I-I-I can't.
This hotel is, like,
super fancy.
- No, you can do this.
You can do this.
You are the granddaughter
of two legendary bakers, okay?
They're gonna love
whatever you do.
And then the Rossis
are gonna have locations
in all five boroughs,
and you and Eddie
are gonna get married
whenever you actually
set a date.
When is that happening again?
- One crisis at a time, Dee.
- All right, um,
here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna handle prep,
you're gonna bake
like you do every day,
and then I, your cousin
and very best friend,
am going to hand-deliver
the pastries
to fancy Manhattan,
to hotel hoity-toity,
and you're gonna finish that
over-the-top wedding cake.
- Dee!
- You know it's true.
It's gonna be great!
- Yeah, what could go wrong?
- Lovely, isn't it?
There is no better way
to experience New York
for the first time
than at Christmas.
- I couldn't agree more.
- Now, Sire,
remember you're here
on business.
We don't want another
paparazzi incident,
especially on a first day.
- You never let me have any fun.
- Yeah. And yet you find it
nonetheless.
- Oh, I will.
- Oh, oh my goodness!
- Oh, my God! No, no, no, no!
No, please! Tell me
that did not just happen.
- That did not just happen.
Though, of course, it did. Um...
Facing reality just
isn't one of my strong suits.
Whatever this is...
Was. Whatever this was,
um, let me replace it?
H-how much do I owe you?
- Nothing.
You can't replace this,
and you can't just buy
your way out of it
because of your accent.
- Well, you have
an accent yourself.
I can remind you of that.
- Do you have a problem
with my accent?
- No, I think your accent's
rather lovely.
Um, my sincere apologies.
Please, let me know
if there's anything I can
do to remedy
this unfortunate accident.
- Do you have a time machine?
- I wish but unfortunately not.
- Time! Ah! Zoe's gonna kill me!
Some guy in the lobby decided
he was playing running back
for the Jets and wham!
- Have you looked inside?
- No, I'm afraid to.
- Ed, you do it.
- Oh...
I-It's not that bad.
- You're lying.
- I am. I'm lying. I'm lying.
But, hey, look, we could try it.
Right, Chef?
- Okay.
- Try...
- Oh la, la, Eddie!
- Huh? Didn't I tell you?
Zo's the best.
- Can you guarantee me
1,500 assorted pastries
of this quality on Saturday
for the International Children's
Charity Ball?
But not smooshed up.
- I mean, yeah,
but with an order that large,
you'd have to pay a rush fee.
- Of course.
- And you have to promote
that the pastries
are from Rossi's at the event.
- Done.
- And, you know, we could use
a glowing recommendation
for our website.
- Fine. Anything else?
- No, you got a deal!
- All right.
- Nice.
Oh, gosh...
- One more for the coffee.
- Oh, thank you.
- Very nice, sir.
Now may we move on
to some less visible activities?
- Oh, Whitbey. Come on.
You can let me enjoy
some of my time
here in New York.
- Your parents have
expressed a desire
for you to move on
from rock bands and race cars,
and prepare yourself
for when you rule.
- Whitbey, that's years away.
- Not necessarily.
- What are you saying?
- I believe the discussion
of your...
succession might be coming soon.
- How soon?
- I'd enjoy these days in this
glorious city if I were you.
- Is my father in good health?
- Yes. But the Queen has told me
they hope to pass
the crown to you
while they're still
young enough to be able
to spend time together
without the demands of state.
- Well, that's a relief.
But unless Parliament
has changed the law,
I have to be married
to assume the crown.
- Another reason I thought
you'd appreciate
some more time to prepare.
- Oh, heavens.
You're going to tell me next
that they've chosen
a wife for me as well?
- Not exactly chosen.
More of a strong suggestion.
- I was joking!
- I was not.
- W-Well, do I know her,
or will I simply meet her
on my wedding day?
- Duchess Adriana.
- Adriana? Why?
- They saw you together
at last year's
Exeter Quadricentennial
celebration.
You seemed to be enjoying
each other's company.
- Of course we were.
We've known each other
since we were children.
I love her like a sister.
There's never been any spark.
- Well, sir, it is Christmas.
Perhaps there'll be one
in your stocking.
Glad to see you haven't
lost your sense of humor.
And on that note, I am off
to prepare your suite.
- Zoe, you got the job!
And some amazing advertising.
I'll tell you everything
when I get home!
Oh. Pop's calling. I gotta go.
- Okay, bye.
- 'Kay, bye.
Hey, Pops!
- Hey, baby girl.
I hate to bear bad news
but I got a broken-down bus
I gotta tow in. It looks like
I ain't gonna make
choir rehearsal.
- But the concert's
in three days!
I mean, where am I gonna find
a piano player
at such short notice?
- Okay, I wish I could
do something, but right now,
I'm as stuck as this bus is.
- You know what?
I got an idea, Pops!
- Yeah, I love--
I love you too.
- Hi. Excuse me, I know this
is gonna sound a little funny,
but what are you doing la...?
You?
- Uh...
Uh, yes, it's still me.
You were saying
what sounded like
the beginning of a question?
- Did you mean it earlier
when you said you'd do anything
to repay me for crushing
all the pastries?
- Oh, I most certainly was.
Uh, at your service,
Miss, um...?
- Dee Dee.
- Dee Dee? Like the letters?
- Uh, like my name.
Daphne Dolores Paretti.
- Ah, Daphne. One of my favorite
writers is Daphne du Maurier.
- And you are?
- Colin.
St. Bernard.
From Exeter.
At your service, Miss Daphne.
So how much do I owe you?
- Oh, no, no.
This isn't a financial favor.
Follow me, Fancy Pants.
- May I ask where we're going?
How do I know
you're not a kidnapper?
- How do I know you're not one?
- Ah, touché, Miss Daphne.
- It's Dee Dee.
C'mon, Mr. St. Bernard.
We're goin' to Queens.
- Children.
- Is that gonna be a problem?
- Absolutely not!
I've sometimes been accused
of being a big
overgrown child myself.
- Good to know.
Sheet music's on the piano.
- May I ask how long
this repayment will last?
- As long as it takes.
All right, guys!
Let's get in our spots.
Let's start.
Mr. Colin is going to be here
today to cover for Mr. Mickey.
He could not be here, all right?
So, let's all say
thank you, Mr. Colin.
Thank you.
- You're very welcome!
- All right. You ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
All right.
Remember, straight posture
and a nice deep breath.
♪ Deck the halls
with boughs of holly ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 'Tis is the season
to be jolly ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la... ♪
♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride ♪
♪ In a one-horse open sleigh ♪
- That was good, you guys.
Good job.
What?
- Uh, nothing.
It's just a bit dull.
- Dull?
These are like,
classic Christmas songs!
We've been singing these
since I was a kid.
This is the tradition.
- Yes, tradition.
I know tradition,
and in this instance,
tradition is dull.
- All right. What would you
have them sing, then?
♪ Joy to the world ♪
♪ The Lord has come ♪
♪ Let Earth receive her king ♪
- Something like that.
- All right, that was great.
Everybody thank Mr. Colin for
gracing us with his presence.
Thank you!
- You guys. Have a good night.
Pack up your bags.
Leave your music books
on the table or the piano.
Thank you.
- He's so cool!
- Good night, Ava.
- Good night, Miss Dee.
Bye, Mr. Colin!
- Goodnight, Angel!
- Night, guys.
See you guys later.
All right.
That was pretty good.
I gotta say, you really added
something special
to the music tonight.
A little spark.
- A spark? Interesting.
- Come on. You gotta
get that reaction a lot.
- Ah, yes, but typically,
it's because they've had
a few pints.
- So, what? Do you just play
to bars and empty hotel lobbies?
- I play wherever I can
in a spare moment.
My parents aren't exactly
supportive of my life
in the performing arts.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm kinda lucky that my parents
have had me up on those risers
since before I could walk.
- You were in this choir
as a child?
- Yeah, yeah. My dad was always
like, the guy on the piano.
They're big into music.
My folks actually started
this whole choir
because schools were cutting
use of school funding,
and... the city gives us
money for this,
but really,
the Christmas concert's like,
the big fundraiser.
- I'm sure it'll be
a lovely night.
- I hope so. Christmas is a big
deal around here.
We have, like, a whole
week of celebrations.
Everybody decorates
their houses,
and then there's
a snowman-making competition,
and then there's a Secret Santa,
and then there's this, like,
massive block party
where we decorate a huge tree
and everybody hangs ornaments
and makes wishes.
- I've never heard
of that tradition.
Have you tried it?
- Yeah. Yeah, it didn't really
work out for me, so...
- I'm sorry.
I'm sure your bakery does well
during these festivities.
- Ah, no. It's not my bakery.
My cousin Zoe runs it.
I've just... been working there
since my last tour,
just kind of, like,
figuring out
what the next step is, so...
- I'm sorry. Tour?
- Of duty, but that's a story
for another day.
So, uh,
what brings you to town?
- Um, I'm here with my...
for a family business.
- Hey! What's this I hear
you found some guy
who plays piano
better than I can?
- What happened to you?
- Ah, just a little strain.
That's what you get when you
try to pick up a school bus
with one hand, I guess.
- Yeah, Dad, this is Colin.
Colin, this is my dad,
Mickey Paretti.
- Hey, you really saved
my bacon today.
- It was my--
- Thank you, my man.
- Uh, pleasure, truly.
- Okay, your mother's got
some chicken caprese
in the oven,
so let's go eat some dinner.
- Dad...
- What? You know your mother
always makes enough food
for the whole neighborhood.
- That's very kind.
- I'm sure you have other plans.
What?!
- Not a one.
- Hey!
My Angie's gonna love
your accent.
She may never let you leave.
Come on, now.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Queens?
What are you doing in Queens?
♪ They hang the lights
in Sicily ♪
♪ The manger scenes of Napoli ♪
♪ Remind us of
Jesus' birth... ♪
- Truly, it looked more
like an accordion
than a box of pastries!
- Oh. Colin,
you want some gravy?
- Gravy?
- Yeah, for your pasta.
- Italians call
pasta sauce "gravy."
- It is gravy!
- Well, the gravy
smells delicious.
- How was work, Ma?
Uh, Ma's a nurse over at--
- Head nurse.
- Head nurse over at
Meadows Nursing Home.
- Okay, relax, you two.
My job, so glamorous.
I mean, the highlight
of my day today
was when Mr. Bloom
wandered into the wrong room
and wound up wearing
Mrs. Strasser's velour suit.
- No, no!
- Which is like three sizes
too small for him.
- Ma!
- I mean, okay, well, you asked!
Come on!
- How fun.
Your family is so different
than my own.
- Right, now that
sounds wonderful.
- You'd be surprised.
- Hey, so, uh,
so what's Christmas like in...?
- In Exeter?
- Exeter, yeah.
- The royal family is, um,
a bit old-fashioned,
but they put on
a fine holiday celebration.
A beautiful tree, wreaths,
banners, ribbons,
and if it doesn't snow enough,
they bring in machines
to create it.
- Wow.
- Wow. Must be nice.
- So, what is it
you do for a livin'?
- Ma!
- The young man can answer
if he wants!
You don't mind, do you?
- It's fine.
- There you go.
- Management. Family business.
- Huh.
- It's what brought me
to New York.
- You must do good
if you stay at The Grand.
- It's great that
you're on a path.
You know,
you gotta set direction.
I mean, my little Dee
could use something like that
these days.
- Mickey! Come on.
- Just saying.
- She just got outta the army!
That's not fair.
She was in the army.
- Nah. I mean, he's got a point.
It's fine. It's been,
what, six months now?
- You were in the army?
- She sure was. She followed
Mickey's footsteps here.
That's how we got the General.
- Yeah, I spent the last,
what, five years
in the K-9 unit.
He was by my side
every step of the way.
Got so attached, you know?
Couldn't leave him there.
- So, um, Mr. Mickey,
you served as well?
- Yeah, 20 years as a mechanic.
You know, on the big beasts.
Now I got a nice little
towing and plowing company.
I got three guys working for me.
It's nice.
- Oh, no, no, no!
You sit, sit. You're our guest.
- I'm gonna go to the Lees.
They're hosting
Mahjong tonight!
- Have fun!
- Say hi for us.
- You sit and relax your hands.
I'm gonna get
you ice for that. Okay?
- Okay.
- How can I be of service?
- You can dry.
You look like
more of a dryer than a washer.
Here, you can use this cloth.
- So, use the cloth
to dry the wet dish.
- I'm guessing you grew up
with a dishwasher, am I right?
- Yes, of sorts.
- Ah, this life must seem
a million miles away
from what you're used to.
- And surprisingly comfortable.
- Give it a few days.
So, um, your family company.
What do you do there?
- Well, up till now,
to be honest,
as little as possible.
But it seems as if
I'm gonna be kicked upstairs
to an executive position.
- Congrats.
It's exciting, isn't it?
- Some of the requirements
pose a challenge.
- Anything you can't handle?
- No. I'm just not
too sure I want to.
- Oh.
Well, I guess there's
always gonna be things
you don't wanna do in life,
like dishes.
But if it's bigger than that,
I guess you have
to ask yourself, you know,
is it worth the sacrifice?
You've only got one life.
It's important that you're
the one in charge of it.
- Sage advice, Miss Daphne.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What are you gonna do?
Nah, nah. Just get home safe.
Don't worry about it.
Talk soon.
- Well, thank you
for a wonderful evening.
I'm afraid, though, that I must
I depart for my hotel.
- Oh, no, no.
That's not gonna happen.
Joey D says those roads
out there
ain't fit for nothing
but the Ice Capades tonight.
- Oh, well, then,
you're stayin' here.
- Spend the night?
- Mom, I'm sure Colin--
- It's all right. Dee Dee
will make up the couch for you.
- Ma!
- I couldn't possibly impose.
- Don't be silly.
You're not imposing.
- Hey, she's right.
That couch has seen more guests
than the Grand Park Hotel.
- It's true.
- Yeah.
- This is very generous,
Thank you.
I just need to make
one quick phone call. Excuse me.
- Ma. Really?
- What? Don't blame me
for the weather!
Anyway, let's get
the good linens.
- Now, Whitbey, don't be upset
but I shall be
sleeping here tonight.
- And where exactly is "here"?
- Don't pretend you're not
tracking my whereabouts
on the app. Now, Whitbey,
don't worry. I'm utterly safe.
I'm told the sofa
sees plenty of guests.
- They're giving a prince
the sofa?
- Yes, that.
Look, Whitbey,
the Parettis have
no idea who I am,
and I'd very much like for it
to stay that way.
- Instinctively that feels
like a very poor decision.
However, I don't wish
to argue the point.
Tomorrow, though, we must
discuss your royal obligations.
- Yes, yes.
Tomorrow, absolutely.
Listen, one other thing,
Whitbey?
- Yes, sir?
- Did you know that I don't
have a surname?
I mean, Father
has the House of Dansey,
and Mother has
the House of Knowton,
but what do I have?
- You don't require
a surname, Sire.
You are Prince Colin Alfons
Marcus George of Exeter.
That is more than enough.
- Right, yes.
Of course.
I'm all yours.
- Hey, there he is.
- Oh, wow!
- Got cannolis!
- Look at these!
These are incredible.
- They're delicious!
- You're gonna love 'em.
- Have you ever had it?
- I haven't.
- You have to have one.
- She makes them like nobody.
- What do you think?
It's delicious.
- They're so good, right?
Here, have a napkin.
- Wonderful. Your cannoli
is absolutely incredible.
- I know. It's a family recipe.
Have one. Just one.
- You can eat as many
as you want.
I just can't tell you
how they're made.
- I'm gonna eat all of 'em.
- See. I know he'd like 'em.
- What's not to like?
- I think you should have one.
- Hello?
- Good morning, Your Highness.
How was the sofa?
- Oh, it was, um...
My back is sore,
there's a crick in my neck,
and at one point I had
to share my pillow
with a Belgian Malinois.
- Ugh. Sounds five-star.
Now, your official commitments
start at noon.
And I suggest you make
your way back to the hotel--
- Yeah, I'll be back
in plenty of time, Whitbey.
Don't worry.
Listen, I've gotta go.
- Dare I trust him?
Oh, Whitbey, why start now?
- ...so your back
doesn't get sore.
- Use my knees? In what sense?
- Bend 'em, bend 'em.
Oh, hey!
- What's going on here?
- Oh, thank God you're here.
Thank you, Miss Daphne.
Your father here is teaching me
the tools of the trade
while his wrist heals.
What that trade is,
I haven't a clue.
- So, how's the wrist?
- Ah, Doc says it'll be
about a week.
What, uh, exactly is happening--
- You know it's the annual
snowman competition!
Come on. So, every year
after the first big snowfall,
we get paired with a kid
on the block and we help them
make their snowman.
Zoe even gets someone to cover
her shift in the morning
so she can sleep in,
like it's a national holiday
or something.
- Sleep is important.
- Do you need to be back
to your hotel? For your job?
- My duties commence
at noon... ish.
- In that case, follow me,
Mr. St. Bernard.
- Am I allowed to know
where we're going this time?
- Nope.
- I got it. Thanks so much.
- Thank you.
- You look like you've never
done this before.
- The snow rolls differently
in Exeter.
- What do you think, Eli?
- Excuses!
- You tell him!
- You two are worse than
my headmaster at the academy.
- I am in need a car to Queens,
please. I'm in a bit of a rush.
- Of course, sir,
but with the conference,
I won't have a car or driver
ready for a few hours.
You could try the subway.
- Oh, you're serious.
- Very.
- Oh gosh.
Next stop, Queensborough Plaza.
It has to go
around the neck like this.
- Oh.
- A traditional snowman.
Okay, here we go.
- Oh, that's fantastic.
- More snow.
- Hello!
- Oh, look who finally
showed up.
- So, I slept in
for once in my life.
- So, this must be
the famous Zoe.
- And this must be Colin,
the famous pastry-smushing
piano player.
- Guilty as charged.
Are you joining
the festivities?
- No, I'm just dropping off
some sustenance for the troops.
I gotta get back to the bakery.
I've only got two days
to prep for that
big order you almost...
- My apologies for that
near-disaster.
Luckily, Miss Daphne
managed to save the day.
- Yeah. Miss Daphne's
good like that.
Bye!
- Okay. This looks good.
Finally picked a good
partner this year.
- You like him.
- I don't--
H-He's here not even a week.
- So? It's time you got over
the whole Billy situation.
- What?
There's no Billy situation.
- Then how come you haven't
dated anyone serious-like since?
- I've dated.
- For longer than a month!
- That just speaks the quality
of the guy,
not that I've been
stuck up on one person.
- I just don't want you
to miss out.
- Says the girl who's been
engaged for how long?
- Two years.
Just feels like longer
'cause we dated for ten.
- What's the deal?
- I don't know.
I guess it's just more romantic
to be engaged
than married, you know?
And, like,
what if we lose our spark?
And I'm a Rossi, okay?
What's a Rossi's Bakery
without a Rossi?
- You know, there are ways
around that, right?
- Daphne, we need you
for the final push.
All good?
- Yeah. It's all good.
- Good.
- Okay. This looks good, guys.
- Does it?
- Thanks!
- That was awesome!
Grab the ribbon, you get
to take it.
- Good job, Mr. St. Bernard.
- Thank you.
- Oh, it's on!
- What're you gonna do about it?
- No, I could never hit a lady.
Come and get me! No!
- Your Majesty.
- Whitbey.
Yes. How are things going?
- How are they going?
- Ah!
- I'd say smashingly.
- Oh, excellent. Excellent.
And the Prince.
Now, is he behaving himself?
- Absolutely.
- Oh, that's excellent, Whitbey.
Excellent.
Goodbye Whitbey.
All right, Vlad.
Once more around.
- Sorry.
- Okay, fine.
- Truce.
- Okay, fine. A truce.
Oh!
- Thanks.
- Oh, no, no.
- Ah! Oh!
Whitbey. Hi.
Uh...
This is my executive assistant,
Whitbey.
- Oh, hi. It's nice to meet you.
- A pleasure to meet you.
I apologize
for the interruptions,
but we do have
those meetings this afternoon,
and "the boss" insists
that you be there on time.
- I'm sorry.
It appears that I-I have to go.
- No, for sure, yeah.
I hope you have
a great rest of your trip.
- Dee Dee?
This doesn't have to be
goodbye quite yet.
Your father asked if I could
cover for him for rehearsals.
- Really?
- That's quite impossible.
- I said, "With pleasure."
Sorry, old chap.
- Here's your music books.
Here you go.
Thank you.
- Mr. Colin! Yay!
- Mr. Colin's gonna be helping
out until Mr. Mickey's back
with his wrist healing, okay?
All right, beautiful,
talented elves,
let's get in your spots.
We're gonna start
with Oh Christmas Tree.
All right?
What's that?
- Oh, that's my lucky charm.
I've had it with me
since I was a child.
I never play without it.
- Where'd you get it?
- My grandfather gave it to me
when I was a boy.
We were in Exeter,
just the two of us.
We found it in a shop there.
He knew how much I loved music
so he bought it for me.
Why do you ask?
- Oh, no, it's just funny
'cause I also have
a piano Christmas tree ornament
that my Nonno Giuseppe got me
'cause he knows
how much I like music, so...
- Interesting.
- But I mean, I'm sure
a lot of people
have piano Christmas
tree ornaments?
- Oh, yeah. Given to them
by their grandfathers?
- Lots of people.
It's funny, for sure.
Um, we should
probably get started.
- Yes.
- Good evening.
- Whitbey, I'm looking
at the press coverage of today,
and I must say, I'm delighted!
- Ask about Adriana.
- Shh, shh.
- The Prince seems to have
acquitted himself admirably.
And the suit,
oh it's a nice step up
from a t-shirt and torn jeans.
- Did he mention Adriana?
- Shh.
Just the kind of image
the people of Exeter
need to see.
- I'm so pleased you're pleased.
- Adriana. Adriana!
- Have you spoken
to him about Adriana?
- Yes, Your Majesty.
- And how did he take it?
- He was surprised,
but he did express
affection for her.
- Oh, excellent! Excellent!
Things couldn't be going
any better.
Goodnight, Whitbey.
- Your Majesty.
Oh, Whitbey.
Technically, everything
you said was true.
- The kids are getting
really good.
- They're all right.
No, they're good.
- All right.
Best and worst Christmas gifts
you ever received?
- Okay, that's easy.
Spice Girls roller skates.
I literally wore them everywhere
all the time
like they were shoes.
I actually got
sent home from school
because they weren't
appropriate.
- What?
- I know. Who knew?
- And worst?
- Uh, getting stood up.
- Who would dare stand you up?
- Right?
All right,
same question for you.
Maximillian Chesterton
Ridley the Third.
- I'm sorry. Did you get
a person as a present, or...?
- He was my Cavalier
King Charles Spaniel puppy.
- Aw. And worst?
- Spice Girls roller skates.
- I'd like to see that actually.
You sure you're up for this?
Not too soon to bail.
- I wouldn't dare miss Angie's,
or anyone else's delicacies,
for that matter.
This is so much food.
Is there always this much?
- Welcome to Queens.
- I wish my parents
could see this. It's inspiring.
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Hey, Dad.
Wow! You got
a good one this year!
- This year?
When has he not?
So, Dee,
nice you brought your friend.
- Yeah, well, you know,
rehearsal ran late,
and I though the least
I could do was feed the guy.
- Least you could do, huh?
- Please allow me.
- Ah! No, Prince Charming.
No one touch the manicotti
but me.
Hmm? Carmine!
Come and help me
with the manicotti!
- You've done it again,
Uncle Mickey.
It's the kind of tree gonna make
any true love dream come true.
Right?
- Hey, I'm Eddie.
- Hello, I'm--
- Buddy, we all know
who you are.
- Yes, I should, um--
- That pastry-collision story
is already legendary!
- So, uh, tell me about
the wishes on the tree.
- Oh, that is true love.
So, you take
your favorite ornament,
place it on the tree,
you close your eyes,
you make a wish,
and when you open 'em,
if they're staring
back at you...
- It's true love.
That's how I got my Ang, here.
- It's true.
- All right, all right,
all right.
There's not gonna be any
true love
if the tree is on the truck.
- Get to it.
- Fair enough. Have fun.
- Come on, Eddie.
Give me a hand.
♪ I don't want nothin'
melancholy ♪
♪ Just a little eggnog
and holly ♪
♪ On this holiday with you ♪
♪ So hurry up
don't keep me waitin' ♪
♪ I'm in the mood
for celebrating ♪
♪ Just want a holiday for two ♪
♪ As long as I'm with you ♪
♪ I don't care what we do ♪
♪ A cozy fire
or snowflakes under the moon ♪
♪ Grab some candy canes
and go ice fishin' ♪
♪ As long as we're together
we can only win ♪
♪ When you're around
it's Christmas ♪
♪ The whole year through ♪
♪ Oh, I don't want nothing... ♪
- Thank you.
- Well done, Sire.
- Quite a bit different
from last night's gathering.
You should have seen it,
Whitbey.
A whole neighborhood
working together
and doing it in a joyous way!
Wouldn't it be wonderful
if we could get the people
of Exeter involved
rather than simply
presenting them
with the palace's
ideas of Christmas?
- Your Highness,
the good people of Queens
obviously have their traditions,
but Exeter has its own.
- Something else for me
to attend to when I become King.
- Your father will be delighted
to know
you're already thinking about
your future role.
- Yes, a future apparently
not so far away.
Hello.
- How's it going back here?
- Well, I ordered all
the extra ingredients
for the Charity Ball,
and I figure if we prep
the day before, then we can get
the delivery to the hotel
in time for the event. Easy!
- Did you talk to Eddie?
- No, but we talked about
setting a time to talk about it.
- Okay, well, that's a start.
- Yeah, speaking of starts,
you and Mr. Piano Man
seemed to be hitting it off.
- He lives 3,000 miles away
and he's only here for, like,
a week and a half.
- Blah, blah, blah.
You like him.
- Okay. I like him.
- Yeah, you do.
Hello, Rossi's Bakery,
how can I help you?
Why, yes, Colin!
She's right here.
Let me get her for you.
- Hi, Colin.
- Hi, Dee Dee.
So, listen, I've finished
my professional obligations
for the day, and I was
thinking of going out
and exploring the city.
I'm sure you probably can't get
away from the bakery right now,
but in case you wanted
to join me, I'm--
- She'd love to!
- Sorry, Colin,
that was my cousin Zoe.
Um, but, yeah,
I, uh, I'd love to.
- Well, that's smashing!
- And I know
just where to take you.
It's amazing, right?
You know it takes, like,
all year for them to do this,
and it's like 100 people
that it takes to pull it off.
They even pick music
that perfectly
balances the senses.
'Kay, there's another one
I want to show you.
Look, over here.
Beautiful, huh?
- Yeah.
- My Dad and I would
do this every year.
We'd go window shopping
and then we'd make up
these elaborate stories
about what was happening
in each one. Kind of like
our way of seeing the world.
Like, for these people,
I feel like,
it's a snowstorm, you know,
and they're rushing to get--
- To the mountains in Sweden.
- Yeah, for, like,
a big Christmas vacation.
- 'Cause they're secretly
in love, and they want to elope.
- No, no, no! They wanna have
a big elaborate wedding
with all their family
and friends!
That's the energy
that I'm feeling.
Specifically from her, actually.
- I like this game.
- Yeah, it's cool.
And especially when I was a kid,
you know, it was sort of, like,
a way to travel
to all these different places
when, you know, we couldn't
always afford to do that.
- It's understandable.
- You know, I, um...
I had this very serious,
long-term boyfriend, Billy,
who I met in
high school, actually.
And we were together forever,
and we sort of had, like,
our entire lives planned out.
We were supposed to meet
at the Christmas Wishing
Tree together
and put our ornaments on,
and make a wish,
and, um...
- The worst Christmas gift ever.
- Yeah.
- I think you're very brave,
Miss Daphne.
A natural leader.
- I don't know about that.
I feel like maybe the army
is more about following.
- I don't know.
I think if you
set your mind to it,
there's nothing
that you can't do.
- That's easier to say
when you have the means.
Actually, I didn't mean
that about you or anything.
- No, it's fine.
I sometimes think
that with my position,
there's more I should do.
More I should be.
- Hey mom, look!
That's so cool!
- Um...
There's this really cool place
around the corner
if you wanna go check it out.
Okay.
Follow me.
- It's like being trapped
inside a Christmas tree.
- Yeah, it used to take them
weeks to hang it all up
so at one point they just
decided to leave it up all year.
So, people actually come here
just to hang up
their own Christmas ornaments.
- So, will I find
your piano ornament
hanging up here somewhere?
- No, you will not,
because it's at my house.
It's very important to me.
I have to keep it safe.
- Not even on the Christmas
Wishing Tree?
- I almost hung it there, once,
but I did not.
And I'm very glad that I didn't.
- Perhaps when the time
is right. Maybe.
- Perhaps, yeah.
- Cheers to that.
So, are you ever going
to pursue music
outside of hotel lobbies
and bars?
'Cause you're really good.
Like honestly,
I think you're amazing.
- Thank you.
Um, it's not an option for me.
I mean, if I could, I would.
When I play, I feel...
I feel free.
It's like I feel...
like...
Just myself. Like, just Colin.
- Instead of...?
- My parents' son.
- Right.
- I don't want
to sound ungrateful.
It's just simply...
- It's not all of who you are.
- Exactly.
- Right.
- And I don't have much choice
in the matter, so...
- You know, it's funny.
- What is?
- It's just, you have all this
direction and no freedom,
and I have all
the freedom in the world
and zero direction.
- One of the things
I admire most about you
are your many interests.
And I know that
when you choose a direction,
you're gonna absolutely soar.
- You're so good for my ego.
I need to keep you around.
- Good. 'Cause I calls 'em
like I sees 'em.
- No. Never do that again.
Ever.
You are gonna be great
tomorrow!
Just remember to wear
red and white,
and be on time, okay?
All right, let's get ready,
'cause what's in an hour?
- Secret Santa!
- That's right.
- Thank you, Miss Dee Dee!
This year has been the best!
And Mr. Colin, thank you, too.
- Thank you, Ava.
You have the voice of an angel.
- I like the way he talks.
- You did great today.
I'll see you later.
- Bye.
You can come
to the Secret Santa,
if you want.
- Thank you. I'd love to.
However, since I wasn't around
for the name selection,
I have no gift to give.
- Right.
Well, Santa works
in very mysterious ways,
so I could probably
get you, like, a...
- A delicious free meal?
I might just need new trousers
when I return.
- They sound perfectly rustic.
Well, I'm thrilled to know
the lasagna is delicious,
but I... Oh, dear.
Oh, I'm-I'm so sorry,
Your Highness,
I'm going to have
to call you back.
Your Majesties.
What... We weren't expecting you
until tomorrow.
- Well, your report on how well
the Prince had responded
to the discussion of his future
was so positive
we couldn't resist
joining him early.
- And bringing him
a wonderful surprise.
- How incredibly
thoughtful of you.
I'm sure he'll be thrilled.
- Whitbey, how lovely
to see you!
- Duchess Adriana!
Isn't this amazing?
One incredible delight
after another.
- Oh, thank you, Whitbey.
You always know what to say.
- And what to do! I know
it hasn't always been easy
being Colin's guardian,
but you're more than that.
You're his friend,
and it comforts us to know
that you give him
such good guidance.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
He can be a bit headstrong
at times,
but his heart is always
in the right place.
That is an important
thing to remember.
- Speaking of Colin,
where is he?
- He's, uh, presently engaged
in a local children's
art program
that has really had
quite an impact on him.
- Excellent! Another example
of royal behavior
we were hoping to see from him.
- Why don't we pay this
arts program a visit ourselves?
Oh, wouldn't that
be delightful, Adriana?
- Of course. It's been
far too long
since Colin and I
have seen each other.
- Let me just text him
so he's able
to receive you properly.
- Oh, let's make it a surprise!
I can't wait to see his face
when we walk in
with Duchess Adriana.
- Neither can I, Your Majesty.
- Then it's settled.
Lead on, Whitbey! Lead on!
- Parents here, on our way.
- Weren't the kids so adorable?
- Like a school of piranhas.
You never told me
about the costume change.
- Ooh, I dunno.
That must've slipped my mind.
I don't know what happened.
- How come you got away
with playing dress-up?
- Well, 'cause you're here!
So, well, thank you, buddy!
Ho, ho, ho!
- "Honor's ear. Baron's elf."
- Is everything okay?
- Yes. I think my assistant
Whitbey just sent me
what we in Exeter
call a "pocket text."
- Ha. In our house,
we call that a Mickey.
- Hey! It happened one time
that happened!
Okay, maybe two times.
- Hey, look, there's still
one present left.
- Hmm.
Oh, it's for you.
- "To Colin St. Bernard."
- Open it.
- I mean, this is amazing.
Somehow Santa knew
where I was gonna be.
A keyboard scarf!
This is perfect.
Let's see this.
It's lovely.
- It looks good.
- I have a feeling I know
who my Secret Santa is.
- Well, if you know, you're not
supposed to say anything.
- This is too much.
I feel bad that Santa
didn't get you anything.
- Are you kidding me?
He got me a piano player
when I needed one the most.
- Should you happen to find out
who my Secret Santa is...
give them this for me.
- Surprise! Your Highness.
- Uh... Mother, Father,
um, Adriana?
- That guy just call Colin,
"Your Highness?"
- I had no idea you were
arriving tonight.
- It was a last-minute decision.
And your mother
wanted to surprise you, Colin.
- Yes, and by
the look on your face,
and your outfit, we did.
- How did you know where I was?
- I told them you were involved
in this wonderful
children's art program,
and they insisted on seeing it.
- Right, yes, of course. Um...
Well, the children
have all gone,
but allow me to introduce you
to some new, but very dear
friends of mine.
Uh,
Angelica and Mickey Paretti.
- Hi.
- Their daughter Dee Dee,
who runs it, her friend, Zoe,
and her fiancé, Eddie,
who is a chef at our hotel.
- 'Sup?
- Ah, yes,
and this is Miss Sophie.
- King Sebastian,
Queen Alexandra of Exeter.
- Queen?
- King?
- Ma, you knew?
- I used the Google.
- So, when you said
family business,
you meant that you're a prince?
- Yes.
- So, I'm gonna guess
your last name
isn't St. Bernard either.
- No.
- Colin.
- Right, yes, sorry.
Um, and let me present
Duchess Adriana, my, um...
- The Prince's companion
for the Children's Charities
Christmas Ball.
- Oh, well, uh, Your Highness,
you must be parched.
We got lots of hot chocolate
here. It's delicious.
- Excuse us.
- Thank you.
That would be delightful.
- Oh, we'd be honored.
- Go ahead.
- Miss Daphne, please wait.
- Look, I know we're not
a fancy Royal Family,
but we have integrity.
You should have told me.
- I wanted to tell you.
This was the first time
in my life
that people didn't
recognize who I was.
You and your family treated me
like a regular person,
and I loved it.
And the longer it went on,
the harder it was
for me to say anything.
I'm sorry.
I really liked being
Colin and Dee Dee.
- Well, I'm sorry
that you're not gonna be able
to play with us tomorrow night.
The kids are really
gonna miss you.
- Mickey's wrist
is still injured.
You don't have a backup.
- I'll find someone.
- Christmas week?
- Yeah, sure. I'll just go scour
all the fancy hotel lobbies
and ask all the piano players,
"Hey, are you a secret member
of royalty?
No? Great. You're hired."
- Then I'll tell them
we don't need their services
because I will fulfill
my promise.
- It's ridiculous. You can't.
You're a prince!
- And a prince always
fulfills his commitments.
- Commitments?
Is that all
this has been to you?
- Of course not.
- Honestly, it's fine.
The kids will just sing
a cappella.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
Your Highness,
I have to go clean,
like a real person.
- And I'm telling you, Dee,
I did not see any chemistry
between Colin and Duchess
whatever-her-name-was.
It's probably just one of those
PR dates.
You know, photo-op.
Means nothing.
- I know you're trying
to make me feel better,
and I appreciate it,
I really do, but I'm fine.
- Dee, it's me
you're talkin' to.
- I mean, sure,
was he super handsome,
and charming, and kind,
and talented?
But he lied to me.
I mean, fool me once,
it's not gonna end well.
- Dee--
- Zo, he's a prince.
I'm not a princess.
- But you felt like one.
- Once again, Sire,
my apologies,
but I did try
to text you a warning.
- Yes, in this instance,
Whitbey,
autocorrect was not our friend.
- Um, four-letter word
for buffet.
- Buffet, hmm? Cart!
- Ha ha ha! Cart!
- Oh, good morning, son.
How handsome you look.
- Thank you, Mother. Father.
So, what's on the agenda
for you two today?
- Your mother and I are hosting
a luncheon for VIP donors,
and then overseeing
final preparations
for tomorrow's ball.
Which means you have
the entire day
to spend with Adriana.
- The entire day?
- Yes.
Whitbey tells me you've become
quite a fan of the city,
so you can show her
some of your favorite spots.
And then tonight, you two
have a dinner reservation
at La Bernadine at 7:00.
- I'm afraid I have
a commitment tonight.
- Cancel it.
- I can't.
- What?
- I promised Dee Dee
I'd help with their concert.
- Colin, you have been
very generous with your time,
but you have other obligations
we need you to attend to.
And Adriana is one of those.
- Your father's right.
Sit down, son.
We know that Whitbey
has broached the subject
of your future.
Your father and I have decided
it's time for us to retire,
and for you to begin
assuming your responsibilities.
- As you know, it is our custom
that we find the proper
companion for you.
- And we believe Duchess Adriana
is that person,
and it would be good for you
to spend some time with her.
- Mother, I think Adriana
is lovely--
- And here she is,
looking as lovely as Colin
just said you were.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
Thank you, Colin.
- The shop windows were designed
by local artists.
- Shopping!
Oh, there must be
all sorts of things
we can't get in Exeter. Come!
- Have a good day! Ava!
Mrs. Rodriguez! Hi!
- Hi, Miss Dee Dee.
- Dee Dee,
have you met my daughter,
Ava's mother?
- Principal Deacons, right?
From P.S. 267?
- Yeah, that's right.
I can't wait to hear
her sing tonight.
- Well, I think you'll be
very proud.
- Mr. Colin says I'm an angel.
- Mr. Colin?
- Uh, yeah, that was our
temporary piano guy.
- The Prince?
- Does everyone know?
- Well, I'm most interested
in hearing the concert tonight.
Ava's been raving about
Miss Dee Dee all month.
- Well, I think you'll...
I think you'll be pleased
with or without a piano player.
- Let's go see what she's got.
- You are an excellent
tour guide, Colin!
I've had a delightful time.
I'm just not sure you did.
- Is it that obvious?
- Colin, we've known each other
a long time.
What is it? You can tell me.
- I know we're supposed to have
dinner this evening,
but I already promised friends
that I'd help them
with their arts program.
- Well, that's not a problem!
Oh, we can push dinner
until later.
- Really?
- Of course.
In fact, why don't
I come with you to the event
and we can go to dinner
from there?
- You might find it boring.
- Colin, I insist.
If it's important to you,
then it's important to me.
Come.
Honey, you look
beautiful. Don't stress.
- Thank you, Mom.
- It's gonna be great.
- Sorry! Christmas traffic.
- No, no.
No apologies necessary.
We're just happy
you could make it.
Oh, Duchess Adriana,
so happy you could join us.
- Thank you. I'm really
looking forward to this.
- Hello, Mickey, Angie.
- Hmm.
- Sophie.
- Uh-huh.
- Hey, Colin.
- Come on. Let's go sit.
- So, you ready, Your Highness?
- It's still Colin.
- Yeah, I dunno
if I can do that, so...
We gotta get this show
on the road.
So, excuse me.
Hello. Welcome to the annual
Little Queens Christmas Pageant!
Thank you guys so much
for your generous support.
Your amazing kids have been
working so hard.
We can't wait for you
to hear how amazing they are.
So, you guys are in for
a very special treat tonight.
Enjoy. We have some
surprises for you.
Okay, ready?
Eyes on me. Deep breath.
Have fun! Okay?
Get ready.
♪ The first Noel ♪
♪ The angels did say ♪
♪ Was to certain
poor shepherds ♪
♪ In fields as they lay ♪
- Look!
- Oh, she's so cute.
♪ In fields as they lay ♪
♪ Keeping their sheep ♪
♪ On a cold winter's night ♪
♪ That was so deep ♪
♪ Noel, Noel ♪
♪ Noel,
Noel ♪
♪ Dashing through the snow ♪
♪ In a one-horse open sleigh ♪
♪ O'er the fields we go ♪
♪ Laughing all the way ♪
♪ Bells on bobtails ring ♪
♪ Making spirits bright ♪
♪ What fun it is
to ride and sing ♪
♪ A sleighing song tonight ♪
♪ Oh, jingle bells,
jingle bells ♪
♪ Jingle all... ♪
♪ Joy to the world ♪
♪ The Lord has come ♪
♪ Let Earth receive her king ♪
♪ Let every heart ♪
♪ Prepare Him room ♪
♪ And heaven and nature sing ♪
♪ And heaven
and nature sing ♪
♪ And heaven, and heaven ♪
♪ And nature sing ♪
♪ Joy to the world ♪
♪ Joy
to the world ♪
♪ Heaven, and heaven ♪
♪ And nature sing ♪
♪ Nature sing ♪
- Oh, there's my girl.
- Hey, Ma.
- Hey. I brought you some tea.
- Ah, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hey! We made the papers!
- What? Wow.
- Can you believe it?
We brought in three times
the donations
from the last year.
- Are you serious?
- Can you believe it?
- Wow! Well, I guess something
good came outta all this.
- Oh, honey.
It was for something,
and it was because of you.
Don't kid yourself.
A lot of good came outta this.
- I had nothing to do with it.
- Of course you did!
You had everything
to do with it!
This wouldn't have been possible
without you!
I mean, it's just like
this guy here. Right, buddy?
I mean, he wouldn't be here
if you hadn't brought him
back with you,
and then you helped, like,
a dozen of your fellow
service members
get their K-9's, too.
- Yeah, I mean,
it was important.
- That's right.
And, hey, you brought
real live royalty
right here to Queens.
You?
You're a little dynamo,
Daphne Dolores Paretti.
And don't you forget it.
- Okay.
Oh. I love you, Ma.
- I love you too.
- I'm gonna go shower.
- Okay.
- You know, I still
can't believe
Nonna knew about this
the whole time!
- Right? I mean, who knew
out of everybody in the family,
she's the one
who could keep a secret?
- Who would've thought?
- Go figure.
- What were you thinking?
Do you know how this looks?
- Like a member
of the Royal Family
contributing to a very
worthwhile neighborhood cause.
- Really?
- That's a snowman competition!
- And the young lady?
- A friend.
I hope.
- Well, the Times of Exeter
is asking all sorts of questions
about you and this young woman.
- Dee Dee. Her name is Dee Dee.
- Colin, we wanted the people
of Exeter to get used
to the image of you and Adriana,
not you and some random girl
from Queens.
- She's not some random girl!
She's a remarkable woman
who's utterly blameless
in the situation.
- That may be,
but it's not the issue!
The press is!
Now, Whitbey has managed
to placate them
as long as you make a statement
to the press before the ball.
- Perhaps on your relationship
with Duchess Adriana?
Oh, Colin, we know
your feelings for her
are not as deep
as you would like them to be.
But your father and I,
we barely knew each other
when we were married,
and over time,
we grew to love and respect
one another completely,
and there's no reason
that couldn't happen for you,
even if you can't believe
it quite yet.
- No, Mother.
I absolutely believe
love can come
in unexpected ways.
- Well, I'm glad
to hear you say that.
- As am I.
And, Colin,
your mother and I know
that in the end,
you'll do the right thing.
- Yes. Of course.
- And Colin, your mother and I
are not completely
without interest in change.
We saw your performance
last night.
- You did?
- Yes, darling, we did.
And you have quite
the musical talent.
In fact, we plan
to incorporate it
into many future royal events.
- Your mother and I very much
desire your happiness, son.
- Yes, but only when
it's convenient for you both.
- That was not fair.
- Have a good day.
Hi! Principal Deacons.
- Dee Dee. You know,
I wanted to talk to you
after the concert.
Thank you so much.
Ava has been over the moon
throughout the whole experience
with the choir.
- Aw, that's so sweet.
Ava is such a joy.
- Look, there's something else.
And feel no pressure,
but one of the things
I've been looking to do
for a while now is bring
programs like what you did
to the school. You know,
music and art activities?
What you did with the choir
fits in line
with what I had in mind.
Have you ever considered
anything like that?
You know, creating after-school
enrichment programs for kids?
- No, not, not really.
Not outside of the choir.
- Well, would you be interested?
- Yeah, actually, I would.
- Good.
- And it'd be, like,
an after-school
kind of arts program, you know,
but more than just music?
Kim said she's been trying
to get it going
since they've been
cutting funding at the school.
- That's amazing!
- I'm excited.
Something about it
just feels right, you know?
- Look at us, all grown up.
You got a future,
Eddie and I set a date.
- Wait, what? When?
- Next New Year's Eve.
- I'm so excited for you, Zo!
- Thank you. Thank you
for all your advice.
- That's what cousins
are for? Come on.
- You know,
if you took your own advice,
things could turn out different?
I mean, just think about it.
If the Prince told you he was
a prince from the beginning,
would you have asked him
to play piano?
- That's not the point.
- So, what's the point?
- I don't know.
- I'll tell you the point.
The point is, he wanted
to get to know you.
And he was afraid that if you
knew he who he really was,
it would change
your relationship. Which it did.
- There is no relationship, Zo.
The duchess was on
his arm last night.
That's the only
relationship I see.
- Okay.
- It pains me to see you
so unhappy, Sire.
- Well, I've made my bed
and I have to lay in it,
Whitbey.
- I'll talk to the hotel chef
about making you
some of that special tea
you liked the other day.
- Thank you, Whitbey.
- Sire? Sire!
- Whitbey, what is it?
- Didn't you see my text?
She's downstairs in the kitchen!
- Dee Dee?
- Well, I'm not talking
about your mother! Oh.
Sorry, Your Highness.
This situation has me flummoxed.
- Yes. You're forgiven.
Uh, right, let's, um...
Come on...
- Thank you so much.
Everything's perfect.
It's magnifique .
- Thank you for the opportunity.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
- Oh.
- I'll be in the van.
- I'll come with you.
- Ah, ah. No.
- Dee Dee, I, um...
- Really, Colin, you don't
have to apologize again.
- This isn't an apology.
It's, um, it's a statement
and a question.
It's gonna sound crazy,
we've just known each other
a short time.
I've never felt for anyone
like I feel for you right now.
And I just need to know
if you feel the same way.
- What does it even matter?
I mean, we come from
two completely different worlds.
It's like, yeah, a bird
and a fish can fall in love.
Where are they gonna live?
- But, um...
- Colin, you're a prince.
- Yeah?
- You have obligations
about what you're supposed to do
and who you're supposed
to do it with.
I'm the daughter
of a truck driver and a nurse.
Tonight you're going to a ball
and I'm going
to a tree lighting in Queens.
And tomorrow you're gonna be
back in Exeter,
and I'm still gonna be here.
- It doesn't have
to be that way.
- Yeah, it does.
This isn't a fairy tale.
I'm not wearing a glass slipper.
And I would be lying if I said
that I didn't feel the same way.
But it's not possible.
I'm sorry.
- Oh, hello.
- Colin, I say this
with greatest affection,
but you look rather
a misbuttoned mess.
- Great. Perfect symbol
of my life right now.
- Colin, we've known each other
our whole lives.
I would hope you'd feel
you could tell me
whatever it is
you're going through,
as I would want to tell you
what I'm feeling.
- Yes, of course.
Um, here, let's sit down.
- All right.
- Adriana, I...
We have too long a history,
and I have too much
regard for you not to be honest.
While I have enormous
affection for you,
I don't feel the way
my parents want me to feel.
- Well...
It's about time you admitted it.
- You knew?
- Of course I knew.
Any woman who saw the way
you looked at Dee would know.
- Can you forgive me?
- Colin, I spent
the entire flight over
trying to figure out
how I was going to tell you
I don't want to go through
with the marriage!
- You don't?
- Do you think
you're the only one
struggling with a conflict
between duty and heart?
- Are you telling me you're
in love with someone else too?
- Yes.
- Oh, my!
I've never been more happy
for anyone my entire life!
- So, what do we do now?
- I have to tell my parents
how I truly feel.
- That's a push.
- Oh, I think it sounds superb.
- Mother, Father.
I need to talk to you
before we face the press.
- Oh, yes, the press.
We need to discuss
that with you as well.
- It seems your father and I
owe you an apology.
- For what?
- Whitbey has briefed us
on the public reaction in Exeter
to your performance in
the children's Christmas choir,
and the reaction has been
overwhelmingly positive.
- It has?
"A new generation
of Exeter royalty has emerged.
A true prince of the people.
Prince Colin shows
he is a breath of fresh heir."
You see, they spelled air,
H-E-I-R.
- Er, thank you, Whitbey.
Thank you.
- It was funnier in print.
- It appears your father and I
may have been,
as you suggested,
a bit too rigid.
Your lighter, warmer touch
may be exactly
what the country needs.
- It means so much to me
to hear that.
- However, there is still
the issue
of you and Duchess Adriana.
- Yes, about that--
- We know of your feelings
for Miss Paretti.
And I do understand.
We are not without heart.
- However, it is simply
quite impossible.
- For a multitude of reasons.
- Why? Because someone
centuries ago
decided who and who
is not acceptable?
- Son, you do not speak
to your mother that way!
We will announce your engagement
to Adriana
and my retirement to the press
this evening at the ball.
- Father!
- That is the end
of this discussion.
There is simply no choice.
Well, is there?
- Well done. Nice.
- Ma, those came out perfect.
Honey, you want cinnamon, right?
- Please.
- Yeah.
Okay, so you really used
Nonna Sophie's bird fish line?
Really?
- I mean, it seemed fitting!
- Ah, your Nonno Giuseppe
said that line to me.
- Oh, geez.
- Really?
- In Italy. I was 18,
from a good family in Naples.
He was a fisherman's son
from Sicily.
But that summer
when we visited,
he was working at the hotel
where we fell in love.
But we kept it a secret.
- What happened?
- Uh, we eloped!
- They jumped on a ship.
- And landed in Queens.
- Where we were happily married
for 55 years.
Wasn't always easy,
but love always finds a way. Mm?
- Thank you, Nonna.
But I think I'm gonna focus
on finding my own
happily ever after.
I'm gonna meet
with Principal Deacon
over at P.S. 267
and, I don't know,
maybe talk about starting, like,
a music enrichment program.
And then if it goes well,
we could expand it
to other schools
in the districts.
- Really?
- Yeah, I mean,
nothing's set in stone,
but she came to the concert
and she really liked it,
and I just...
I don't know,
when she mentioned it,
something about it
just felt so right, you know?
- Honey, that's wonderful!
- That school is so close.
It means you can stay here
and live with us
while you're working over there.
- Dad, it's time
I got my own spot.
- Your own spot?
- In the neighborhood.
In the neighborhood!
- This house is
in the neighborhood!
- Oh boy.
- Okay.
That, or you can
stab me in the heart.
- Stop. Okay, you ready?
- Go ahead.
- Good evening. First of all,
let me say that the Queen and I
are very proud
to be honorary chairs
at this year's
International Children's
Charity Ball.
And I'm so pleased to announce
that we have raised
a record amount
for this wonderful cause.
- But as you know,
this charity focuses
on the largest
international programs,
and as wonderful
as their work is,
our son, Prince Colin,
has reminded us
that there are countless
smaller, local charities
that don't get the attention
or the funds they deserve.
- Yes, indeed.
First, thank you
to the amazing city of New York
and especially Queens
and the Paretti family
for showing me the true
meaning of Christmas.
I know that you're here
eagerly anticipating news
on the King's retirement
and plans for me to take over--
- Ah, not quite yet.
If this week and my son
have taught me anything at all,
it is that I still
have work to do.
Changes to be made.
- Although we will be spending
more time
within our private lives,
when the time comes
for us to retire,
we will first discuss
with our son
what is best for him
and the future of Exeter.
Out of respect for his wishes.
- Oh, thank goodness!
- What made you
change your mind?
- You did, of course.
Your passion and conviction,
for yourself and others.
All quite right.
- And I realized
I'm not quite ready to retire.
But when I do, Colin,
you will be the one
to decide your future,
whatever that may be, son.
- Even if that doesn't
involve the throne?
- Well, your cousin Louis
has been eyeing the job
for years, so...
- Now, don't you have
someplace else to be?
- Indeed I do.
Father. Adriana.
- Rock and roll, Sire.
- I will.
- Aw, see, this is nice, huh?
Getting outta the house is good.
- Yeah. I'm not closing my eyes
and making a wish, though.
- Yeah, well. You got me so,
really, what more do you need?
- That's true.
- Come on!
- What would you sell
this scooter for?
- Are you serious?
- I've never been more serious
in my entire life.
- Thousand bucks.
- Um...
Oh. Would you take a watch?
- Yeah.
- Sorry! Oh!
Sorry! Oh, oh!
- Hey, Ma?
- I put it in there.
Just in case you change
your mind, you know?
- All right.
- It can happen.
- Okay, here we go.
- Ow!
- Geez!
- Sorry, sorry! Okay, everybody!
Here we go!
What time is it?
Countdown time!
- That's right.
Now, keep it loud and clear,
and don't forget to bring
your wishes! Here we go!
Ten!
- Nine!
Nine!
- Eight!
- Seven!
- Six!
- Five!
- Four!
- Three!
- Two!
- One! Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
- Oh my gosh.
What are you doing here?
- Shh.
Hello.
- Hi.
- You had your eyes closed.
- Yeah, I was making a wish.
- Please tell me it came true.
- I don't know yet.
Did you make a wish?
- I did.
- Did it come true yet?
- I don't know yet.
But I'm hopeful.
You once told me
that I should be in charge
of my own life.
Simple words, and yet no one
had ever said that to me before.
I don't think anyone
had thought it possible,
much less me, until now.
- What are you saying by that?
- Daphne Dolores Paretti,
you have always taken me
for who I am, not what I am.
And that means everything to me.
You mean everything to me.
You are my wish.
- But what about your parents
and all that stuff?
- I have my parents' blessing.
They know how much
you mean to me.
Now, tell me...
Did your wish come true?
- Does that answer
your question?
- I believe it does.
Though one can never
be too sure.
difuze