♪♪
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This is
an ABC color presentation.
♪♪
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[ Bells jingling, wind gusting ]
And now
"A Very Boy Band Holiday."
All right, I got the candles,
I got the pillows,
I'm making sure
everything's all right
'cause the guests are coming.
I got the chestnuts roasting,
egg is nogged,
paparazzi at bay,
we got lights ‐‐
Joey,
I got the wine,
and you got the...
cards?
Boyz II Men's very own
Wanyá Morris,
how you doing,
my friend?
And, uh,
is Shawn on his way, too?
Yeah, bro.
But what's going on, Joe?
I thought
we was playing poker tonight.
No, no, I got something
way better, all right?
Oh, my God.
"A Very Boy Band Holiday."
What the hell
is that?
Wait, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
You don't know what
a Boy Band Holiday is?
No.
Dude, do I got to
teach you everything?
[ Sighs ]
It's always been
so sweet to me
to be in
such a tight fraternity.
So, tonight,
around this Christmas tree...
♪ It's a
Boy Band Holiday ♪
Joe, we're the group
that does "Motownphilly."
So should I just leave?
No,
don't be silly.
But we're not
a boy band.
That's insane.
Wan, the word "boy"
is in your name.
♪ We were boys,
but now we're men ♪
Let me
break this down again.
♪♪
♪ Your group
likes to harmonize ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ooh ♪
♪ Sing of love, and there's
at least three guys ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ooh ♪
♪ My guests for tonight
are all likewise ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ooh ♪
♪ On this
Boy Band Holiday ♪
♪ Now, have I convinced you
through song? ♪
Nah, I still think
you've got it wrong.
No, Wanyá, face it ‐‐
you belong...
♪ On this
Boy Band Holiday ♪
Plus NSYNC
and 98 Degrees
are waiving
their appearance fees
for yuletide camaraderies.
♪ It's a Boy Band Holiday ♪
Okay.
♪ Can you prove to me
they're on the way? ♪
Chris,
you en route?
Sending ETA.
And what about you,
Drew Lachey?
I wouldn't lie to you,
Wanyá.
All right.
And Joey Mac,
he's come to town.
Any wild cards?
Yes,
Bobby Brown!
Oh, so tonight,
we throwin' down...
♪ On this
Boy Band Holiday ♪
♪ This could become
a new tradition ♪
♪ With New Kids
and New Edition ♪
♪ I do love all the musicians
at the Boy Band Holiday ♪
So, Wanyá,
will you do it?
A'ight, cool,
I'm in.
Whatever,
screw it.
That's all
I needed to hear.
It's time to spread
some joy and cheer.
And it's the best way
to end the year.
Hey, I'm so glad
that you are here.
♪ It's a Very Boy Band Holiday ♪
♪ Hey‐ey‐ey‐ey ♪
Yes!
♪ Boy Band Holiday ♪
I know no other boy band
can do that like you do.
Yeah!
I'm gonna try it.
♪ Whoo, hoo, hoo,
ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Whoo, ooh ooh,
whoo, ooh ooh ♪
Joey, Joey...
♪ Whoo, hoo,
whoo‐ooh‐ooh oooh ♪
Joey, Joey.
Yeah.
When is everybody
getting here, bro?
Did that sound good?
When is everybody
getting here, bro?
Yo‐ho‐ho!
Ho ho ho!
Fatone: Hey,
what's up, Chris?
What up, what up,
what up, what up?
What do you say,
Shawn?
What's good?
Happy holidays, sir.
Happy holidays.
Hey, man.
Good to see you, man.
Man,
you look good.
This looks amazing.
Um...was I
supposed to bring
a wagon full of ornaments,
too, or...?
No, but, Chris,
what are those for?
Decorating the tree.
Yeah, but the tree's
already decorated.
You call that decorated?
Yeah.
Oh, listen.
This is a Boy Band Holiday,
right?
Right.
We need
to take this up a notch.
I'm sorry.
What is
a Boy Band Holiday?
Wait, wait. You don't know
what a Boy Band Holiday is?
Wan, do you wanna
sing the song?
We should sing it,
right?
No.
Okay.
Not doing that.
All right.
At all.
Listen, let's just
put the "Chris"
in the Christmas tree.
Ah.
Sounds good to me.
You guys handle that.
I'll see y'all later,
brother.
Kirkpatrick: Really?
You aren't gonna help?
I'm gonna get
some egg nog.
It's time
to rock it.
Rockin'.
Around.
♪♪
♪ Rockin' around
the Christmas tree ♪
♪ At the Christmas
party hop ♪
♪ Mistletoe hung
where you can see ♪
♪ Every couple
tries to stop ♪
♪ Rockin' around
the Christmas tree ♪
♪ Let the
Christmas spirit ring ♪
♪ Later we'll have
some pumpkin pie ♪
♪ And we'll do
some caroling ♪
♪♪
♪ You will get
a sentimental feeling ♪
♪ When you hear ♪
♪ Voices singing,
let's be jolly ♪
♪ Deck ♪
♪ The halls
with boughs of holly ♪
♪ Rockin' around
the Christmas tree ♪
♪ Have a happy holiday ♪
♪ Everyone dancing merrily ♪
♪ In the new
old‐fashioned way ♪
♪♪
♪ You will get
a sentimental feeling ♪
♪ When you hear ♪
♪ Voices singing,
let's be jolly ♪
♪ Deck ♪
♪ The halls
with boughs of holly ♪
♪ Boughs of holly ♪
Get it, Chris!
♪ Rockin' around
the Christmas tree ♪
♪ Have a happy holiday ♪
♪ Everyone's dancin' merrily ♪
♪ In the new old‐fashioned way ♪
They don't call me the
Christmas Tree King for nothing.
Literally no one
calls you that, Chris.
Yeah, well,
they will now.
♪♪
Hey, hey, hey,
happy holidays!
Fatone:
What's up, 98 Degrees?
What's going on?
What's crackin'?
How's everybody doing?
What's up,
what's up?
Good to see you.
Justin, Jeff,
good to see you.
My man.
Wait, one, two, three ‐‐
Where's Nick?
Oh, he's in, uh ‐‐
he's in Hawaii,
working with
his family, so...
You know,
he felt really bummed about it,
so he spent extra money
to send extra gifts.
Fatone:
Must be nice.
Morris:
He could do that.
Drew: Yeah.
And we ran into Erik
from O‐Town outside.
What's up?
He's bringing
the rest of them.
You guys gonna help me
with these?
Yeah, we could help you
with that.
Come here, I'll grab that
for you over here.
There you go.
Be careful, be careful.
Let me grab that one
right there.
And I'll give this one
to Joey.
Estrada: There you go.
Right ‐‐ Right ‐‐ Right there.
Hey, hey, hey!
Thought we said no gifts?
Wait,
hold on a second.
Did you not get me anything
this year again, Chris?
Uh,
subject change.
Uh, Drew, didn't your band
write a song about gifts?
You mean this one.
[ Fingers snap ]
Yo.
When did you put
a lighting cue in here, Drew?
Stay in your lane,
Fatone.
It's over here.
♪♪
♪ The snow is falling,
the city is white ♪
♪ Your eyes are shining
like diamonds tonight ♪
♪ And we're all alone ♪
♪ There's no one home ♪
♪ You're finally
in my arms again ♪
♪ The night is silent,
and Christmas is here ♪
♪ I couldn't ask for more
than having you near ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you,
girl ♪
♪ Love you, girl ♪
♪ And I always will ♪
♪ Always will ♪
♪ And now I know
the moment is right ♪
♪ The moment is right ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been waiting
to give this gift tonight ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees ♪
♪ There's no better time ♪
♪ It's something to last
for as long as you live ♪
♪ Tonight, I'm gonna give you ♪
♪ All my heart can give ♪
♪♪
♪ Mm, mm ♪
♪ Oh, I feel the magic
whenever you're near ♪
♪ I feel it even more
this time of the year ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you,
girl ♪
♪ Love you, girl ♪
♪ I always will ♪
♪ Always will ♪
♪ And now I know
the moment is right ♪
♪ The moment is right ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been waiting
to give this gift tonight ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees ♪
♪ There's no better time ♪
♪ It's something to last
for as long as you live ♪
♪ Tonight, I'm gonna give you ♪
♪ All my heart can give ♪
♪ You know I'll always be
true to you ♪
♪ And you know
I'm the one you can turn to ♪
♪ Anytime, any place,
or anywhere ♪
♪ You know
that I'll always be there ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been waiting
to give this gift tonight ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees ♪
♪ There's no better time ♪
♪ It's something to last
for as long as you live ♪
♪ Tonight, I'm gonna give you ♪
♪ All my heart ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been waiting
to give this gift tonight ♪
♪ This gift tonight ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees ♪
♪ There's no better time ♪
♪ It's something to last
for as long as you live ♪
♪ Tonight, I'm gonna give you ♪
♪ All my heart can give ♪
♪♪
♪ Ooh‐ooh, ooh ooh ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah ♪
♪ All my heart ♪
♪ Can give ♪
♪♪
Speaking of gifts,
happy holidays, Chris.
Are you serious?
Yes, man.
Joey...
♪♪
You got me NSYNC merch.
[ Chuckles ] Yes!
You're so welcome.
♪♪
Is this the only size
it comes in?
Yes, it's a shmedium.
Looks good, doesn't it?
Sure.
Thanks.
You look cute in it.
I know.
Tonight,
on "A Very Boy Band Holiday,"
roast chestnuts with NSYNC's
Joey Fatone, Chris Kirkpatrick,
and Lance Bass.
Let it snow with Boyz II Men's
Wanyá Morris
and Shawn Stockman.
Hang stockings with 98 Degrees'
Drew Lachey, Nick Lachey,
Justin Jeffre,
and Jeff Timmons.
Go caroling with O‐Town's
Erik‐Michael Estrada
and New Kids on the Block's
Joey McIntyre.
Deck the halls with
New Edition's
Michael Bivins and Bobby Brown.
So go grab some egg nog.
It's "A Very Boy Band Holiday."
Welcome back.
Let's see if the guys can
stomach Joey Fatone's egg nog.
"A Very Boy Band Holiday"
returns now.
All right,
I got the egg nog here!
♪ Yeah ♪
Just to celebrate.
You know, a little starter
before everybody gets here.
Help yourself,
help yourself.
It looks good.
What'd you put
in this, dude?
I put so much stu‐‐ Actually,
I got it from the carton.
There's no way
I can make egg nog.
I don't trust you.
Sorry.
Man:
Ho ho, ho ho ho!
[ Knock on door ]
Is that Santa?
Santa?
[ Laughs ]
No, Chris.
I mean, come on, really.
It's Joey McIntyre
from New Kids.
♪ Ho ho, ho ho ♪
Really, Dad?
Come on, Griff!
You know these guys
got the right stuff.
Hey, fellas, you remember
my son Griffin, right?
Hey,
what's up, man?
Good to see you,
buddy.
Happy holidays.
Look at that.
Buddy!
Good to see you, brother.
What's up, Griff?
[ Chatter ]
Dark plaid for the holidays.
I love it.
How come time
is going by so fast?
I mean, Griff,
how tall ‐‐
Oh, man.
5'5".
That's twice
your dad's size.
[ Laughter ]
Man, I love
spending time with family
on the holidays,
and you, too, Joey.
Thanks, Chris.
[ Laughter ]
We always spend ‐‐
But that's the thing, you know?
We were always on the road,
but now ‐‐
We were on the road.
Now we have
families of our own,
so we start
our own traditions.
Yeah!
What do you do
for the holidays?
I mean, dude,
I mean, you know, it's amazing.
Being a young child, you know,
we always have
different traditions,
you know, with your parents,
and now it's cool
that my parents, you know,
bringing that kind of tradition
kind of on,
I do like the Seven Fishes
kind of thing,
I'm doing, like,
this Italian dinner thing,
we do all the sauce,
the meatballs.
Nice.
We do, like,
the Italian dinners
when we do
get together.
So it's great.
A lot of food.
Kids are back
from college.
What about you,
Chris?
I do ‐‐
I'm in Tennessee,
so I got
a little, tiny kid now.
How old is he now?
And ‐‐ He's 4,
and I get to start what you guys
have already got to start,
and that's our own traditions
and saying,
"Hey, this, when you grow up,
you're gonna love this."
We get to start our own,
the stockings,
Elf on the Shelf,
all those little things.
It's a lot of fun.
What about you,
Wan?
Well,
we actually just,
you know,
relax around the house.
You know, we ‐‐
I haven't celebrated Christmas
in a long time.
I do Hanukkah.
Okay.
But my wife
does Christmas,
and I do Hanukkah.
And so
we created "Hanumas."
Hanumas.
We use
the colors of Hanukkah.
We use the blue
and the whites
and the silvers
and all that type of stuff.
So that means
you get more gifts?
The stars, we do the menor‐‐
Oh, yeah, we get eight days.
And the kids get
the best of both worlds.
Eight days ‐‐
Eight days of gifts,
whatever you want.
It's an awesome occasion.
It's beautiful.
It's called Hanumas,
y'all.
How about you,
Joey?
Do you still spend the holidays
in Boston, or...?
Well,
we're back in Hollywood now,
but Boston will always be
my hometown, of course.
And, you know,
we got the best bands.
You know,
there's us and ‐‐
New Edition!
New Edition!        New Edition!
I know, right?
Aren't they the best?
No, no, no,
Bobby Brown and Michael Bivins
from New Edition
are right behind you!
Wha‐‐
Hey!       Hey!
Hey!                        Hey!
Yes, fellas.
[ Chatter ]
Hey!
Wow.
Better than Santa Claus.
We apologize.
We a little late.
We couldn't find it.
He was driving.
We kept going
around and around,
and we said, "B, that looks like
the house right there.
What you think?"
It had to be
the house.
Had to be
Glad you found it.
Yeah.
It's pretty cool
you brought your son with you.
If y'all don't mind,
I would like to sing a song
that was really close
to my heart with my father.
Yes.
Of course.
Definitely.
Definitely, bro.
♪♪
♪ People making lists,
buying special gifts ♪
♪ Taking time to be kind
to one and all ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
Shawn.
♪ It's that
time of year ♪
♪ When good friends
are near ♪
♪ And you wish
you could give more ♪
♪ Than just presents
from a store ♪
♪ Why don't you give love
on Christmas Day ♪
♪ On Christmas Day ♪
♪ Oh, the man on the street
and the couple upstairs ♪
♪ All need to know
there's someone who cares ♪
♪ Give love
on Christmas Day ♪
♪ On Christmas Day ♪
♪ No greater gift is there
than love ♪
♪ What the world needs
is love ♪
♪ Yes, the world
needs more love ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ooh, ooh ooh,
ooh ooh, whoa yeah ♪
What the world need
around this time of year
is a lot of love.
Family, friends
are so dear.
From us to you,
give love.
♪ Why don't you
give love ♪
♪ Give love ♪
♪ No greater gift
is there than love ♪
Give love
on Christmas Day.
What a nice idea.
Love and a PS5.
♪♪
You're just in time.
Some carolers popped by
to perform
with Joey and Griffin McIntyre
on "A Very Boy Band Holiday."
Hey, fellas,
looks like we got
the next generation
on our hands.
♪♪
Like my friend Jordan
would say,
this is
a very serious message.
♪♪
♪ There are
some people ♪
♪ Living in
this world ♪
♪ They have
no food to eat ♪
no place to go ♪
♪ But we are
God's children ♪
♪ We have to learn
to love one another ♪
♪ Just remember
they could be us ♪
♪ Remember
we all are brothers ♪
♪ I'm not trying ♪
♪ To darken up
your day ♪
♪ But help others in need ♪
♪ And show them
there's a better way ♪
♪ This one's for the children ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ah ah ♪
♪ The children of the world ♪
♪ This one's for the children ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ah ah ♪
♪ May God keep them
in His throne ♪
Let's go.
♪ This one's for the children ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ah ah ♪
♪ The children of the world ♪
♪ This one's for the children ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ah ah ♪
♪ May God keep them
in His throne ♪
♪ Only for
the children ♪
♪ Mm, yeah ♪
♪ This one's for the children ♪
♪ The children
of the world ♪
♪ This one's ♪
♪ All around
the world ♪
♪ For the children ♪
♪ We can
come together ♪
♪ This one's ♪
♪ For the children ♪
♪ For the children
of the world ♪
♪ This one's ♪
♪ For the children ♪
♪ The children
of the world ♪
♪♪
Great job,
guys.
Give it up
for the Newer Kids on the Block.
Nice job,
Griff.
Well, we got
some more caroling to do.
Let's go!
[ Laughs ]
All right, Joey.
Bye, Griffin!
Be safe, guys.
Be good, little dude.
All right.
What I remember most about
the holidays or about Christmas,
listening to music
and the holiday music.
You know what I mean?
Of course.
But some of those songs don't
make any sense whatsoever.
What do you mean?
Oh, no.
Know what I'm saying?
They're weird. Like...
♪ All I want for Christmas
is my two front teeth ♪
♪ My two front teeth ♪
♪ Oh, my two front teeth ♪
Exactly! Exactly.
If you don't have
your two front teeth,
you want
your two front teeth.
Bro, but, like, what kid asks
for body parts for Christmas?
What if you just want
to eat an apple?
I mean,
you don't have two front teeth.
You got the chompers
in the back.
What about "Grandma Got Run Over
by a Reindeer"?
Mm.
♪ Grandma got run over
by a reindeer ♪
♪ Walking home from our house
Christmas Eve ♪
Yeehaw!
Morris:
That's a horrible song.
It's morbid,
it's macabre.
Well, that one's morbid,
that one's morbid,
but I got one
that's actually even funnier
because it's happy,
it's go‐lucky,
it's "I Want a Hippopotamus
for Christmas."
♪ I want a hippopotamus
for Christmas ♪
♪ Only a hippopotamus
will do ♪
Uh, you're alone
on that one, bro.
What?
You never heard
that song before, dude?
How do you wrap
a hippopotamus?
That's ‐‐ That's enough
for you, bro.
That's enough.
That one didn't last.
It's a good song.
Appreciate you, but there's
one holiday song that,
I have to say,
I have a major,
major issue with.
I mean, more than
any of the other ones.
Okay.
"I Saw Mommy
Kissing Santa Claus."
What's wrong with that,
though?
That's a classic.
First of all, your mom
is kissing Santa Claus.
Where is your dad?
Right.
It never explains.
Like, come on,
think about it.
Well...
♪ I saw Mommy
kissing Santa Claus ♪
Drew:
But it's romantic!
No, no.
♪ Underneath the mistletoe
last night ♪
But that's a tradition.
In my house,
Mommy is just sitting down,
kissing a dude in a red suit
and a white beard.
Shouldn't he be working
anyway?
You know what I'm saying?
Think about it.
♪ She didn't see me creep ♪
♪ Down the stairs
to have a peep ♪
What were you doing out of bed,
anyway?
♪ She thought that I was stuck
up in my bedroom, fast asleep ♪
But you should've been.
I mean, honestly.
♪ Then I saw Mommy
tickle Santa Claus ♪
Okay, I see it.
Okay,
I see where you're going.
Okay, that's practically
third base.
"I saw Mommy
tickle Santa Claus."
Where did she ‐‐ Where was the
tickling? Where, where, where?
♪ Underneath his beard
so snowy white ♪
Yeah, that's a little ‐‐
that's a little off.
Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
I got you on that one.
♪ Oh, what a laugh
it would've been ♪
♪ If Daddy had only seen ♪
♪ Mommy kissing Santa Claus
last night ♪
Mommy ain't supposed to be
rockin' out with Santa Claus.
No.
[ Laughter and applause ]
Dude, oh.
Does he really not know
what the song is about?
But he's having
so much fun.
Man: Bravo, bravo.
I like that.
I don't know about you guys,
but, uh...
‐Oh, hello!
‐Ooh!
During the holidays,
my mother used to make
these special wings,
so I thought I'd make some up
for you guys.
‐Oh, yeah, they look nice.
‐Appreciate you, man.
‐Yeah.
‐That's good stuff.
Me first,
me first, me first.
Yo, yo, yo!
Yo, check it out.
‐This is what we do.
‐That's great.
Oh, okay.
Snow.
I feel a song coming on,
brother.
♪♪
♪ Ooh ooh,
ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ No‐oh‐oh,
ooh ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ It's another
Christmas holiday ♪
♪ It's a joyous thing,
let the angels sing ♪
♪ 'Cause we're together ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ We got a thing ♪
♪ Can't let it slip away ♪
♪ Though outside
it's raining sleet ♪
♪ When our bodies meet ♪
♪ I don't care
about the weather ♪
♪ Let it snow,
let it snow ♪
♪ Outside it's cold ♪
♪ But the fire's blazin' ♪
♪ So, baby, let it snow ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Let it snow ♪
♪ Ohhhh ♪
♪ And, ohhh ♪
♪ You are my everything ♪
♪ Come a little closer ♪
♪ God must have sent you down
from heaven ♪
♪ Let it snow ♪
♪ Outside it's cold ♪
♪ But the fire's blazin' ♪
♪ So, baby, let it snow ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Let it snow ♪
♪♪
Man, I love that song.
I think
that snow might be fake.
But the emotions
are real.
Pull up a seat. Drew Lachey is
hanging stockings by the fire.
"A Very Boy Band Holiday"
continues now.
Actually, I embroidered every
single one of those stockings.
I didn't even know you could
spell everybody's name right.
No, no, I can spell the names
'cause I looked at it online.
[ Cellphone rings ]
Oh, hey.
Hey, hey.
Nick: What's up, fellas?
Nick, what's up, man?
Happy holidays!
Drew: You're missing out.
Boy Band Holiday's
been a lot of fun.
Heck yeah.
Better than most
of Joey's parties,
but, you know, good people,
good music, good times.
I am so bummed
I'm missing this thing.
It looks incredible.
Well, we hung
your stocking up,
so it's kind of like
you're here anyway.
Except for some of us can get
a word in edgewise.
You know what, Drew?
You've always been
my favorite.
I don't care what Mom says.
Wait. What ‐‐ What ‐‐
What did ‐‐
What'd Mom say?
Alright, man,
happy holidays!
No, but seriously ‐‐
Bye, Nick!
Sorry, bad ‐‐
bad connection.
I'm ‐‐ I'm losing you.
I'm ‐‐ I'm losing you,
but alright.
Take it easy,
yep, bye, bye!
He didn't want to talk
to me?
I don't think
he likes you.
He doesn't like you,
either.
Hey, guys, I know
you guys are having fun.
Can you ‐‐
Can you come sit here?
We're having a conversation
about something.
‐Yeah.
‐Come on.
‐Alright.
‐Have a seat, fellers.
So, we were talking
about the rivalries
between the boy bands.
Oh, yeah.
Y'all had one with kind of,
like, the Backstreet?
Who?
[ Laughter ]
Yeah,
the Backstreet Boys.
It was
between the fans.
Right, right.
A kid starts to grow up,
and one kid goes, "Hey,
I like the Backstreet Boys,"
and the other kid goes,
"Well, I don't want
to like what they like,
so I'm gonna like NSYNC
or 98 Degrees or O‐Town."
I'm not gonna lie, though.
When I saw, you know,
album sales hit a certain mark,
I was like, "Okay.
Now we gotta ‐‐ we gotta ‐‐
We gotta ‐‐ Come on."
Music stores, we'd see
this big display of NSYNC,
and then we'd go,
"Well, where's our...?"
And we're rifling through ‐‐
"Here it is!"
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait. You guys could walk
into music stores?
‐Oh!
‐Exactly.
Honestly,
this is proof positive.
We enjoy
each other's music,
and, you know,
we respect each other
because we all have
that fraternal walk
that no one else really knows
what we went through.
This is something special,
and we went through,
especially in that era,
that was such a special time
for music.
And it was a lot of records
being sold.
Estrada: For my band,
obviously,
I was put together on ABC
on "Making the Band."
Right.
So these guys
had already been ‐‐
you know,
Backstreet and NSYNC,
we were part of the same
management team for a while,
and, you know,
we came into the game,
and we just had these guys
to look up to.
Kirkpatrick: Well,
I will tell you, though,
if we would've had to audition
for our bands,
we wouldn't have made it.
[ Laughter ]
So that's why we had
to put ourselves together.
Nobody wanted us,
so we're like,
"Alright,
let's do this ourselves."
He put it together,
and I jumped in front of him.
[ Laughter ]
Hey, man, but y'all do
y'all thing, though?
You know what I'm saying?
We try.
Y'all do y'all thing,
you know?
We're good with our roles.
Yeah,
and that's what it's about.
Well, you guys
don't understand what it's like
to be the cute one.
Right.
Like, let me tell you ‐‐
with me, it's tough.
Morris: [ Laughs ]
Say, for instance,
people on a football team.
They know exactly
the same thing, like,
what they feel when they're
out there on the field.
Same thing with us
when we're on stage.
But this ‐‐ I think
this is even deeper than that,
because on a football team,
you can get traded.
Yeah, that's true.
This is something that ‐‐
News flash.
You just got traded.
We traded Drew
to you guys.
You're on our team now.
‐There you go.
‐No more dancing.
No more dancing
for you, bud.
Now you actually have to sing,
though.
But, like ‐‐
[ Laughter ]
I get that, 'cause I don't.
But growing up, and,
you know, you were lucky ‐‐
you were in a band
with your brother, right?
That's lucky?
Well, I'm saying,
I didn't have any brothers.
I had all sisters
growing up.
So when I started this band,
I suddenly got four brothers,
you know?
And it is ‐‐
And he didn't even want them
at all.
Like we're saying,
like, you know,
I know more about
this human being right here
than I do 99.9% of people
I'm related to.
Right.
Five guys,
and we had a tour ‐‐
We're on one
small little bus.
And then, obviously ‐‐
And we didn't have
five rooms.
We had, like ‐‐
No, we had three rooms.
So it was like two ‐‐
Me and him
had to bunk up, yeah.
We had no tour bus.
We had a Winnebago.
Really?
That we drove.
We drove ourselves around
in a Winnebago.
Wow.
We had one room to it.
What about you, Wan?
It was ‐‐
It was similar, you know?
Very similar.
We had one bus.
We all stayed
on that bus.
We called it Amistad.
Amistad, yeah, it was ‐‐
it was the bomb, yep.
We sure did.
[ Laughter ]
Hey, Joey.
I've been getting
noise complaints.
You guys aren't getting
too rowdy, are you?
Timmons: Wow! You guys got
Sporty Spice to come by?
Well, I'm actually renting
this house.
It's hers.
Morris:
Oh, this your house?
Well,
this is my guest house.
All of the electronics
are run on girl power.
Excuse me?
So, how's
"A Very Boy Band Holiday" going?
It's going great.
Yeah?
Awesome.
Yeah.
Well, actually, we're having
"A Very Girl Group Holiday"
up at the main chalet,
so I'd better get back.
Oh, wait.
Can we come by later?
Yeah, of course you can,
if you want, yeah.
If you really, really want.
Oh!
Good to see you, Mel C.
I'll see you later!
Be good.
See what she did there?
Yeah, I saw that.
Well, I'm so glad
we're all together again.
And I just want to say,
merry Christmas
and happy holidays.
Yeah,
but who wants to sing it?!
[ Laughter ]
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Merry Christmas ♪
♪ Happy holidays ♪
♪ Merry Christmas,
merry Christmas ♪
happy holiday ♪
♪♪
♪ We've been waiting all year
for this night ♪
♪ And the snow is glistening
on the trees outside ♪
♪ And all the stockings are hung
by the fireside ♪
♪ Waiting for Santa
to arrive ♪
♪ And all the love
will show ♪
♪ 'Cause everybody knows ♪
♪ It's Christmastime and ♪
Timmons: ♪ All the kids
will see ♪
♪ The gifts under the tree ♪
♪ It's the best time of year
for the family ♪
♪ It's a wonderful feeling ♪
♪ Feel the love in the room ♪
♪ From the floor
to the ceiling ♪
♪ It's that time of year ♪
♪ Christmastime is here ♪
♪ And with the blessings
from above ♪
♪ God sends you his love ♪
♪ And everything's okay ♪
♪ Merry Christmas,
happy holidays ♪
merry Christmas ♪
♪ Happy holiday ♪
♪ Merry Christmas,
merry Christmas ♪
♪ Happy holiday ♪
♪ No matter
what your holiday ♪
♪ It's a time to celebrate ♪
♪ And put your worries aside ♪
♪ Worries aside ♪
♪ And open up your mind ♪
♪ Open up your mind ♪
♪ See the world
right by your side ♪
♪ It's Christmastime ♪
♪ It's a wonderful feeling ♪
♪ Feel the love in the room ♪
♪ From the floor
to the ceiling ♪
♪ It's that time of year ♪
♪ Christmastime is here ♪
♪ And with the blessings
from above ♪
♪ God sends you his love ♪
♪ And everything's okay ♪
♪ Merry Christmas,
happy holiday ♪
merry Christmas ♪
♪ Happy holiday ♪
♪ Merry Christmas ♪
♪ Merry Christmas,
happy holidays ♪
Come on!
♪ Merry Christmas ♪
♪ Merry Christmas,
happy holidays ♪
‐Hey!
‐Yeah!
I still don't think
we're a boy band.
Just let Joey
have this one, man.
And now the hot cocoa
we've all been waiting for.
"A Very Boy Band Holiday"
continues.
[ Laughter ]
I'm still not sure
if we a boy band, bro,
but I want to thank you, man,
for, you know, lying to me.
I truly appreciate it.
Fatone:
My pleasure, my pleasure.
But you know what?
I want to thank you guys
for all coming here,
but I really ‐‐
You know, we can't thank
the fans enough, really.
I mean, honestly,
those are the ones
that put us here
on the map,
they go to our shows.
I mean, I really did it
for the fans.
Absolutely.
Without every one of them,
I mean, none of this
would be possible.
We wouldn't know
each other.
We had a time
we couldn't get arrested.
I find that hard
to believe.
Yeah, no,
it was pretty easy.
There was one time
we were getting on a plane,
and some girl goes,
"That's them!"
Right, yeah.
"That's the guys,"
and we were all going
down the walk ‐‐ err!
"Wait.
You know who we are?"
Exactly. What?
"You know who we are?"
That's the moment
where you're like,
"We just did something that
some stranger knows us for."
Right, yeah.
And it's ‐‐ it's awesome.
Bobby, what was the first moment
for you,
that you remember you felt
that fan appreciation?
When we first heard the song
on the radio.
It's like...
Yeah. Yep.
You try to ‐‐
You go to the phones,
and this is when phones
were...
[ Laughter ]
To the wall.
You would go to the wall,
and...
The rotary.
The rotary phones,
and you'd call each other.
"Do you hear this
on the radio?
Do you hear
us on the radio?"
And then going outside
and everybody ‐‐
everybody knowing
that it was you
that was playing
on the radio.
It was ‐‐ It's the most
incredible experience.
But I think, also, something
else that's pretty magical is,
our songs have lived on,
you know?
Whether they become
wedding songs or first dances,
the fact that your song
can be with that couple
for, you know...
Forever.
...the next 50 years,
the rest of their lives...
Kirkpatrick: Like, when we used
to go over to Europe,
and some of those kids ‐‐
I mean, they would jump
on the luggage racks.
Hiding behind, they're hiding
in the bathrooms,
like,
in the shower curtains.
To this day, I go to a hotel,
first thing I do...
Check the shower.
...check the shower.
'Cause they learn
our aliases.
They know ‐‐ yeah.
They learn the aliases.
And they know
where you're staying.
Chris, something like that
happened to us in Asia.
When we were in Southeast Asia,
we had ‐‐
you know,
we ordered room service,
and they brought in
the food‐service cart,
dropped it off, there were girls
underneath the cart.
What was your alias,
Bob?
My alias was Justin Case.
[ Laughter ]
Do you guys identify
with the roles
that were placed upon you
by the public?
You know, like, the bad boy,
the shy guy...
You know what?
Yeah.
Hey, Bob, who was who?
I think I know.
Oh, everybody know.
Hey, everybody knows who he was.
Come on.
That's not even a question.
Come on, now.
[ Laughter ]
Besides you.
Leave me alone.
[ Laughter ]
Drew: For us,
it was the teen magazines.
You know, they would give you
those questionnaires.
They'd be like, "Alright,
what's your nickname?
Who are you in the group?"
"What's your favorite color?
What do you like to eat?"
So we made nicknames up.
Next thing you know, they're
in the 98 Degrees board game,
and then they're,
you know, on the ‐‐
You guys had
a board game?
‐It was great.
‐We had a board game.
We did?
You had to be bored
to play it,
but, you know,
it's...yeah.
Well, it's interesting
to talk about fans,
'cause I know
that we all come
from different generations,
right?
We all had an affinity
or respect for the groups
that came before us,
'cause I know, obviously,
I was a superfan
of Boyz II Men
and what you guys
were able to do
meant to my life.
How you feel about us
is how we feel about these guys.
You know, New Edition,
even our name, Boyz II Men,
was an actual song
from a New Edition album,
called "N.E. Heartbreak."
Oh, wow.
And, you know,
me and Nate were on the phone,
and we hated the name
that we had before.
We're not gonna tell
anybody.
Please tell us.
And "Boys to Men"
came on the radio,
and I was like,
"Yo, that should be our name."
You know, even before I was
in Boyz II Men,
the All For Love Tour...
Uh‐huh.
...the All For Love Tour,
my auntie took me
to that.
And I got an outfit
and everything,
and I remember sitting
in, like, maybe the third tier,
and I literally cried.
I was like,
"I want to be that.
I want to be on that stage
one day."
So I guess what we're saying
is that
the biggest fans are us.
Us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, guys, guys, guys,
what do you think?
One more song
for the fans?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Alright, let's go.
Come on.
♪♪
♪ Hang all the mistletoe ♪
♪ I'm gonna get
to know you better ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ This Christmas ♪
♪ And as we trim the tree ♪
♪ How much fun it's gonna be
together ♪
♪ This Christmas ♪
♪ Fireside blazing bright ♪
♪ Oooh, ooooh ♪
♪ We're caroling
through the night ♪
♪ Through the night ♪
♪ And this Christmas ♪
♪ Will be, yeah ♪
♪ A very special Christmas
for me ♪
♪ Special Christmas for me ♪
♪♪
♪ Shake a hand,
shake a hand now ♪
Fatone: J and J ‐‐
let's go, fellas.
Both: ♪ Presents and cards
are here ♪
♪ My world is filled with cheer,
and you ♪
Let's go, Joe.
♪ This Christmas ♪
♪ And as I look around ♪
♪ Your eyes outshine the town,
they do ♪
♪ This Christmas ♪
♪ Fireside
is blazing bright ♪
♪ And we're caroling
through the night ♪
♪ Through the night ♪
♪ And this Christmas ♪
♪ Will be ♪
♪ A very special Christmas
for me ♪
♪ Special Christmas for me ♪
♪ Shake a hand,
shake a hand now ♪
♪♪
[ Vocalizing ]
♪ Fireside blazing bright ♪
♪ We're caroling
through the night ♪
♪ Through the night ♪
♪ And this Christmas ♪
♪ Will be ♪
♪ A very special Christmas
for me ♪
♪ And this Christmas
will be ♪
♪ Will be ♪
♪ A very special Christmas
for me ♪
♪ Special Christmas for me ♪
[ Vocalizing ]
♪ Merry, merry Christmas ♪
Hey!
[ Cheering ]
Happy holidays!
Good job.
By God, we did it.
What a Boy Band Holiday
it's been.
Bobby Brown shared
his family's wings,
and Wanyá Morris
spoke of Hanumas things.
Shawn Stockman spotted snow,
and Joey Mac said,
"Ho ho ho."
What a time
to see old friends.
Such a shame it has to end.
Joey, enjoy some rest
near the tree,
on a couch
owned by Melanie C.
Your phone's about to ring.
Who will it be?
[ Cellphone rings ]
Oh.
♪♪
Hello?
[ Baby crying ]
Oh, hey, Joey.
Yeah, ma‐‐
maybe next year?
Alright, well, see ya.
Bye.
Bye‐bye.
Bye, bye, bye.
We prime time ‐‐
prime time.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
[ Laughter ]
Roll the tape, baby.
Hey, Drew,
what are you doing, man?
Nick really wanted me
to hang our childhood stockings
so he could feel
like he was really here.
Did your mom make those?
You know, moms don't have
the same amount of time
when the second kid comes.
Does it work?
Is it too pathetic?
Alright.
[ Laughs ]
Hold on!
I got a better one in me!
Wait. You don't know what
a Boy Band Holiday is?
Shawn, you want
to sing the song?
Let's start it.
No.
Well, his name's Wanyá.
I've always
been Wanyá.
Wow.
Lookee here.
It is snowing.
[ Laughter ]
We live in Philly, man.
We from Philly.
Like,
we've seen it before.
[ Laughs ]
Merry Christmas
and happy holidays!
[ Cheering ]
[ Laughter ]
Chris just got kicked
in the head.
I didn't take too long,
did I?
Yes, you did.
Alright, I'm sorry.
Prime time, let's go.
Oh.
Did I forget to call you?
Were the Backstreet Boys
even a boy band?
[ Laughter ]