Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Do not get trapped in
desperate quests for love.
We acknowledge your generation's
right to be happy.
We will find your true soulmate for life.
A bright future awaits you
Wow! this gives me goosebumps
It's all because of
the narrator's voice, right? So fatherly.
Every time I see you post
childhood pictures with your dad,
I'm always envious.
I've never experienced moments like that.
Ulfah can only post pictures of her dad.
It's obvious that she has no choice.
I've long accepted that life isn't fair.
I actually want to be like you, Ul.
I don't have to stress over replying
to all these guys' comments.
The point is,
we're going to find everything
we've been searching for at The Light.
And we can always be together.
Today, I'm just grateful
to be chosen by The Light
along with my childhood BFFs.
Almost all girls
have their own version of a dream wedding.
In this uncertain era,
many of us become numb,
losing hope.
After the pandemic,
our space to grow is still limited.
Are we there yet?
I'm so nervous.
Many of us have never
even directly experienced
the beauty of forests and nature.
The last time I saw green forests
surroundings like this
was seven years ago.
My mom said that
after the pandemic, the world rapidly aged
and that's probably why she's depressed.
Well… I'm Salina.
My late father used to teach me
to believe in dream manifestations.
The Light is going to be
beautiful like this, right?
-What's wrong?
-What's happening?
What's going on?
Let's see.
Hurry up.
Oh, my goodness!
Help us, sir.
-Are you okay?
-Don't worry. I wasn't hit.
-I was only shocked.
-Are you hurt anywhere?
I saw the big bus and fell.
-Maybe you should walk with her, sir.
-No need. I'm fine.
Here, let me help.
Watch your step.
Careful, ma'am.
You're the one who ought
to beware, young one.
Yes, ma'am.
Come on, let's move.
And definitely, at The Light,
all of my dreams will become reality.
We have arrived at
The Light Training Center.
-Please get off the bus carefully.
-Thank you.
-We will distribute your luggage.
-You are welcome. Hello!
I'm Santi. This is my husband, Iwan.
-Good morning.
-Look towards the camera.
Straight at the camera. So beautiful.
CLASS OF JANUARY 2030
REGISTERED
Okay.
Please enjoy yourself.
-Salina.
-You guys are free to explore The Light.
You have 15 minutes to explore.
The map of The Light
has already been sent so don't get lost.
-Thanks!
-How nice!
Is this for real?
Congratulations, Salina.
You have become a part
of The Light's family.
From now on, we shall make all
your dreams and aspirations come true.
All your dreams…
And congratulations, Hafiz.
By becoming a part of The Light,
you don't need to worry.
Everyone here is considered equal.
We don't believe in rich or poor.
Welcome to The Light, Tara.
We accept members
regardless of their past.
How much do they know?
I bet they did a ton of research on us
before accepting us.
But they still want me, how come?
That's a good thing!
I wonder why.
Did you know that 20% of all profits
from my makeup line
are donated to people with disabilities?
You can fight the good fight
by swiping right, right now.
So cute! So precious!
Excuse us. Ul, let's go.
-Excuse me.
-Go ahead.
This is the reality that
your generation has to face
after the pandemic
that happened ten years ago.
Plastic continues to contaminate
our sea and land,
hazardous waste polluting most of the soil
on our planet.
Soon our ocean will die.
Global warming is at its peak.
All beings' quality of life
is in critical condition.
Birth rate has been drastically declining,
incomparable to the death rate.
Will the human race survive?
Only at The Light
can you be a real agent of change.
Welcome to The Light!
You came here
with a clear purpose.
Now, I'd like all of you
to repeat after me.
On my cue.
But in order to do that,
you need a support system.
For a sustainable future.
You need to be married,
not just dating.
Find the ideal spouse.
And you do not need to worry.
At The Light, we have
prepared everything for you.
Now, I proudly present
my number one support system.
My wife, Sofia.
Ten years ago,
the prototype
of the matchmaking system I invented
led us to each other.
Good morning, everyone.
I am well aware
that you're all at the age
of raging hormones.
And that is the perfect time for you
to practice abstinence and control.
Yes.
Keep this in mind. Control.
Control the lust and urge to date.
Because there will come a time
where all of you here will be married
to your perfect match.
Rest assured
that each of your future spouses
are here in the training center.
However, if any of you
are still feeling doubtful…
that's normal.
Does anyone want to share their feelings?
Please don't hesitate. We're here for you,
so please raise your hand.
You.
Salina.
Thanks for raising your hand.
I reckon the three of you…
are best friends?
I notice that Tara, in the middle,
is keeping her head down.
Is there anything wrong?
Tara?
Excuse me.
Tara.
I…
I don't think…
I deserve to be here.
Why?
I…
I've been dating
since sixth grade.
I switched boyfriends around a lot.
I'm not here to judge you, Tara.
What's your biggest wish at this moment?
I…
I want to apologize…
to everyone
that I've hurt.
But I can't.
Okay.
What you have to do…
is to forgive yourself.
Will you do that?
Now, I would like
everyone in this room…
to stand up.
We should support Tara,
we should send positive energy to her.
Close your eyes.
Put your right hand on your chest.
Feel the rhythm
of your heartbeat.
Inhale…
Exhale.
Whisper to your heart…
Forgive all of your past mistakes.
You may slowly open your eyes.
Reset and start over, okay?
Salina.
You have been an excellent friend to Tara.
Now I want to ask you a question.
Are you willing to accept all of us here,
including me…
as your new family?
So?
Are you relieved?
I only hope that…
those who got hurt
from that highway accident
would forgive me.
It was your ex, Andi,
who drove that car, not you.
Yeah, but I started kissing him
so he lost control of the wheel.
Tara…
Just remember what Ali said to us earlier.
Here, we have to reset and start over.
I'm happy
to see you calm like this, Na.
It's only today that I feel
so protected as if I have a dad again.
Ali's future child
is going to be so lucky.
It's also the first time that
I don't feel insecure about myself.
I'm ready
for whoever my partner will be.
You're so lucky to be the first
to turn 17, Ul.
It's going to be beautiful, Ul.
You have chosen training programs
in the fields you're passionate about.
We have prepared the best mentors for you.
The girls' dormitory
will be supervised by Ms. Nanik.
She will act as a mother to you all.
I will now read you the house rules.
First rule.
Keep your rooms clean and tidy.
Our Extraordinary Leader
has built all these accommodations
and facilities
for us to maintain together.
Secondly, everyone is expected
to get up and get ready
at 5 a.m.
Good morning, Tara.
It's already five past five o'clock.
Third rule. There is only one
mandatory class
for all members,
which is home economics.
Fourth. In order to protect you
from lustful urges,
members of the opposite sex
are forbidden to meet
other than for work purposes.
Fifth. Our shuttle vans
can only be used for work purposes,
and everyone is obligated
to return to the dormitories by 8 p.m.
You will only live here
for a maximum of one year
until you get married
at 17.
After getting married,
you will transfer to
and live independently
in the apartments
built specially by The Light.
Automatically,
this will make you property owners,
which is a rare privilege these days.
Optimize the teachings of The Light
and spread them to your family,
friends, and the world.
Female activists are gathering signatures
for a petition to raise the
legal marital age in this country
from 17 to 19 years old.
Meanwhile, The Light,
an educational institution
for youth training
led by the handsome
and charismatic Ali Khan,
has managed to gather many more signatures
to maintain the legal marital age
at 17 years old.
All the news outlets
always use the words
handsome and charismatic
to describe you these days.
Turn around.
It's our third time.
Let's hope it works this time.
Okay. Stay still.
Almost there.
Remember. God is testing us.
Our child will be perfect.
Today, you will all be trained
to present yourselves on social media
as a new person
who will redefine beauty
to be healthy and natural.
In front of you are several products.
You are free to make captions
and take photos as you will,
just make sure to include
the hashtag #BeautyAlaSofia.
But beforehand,
you must change your
profile picture and delete
all your pre-existing social media feeds.
We will all start anew with a clean slate.
Tara.
I know
you have the most followers
among everyone.
This must be hard for you.
I will make a new line
for tan-skinned girls like you.
Do you want to help me develop it?
Seriously?
I feel like hugging you!
Not here.
This is still confidential. Okay?
Got it.
Attention! We'll go to the city
to practice shooting content.
After that, we'll come back here.
Good morning, everyone!
-Good morning!
-Morning, sir.
Joko Liauw!
I've watched his video
about the origins of the pandemic virus
a thousand times!
Welcome to The Light's content lab.
You have chosen to be
The Light's content creators.
Keep this in mind.
The media is our strength.
Contents are our weapons.
As for this man standing next to me,
he does not need any introductions.
Your duty is to create content
that can garner the most likes.
If you succeed,
one of you
will have the honor
of working with me
on a prestigious
documentary project.
-That's right.
-As…
a co-dir.
"Co-dir" means
co-director.
What does the job entail?
That depends.
If I'm not in the mood,
you have to do the job.
If I get confused on
how to direct some scenes,
you'll be the one doing the thinking.
But this is about teamwork.
That's right.
That's the most important thing.
Teamwork, however small,
is key.
-Best of luck!
-Thank you!
Do your best!
Let's go, guys,
make teams of two.
Once you've found
your teammate, follow me.
Hurry now. We don't have much time.
I'm better at editing. Is that fine?
Perfect, because I prefer filming.
Let's go.
All right, you can spread out.
Be back within two hours.
The more shots you can get of
immoral attitudes and behaviors,
such as extramarital hand-holding
and kissing,
girls wearing miniskirts,
the more the better, okay?
Got it!
Hurry now!
What a ridiculous instruction.
We'll work with what we get.
VERBAL ABUSE IS NOT TRIVIAL ISSUE
Salina?
Hi, do I know you?
I was your senior in middle school.
I can't believe you've joined The Light!
Sorry, I'm doing an assignment.
No, wait!
I managed to leave The Light.
Don't believe their propaganda.
Leave before it's too late.
Just search the keywords, Arya Teja!
-Let's turn right.
-Okay.
Who are you?
-Sorry, it's for a school assignment.
-About what?
-About people dating.
-The hell you are.
Dating? This is my husband!
-I'm sorry!
-Screw you!
I'm sorry!
Judgy title bitch!
Don't you see we are old?
Let it go, honey.
Hafiz, this definitely needs
your magic touch.
Please make it work.
I'm sorry…
I couldn't capture anything good.
Relax.
I can combine them with my footage.
But your footage is only shots
of ads and posters…
Be patient.
Is there anything I can see?
Yes, there is.
-Screw you, bitch!
-Enough, darling.
Stupid bitch!
Have mercy.
You dumb idiot!
Let it go, honey.
NO DATING, NO VIOLENCE
I'm speechless.
I love this one.
Don't be scared
to explore different styles.
Improvise.
Our admins…
will only upload your best works.
Okay?
Go on.
-Good job, Iwan.
-Thank you, sir.
All right, improvise!
Dig deep for new ideas!
Thank you, Fiz.
It's a bit slippery here.
Watch your steps.
The almonds here are so plentiful.
But I still couldn't bring myself
to eat all of them.
Why not?
Go to town with it.
They're so expensive in the city.
That's right,
the almonds are among
the most popular items in my Light Mart.
But I think the packaging can be
redesigned to be more appealing.
If you have ideas
for the packaging, you should draw them.
We can present them to The Extraordinary.
Are you sure I'm allowed to do that?
Of course.
Oh, both my husband and son are here.
How nice, to be able to come home
with your husband and son.
Little baby, you're so cute.
Hi, little baby.
What's his name?
Edy.
Hi, baby Edy.
You're so cute!
Your time will come, Ul.
Okay.
Bye, you!
Bye!
See you soon.
EDITING LAB AT THE LIGHT
Hi.
Just for you girls.
Are you sure you can give these away?
Of course!
Plus, I'm the only one
Sofia gave extra bottles to.
I have a confession to make.
I actually feel so at home here.
And surprisingly,
I don't miss dating at all.
And I love your new image on social.
Wait, I haven't seen it.
A lot of people unfollowed me
and bashed me
for being part of The Light.
But I have gained even more
new followers ever since.
There are bound to be haters
trying to bring down The Light.
That's right.
Welcome, Father.
I really like the renovations
you've done to this house.
Sofia.
Thanks, Father.
I'm certain
that your establishment
will bring in a revolution.
It's still in its early stages, Father.
Since you were a boy, I've always known
you'll be a great leader.
We have started
planting the seeds.
And soon, you'll reap your harvest.
Careful, don't look down all the time.
-You'll fall.
-Hafiz!
Our new video got uploaded!
Check this out.
I gained weight,
but my husband doesn't mind!
-To me, you're sexier.
-Yes, nice.
You should read the comments too.
It's so much fun.
Salina, let's go.
Sure, I'll be right with you!
There you are.
"I really want to be like them…"
"How do I apply?"
"Oh, couple goals."
"Bless this perfect couple."
You're too funny…
-"Love this!"
-Stop it, Hafiz!
Oh, no. Is there a CCTV here?
You're so annoying!
You almost gave me a heart attack!
Na.
Stop being silly.
Ul, don't look too gloomy.
You have to own it, Ul!
Their concepts
are quite interesting after all.
Like this?
Tara's makeup turned out well.
You look very pretty, Ulfah.
Because it all depends
on the makeup artist!
You're really glowing.
All right, just like that!
Hold that pose,
remember the words, and action!
-Hi.
-Cut!
Hafiz!
Fiz, do you have an extra memory card?
-Mine is full.
-Ulfah, look.
That must be Salina's match.
But…
he looks weird.
How come your memory card is full?
I thought you had backups.
Error, I think.
Okay, Ulfah, stand by.
I've been standing by for ages.
Okay, now it's The Light's
male sports team's turn.
You boys need help with the makeup?
Tara, resist temptations!
Hi, I'm Ulfah.
I'm about to turn 17,
and I'm ready for my match!
There you are.
I've been looking for you.
I've been here waiting for you.
Sorry about earlier.
Ulfah and Tara
have a habit of making fun of me.
I don't mind.
You girls were cute teasing
and bullying each other.
I know right, they always make up stuff.
Oh, so that was made up?
What if…
it's true?
What do you mean?
You miss dating that much, huh?
-Hi, Fiz.
-Hey.
To be honest…
I'm 17…
and I have never dated anyone.
And I've always wanted
to know what it feels like.
Dating's not all that.
I've experienced it, and I don't miss it.
When's your birthday?
The day I got here.
I see.
Congrats.
That means you're going to marry soon.
Well, I'm just waiting.
There are lots of guys here
who are already 17 and still unmarried.
Maybe…
the algorithm hasn't found the match.
Fiz, this is forbidden.
But I'm so certain you're my match.
Why are you so sure?
I knew it…
since I saw you step down
from the bus to help that old lady.
I'm certain because
you appreciated my editing
so sincerely.
I know you come from a rich family
but you have empathy…
and ambition.
And you're not lazy
to actually put effort into things.
Don't you feel any kind of certainty…
that we're meant for each other?
I'm afraid to expect too much, Fiz.
I'M ON THE WAY
TO TAKE PHOTOS OF THE SUNRISE
I'M ALREADY HERE WAITING YOU
Let's set up here.
Sure.
Ever wonder what the people
in the city are doing?
It's absolutely better here.
You miss living in the city?
I only miss…
my parents.
When we're married…
and live in an apartment,
they will be so proud to see
I have a cool wife like you.
Your imagination's running too wild, Fiz.
Just enjoy what's in front of you.
It's you then.
Hopefully, your parents
will be proud of me too.
My late father would definitely be proud.
Once we live in the apartment,
we won't get this view anymore.
I'll be your view.
Bye!
Where have you been?
Did you bring the candles?
Of course, relax.
Can I have a taste?
ACCORDING TO YOUR CHOSEN FIELD
YOU WILL MANAGE THE LIGHT MART DESIGN
AFTER GETTING MARRIED
Make a wish first.
Okay.
-Yay!
-Hurray!
How's the bride-to-be?
Are you nervous?
I'm so happy this day has finally arrived.
By the way, look at this.
Ms. Nanik sent me this.
She said this is how my store
is going to look.
So how do you feel
about marrying someone you've never met?
I'm fine. I'm only worried
about the first night…
Will it hurt?
Just chill, Ulfah. Let it go.
Can we have one last sleepover?
This is my last night here.
Shoot, that's true.
-Tar, do you dare?
-No.
I need to keep Sofia impressed.
Can't taint my record.
With our matchmaking system,
two fated souls shall meet today
in this beautiful and sacred place.
I thought he was going to be your match!
Ulfah and Hafiz.
Hafiz.
Do you accept Ulfah
whom we've chosen as your wife?
She's the best match for you, Hafiz.
I accept.
Ulfah, do you accept Hafiz
whom we've chosen to be your husband?
I accept.
-Our Extraordinary Leader.
-Please don't mind me.
Continue with what you're doing.
You've been chosen
as Joko Liauw's co-director…
for our special documentary project.
Wow, thank you so much
for this opportunity.
You're very welcome.
No need to be so tense.
You pushed yourself too hard.
You need to take care of yourself.
If I may know…
What's the documentary going to be about?
Me.
All right.
I shall not disappoint you.
Remember to rest.
FIZ! I HAVE BEEN CHOSEN…
I don't think my clothes
would fit into our small apartment.
Let's put them in the stock room here
until we get a bigger unit
once we have children.
Sure. I'll head upstairs.
Aren't you going to help me?
I'll help tomorrow morning.
When will your parents be here?
I want to get to know them.
That will have to wait.
Na. Oh, my god.
Ulfah's wedding video is dope!
-Here, look at it!
-I'm the one who made it.
I know, I mean, look how beautiful she is.
And Hafiz looked so good with his haircut,
even more dashing in a suit.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Ulfah and Hafiz. They don't seem
to have anything in common.
Unlike you and him.
We're just co-workers.
Don't get the wrong idea, Tar.
-Chill. Don't get all defensive.
-Of course not.
Anyway, I have to focus on a new project.
A documentary about the life
of The Extraordinary Leader.
That's very cool!
Please find out about my match.
I've got to go. I need to pee.
NA, MY MARRIAGE
IS ONLY AN OBLIGATION.
YOU MUST KNOW MY LOVE IS ONLY FOR YOU.
The test results came out really good.
We can start the transfer
to the mother's uterus.
Are you ready to be filmed?
Okay, go ahead.
Are you ready, Sofia?
-Let's wait for Ali first.
-Sure.
Take the book with you.
Keep it.
-Thank you, Extraordinary Leader.
-You're welcome.
Capture me and Sofia's moments well.
I want the audience to relate to us.
-Doc, please excuse…
-Hi.
-our documentation team.
-Go ahead.
Just relax. We'll begin
the procedure shortly.
Direct it to me, please.
Inhale. Control your breathing.
Control your breathing.
What a tragedy, to lose one's child.
But they are very strong together.
This is confidential stuff, Tara.
My responsibilities are huge
in this project.
Okay.
My, it's almost 8 p.m.
Relax,
they are still glam living
like a king and a queen…
I'M BACK TO WORK SOON,
CAN'T WAIT TO BE WITH YOU
IN THE EDITING LAB. PLEASE REPLY, NA.
DELETE CHAT
ARE YOU SURE?
DELETE
From sports
to sustainable food chain,
eco-friendly fashion,
and beauty products.
And now, let me show you
The Light's Beauty Lab.
Now we have to study the product.
Let's start working!
At The Light, we have many facilities.
This is one of them.
Good morning, everyone.
Sorry to interrupt.
Sofia sends her regards.
Tara is here and I am sure
you will learn a lot from her.
This is unusual
for our Extraordinary Leader
to stop by.
Let's all take a selfie.
-Salina, please join us.
-It's okay.
-Come, Na.
-Don't just stand there.
Come here,
let's take a photo together.
Okay. Santi, you too.
Okay. Tighter, please.
One, two…
Three.
Hey.
Na?
Can I preview your cut?
Just relax. We'll begin
the procedure shortly.
Direct it to me, please.
-Inhale…
-There are no interviews yet.
But I'm certain it'll turn out great.
I didn't expect the editing
to turn out like this.
I'm taking a short break.
Wow, the decor's cute.
-Very Ulfah.
-I've missed you both!
Hey, girl.
Have you done it? Awesome, right?
It hurts a bit at first.
But Hafiz was gentle
and he turned out to be so sweet.
Watch over him, please?
Since he's your co-worker.
What do you mean?
He keeps skipping lunch at work.
Please remind him to eat.
All right, I will.
By the way,
how is the documentary going so far?
It's cool to be able to work
on such an important project.
I've been tagging along
on all of his activities.
It's exhausting but very rewarding.
But
something felt off yesterday.
Really? What happened?
Ali caressed my cheeks.
Was that captured by your camera, Na?
He was really handsy.
Oh, please.
Tar, he's just being attentive.
He's harmless. Don't overreact.
Let's just shoot.
Are you ready?
Smile, Ul.
Chief Ali, Sofia,
congratulations. You're finally expecting.
Thank you, Endru.
But please keep this to yourself.
This is still at a very early stage.
Noted, ma'am.
Okay. Good.
Who else are we going to send off
for marriage this time?
Please start, Ms. Nanik.
Diana and Doni.
Diana's skills include sewing
and making patterns, but she can't draw,
while Doni is a great illustrator.
I think they are compatible.
-They're going to be a productive couple.
-Agreed.
Who's next?
Tara's supposed to be next,
but it's hard to find a match for her.
She's influential, with lots of followers.
Tara is too progressive
for someone her age,
She even made a digital marketing plan
for Sofia's makeup line.
I can't picture any boys here
to be her match.
Endru?
Ever think of taking a second wife?
No, not for me, sir.
Don't you want to have more children?
-Tara can…
-Al.
Endru's wife is battling cancer,
don't you remember?
Oh, sorry, I forgot.
Dru.
It's okay, chief.
How about we focus on Diana first?
Tara can wait.
What did you shoot today?
The next wedding plan.
My batch! So?
I felt uncomfortable.
I didn't expect
Ali to talk about polygamy so casually.
You mean
we'll be matched
to an already married guy?
Shit.
Where's the file?
I already submitted it
to the editing room.
I don't feel good about this.
That's why you always have to keep a copy.
Go rogue a bit, Na!
I know.
Na, I understand
you want to keep your space.
Hopefully, we can stay friends.
That's enough for me.
I want to remind you
to always delete
all of our chats and emails.
Thank you.
DON'T WORRY, I ALWAYS DELETE ALL.
WE'RE WRONG FOR HOPING TOO MUCH.
PLEASE TAKE CARE OF ULFAH.
SHE'S THE BEST. STOP TEXTING ME.
I WILL EDIT MY FILM MYSELF.
It always feels like paradise here.
It's been a while since my last visit.
Yes, it has, sir.
I've been too busy with my constituents.
Of course, sir,
I understand that you're busy.
If you ever feel tired,
or in need of a change of scenery,
this place is always open for you, sir.
Thank you.
Without you, Mr. Frans,
none of this would have prospered.
When many were skeptical…
you, sir, were the first one to invest.
Ali.
Now it's my turn
to ask you for a favor.
Please find a wife for my son, Aditya.
He's already 25
and he should marry soon.
I might just have
the perfect solution for you, sir.
Tara.
Wake up, Tara.
Go take a shower.
It's not even 5 a.m. yet.
Today you'll have breakfast
with The Extraordinary,
Sofia, and your future husband.
Since when do we have
this breakfast thing?
Since we found you a match.
What is she talking about?
Na!
Maybe he's not a member of The Light.
My bad karma is haunting me,
even now that I'm here.
What repentance must I make now?
Don't be a drama queen.
Just meet him first.
Okay?
We'll leave you guys to it,
so you can get to know each other better.
Tara, Aditya,
you will become an exceptional couple.
Thank you.
HOW IS IT?
FINALLY, A GOOD KARMA. MY FUTURE HUSBAND
IS HANDSOME LIKE A MOVIE STAR.
-So, Tara.
-Yeah?
So happy to see both of them.
I'll make Tara the spokesmodel
for my makeup line.
Mr. Frans will have stronger ties to us.
Your gut is never wrong, Sof.
-Of course.
-Watch out.
I want you to slow down.
Don't work too much.
Tara will do all the work
UL, FINALLY SOF AND ALI
GOT THE BEST MATCH FOR ME
I MISS YOU, UL. READ THIS!
HOPE YOU ARE HAPPY FOR ME.
RICH, YOUNG, HANDSOME ENTREPRENEUR
ADITYA FRANS PROFILE BY JAFAR KURSIDIN
Hey.
Hey. How's work today?
The usual.
Don't you want to know how my day went?
Oh, yeah. How was it?
I was sick all day.
And I can't stand your smell.
Go take a shower after this.
Are you that hungry?
Poor thing.
Thank you.
Tara's perfect for Aditya.
Here.
A little something as a form
of my appreciation.
Mr. Frans, please.
There's absolutely no need for this.
We're just returning the favor to you.
Ali, no matter what,
cash is important.
Think of a car.
And that car is your ambition.
But it doesn't have fuel.
Can the car go without fuel?
This cash is just that.
-Mr. Frans…
-We will not disappoint, sir.
Great. Let's greet our guests.
Sofia! What the hell is Salina doing here?
Now!
Salina.
Yes?
Delete the footage you shot just now.
Why, is something wrong?
Delete it now.
You should only focus
on Tara and Aditya today.
Not us!
Yes, ma'am.
Na?
Ulfah?
Looking gorgeous!
Let's congratulate Tara.
It turns out that married life
is not as easy as it seems.
I shouldn't be saying this.
But I don't think Hafiz is for me.
It's probably because
you're just getting to know each other.
It takes time.
You're probably right.
I shouldn't complain.
Actually, I have great news
to share with you.
Oh, what is it?
I'll tell you when we're with Tara.
Look at her. Isn't she the luckiest?
I mean, look at him!
Aditya is so handsome!
His father is The Light's main donor,
a powerful businessman,
and a politician.
Congrats, newlyweds!
You look stunning!
Finally, dreams do come true!
For me too.
I'm pregnant!
Oh. my god, Ul,
this is my wedding day
and you're stealing my thunder!
Congratulations, you two!
Adit?
-Adit?
-We'll be on our way then.
These are my childhood best friends.
-Ulfah and Salina.
-Thank you for coming.
Congrats.
-We'd better head on.
-Don't go home just yet!
-Bye.
-Congratulations!
-Ul. Are you done?
-Yes.
What took you so long?
-Sorry.
-All right then
-There was a long queue over there.
-Na, where are you going?
I have to continue working.
-You go ahead.
-All right.
NA, I JUST REALIZED I'LL BECOME
A DAD SOON. ULFAH'S BELLY IS GETTING BIG.
I MISS EDITING WITH YOU,
HOPE YOU GET THE BEST MATCH.
-I'm hungry.
-She always counts calories.
Here's your clip-on mic.
Can you put it on?
Okay.
Where should we start?
First question.
Can you…
Sorry.
-Kids my age think…
-Salina.
Right.
Are you ready?
I think…
my generation
would be more interested in the love story
of Your Extraordinary and Sofia.
There's no love story.
Our love starts right after marriage.
So when did Your Extraordinary
realize that Sofia was the one?
When I first presented
the matchmaking system that I developed
to fellow student activists.
They all laughed at the idea.
But not Sofia.
Next question.
Sorry.
Can we talk about
the funding of The Light?
Funding?
Salina.
Instead of funding,
why don't we talk about
the humanistic side of things?
Such as the traumas we experienced.
Sure.
The reason that I believe everyone
should have a match,
and that no one should postpone
or refuse the arrival
of children in their lives.
It's because of Rama,
our firstborn.
City life after the pandemic,
plastic pollution,
illnesses, those were the forces
that killed Rama.
Meanwhile, the world completely neglected
the rights for babies to live.
That urged me to take action.
I understand how you feel.
Those who had suffered loss
would understand.
Sofia!
Sof!
-I'm bleeding, Al.
-It's okay.
-Let's go to the hospital now.
-No.
-Sofia.
-I don't have the energy, Al.
I called our doctor already.
Excuse me,
can I be of any help?
Salina!
Sorry.
We need privacy.
Al, it's time for you to take my advice.
Our legacy can't end here.
Sofia, please don't.
Don't think about that now.
-You…
-You need to recover!
-But you have to…
-Sofia.
-Madam Sofia.
-Please, Doctor.
-Doc, my wife.
-Al!
I have to choose for you, Al.
Salina,
are you asleep?
It's not even 8 p.m.
Yes, ma'am.
I feel so tired today.
I know
you've witnessed the tragedy
befalling His Extraordinary and Sofia.
We're all mourning.
I'm always here for you.
Especially since
your best friends are both married
and are no longer here.
You can tell me.
I just miss everyone so much.
I miss Ulfah,
Tara…
and I also feel sorry for Sofia.
I know. What a pity.
But as a filmmaker,
you have to be strong
and ready to face anything
that befalls your subject.
I have to be strong.
The Extraordinary Leader
is so proud of you.
So is Mr. Joko.
You are our pride.
Hello, darling.
Hey.
Darling.
This is the new ad for Sofia Makeup.
It will be uploaded tomorrow,
do you like it?
It looks great.
Darling, please.
What is it, Tar?
Aren't we shooting for The Light tomorrow?
We have to sleep.
But, your mom keeps reminding me
to get pregnant soon.
Don't worry about Mom,
it's typical of her.
Relax.
Sofia.
I hope you're feeling better.
I'm fine.
Let's not talk about my miscarriage.
You have to continue working
on the documentary, my dear.
Now please make
a good video for Tara. Understood?
Welcome, newlyweds!
-So sweet!
So sweet!
I'm honored to be able to work here
in Sofia Makeup.
And also to have
a very supportive husband.
I'm delighted to accompany Tara
on her first day back at work as my wife.
Every dedication
and the hard work we put in,
they will all pay off.
SALINA, EXTRAORDINARY LEADER AND I
NEED TO MEET YOU. NOW.
What position do you prefer this time?
Wait. Hold on a second.
Hold on a second, Tar.
-Who are you?
-Evening, boss.
Leo.
-Shall I make it quick?
-Adit…
Don't be scared,
I'll be watching over you.
Take it easy.
Easy, Tar.
Are you crazy?
Leo!
He's not moving…
Go to hell!
Tar, don't!
Good evening.
Hi, Salina.
We're not shooting today.
Oh, I see.
Okay then.
You look like a mess.
Sorry, all I had
on my schedule today was editing.
You'll be turning 17 soon, right?
Yes, ma'am.
And you are the only member
that I ever summoned…
before your birthday.
Yes,
only you.
Did I do something wrong?
Salina?
Because there will come a time
where all of you here will be married
to your perfect match.
Our baby hid
from the sonogram.
-Right, Fiz?
-Probably shy just like the dad.
I'm strong enough to not
be poisoned by romance.
My husband and I
accept each other as who we are.
Rest assured
that each of your future spouses
are here in the training center.
Tara.
ARYA TEJA, YEAR 2028
OUR SON NEVER CAME BACK FROM TL
"Our son joined The Light
without our consent."
"His name is Arya Teja,
missing since 2028."
"We cannot contact him ever since."
THOSE WHO SUCCESSFULLY ESCAPED FROM TL
"I survived escaping The Light."
"But one of my friends is still inside,
with no news of where they are
and how they are doing."
I understand. Thanks, Doctor.
Na. What's up, Na?
Tara. I want to escape The Light.
But we must do it together.
Na…
-I…
-I sent you a few articles.
Check your email.
Tomorrow before 12,
meet me at Ulfah's Light Mart
with your car, okay?
-Okay.
-I'll handle the payment. Surely.
Tar, all has been taken care of.
Stay tuned for more!
Tara!
You left this,
you won't be able to get in without it.
It doesn't matter.
People already know I'm your wife.
They'll let me in no matter what.
Tara, are we cool?
Don't worry about it.
Just forget it.
Na, why didn't you tell me
you're visiting?
I sent you a link.
You must be ignoring your emails.
Here.
What do you mean?
Ul, you know that my birthday
is approaching, right?
Yes, I've been praying
for you to find the best match.
Sofia and Ali…
They want me to…
to be his second wife.
-The fuck?
-Isn't that insane?
Ul, I have to get out of The Light.
Calm down, Na.
But you have to come with me!
Read the emails I sent you.
It's about an ex-member
who successfully escaped.
But it endangered their friends
who were still inside.
I don't want to leave by myself
and put you and Tara at risk.
Endangered? At risk?
Yes, Ul.
I feel so dizzy.
Fiz, where's my juice
and vitamins?
At the back, Ul.
Na, sorry. I'll be back.
What was that? They're going to
make you his second wife?
Motherfuckers!
I'll kill that bastard!
This is unacceptable!
Hafiz, calm down!
You can help
by editing our own version
of the documentary, okay?
-Forget about that!
-We're leaving all of this together, okay?
Calm down.
We're leaving all of this together, okay?
I will leave with you.
Wait…
What…
What is this?
-Ul, I can explain.
-Ulfah,
Salina and I love each other.
-What the fuck, Fiz? Shut up!
-Na?
I can explain, that was long
before you two were matched.
It's over now, there's nothing
-going on with us.
-Ulfah, you're a nice person, but…
-Shut up! Stop it, Fiz!
-I don't feel the same way about you.
-Ulfah, please trust me.
-Listen to me.
-Leave me alone!
-It's over!
-It was way before you were married.
You're a good person
but you need to know, Ulfah.
Leave me alone!
Get the fuck out of here!
Get out!
Ul, I'm so sorry, please hear me out!
I know, but we really have to leave!
Ul!
Salina, please take a break from work.
I want to have brunch with you
in the gazebo. Tara is here too.
I'm waiting!
Is that all?
That's it?
It is your duty to serve your husband.
I never imagine…
to be a good wife
includes permitting that.
Your husband is Aditya.
You are aware of that, right?
But this counts as
domestic violence, right?
Don't rant about
your husband's flaws to other people.
But you are not just some other people.
Please hear me out.
I don't want it to happen again.
As women,
we have to benefit
from the power of our men.
So just make up with your husband, okay?
I'm even traumatized by our own bed.
I need to file a report.
You think they'll believe you?
Tara.
You should be grateful.
We couldn't find a match for you here.
But Aditya
was willing to accept you
despite your wild dating records.
Fuck you!
Okay.
Guess I'll have to learn more
about gratitude.
Think of this as a process.
Where you can atone
for your past sins.
Okay?
NA, HURRY UP!
I'VE BEEN WITH SOF, I LOST MY MIND…
PLEASE WAIT…
I'LL JUST SMACK THIS DRIVER,
AND WE CAN ESCAPE
Na?
-Stay put.
-What's this?
Come with us.
-Why?
-Take him.
Salina?
Scoot, Tara.
-Hello.
-Tara's been waiting.
Let's all eat together.
-Just stick to our plan, Tar.
-How's Ulfah?
She must be so happy having a baby.
You didn't tell her anything yet, right?
Ulfah is well and healthy,
always so energetic.
So who's going to break the news?
The mic's yours, Sofia.
So…
This is the rundown for Salina
and Ali's wedding.
You'll walk onto the altar.
The screen of our matchmaking system
will do the usual shuffling.
The Extraordinary Leader's photo
will pop up next to you
and the crowd will be amazed
So the system can be manipulated?
Of course, you know that
it is just for show, right?
I can tinker with the matchmaking
system according to my will.
What is it, Endru?
An emergency has occurred, ma'am.
Regarding what?
About Ulfah.
Salina was just at her place
and she's fine.
She has evidence that
her husband has been unfaithful.
For God's sake.
Tara.
Go ahead and give
the most special treatment for Salina.
Let me handle this first.
Salina,
dinner tonight at ours, okay?
What the hell?
-Stupid boy!
-Have mercy, please!
Please have mercy on me.
Please…
He finally confessed, ma'am.
The letters…
were from before his marriage.
In accordance with our protocols,
we have to investigate further.
And make sure that this does not
involve another member of The Light.
Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am, his wife's here.
Sofia.
You have to protect
your health and your baby.
That is what matters most.
Maybe this is just me being hormonal.
-So I overreacted.
-Okay.
I fully understand.
Is it possible to revoke the charges?
The two of you need to have
a heart-to-heart talk first.
You stay here, watch over her.
What have I done?
I should be running away
and yet I have to do this shit!
Don't!
Where did you keep the footage?
In that bag.
My goodness, you should never
smuggle it all in one bag. It's risky.
Here.
Go sneak into the basement first.
Here's my car key. At B2.
I'll catch up with you.
Ulfah.
-How about Ulfah?
-We'll go to her apartment.
No alarms in The Light Daily
about you and Hafiz or the affair.
-Tara.
-Yes, Ms. Nanik?
Why don't you put on
a hair mask for Salina as well?
Wow, it's full-service today!
I can call in new members to help.
It's okay, I can handle this.
Ma'am.
Where are you taking those?
To class.
But they're face powders, ma'am.
We're only doing skincare today.
The class demo will be
using these cleansers…
My goodness, I really am getting old.
Thank you, love.
Please forgive me, Ulfah.
Ulfah.
The moment we were married,
I tried with all my might to be faithful.
Yet, I made the situation worse.
Ulfah.
I'm powerless.
But there might still be a way
for you three to get out of here.
Hafiz,
no one deserves to be locked up
in a place like this
just for falling in love.
Tar.
Ul?
I got mad and didn't know what else to do.
But I just revoked
the charges against Hafiz.
Ul.
Once again, I'm truly sorry.
But we have to leave all this behind.
Together.
I prefer to raise my child alone
instead of staying with a husband
who's in love with someone else.
You're not alone,
you have us.
But I don't want you to leave
your perfect life with Aditya,
just because of us.
You don't need to worry, Tara.
Just drop us off in the city.
No.
I want out too.
To hell with Aditya,
to hell with The Light.
What a waste of time,
handling some jealous brat.
Ulfah is pregnant,
so she's just being hormonal.
We must focus on my wedding ceremony.
Is the rundown still the same?
Yes.
I think that
Endru should be the one officiating.
Sounds good.
Salina?
Done with the treatment?
Oh, not yet.
I just need to use the toilet.
To the apartment, please.
Ma'am.
Is dinner with Salina still on?
Of course.
I texted her.
Ask Ms. Nanik to fetch her.
Stay put until we reach the highway.
Tara, please slow down.
The road's too bumpy, my tummy hurts.
Okay, I'll slow down.
I'm sorry, girls. I can't bear it anymore.
My tummy hurts so much.
Try the breathing exercises.
Do you remember it?
-What was that?
-Are you okay, Ul?
I think I peed my pants
I'm so sorry, ma'am!
Are you okay, ma'am?
-Wow, it's you again?
-We're so sorry, ma'am!
Na! Ulfah's peed her pants.
What?
It's not pee…
Remember what we learned in class?
Our water breaks before birth?
How far along are you, child?
She's seven months pregnant.
Seven months, ma'am.
Oh, a baby born
during the 7th month of pregnancy
brings a prophecy.
What's she talking about?
Follow me, we must help her.
Come with me.
I can't hold it in anymore.
Ulfah?
Inhale, Ul.
Come on breathe, Ul! Push!
It's almost there.
Yes, Ms. Nanik?
Salina is nowhere to be found.
Her room is empty.
Ms. Nanik,
check with security now.
-Now.
-Yes, sir.
Has anyone seen Salina?
Maybe in the restroom, ma'am?
Push, Ulfah.
Stop saying that!
You don't know how this feels.
It hurts so much!
-Yes, Ul.
-Keep calm.
Calm and in the name of Allah…
That's it!
Thank God, it's a girl!
Here, cut the umbilical cord.
I want to hold her.
There you go!
You must take this baby to the hospital.
Baby Padma.
Her name is Padma.
Spoiled brat!
She even went to the Beauty Lab!
I can't do this anymore.
How can we be fooled by these brats!
Where the hell was our surveillance team?
Fucking brats!
Our guards are all idiots!
How…
It's comfortable enough. Thank you, Tar.
Take a picture of Baby Padma
and send it to Hafiz.
What should I write?
Anything that will lift his spirit.
THIS IS BABY PADMA,
SHE WAS BORN EARLY, STRONG, HEALTHY,
AND WE'RE OKAY.
Take a look at this, Ms. Nanik.
We've checked the GPS tracking
and it seems that they have stopped.
They're not too far away from here.
Shall I command security
to search the area?
You should've done that ages ago! Quickly!
Yes, sir.
Bring Hafiz here!
He must be sacrificed.
Coordinate with the entire
apartment security team.
This is exactly like
the incident two years ago!
I terminated those punks easily.
But not these girls!
How will our relationship
with Mr. Frans be?
And tomorrow's your wedding day!
Don't you dare force me
to marry a spoiled traitor!
Fiz, thank you for reminding me
what's important in life.
Now, we need your magical editing touch.
Okay, I've sent the files
and uploaded my first video online.
I'm Salina and I'm turning 17.
This is my room
at The Light, and joining them
was the biggest mistake
I've ever made in my life.
-Stay tuned for more!
-Bastards!
@ME_LISA: I CAN HACK THEIR FUND SOURCES
Sof, we must protect
our estate and assets.
You know that it is just for show, right?
I can tinker with the matchmaking
system according to my will.
Call our lawyer now, Sof.
You know. I never approved
of your narcissistic documentary.
Damn!
The apartment is empty too.
-I hope Hafiz is safe.
-The boy is gone.
I never regret being in love
as it trains me to be courageous.
Also, I've understood heartbreak,
which developed my intuition.
Go back to sleep, Padma
By the way, what did
the old lady say earlier?
That?
She said that in ancient times,
babies born at seven months young
bring along a message,
like a prophecy.
A message for her mom and aunties
to stick together and love each other.
Ul, how do you feel?
It must have hurt like crazy.
It still hurts everywhere.
But I feel like gaining a superpower.
I think Tara and I can totally relate
to Ulfah's embracing her superpower.
As girls, we've never been taught
that strength
and independence are possible
even without the approval of others.
But now, the three of us
definitely believe
that the superpower
has always been embedded in us.
Since forever!