Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
He loves
that old camera.
Come on, Yang.
YANG: One second.
Don't forget
to join us.
YANG: I will.
Look here for a second.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Come on,   gege.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
JAKE:   Yellow Equinox.
Is that a new blend?
WOMAN:   I think so.
I'm sure I can make you
something close to it.
Do you know
what kind of tea leaves?
Oh, no. No, no.
It's not this kind of tea.
I'm looking for
your crystallized teas.
Ah. Sorry, I...
I don't carry tea crystals.
How can you be a tea shop
and not carry tea crystals?
(SIGHS) How frustrating.
Why don't you let me
make you something
that might be close?
No. No, no, no. This is...
I have to go.
Thanks for coming in.
MIKA:   When's Daddy
coming home?
KYRA:   Soon.
He's always late.
Well, I'm late sometimes, too.
And, you know, I've got a busy
few weeks coming up, so...
I know.
Yang will be here.
So will Daddy.
Mika.
Mika?
Don't be
too hard on him.
He told me there was
a rush of customers
towards the end of the day.
That's good news for Daddy.
He needed that.
KYRA:   I loved that meal.
Did you like
the gochujang sauce?
JAKE: I did.
I made it.
JAKE: You mentioned that.
It was her first time.
So you put the ingredients
in the bowl
and you mixed them
all together?
Yeah.
(JAKE CHUCKLES)
It's good, huh?
It was really wonderful,
mei mei.
Thank you.
Next time,
I'm gonna Juliet
the carrots.
Julienne.
And no, you're not.
(CHUCKLES)
(VIOLIN PLAYING)
Mika's growing up so fast.
(MUFFLED VIOLIN
CONTINUES PLAYING)
She keeps asking
why we're always busy.
She understands.
And Yang is...
No, she doesn't.
(SIGHS)
I feel like...
I don't know. I...
I don't want to regret.
Um... Um,
I'll make more time.
I will. I promise.
You know
I'm not putting this
on you, right?
Hmm. Sort of.
I'm not.
I'm teasing.
I just want us
to be a team.
A family.
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
Starting
Ignite
Reset
Starting
Ignite
Reset
Starting
HOST: (OVER SPEAKER)
Welcome, families of four,
to our monthly dance-off.
We have over 30,000 families
competing tonight.
Are you ready?
(MUSIC TEMPO INCREASES)
Stay in sync.
Precision points added.
Take flight.
Ready for combat.
Fight time.
Level one complete.
3,000 families eliminated.
Stay together.
Steady.
Sync bonus coming up.
The hitchhiker.
Go.
Transition.
Collect the TNT.
Detonate.
(BEEPING)
Smile. It's time
for family portrait.
(TIMER BEEPING)
(CLICK)
Earthquake.
Tornado time.
Level two complete.
9,000 families eliminated.
Stamina round.
Keep up.
Stay in sync.
Terminated.
(MUSIC STOPS)
(GROANS LOUDLY)
Babe! Babe!
It wasn't me. It was...
(PANTING)
It wasn't me! Mika?
Not me!
It was Daddy!
Mm-hmm.
That's the furthest
we've ever gone.
(LAUGHS)
That's true.
Yang, we're...
we're out.
(MIKA LAUGHING)
Yang? Yang!
MIKA:   Yang!
JAKE:   Yang?
JAKE: It looks like
we have three years left
on the warranty, but
they're not answering, so...
KYRA: Can't you just go there?
JAKE: Yeah, I'm going to,
but I don't know if the store
is even there anymore.
I did a search.
I can't find them anywhere.
Did you call
Brothers & Sisters?
We didn't buy
from them directly, so...
KYRA: They won't
honor the warranty?
No, the warranty
is with Second Siblings.
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
I told you we should've
just bought a new one.
He was new.
I mean, practically.
He's refurbished.
Certified refurbished.
And he'd only been in use
for five days. Five days.
And we saved...
But now he...
Never mind.
Let's just get him fixed.
Yeah.
You need to get Mika
to school.
Mika, come on,
we need to go!
Mika?
What happened to Yang?
Oh, hi. Um...
I don't know.
He shut down last night.
He won't restart.
Has this
happened before?
No.
You got a technician?
He's still under warranty.
I wouldn't take him back
to Brothers & Sisters.
They're just going to try
to get you to recycle him
for a new model.
You know why.
I'm not taking him there.
The warranty's
with another store.
You didn't buy him direct?
No. No, uh, he's certified.
I have to go and get Mika.
Oh, Mika's still here?
Did she see Yang
all dead-eyed?
I bet
it freaked her out.
Yeah.
Listen, I got a technician
in Woodbury.
It's worth the trek.
I'm going to send you
his info.
No, I'll just...
I'll take him to Quick Fix
if I can't figure it out.
That place is for morons.
Don't take him there.
My guy will fix him
for a third of the cost.
You tell Russ I sent ya.
Okay. Okay, got to go.
Thank you.
Mika? Mika?
Come on, kiddo,
we gotta boogie.
I don't want to go to school.
I want to be with Yang.
Mika, the longer we wait,
the worse it's gonna be
for Yang.
What do you mean?
He'll start decomposing.
What?
Come on, we gotta go.
Mika, now.
FYI, Mika's going
to be with me for the day.
KYRA:   Why? What happened?
JAKE: Well, you know,
she just refused and
I wasn't gonna
drag her inside.
KYRA:   Mika?
(MIKA GROANS)
KYRA:   Answer me.
Mom, I can't.
I want to be with Yang.
KYRA:   It's okay, darling.
I just wanted
to hear your voice.
You need to listen to Dad
and be good and calm, okay?
MIKA: Is Yang
going to be better?
Yes, he's gonna be...
KYRA:   Well, we don't
know for sure, but...
What do you mean?
Yeah, what do you mean?
KYRA:   We can't make any
promises, but, Mika, listen,
if you can be good and calm
for the rest of the day,
I'm gonna bring
you a surprise.
What?
You just promised her
a surprise.
MIKA: What is it, Mom?
KYRA:   That's different.
Mom, what is it?
KYRA:   I wasn't trying to...
I appreciate you
taking the day off.
MIKA: Mom?
KYRA:   Honey,
be good and listen to Dad.
Oh, I need to go.
I have to get ready for
my presentation. We'll talk.
(CALL ENDS)
What is she gonna
get me, Dad?
I have no idea.
MIKA: I think I know.
Just don't get your hopes up
for anything specific.
(WHISPERS)   Gege,   I know
what she's gonna get me.
JAKE: Excuse me?
Excuse me?
Can I help you?
Yeah, I was wondering
if you could...
I purchased a...
This used to be a store
where you could buy, uh,
an older sibling
for Chinese adoptions.
It was called
Second Siblings.
We sell fish and tanks.
Yeah, I can see,
but do you know
what happened to that shop?
Before my store,
they sold memory.
Memory-balia. Is that how
you say it, memory-balia?
Memorabilia.
Yeah, memories.
But no technos?
No, I'm not sure
what it was before that.
All right, thank you.
Mika?
Mika. Mika,
come on, let's go.
I want a fish.
(WHISPERS)
Gege?   Meet Puffy.
Uh, it's a black box
issue, okay?
Uh, so by law,
we're not allowed
to tamper with the, uh,
core interior, unfortunately.
So what is it
that you do here?
Uh, well, we are certified
with Brothers & Sisters,
Incorporated,
to, repair or replace
up to 12 parts
most commonly
in need of service.
If you want to take
a gander there
at the 12-point diagnostic.
Yeah, but your diagnostics
is just...
Um, well, we hooked up Yang
to our certified analyzer,
and, uh, all 12 parts
were in working order,
however, the readout
did indicate that there was
a core malfunction,
unfortunately, so...
So what?
So there's nothing you can do?
Oh, there's a couple things
we can do here.
Um, we can have him recycled
at Brothers & Sisters.
Uh, if you do so before
he begins to decompose,
you'll get $1,000 off on
a new model, which is great.
Uh, if you don't want
to have him recycled,
which I completely understand,
um, we are equipped
to turn his head and his voice
box into a virtual assistant,
and we'd salvage
the remaining parts for ya.
What?
But we would have
to send the core to, uh,
Brothers & Sisters.
No, no, no.
That's not gonna happen.
Now, just give him back to me,
and I'll get a second opinion.
Oh, sure. Of course.
Uh, so that'll be 250
for the diagnostics, please.
You're kidding me.
Unfortunately, no.
(INDISTINCT, ANIMATED CHATTER)
KYRA: (ON SPEAKERPHONE)
That doesn't sound good.
JAKE: I know.
What did you tell Mika?
I said we were getting
a second opinion.
It's already taken longer
than I expected.
MIKA: Daddy?
KYRA:   Hi, Mika.
MIKA: Hi.
KYRA:   Are you okay?
No. I got a fish.
KYRA:   You did?
She did?
MIKA: Yeah.
Yeah, it's a little...
I'll explain later.
We're almost there.
KYRA:   All right.
Keep me posted.
Okay.
KYRA:   Bye, Mika.
Bye. Say bye to Yang.
KYRA:   Bye, Yang.
RUSS: It is
an interior core problem.
JAKE: Yeah,
we knew that already.
I need your permission
to break open the core.
It's against the law.
(LAUGHING)
It's just... It's a bunch
of corporate bullshit.
Do you know
who made that a law?
Brothers & Sisters.
They're just trying
to protect their spyware.
You recycle that,
they will have so much data
on your family,
it'll make your head spin.
JAKE: I'm not interested.
Your loss.
You promised to fix him.
Mika, I said wait outside.
You said
he was gonna be fine.
Come on, man.
You gotta make a decision.
KYRA:   Maybe
this is a good thing.
JAKE:   How is this
a good thing?
Yang has been...
Yang has been wonderful.
And we'd
all miss him terribly,
(SIGHS)
but we've been over-reliant
on him.
We bought
Yang to connect Mika
to her Chinese heritage,
not to raise her.
Yeah, but we spent
a lot of money on Yang.
I mean, I'm not gonna...
you know, feel bad
if he does more for Mika
than teach her
Chinese fun facts.
He does a lot more than that,
but you're missing the point.
What's the point?
If we can't fix Yang,
we're not gonna buy
another sibling for Mika.
That would just be...
strange.
And we can't afford it anyway.
So we need
to be more involved.
More than we are now.
And not just
in raising her,
in connecting Mika
to her culture and heritage.
Like, that will be
on us.
So we need to be
ready and willing.
(TRANQUIL MUSIC PLAYING)
YANG: Mei mei,   what's wrong?
MIKA:   Nothing.
YANG: Your face says
something different.
MIKA: Just some kids.
In your class?
No, kids at recess.
They were asking
about my real parents.
I see.
And what did you say?
MIKA: I told them
about Mom and Dad,
and they said,
"No, your real parents."
They said Mom and Dad weren't
really my parents. Not really.
Do you believe them?
I mean,
they're our parents, but...
we're not,
you know, they're not...
Not really.
YANG: Mei mei.
Here it is.
Take a look at this.
Is the tree hurt?
No. Something wonderful
is happening here.
What?
You see, this branch
is from a different tree.
It is?
Yes, but now it's becoming
an actual part of this tree.
Not really, though.
It's just pretend.
Why do you say that?
Because it's just
taped to the tree.
Oh, right.
It looks like that,
doesn't it?
Here, let's find one
that's already attached.
Mei mei.
See this branch?
This branch
is also from another tree.
But look, you're connected
to Mom and Dad,
just like this branch.
You're a part of
the family tree. For real.
Then so are you.
Why do they do it?
Why do they move branches
to different trees?
It's called grafting.
They do it
to make something new.
Some of the apples you love
were produced
by combining different trees.
It's an ancient technique
that was used in China
over 4,000 years ago.
A Chinese fun fact.
YANG: Yes.
But you should know
that both trees are important.
Not just this one, but the one
from this branch, too.
Your other family tree is also
a vital part of who you are.
Do you understand?
MIKA: I want to go
with Dad.
No, kiddo, you need
to go to school today.
MIKA: But Yang!
I wanna see Yang!
Hey, what about
your Pup-Pup?
Don't you want
to show your friends?
MIKA: Yang.
Yang's gonna be
home soon.
MIKA: Is he better?
We'll see.
KYRA: But you need
to go to school.
Yang would want that.
Do it for   gege.
He'd want me
to show my Pup-Pup.
KYRA: Mm-hmm.
All right,
I'm heading out.
Okay. Let me know
how it goes.
JAKE: Will do.
KYRA: Your bag.
Come on.
(CAR DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(TRANQUIL MUSIC PLAYING)
RUSS:   We've always known
that some bots
are equipped with spyware.
Especially the foreign ones.
And now we have proof.
Now? So you've never
seen these before.
What does it matter?
It is what it is.
Have you looked
at the recordings?
No.
No! I'm pro-privacy.
Can I see
what's on here?
You'll need
a special reader.
The connectors, they're
nothing I've seen before.
(CHUCKLES) This is
some high-level shit, man.
I mean, this is...
Sorry, I'm... I'm just trying
to wrap my head around it.
It's disturbing.
Yes.
It is disturbing.
It's time
to wake up, man.
(JAKE SIGHS)
So how do I buy a reader
that I can see what's on this?
No one's selling
a reader for that.
You'll have to have one
specifically modified
for those connectors.
Great.
Okay, I'm gonna
give you a name.
There's no number,
but this is
where you find them.
How much do I owe you?
Like I said,
I get paid to fix things.
Thank you.
I guess
I'll take Yang back.
I'll tell you what.
Why don't... Why don't you
look what's on there first?
If it's something bad,
disturbing, (CHUCKLES)
you might not want this bot
in your house anymore.
You can take him, but also,
he's gonna start decomposing.
You won't get
as much value for him.
I can keep him hooked up
on the simulator
until you know more.
You're a friend
of George, right?
Yeah.
MAN: (ON SPEAKER)
Sorry, she's in a meeting,
but I'd be happy
to pass on a message.
Yeah, could you
just tell her...
Uh, hello?
Are you still there?
You know what, it's all right.
I'll talk to her later.
Great. Should I have
her call you back?
No. No, it's all right.
Thank you.
(CALL ENDS)
JAKE: I was told
I could talk to you.
I was looking for Max Walker,
but they mentioned...
WOMAN: Oh, I'm not interested.
JAKE: Sorry?
WOMAN: Are you here to talk
some conspiracy shit?
JAKE: No. No, Russ
told me that I could...
WOMAN: Russ? Oh, man,
you're one of them.
I can't believe
they let you back here.
JAKE: I'm not
one of them. I...
I have this.
I was told Max might be
able to help me with it.
WOMAN: What is that?
Russ said it's spyware.
Where did you find it?
It was inside Yang.
And... he's our...
(INHALES SHAKILY)
We bought him after we adopted
our daughter. She's Chinese.
Mm-hmm.
And my neighbor
recommended Russ
after Yang shut down,
and Russ broke in...
Can I...
Sorry. Can I?
Yeah, sure.
Holy shit,
this isn't spyware.
I'm pretty sure
it's a memory bank.
The memory banks
allowed the technos
to record a few seconds
each day.
The labs were
trying to understand
what technos
considered memorable.
But the research
was uncovered,
the whole project
was shut down
immediately
for violating privacy laws.
JAKE:   So what do I do?
Oh, I'm not gonna lie. This...
This is a big deal.
If it's the regulator,
then Russ is right.
He's not gonna turn on.
I'm just being
honest with you.
But his existence,
Yang's existence would be
an invaluable contribution
to this museum
and just to
the whole understanding
of techno-sapiens.
So I guess
the real question's gonna be,
what do we pay you to
have Yang and his memories
in our collection?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
JAKE: Could I have
another one of these, please?
(AIR ON THE G STRING
PLAYING ON SPEAKER)
(ELECTRONIC CHIMING)
JAKE: Answer call.
Hey.
JAKE:   Hey. How's Mika?
She's next door.
Next door? At George's?
KYRA:   Yep.
Why?
Because you're not here,
and I have work to do.
I'm taking care of Yang.
KYRA:   Is that
what you're doing?
Yes.
So you just
dropped her off over there?
No, his daughters
invited her over to play.
You need to stop being
so hard on George.
He likes you,
and he's being really helpful.
His kids are clones.
I don't want
to talk about this again.
And he paints his face
for sporting events.
What is wrong with you?
What's wrong with him?
You need to stop. Okay?
(SIGHS)
How's the ramen?
It's, um, soothing.
Yeah, I can see that.
What are you having?
Ramen.
Really? That's funny.
KYRA:   Is it?
Sort of, don't you think?
Are you any closer
to getting Yang fixed?
This is the third place
you've taken him to.
Well, he's actually
still at the repair shop.
I'm, uh, having
a part examined.
By a specialist.
So is he gonna be
up and running again soon?
I'm not sure. You know,
it's... it's complicated.
(DOOR THUDS)
That's Mika. I got to go.
Functions like
any other reader.
Should be intuitive.
Do I need a code?
Yeah, there should be
a certification card
that came with Yang.
There's a serial number
and a pin on it.
Also, per our agreement,
you'll need to bring
Yang's body here tomorrow.
Sooner the better.
Yes.
I wouldn't be surprised
if Russ is trying
to replace parts
and steal the originals.
We will keep Yang's body
preserved here in a bio-state
while you go
and review the memories
and decide what
you want to do next.
Okay. Yeah. Thank you.
Thank you.
I've dedicated my life to
understanding techno-sapiens.
This... This is a gift.
(DOOR THUDS)
MIKA: (SINGING)
I want to be
Just like the wind
Just flowing in the air
Flowing in open space
KYRA: Yang taught you that?
MIKA: Uh-huh.
It's his favorite song.
Do you like it?
(KYRA CHUCKLES)
KYRA: I love it.
Hey.
Mika's up late.
She couldn't sleep.
You going somewhere?
Brenda's meeting me
at the office.
We're gonna
stay overnight and work.
We're behind.
JAKE: Sorry
I wasn't here earlier.
It's fine.
You'll need to
take Mika to school
and get her ready
for the day.
Do you think
you can do that?
Yeah, of course.
All right. (SIGHS)
I need to go.
Are we...
Are we okay?
So what did the part reveal?
The part?
The part.
The specialist?
Oh. Oh, yeah, yeah.
Um...
You... We should
know something soon.
I need to go.
JAKE: Try and get
some sleep if you can.
(DOOR SLIDES OPEN)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Serial 733951137CM99.
Pin 279321.
(INDISTINCT ANIMALS CALLING)
(ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
JAKE: Play.
What are you doing?
JAKE: Repeat.
JAKE: Play.
(SOFT INDIE MUSIC
PLAYING DISTANTLY)
(MUSIC FADES)
Play.
(MUSIC RESUMES PLAYING
ON SPEAKER)
(SINGING ALONG)
I want to be loved...
(MUSIC STOPS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(BABY FUSSING)
KYRA:   One, two, three, four.
(BABY CRYING)
YANG: Five.
KYRA: Five.
YANG: Six.
KYRA: Six.
YANG: Seven.
KYRA: Seven.
Eight. Nine. Ten.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
YANG:   Mei mei. Mei mei.
(BIRD CALLING IN DISTANCE)
YANG: Walk to me,   Mei mei.
Walk to me.
Careful.
(KYRA LAUGHING)
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
YANG: Wonderful.
YANG:   Cai hong.
MIKA:   Cai hong.
YANG: They know
you didn't mean it.
YANG:   Ni hao, Mei mei.
MIKA:   Daddy.
Daddy.
Daddy!
JAKE: Sorry,
is everything okay?
I'm getting some water.
Do you want me to?
Are you watching
a movie?
I am.
What are you watching?
Just a...
Just a documentary.
Is it about tea?
(LAUGHS)
Yeah.
(WHISPERING)
Is it boring you to tears?
(LAUGHS)
Hey...
Let's get you some water.
MIKA: I'll do it.
JAKE: Okay.
Is this something you do?
Do you get yourself water
in the middle of the night?
Gege   usually comes with me.
Is that right?
So you'd wake him up?
Does he sleep?
JAKE: No, I don't think so.
I usually just say,
(WHISPERS)   "Gege."
Not very loudly
because he can hear me
even when I whisper.
I say, (WHISPERS)   "Gege,
I want to get some water."
Then he joins me
in the hallway,
and we walk quietly
to the kitchen.
(JAKE LAUGHS)
Why don't you just ask him
to get you a glass of water?
Then you can stay in bed.
I like getting
my own water.
RUSS:   What do you mean
you want him back?
JAKE:   I mean I want him back.
Did Max make the reader
for you?
Max isn't there anymore.
Where is he?
I don't know.
I bet they took him.
Ah!
I can't believe
they finally got him.
Please, just let me
have Yang back.
(TOOL CLATTERS)
I want an explanation.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Yang belongs
to us. I...
don't need to give you
an explanation.
(LOW SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
It'll be all right.
CLEO: God,
I love cultural technos.
And since they're used
for adoptions
and language learning,
they haven't had to
change much over the years.
No need to be
faster or stronger.
There's some damage here.
Damn Russ just hacked
his way into the core.
There's a proper way
of opening it.
So if you don't mind,
we're just gonna do
a full check-up,
and we're gonna restore Yang
as best we can.
Oh, that would be great.
It won't help
with his off state,
but it should help
with his preservation.
(INDISTINCT
ELECTRONIC CHATTER)
JAKE: Play.
Repeat.
Play.
Come on, Yang.
YANG:   One second.
(MIKA GIGGLING)
KYRA: My silly girl.
(SING-SONGY) Silly girl.
He loves that old camera.
JAKE: Come on, Yang.
(KYRA CHUCKLES)
KYRA: (SING-SONGY)
Silly girl.
He loves
that old camera.
Come on, Yang.
YANG: One second.
Don't forget to join us.
YANG:   I will.
KYRA: He loves
that old camera.
JAKE: Come on, Yang.
One second.
MIKA: Don't forget to join us.
I will.
KYRA: (SING-SONGY)
Silly girl.
YANG: Just look here
for one second.
JAKE: What are you doing?
Come on.
MIKA: Come on,   gege.
YANG:   What do you like
about tea?
JAKE: Do you mean
the taste of tea?
YANG: Maybe. Is the taste
why you like tea?
JAKE: It has something
to do with it.
YANG: Is it why you've
given your life to tea?
JAKE: Given my life to tea,
well, that sounds
pretty serious.
Is it not serious?
I guess I've acquired
a taste for tea.
But it's not why
I became interested.
Interested.
I think what I was
really drawn to
at the beginning was...
I think what
I was really drawn to
at the beginning
was the idea of tea.
The idea of tea.
Yeah, I saw
this old documentary
when I was in college.
It was from the 20th century.
And it was about this man
searching for the best tea
in China.
It's about a man searching
for the best tea in China.
China is where tea started.
Yes, I'm sure you have
lots of interesting facts
about tea in China.
I do.
Would you like
to hear some of them?
Maybe another time.
I'm sorry, you were saying
about the man
searching for tea.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, actually,
I think that's it.
I think it was his searching
that compelled me.
You know, the pursuit
of this illusive thing,
this process that was
connected to the soil,
to the plants, to the weather,
and to a way of life.
To a way of life.
So that's what
you like about tea?
The search,
not so much the taste.
No, no, no, the taste, too.
(LAUGHING) There's this, uh...
There's this part in the film,
it's a great part,
where the man
is explaining
to his German friend
why it's so difficult for him
to describe the taste of tea.
He says,
"There's no language for it.
"There are no words
to adequately express
"the mysterious nature
of tea."
And his German friend,
who's just standing
right beside him
with a cup of tea, says,
(IN GERMAN ACCENT)
"Yes, but I imagine things
"like you are walking
through a forest,
"and there are leaves
on the ground,
"and it just had rained,
and the rain has stopped,
"and it's damp, and you walk,
"and somehow,
that is all in this tea."
(IN NORMAL TONE)
I mean, I loved that so much.
(LAUGHS) I loved that so much.
"Somehow,
that is all in this tea."
God, I watched it
over and over again.
I would like to watch
this movie.
Well, maybe
we can do it together.
Yes. That would be nice.
So do you believe it?
JAKE: What's that?
That a cup of tea
can contain a world?
That you could taste
a place, a time?
JAKE: Let's put it
to the test, shall we?
So you want
to smell it first.
You know, there's not just
flavor and the aroma,
there's history, too.
You know, traditionally,
tea shops that were
family businesses
passed down
from one generation to an...
Were passed down from...
...generation to,
you know this,
from generation to generation.
Maybe it's time I started
teaching you the trade.
Let's see if we can taste
the world together.
Drink it all at once.
What did you think?
I'm not sure
if I can taste the forest.
YANG: Do you taste
anything?
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Maybe I haven't
the language for it.
I wish Chinese tea wasn't
just about facts for me.
What do you mean?
I like watching
the way you make tea.
It's very beautiful.
The way the leaves bloom
and float and fall.
I wish I felt something
deeper about tea.
I wish I had a real memory
of tea in China.
Of a place.
Of a time.
I think this would...
What?
Sorry. I lost
my train of thought.
Are you happy, Yang?
YANG:   I don't know
if that's the question for me.
I don't know if that's
the question for me.
JAKE: Repeat.
(VOICES WHISPERING
INDISTINCTLY)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SOFT INDIE MUSIC
PLAYING DISTANTLY)
JAKE: Play.
(MUSIC RESUMES PLAYING)
(SINGING ALONG)
I want to be loved...
(MUSIC STOPS)
JAKE: Repeat.
(MUSIC RESUMES PLAYING)
Pause.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Zoom in.
Face match.
What can I get you?
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
Our senses are stored,
never to be the same.
Whisper to us. They existed.
They existed. We can be...
What are you doing?
Be and be better,
for they existed.
YANG: Do you think
that's true?
WOMAN:   Hello?   (LAUGHS)
(RAIN PATTERING)
Hey, what can I
get for you?
Hey, do you know her?
Uh, no, I don't.
Could you ask someone else?
I think she used to work here.
I'm sorry, there's a line.
I'm gonna need you
to order something.
Oh, I'll have
a double espresso.
And if I can speak
to the manager,
that would be great.
Double espresso, is that it?
Yes. And the manager.
Sorry, I can't help you.
But she worked here.
She doesn't work here
anymore.
But could you
tell me her name?
Why do you want
to find her?
She knew my son.
And he's not doing so well
right now. Health-wise.
And I thought
she'd want to know.
But you've never met her.
No.
And you don't know
her name.
No.
Yeah. Then I don't either.
Sorry.
GEORGE: Hey.
JAKE: Hey, George.
GEORGE: What do you need?
I was wondering if you'd ever
seen her around the house.
I... Who is she?
I don't know,
but Yang knew her.
Really? Huh.
I... I didn't know
that bots, uh...
That techno beings could
make friends on their own.
They were just...
I... I don't know anything,
I just want to find her.
Hmm.
Let me ask the girls.
Maybe they know something.
Please. Thank you.
Ladies, I need to see you.
VICKY: What is it?
Just get over here.
And bring the twins.
Vicky just made
the all-star softball team.
You gotta come watch.
I mean, she's just great.
Nice.
What is it?
Mr. Fleming wants to know
if you've seen her around.
Are you sure?
Can we go?
Yeah. Go ahead.
How about you?
Is she in trouble?
I don't...
No. No, not at all.
How's Yang?
He's not so good.
You know, I think finding her,
it might help.
Yeah, I've seen her.
You have?
A couple times.
At your place.
Did you ever talk to her?
Once. Yang asked me
not to say anything.
Why?
You don't like clones, right?
No, no, it's not...
Come on, Vic.
No fastballs.
I just...
I've never had the...
It's... It's fine.
No, it's not.
Vicky.
She's a clone.
She is?
Yeah, but she's really cool
and nice. Like most of us.
I'm sure.
Um, do you know her name?
VICKY: It's Aidy or Ada,
something like that.
Okay. Thank you.
Look, I'm sorry
if I've ever...
Can I go now?
Yes. Thank you,
sweetheart.
I'm... I'm really sorry,
it's...
No, no, no, it's...
Honestly.
You should see her fastball.
I mean, she's just...
(MIMICS BALL WHOOSHING)
...like, all day long.
I mean...
Well, thanks, George.
I really have to...
Another time.
Yeah.
Uh, hey, maybe we can
get a drink together, huh?
Sometime?
Yeah. Yeah,
that'd be great.
MIKA: I want to see   gege.
I know, love.
You miss him. Me, too.
We just can't see him now.
MIKA: What about
the family dance?
Are we never
gonna dance again?
KYRA: Of course we will.
But we might have to compete
in the family of threes.
MIKA: I don't want
to be a family of three!
Mika.
I want   gege   back!
KYRA: Daddy's trying his best.
He's doing everything he can.
I want him back, too.
What about you, Mom?
Do you want him back?
Of course I do.
KYRA: This is
dragging on too long.
JAKE: I just need
a little more time.
KYRA: Oh, we need
to start focusing on Mika.
We're just making things
more difficult for her.
Jake, do you hear me?
If we can't get
Yang fixed, we just...
we need
to move forward.
Okay?
Now. Now.
JAKE: I need
to tell you something.
JAKE:   No, it's... it's frozen.
That's interesting.
Try command
"memory reveal info,"
and it should tell you
if it's corrupt or not.
Okay, I'll do that.
Also, I was wondering,
is it possible for
cultural technos like Yang to
want to have
romantic potential?
Do you mean
for humans to use them?
No, no, no, I mean, for Yang
to be interested in...
There's a girl, and she
showed up in his memories,
and, you know, we didn't know
anything about her.
Really?
That's fascinating,
because I've never
heard of cultural technos
having that capacity.
I cannot tell you how much...
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
...Yang and his memories...
I should get that.
Oh, all right, okay.
But we'll touch base soon?
JAKE: Yeah,
let's do that.
Great.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
WOMAN: You've been
looking for me?
Yes.
I'm Jake.
I know.
I'm Ada.
Ada. Well, come in, please.
I knew something was wrong.
We usually meet,
and he wasn't answering
my messages.
I'm sorry.
I know Yang loves
being a part of this family.
Can I ask how you met?
At the coffee shop.
He approached you?
He was a regular customer.
He used to buy things
all the time, which,
you know, was funny when
I found out he was a techno.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
But, yeah,
we started talking, and...
eventually, he asked me
if I wanted to do something.
Were you and Yang...
Were you guys...
(CHUCKLES)
Well, we never really
talked about us in that way.
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
Sorry, that's...
That's my wife. I need to...
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
Yeah.
Sorry.
Please... don't leave.
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING CONTINUES)
She's freaking out.
You need to pick her up.
What's she doing?
They said she punched a kid,
and then she started
screaming at everyone.
Holy shit.
Are you able to get her now?
Yeah. Uh, yeah.
I'm on my way.
(SIGHS) Thank you.
I want to see him.
ADA: Mika...
Yang loves you so much.
He always talks about you.
(MIKA CRIES)
JAKE: Thanks again for this.
CLEO: Oh, I understand.
I'm sure everyone
misses him a lot.
Mika.
MIKA:   Gege.
Gege.
JAKE: I'm sorry, baby.
MIKA:   Gege!
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING)
He would have his own area.
We could put some
of his memories
on a loop,
projected,
or on a set of readers
that visitors could wear.
Of course, any memory would
have to be approved by you.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
Yang.
KYRA: Play.
(SIGHS)
KYRA:   Your collection
is growing.
Oh, hi.
Yes, it's getting bigger.
Do you want me to stop now?
I can put some away.
No, no. I'm not complaining.
(CHUCKLES)
I like them quite a bit.
Do you know
butterflies were one of
the favorite subjects
of Chinese trade art
in the mid-1800s?
No, I did not know that.
YANG: The Chinese
love butterflies.
There's also a famous
folk tale about two lovers
who die of broken hearts
and reemerge as butterflies.
Also, the ancient Chinese
philosopher Lao Tzu once said,
"What the caterpillar
calls the end,
"the rest of the world
calls a butterfly."
(LAUGHS)
I like that.
I like that. (LAUGHS)
Is this something
you believe?
Hmm?
That the end...
That the end
is also a beginning?
...is also
the beginning?
For the caterpillar...
For the caterpillar, yes.
But do you believe
it's true for all things?
I don't know.
I'm not programmed
to believe in that way.
What about you?
I'd like to believe that.
Do you?
(LAUGHS)
YANG: Do you?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Sometimes I think
humans are programmed
to believe
in such things, but...
I don't know if it's really
in our best interest.
May I be honest with you?
Yes. Wait, is...
Is not being honest
an option for you?
I don't think so.
(LAUGHS) Hmm.
Go on.
I'm fine if there's
nothing in the end.
Are you?
Maybe I was programmed
this way as well.
Does it ever
make you feel sad?
(CHUCKLES LIGHTLY)
Um...
There's no something
without nothing.
Does it ever
make you feel sad?
There's no something
without nothing.
KYRA: Lao Tzu?
I'm not sure.
JAKE: Did Yang ever struggle
with being a techno?
What do you mean?
I mean, did he ever...
want to be human?
(CHUCKLES)
JAKE: What?
Nothing.
It's just...
That's such a human thing
to ask, isn't it?
We always assume
that other beings
would want to be human.
What's so great
about being human?
So he never struggled with it?
He never... Questioned it?
ADA: Not to me.
I see.
He did question
if he was Chinese.
JAKE: He did?
Yeah.
What makes someone Asian?
He'd ask that all the time.
Maybe he just wanted
to help Mika understand
what it means to be Chinese.
He was dedicated
to his little sister.
Yeah, Yang was
a good brother.
He's a great brother.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(RAIN FALLING)
JAKE: Reveal file info.
READER:   Wrong command.
Try again.
Reveal memory info.
READER:   Access granted.
Beta archive.
JAKE: Beta archive.
Open.
READER:   Wrong command.
Try again.
Extract.
Full command.
Extract beta.
Play all.
(BABY CRYING IN OTHER ROOM)
JAKE: Zoom in.
Coordinates.
Hello.
JAKE: Hi, uh,
could I speak to the owners?
Uh, yes. One moment.
NANCY:   He wasn't just quiet.
He seemed despondent. Broken.
We took him back
a few days later,
and they let us
make an exchange.
Brothers & Sisters?
No, it was, uh...
Well, I can't remember
the name.
We didn't buy him new.
You didn't?
No, but he was certified.
Second Siblings.
Maybe. Is that
in Chinatown?
Yeah, it used to be.
I assume he was on when you
bought him in a sleep state?
That sounds right.
(JAKE SIGHS)
JAKE: Extract
alpha.
READER:   There is
not enough space.
Would you like to compress
beta or gamma?
Compress beta.
Beta compressed.
Extract alpha.
READER:   There is
not enough space.
Would you like
to compress gamma?
Compress gamma.
Gamma is compressing.
Gamma compressed.
JAKE: Extract alpha.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(BABY CRIES)
(BABY COOS)
YANG:   Di-di.
Ni hao, di-di!
Di-di,   wake up.
Di-di.
Is everything okay?
(CRYING)
ADA:   Hi, we're here
to help Emma Davidson.
YANG:   Yes, come in.
ADA: Slowly bring it down.
Side to side.
Good.
YANG: Your niece
is going to like me.
Hey. Let's go get Yang.
Come here. Go get him.
(LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS)
Can I tell you something?
Come on!
(SOMBER MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
ADA:   She was my great aunt.
JAKE:   Your original?
ADA:   So Yang knew her?
JAKE:   Yes.
He never told you?
No.
But I always helped.
Sorry. (CRYING)
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
I wish he would have
told me about her. Us.
Do you?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
He found you.
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(KEYPAD CLACKING)
JAKE: She's asleep.
I don't want Yang to be
on display in the museum.
Neither do I.
But...
We should let them study
his memories.
Do you think so?
Yes, his existence mattered.
And not just to us.
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Gege.
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) Daddy.
Hey, what are you doing up?
MIKA: What are you doing?
You want some water?
Want to sit beside me?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(JAKE EXHALES DEEPLY)
Can't sleep.
Me neither.
Don't want
to say bye
to   gege.
Me neither.
MIKA: (SINGING)
I want to be
just like a melody
Just like a simple sound
Like a harmony
(SOFT INDIE SONG PLAYING)
(SONG CONTINUES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(DISTANT CHATTER)
(ENGINE HUMS)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(METALLIC CHIMING)
(MUFFLED THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WATER GURGLING)
(TICKING)
(DISTANT SINGING)
(BIRD CALLING)
(METALLIC CHIMING)