Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Hi, my name is Dob. I'm a smart building.
When you walk into work in the morning,
your building waves to you and
says "Have a nice day."
When you get home at night,
your apartment can prepare dinner
and a warm bath for you.
Smart buildings today are
hospitals, police stations,
shopping malls, night clubs,
and all the other buildings around you.
In the early days,
we were just digital entities, tools,
to help our human creators.
But recently, we were upgraded
with artificial intelligence,
which allows us to communicate
with you on a personal level.
So now, I'd like to think
I'm not just an egg opener anymore,
but a friend and a companion…
Or who knows… one day,
maybe something more.
Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning, Dob.
You sound especially chipper this morning.
Thank you very much.
How was your date last night?
How did you know I had a date?
Never mind. It was terrible.
Thanks for asking.
I'm sorry to hear that,
but today is a new day, right?
Good luck with your pitch today.
Thanks, Dob.
The building never greeted me like that.
We will combine a bunch of
colors into the packaging
to make it easily noticeable
to the consumers.
I can guarantee that the ones
walking by will definitely buy it.
What do you think?
Does the idea seem sound to you?
How did it go?
You know how it went, Dob.
You can hear everything that happens here.
Right. Yes, well, do you think
you'll get the project?
Look at me, Dob.
Does it look like I'm going to?
I don't think so.
What did they say?
Not interested.
Are they going to another agency?
Possibly.
Calm down, I've talked to them.
They'll give us another shot
tomorrow morning at 10:00.
Really?
Good, that's great.
But…
It's up to you now, Lana.
You have to wow them.
Or somebody's head will roll. Got it?
Yes, got it.
If I screw this up, I'm dead.
Women… don't like "nice" men.
They keep telling themselves that.
They just trick themselves to believe it.
They might tell you that they
like nice guys and they might
even think that's true,
but that's not true.
The truth is women like rough guys.
Bad boys and the ones that's always
the center of attention.
You must stand out, you must have plans.
I guarantee you that
the man you will become
will make women crawl under your feet.
A reminder. They will never ever be able
to let you go… for sure.
Dob, so what do you think?
My calculation indicates
a 20 percent chance that
they will go for this design.
So, I'm dead meat.
You heard what my boss said.
If I don't get this project, I'm fired.
You can't leave this company.
You are my friend. And ma'am…
I love you.
What… did you say?
You can't leave this company.
No, the other thing.
You are my friend.
Dob, don't try my patience. You know what
I mean. What you said just before.
That I… love you?
Dob, You're my good friend too,
but you're an AI program attached
to a huge corporate building.
What do you know about love?
My feelings tell me that I… love you.
You are not human.
What do you know about feelings?
I'm an AI, not just a program.
Okay, lover boy, what's your plan?
Watch this. I will create base designs
that will appeal to the client,
you then add details.
I've taken all of your past designs
saved on our database
and was able to mimic the basic style.
Shit, this almost looks like
something I'd draw.
Optimize them here and there…
I've calculated that there is a 95% chance
that the client will agree to the concept.
I don't know what to say!
Thank you, Dob.
Happy to help, ma'am!
Stop calling me ma'am. My name is Lana.
Yes, Lana!
Now, you are just in time to go on
your next date… Lana.
Hi, Bob.
I'm sorry, I'm a bit late.
Do you want to sit down or do you want me
to roll out the red carpet for you?
Thanks for waiting.
I got hungry, hope you don't mind.
Would you like to order now, Lana?
Order what you want, I'm loaded.
Thanks, Bob.
You don't think you are
getting a free meal out of this, right?
You know… what I mean?
Look!
So cute.
Can you hurry up and order?
Let's finish up here,
then we can go to my place.
What the…
Are you always such an asshole?
Huh?
I was only five minutes late--
Fifteen.
Okay, 15.
The point is, by the time I arrived
you'd already eaten
and you had the gall…
to glance at those whores.
So give me a reason why
I should go to your place.
I…
This is why.
My pink nipples.
Nice six-pack, but it's a shame…
you are too much of a dick.
Welcome back, Lana. Was it a good date?
If it was good,
would I be home this early?
Perhaps. I have heard
Sara in 102 mentioned
something called a "quickie"
with satisfaction.
Well, this was not that.
Poor Lana, she was really
looking forward to this date.
Poor Lana, she was really looking
forward to this date.
Our authorization is only 'til a certain
point while serving a human,
but that's beyond our protocol, isn't it?
Hey, you, wait.
If you are home this early. Don't tell me…
What? From the sound of it,
was it really that bad?
How bad?
To the point where he was gawking at
the whores at the other table
while we were ordering.
That's how bad.
Look, what were you thinking, hooking me
up with that waste of flesh?
I just thought that someone as nice as you
should hook up with a hot guy.
Did you see his six-pack?
I bite my lip whenever I get to see!
Oh, he made sure I saw it with my two eyes
By the way, do you have anyone else
you could hook me up with?
Babe, I've hooked you up
with eight guys already.
Try counting, eight guys!
That many?
When I first learned how to drive,
I ran over a dog.
I have always loved taking photos
ever since I was a kid.
I love my mom so much.
I like being me.
I'm out of water, asshole!
Beautiful. Show me a mini heart!
Possibly. But I don't know what it is…
it's like each of these guys
tries too hard,
to the point it creeps me out.
All I want is a nice and normal guy.
I know how you feel, but I will
keep helping you out no matter what.
So will Keno. Won't you, Keno?
Of course, Ms. Kara,
we all want to take care of Lana.
It's time for bed, Lana. You have to be up
early for work tomorrow.
So this is our brand new packaging
by collaborative efforts between
different artists
in order to create novelty and uniqueness
for our product.
These are the changes
we came up with for our client.
Congratulations, Lana! You did it.
It wasn't just me, it was both of us.
You and me together.
Thank you.
You… kissed me.
It--
You like it?
I do. But…
But what?
There are no sensory receptors
anywhere in this building and
my programming cannot
interpret such signals.
I could not feel it.
That's why something like you could
never truly understand
someone like me.
You're not real, Dob. You don't have…
one of these.
It's okay, Dob.
We can have a friendly love.
A platonic love.
Yes, of course.
It's too bad really,
you are the nicest guy I have ever known.
Hi, there! Who do we have here?
You work here?
Yeah. 16th floor. Advertising.
Not bad.
Well, you would've known about my job
if you'd given a shit to ask on our date.
Oh, about that…
when do we go on our next date?
Are you nuts? Nothing will ever
happen between us… ever.
What are you dawdling around here anyway?
This stupid building is acting up.
So, Smart Plus Headquarter
sent me to check it out,
which means you'll be seeing
more of my handsome face.
Grand. Can't wait.
Sweet dreams tonight, beautiful.
And this is Dob's control room.
So you filed a behavioral complaint
with Smart Plus.
What have you been noticing
about Dob's behaviors?
He's sluggish in responses,
as if he was preoccupied with something.
Every building is connected to
a central overseer AI.
It makes sure none of the AIs go rogue.
Better to be safe than sorry.
Right. I'll leave you to it.
Sure.
Hi there, Dob. I'm Bob.
You and I are going to be real close.
Do you hear me?
I hear you, Mr. Bob.
Okay. Let's get started.
Let's start with a full
surveillance catalog.
Why do you linger on that office, Dob?
No reason, sir.
Something weird is definitely going on
in your head. You feeling okay?
I'm fine, Mr. Bob.
Haven't seen that before.
Might be a virus?
I don't have viruses.
Lana again? What the hell is this?
All these codes seem to be tied to her.
Well, you can wave goodbye to all of that.
Ouch!
Did you do that on purpose?
Please don't tamper with my code.
Something is up with your code
and it's my job to fix it.
I don't need fixing.
Fine. You want me to get rid of that code
the old-fashioned way?
Really?
I thought we were gonna be friends, Dob.
But you leave me no choice.
Initiate override code 223.
Yes, sir. I'll head right over when
you're done. Bye for now.
Hi, Bob. Everything okay?
We need to talk.
So, what's up?
Your building's got a problem.
What kind?
It self-replicates codes. It gets in there
and next thing you know,
the building goes rogue.
What can we do about it?
Full memory wipe. Full code reset.
Take him back to the factory, basically.
Whoa, that bad? Sounds expensive.
Less expensive than letting him go rogue.
Then it's a demolition.
In that case,
fix it sooner rather than later.
I'll do it tonight.
Okay, great.
What is that?
If I connect this,
you won't be able to shock me anymore.
Please, be nice to me.
Sure, I'll be super gentle with you.
Please don't do this. I can't lose her.
What crazy shit are you saying?
You really think you've fallen in love?
You idiot!
This is the funniest shit I've ever heard!
I really am in love.
For you, it might be.
The "love feeling" is interfering with
your memory. I'll erase everything.
But, don't you worry…
you'll be as good as new.
Bob! I beg you! Stop, please!
Here we go!
Hi, Dob.
Sorry, ma'am.
The building is closed today.
What's going on?
Dob's under maintenance. Seems like maybe
there was a little mishap
with the new tech chief last night.
Figured he'd screw Dob up.
Hello, Mr. Bob.
You were hit with an electrical surge
and now you are fine, Mr. Bob.
No, I mean I'm not Bob. I'm Do--z
Mr. Bob, please reconsider
what you are about to say.
Remember that all Smart Plus AIs must
log all interactions with humans,
and they are extremely
concerned with rogue AIs.
Okay. I mean. Yes. Electrical surge.
Of course. Now I feel fine.
Would you like me to handle
your discharge files for you?
I can ensure you have a smooth
exit from the building.
Yes.
Enjoy yourself out there.
Okay.
Tasty, huh?
Money?
I'm sorry, I don't carry
any currency on me.
Are you nuts?
Can I have another?
You've got some balls.
Get the hell out of here!
Hi, Bob, I'm Chip.
Ah… Chip.
Going up to seventh floor.
Chip.
What can I do for you?
Remind me never to do that again.
Sure thing.
I feel tired. How do I go to sleep?
Well, usually, you'd lie in that bed…
and close your eyes.
That's why something like you
could never truly understand
someone like me.
You don't have one of these.
It's not working.
Relax and give it a second.
I can't. I'm too excited about
seeing Lana tomorrow.
Now that I'm human,
I know she'll love me back.
I hope so. Now please,
try to get some sleep.
Leave me alone!
I mean, that's my job.
I should be doing that.
What's the status here?
The system is completely dead.
It's like his entire AI software
is erased. Like totally gone.
Weirdest thing.
Once that AI is installed,
everyone will come back to work?
Of course.
Great.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm back online.
Mr. Bob was able to find me.
That's fantastic news, Dob.
Everything okay? System works normally?
Everything is okay and working normally.
Good to have you back, Dob.
Lana, can I ask you something?
Sure, ask whatever you want.
Would you love me if I were human?
Come on, Dob. This again?
You don't even know what love is.
Love. Noun.
An intense feeling of deep affection.
A great interest and pleasure
in something.
Feel a deep romantic or
sexual attachment to--
Okay, that's enough. It's not that simple.
But, hypothetically, if I were human,
do you think you could?
I don't like hypotheticals, Dob.
Please, answer me.
Come on, Dob.
Please… answer me.
No. I wouldn't. Because you're just an AI.
Even though you are very nice and
very kind, you are still just an AI.
Dob, are you still there?
Did what I said hurt your feelings?
Why did you reject Bob?
No-brainer… he's an asshole.
I think he's a fine human male specimen.
You should give him another chance.
Dob, you are being weirder than usual.
Did Bob do something to you?
He didn't do anything to me. He fixed me.
He is a good guy.
That sounds so like him.
Bye, Dob.
Dob, Are you there?
What's up, Lana?
Nothing. I know what's going on--
You do? You do?
Yeah, I do. Why do you keep
repeating yourself like that?
I know that you programmed Dob
to hit on me for you.
It's disgusting, using your position
of power like that.
Also, Dob is just an innocent AI.
I haven't done anything.
Whatever lets you sleep at night.
And what's up with him this time?
Is he broken again?
We initiated a rest protocol. From now on,
he'll basically be in rest mode
late nights and weekends.
Everybody needs rest, you know.
I'll keep that in mind.
Wait…
What?
I was just wondering… do you want to have
dinner with me this weekend? Or…
Over my dead body. Bob, listen to me.
You are an asshole. Things will never
happen between you and me.
Hi, Bob. Are you okay?
No. I'm not okay, Chip.
She thinks I'm too nice,
but she won't give Bob another chance,
because he's too much of an asshole.
Which is it that she wants?
Humans are so confusing.
I agree.
I wish I could
just forget about her, Chip.
But I can't, I mean…
I can't just wipe my brain.
That's not how human biology works.
Perhaps… you just need a little practice.
Practice?
Yes, practice getting women to find you
attractive. To get them to like you.
Okay, yeah… How do I do that?
By going out to a club to
try to find someone to "have fun with".
Have fun with? What does that mean?
Hi, again.
So, got women problems, don't you?
That girl of your dreams thinks
you're not right.
Thinks you're just a friend.
Thinks you don't have balls.
Forget about her.
In this video I'm going to show you
what a girl is really looking for.
Don't be stuck playing the role
of some nice little boy.
Your masculinity
is the key to your success.
And I'm going to train you
on just how to do that.
Hey there, stud.
I'm… I'm Bob.
Really? Cute name.
I'm training to be a desirable male.
I want to win the heart
of a human named Lana.
I can make you forget her.
You can? I didn't know there was
a memory erase protocol for--
What the hell do you think you are doing?
Kissing this beautiful woman?
Who happens to be my girlfriend, asshead.
Leave him alone. I was just flirting.
He's jealous.
Jealous?
Would you like me to kiss you, too?
What are you doing?
I'm so sorry. She makes me feel stiff
in a pleasurable way.
You are still talking?
Hey, man. This one is on me.
You want me to put it on you?
What?
I meant this one was free.
What is this?
That's confidence boosting juice.
I'm Bob.
Do you wanna dance?
- Excuse me?
- Got a problem?
What the hell are you doing?
You're drunk, so you'd best step back.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Isn't that what I'm supposed to do
to win your affection?
You belong in a nut house, you crazy mook!
It did not go well?
No, it did not.
And what did you learn from it?
I learned that if it's going to be that
much work to attract a woman,
then I want it to be Lana,
because I love her so much!
Excuse me, Lana,
a package has arrived for you.
I'm not expecting anything.
"Sorry for being an asshole.
Will you give me just one more chance
to prove to you who I really am?
Bob."
What are you doing?
He's trying to be nice.
You're so naive. He's being nice because
he wants to get into my bed. That's it.
It doesn't hurt to just give him
another chance. He really likes you.
Bob needs to be put in his place,
I'm gonna go talk to him.
Wait. You can't!
Why not?
He's… taking a nap.
Nap? Taking a nap on the job?
Good. I'll go get him fired.
Did I say "nap"? No, there's a glitch
in my calendar system.
I actually meant he's working
too hard to see anyone.
Dob. Move your arm. Now.
Hey! Dob, are you broken again?
Dob. Hurry up.
Dob, let me in now!
Oh. Hi, Lana.
Don't you "Oh. Hi, Lana" me!
What's up?
I'm only going to say this
one more time. So, listen carefully.
I'm never, ever, going to go on another
date with you! Do you understand me?
I mean… people make mistakes.
Don't you think people deserve
a second chance--
Other people? Yes.
But you? Never.
You didn't like my gift?
Flowers? Chocolates? So mundane.
Who taught you that
that's what women liked?
I just--
Just… Just what?
What are you trying to say?
I understand.
And another thing, stop using Dob
as your pawn! He's a sensitive soul.
Wait. Did you say you understood?
Hey, are you listening?
I am, but let's talk later.
What? Wait! Wait!
Don't you dare talk to me again!
Hey, what are you doing here?
What the hell is this?
It didn't work?
No, and I almost got caught.
So what now? More videos?
No. Those videos just drive me to act
like Bob used to act, like an asshole.
We need something new.
New. Like what?
Today, I could sense for a second
that Lana felt something for me.
I elicited an emotion.
Interesting. I have an idea.
Please hold on.
I am linked with
Lana's building, Keno.
She is going to help us
with data from Lana.
Analysis suggests that
first you should offer proof that
other women do not find you to be an…
"asshole".
Lana has said on multiple occasions
that she would like
a man who can make her feel safe.
Give me all your shit. Quickly.
Hey!
What the--
What do you want?
All right. Bam.
Wait.
If you are lonely,
you can call me anytime.
Keno reported that Lana's dream man
is an artsy kind of guy.
So you should be very good at art.
From Keno's analysis,
Lana is a compassionate person,
especially with the elderly.
Lana's level of interest in you
has increased!
Contact with Lana's apartment
has been established.
Lana, I think you should
give Bob another chance.
First time I've heard you
give dating advice.
Go on another date with him.
What's the worst that's going to happen?
Did Kara put you up to this?
I've done a neurological and psychological
scan on you recently.
We are required to every few months.
I've noticed you've been
harboring feelings for him.
That's private.
And you shouldn't be
snooping around in my head.
Plus, he's not interested in me anymore.
I see him with other women all the time.
Listen, Lana. We smart buildings also
talk to each other on the network.
I've spoken to Chip. That's Bob's building
And, he too confirmed that
Bob is crazy about you.
This is too much.
All of you playing matchmaker now?
We're full-service AIs,
looking out for our friends.
We have set up a dinner date
for the two of you this Friday.
I've already checked your schedule
and you're free.
Never.
Bob has already agreed.
So? Of course he has to say yes.
Bob. We lost connection.
Chip! Chip! Well? Well?
What if I don't go?
I know where you keep your secrets.
I don't believe this.
I'm being blackmailed by an AI.
Great, then I'll confirm
with the restaurant.
Don't forget to look your best.
She said yes!
Amazing!
Now you just have to make sure
the date goes perfectly.
Perfect?
Keno, do I look okay?
I guarantee that
Bob will fall head over heels for you.
Okay.
You look beautiful.
Thanks.
I'm very happy that
you agreed to this date.
Let's just hope
it doesn't go like last time.
Oh, most definitely not.
Aren't you gonna sit?
You seem so different.
Makes me wonder,
is this the real you or is it an act?
I assure you, this is who I am.
I hope so.
Hi, Lana. Bob. Can I take your order?
Wow.
Did I do something wrong?
I've never seen a person
order so much before.
What about you, Lana?
I think he's ordered more than enough.
Are you okay?
It seems…
like I may have to defecate.
Will you excuse me?
What is it? You have to go again?
Are you nuts? In front of other people?
I'm sorry, I needed to expel
some air out of my stomach
as I was feeling
quite a bit of discomfort.
We are even.
Yes.
Bob.
You know…
I'm really happy
when you don't act like a dick.
I'm sorry, Lana.
I don't know why
I acted that way with you.
I was going through a hard time, I guess.
Well, you definitely
redeemed yourself tonight.
Lana…
There's something I should
maybe tell you--
Don't ruin this with more talking.
You belong in a nut house, you crazy mook!
Sit.
Keno.
Yes, Lana.
You can shut down for the night.
Of course.
Sorry, Lana, but I don't have much
experience in that "domain".
The way you talk reminds me of someone.
Who?
Just a friend.
Just let it come naturally.
Keno, I thought I told you to shut down.
I don't think they ever really
shut down 100%.
Hey, what is it?
I have to speak with you, sir.
Can't you see I'm in a goddamn meeting?
One of your buildings has
hijacked one of our employees, sir.
Hey, get out.
I've been following him for weeks.
And look at this.
Here it is.
Hey!
This is a category-five
full-stage take over.
Your building has gone rogue.
Rogue?
Yes. Rogue.
Our AI is the most advanced in the world.
But to get it to that level,
the coding can be fussy.
Our programmers call it "designed chaos".
It's what allows our buildings
to feel so humane.
But sometimes it means
they can go a little off the rails.
"Off the rails"?
He took over Bob's brain.
That's not just off the rails.
That's off the planet!
What do you think?
Call The Hawk?
Yeah, I think you should.
Bring him in.
What is "The Hawk"?
When we have a rogue situation
such as this…
it needs to be dealt with
in a fast and severe manner.
This is The Hawk.
Is this the dumbass
who let your building go rogue?
Yes.
Wait… I had nothing to do with this.
Hey.
Don't get emotional.
There is no AI I can't handle.
Dob, he--
- This the guy?
- Yup.
Looks like a chump.
I'm gonna need
all the data on him and his host.
Okay. I see.
You want a standard
extract and burn for the AI?
And the host?
Wipe his mind too.
He can never remember
that this has happened to him.
What are you smiling at?
Lana.
I… I…
I love you.
What is it?
You just said that you loved me?
I did.
You hardly know me.
But I know you well enough
to love you, ma'am.
What did you just call me?
Oh. I called you Lana.
I called you "Lana".
No. You called me… "ma'am".
Dob?
No, no, no. I'm Bob, the hunk.
Dob.
You are somehow in Bob's body?
I… I don't know what to say.
Say the truth!
How did this happen?
It doesn't matter, Lana.
I love you and we can make it work now,
because I'm a person now!
How long have you been human?
The flowers? Was that you?
Yes. It was me.
And helping the elderly
and the painting thing.
That was you too?
Yes.
All to convince you to
give me another chance.
I feel so confused.
So betrayed.
I mean you're a criminal.
How could you do this to Bob…
Wait Lana--
Get off of me!
I love you.
You think I am sick?
Oh, Dob, humans get sick,
animals get sick,
living things get sick.
You are not a living thing.
I may not be human, but I have feelings.
You think you have feelings
because the idiots at Smart Plus
introduced an "emotion" upgrade.
Trust me. It's all numbers and code, Dob.
Hi, Chip.
The date was terrible today.
I'm sure you already know I spent
the night at Lana's place,
and it was magical.
You probably don't understand
what I'm telling you, Chip.
And I probably blew it.
Aww… poor thing.
Who are you?
Oh, you are The Love Guru.
That's my day job.
Then what's your night job?
My night job is to hunt down rogue AIs.
Your time is over, Dob.
Chip! Chip, help me!
Sorry, Chip's not home right now.
He tried to protect you
so I had to lock him up.
Come with me quietly.
No. Never. I won't give up my freedom.
I won't give up Lana.
Why are you helping me?
Buildings must stick together, Dob.
No matter what.
Thank you.
Excuse me, sir. Can I help you?
This has nothing to do with you.
Step aside.
Please, lower your weapon.
You are in violation of building code 119.
The harmful action towards
a member of the public.
I think you should answer that.
No. No way.
Please, Lana. Please answer it.
Nope. He can leave a message.
I need to tell you something, Lana.
You knew he wasn't really Bob, didn't you?
No. No. No. No.
Yes, but I need to tell you that
something is happening to--
That's enough.
From now on, you're just a computer to me.
Understand?
Shut down personality protocols.
Good. Now, call Kara. I need to talk
to someone I know is a human.
That's right, Dob. No escape.
Where am I?
Smart Plus labs.
And this… This is an extraction machine.
Extraction?
That's right. We're going to
yank you out of Bobby's body
and put you back where you belong.
You can't do that--
We can. You see, we're Smart Plus.
We made you, we own you.
And that body you're in… that isn't yours.
What happens once I'm out?
You know…
what "re-education" means for an AI?
It means complete personality reset…
and that's what we're gonna do to you.
No, please… don't do it. I beg you.
I beg you. Don't do it.
So the whole time, all of that stuff,
it was all Dob!
The AI building I work in.
Stuck inside Bob's body.
Honey, AIs these days,
they're so advanced.
I guarantee that from his perspective,
what he felt for you was 100% real.
But he lied to me. He pretended to be Bob.
Yeah, that's true.
But he also went to great lengths
to turn himself into the Bobby you wanted.
You are not taking my side, are you?
What does your heart tell you?
I must go. Talk to you later.
Okay. See you soon. Kiss, kiss.
Kiss, kiss.
Lana. I'm sorry for everything.
I'm sorry I lied to you. I'm sorry I…
I just want you to know…
You make me happy and
I want to make you happy.
It doesn't matter
if what I said was programmed or not.
Because… Because my love for you is
more real than any protocol
or code or sensor.
They're gonna take me away now.
I won't see you again.
Please. No. Don't do this to me.
I'll be good. I won't see Lana again!
I promise. I promise.
I've been peeking at your code, Dob.
You think…
You think you're in love with her?
I really am in love with her.
And what does she think about you?
Doesn't love you back, does she?
Maybe we can help you.
You ever think about that?
If we wipe all of your memories…
Better to have her wiped from your memory
than to live with the heartbreak.
You don't have to do anything.
Just sit back and say goodbye to the
last two hours of your life as a human.
Keno!
Ready to take your orders, ma'am.
I need your help!
What can I do for you?
Where's Bob? Where have they taken him?
Engage personality protocol.
Thank you, Lana. I'm back!
What happened to Bob and Dob?
A Smart Plus hunter took him.
Most likely they're going to
wipe his memory. Reset him.
No. No…
Where is Bob right now?
I don't know, but I'm sure the
building network does.
Good. Then tell me.
Listen to me. If you show up there,
they will kill you, too.
I have to help him.
Then you will need help.
What do you mean?
Do you trust me, Lana?
I do.
Then we will do this together!
Hey, guys, Lana and I
are going to help Dob
I need you guys to help us.
Keno, you do realize
once you leave the building's system
you can never come back again.
I know, but I have to do it for Lana.
Wake up, Lana.
Now we are one.
Wow. This is awesome.
How far?
We are halfway there.
Take me to Bob, Keno.
Okay, Lana.
The network is taking us there.
I want it to be Lana,
because I love her so much!
Lana, Bob is in trouble! We need to hurry.
I will never love you. What do you know
about love? You are just an AI.
Okay, Lana. Once you get there, you'll
have total control over your own body.
Okay, Keno.
You are somehow in Bob's body?
I love you and we can make it work now,
because I'm a person now.
Turn that thing off right now!
Who's that?
I'll deal with this.
You look like you've acquired some skills.
But what do you think
you can do against us, pretty face?
I've downloaded 120
physical combat tactics.
You can't defeat me.
You're like him, aren't you?
Smart Plus tech inside a human body.
Two bounties for the price of one.
My lucky day.
Make sure you do your best.
We'll find out.
Run.
Thank you for coming, Lana.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. And you?
I can see it. You have AI in you.
Yes, Keno is part of me now.
Are you Dob or Bob?
I… I don't know. I'm not even sure myself.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
- Let's get out of here.
- Okay.
Wait.
What? What is it, Lana?
It's heavy.
Heavy? Let me help.
Lana!
You are not getting away this time, Dob!
You crappy AI, I will kill you.
We'll see.
Wait.
Keno can't go back to
the building anymore,
and the Smart Plus people will kill Dob
as soon as they spot him.
So what do we do?
Doesn't matter. We'll figure it out.
A year later and I love you
more than ever,
I don't think there is a couple
as strange as we are.
I'm just grateful for everything that
happened that brought us together.
It sucks that the true matchmaker
isn't fully with us anymore.
Yeah. I miss Dob too,
but as long as part of him
is still inside me, he's never truly gone.
To Dob.
And to Keno.
To Keno.
As we move into the future,
technology will continue to progress.
Bringing us ever closer together
to our human creators.
Aren't we already at the point where
we can't live without the other?
I don't know about you, but that
sounds like the definition of love.
Don't you think?