Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
752 billion lost
as markets crashed...
15-year bull market
ends in a catastrophic crash,
threatening financial
institutions around the world.
Financial markets dropped
2500 points in one day,
- the largest...
- Experts predict
we haven't seen the worst yet
with looming failures
across multiple...
Oil prices plummet
with the price of crude
dropping over 34 percent.
Big Three revenue
projections continue to fall
as the market becomes
increasingly unstable.
Bank failures
are on the rise
as losses continue to mount.
Debt ceiling
standoff, U.S. rating AA.
MerrickStern,
last man standing.
Will they be able to survive?
President urges
calm as inflation rates drop...
Local law enforcement
has been overwhelmed
by the crowds teeming
into the streets.
Northern and southern
U.S. borders are closed
as panic sets in
among many citizens.
...supply chains disrupted,
food shortages looming,
and in major cities,
store shelves are empty and...
Gun sales rise
to an all-time high
as citizens are prepared to do
anything to protect themselves.
Unstable markets
fuel fear of a global crash
as nations around the world...
National Guard
prepares for unrest
- as people...
- This unprecedented turn of events
has left Americans wondering,
"Is this the next
Great Depression?"
Chickens are social animals.
They establish a pecking order
early on.
It's a natural process they have
to work out among themselves.
The stronger ones eat first,
mate first
and bully their rivals,
while the weaker ones
have to wait their turn.
Once the order is set,
it is very hard to change it...
unless something unexpected
turns it all upside down.
Can you make your brother
some breakfast, please?
- He ate.
- When?
Before you were awake.
You have a class?
One early.
You were supposed to be
with Mia.
I'll be here. She'll be here.
We'll be here.
- I can handle it.
- Kai! Come on.
I have to go
to the market.
Didn't you order
some stuff online?
I tried. It's on backorder.
I have to get Kai a new pen
and... and toilet tissue.
I don't have many needs,
but I do have my dignity.
Come on, Mom.
All right.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Greg.
Hey, Mia.
Show schedule.
Showing schedule.
- Wall Street is...
- Looks like protests
are turning to violence again
for a third night.
Shit.
As you can see
unfolding before our eyes,
this unrest is continuing
late into the night
as many local shop owners
have abandoned
their storefronts.
If you haven't seen,
any real attempt to safely...
You know, we've seen
this path of destruction
sweeping in from the northeast
corner of the state
as early as last Wednesday,
and it's only picking up
momentum as it heads south.
And as you can see right here...
- I... I need to...
- Excuse me.
I really need to.
Please hurry.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I thought
it opened at 8:00.
- The pharmacist never showed.
- I'm a doctor.
Can I just, you know, go back
there and get what I need?
He's the only one with the key.
- Hmm.
- We're about to close up in a few minutes.
- Closing?
- Haven't you seen the news?
No. I...
This unrest is
continuing late into the night
- as many local shop owners...
- Oh.
One minute.
Are you okay?
Everything's gone.
I... I don't know
what I'm supposed to do.
You're about ready?
About.
Uh. Come. Come with me.
Take this. And this.
That's good. No.
And these.
That's really all you need.
- Any nausea?
- It's random.
Yeah. Can come back sometimes.
Take this.
Slice it up, put a little
honey and lemon, hot water.
I'm Helen.
Amber.
I don't think I've seen
you around here before.
Oh, my family just moved out
here a few months ago.
Well, you picked
a heck of a time.
Yeah.
Uh. You know,
this is a panic driven drop.
Much like the Great Depression,
this is not a monetary...
Looks like that's
your college tuition.
Okay, my girl. All right.
Are you interrupting me, huh?
Oh, what's going on?
You okay?
Hey, sweetie.
You have to come get us, Dad.
- They're ending classes early.
- Why? What's going on?
Something's going on
in the city.
- Everybody's leaving.
- Why?
It's bad. Everything they said
on the news,
they think it's happening.
Oh, okay, uh...
Shit.
All right, let me, um,
call your mom.
You see this?
It's picked over.
Nothing left.
I'm sorry,
but we're about to close up.
Hey,
your mom's not answering.
I'm with the baby. Where's Kai?
He's with me. He's fine.
Sit tight.
I'm an OB, by the way.
Uh. You know the farmhouse
on Shingle Mill Road?
Oh, I think we're neighbors.
You know where to find me.
If you need me.
Where's Greg?
- Famous last words.
- All right. Seriously?
Not time for jokes.
I'm just standing out here
in the fucking wilderness.
We didn't move
to the middle of nowhere
so I could wonder where he is.
Don't be mad at me.
I'm on your side.
I mean, I love Greg too,
but standing out here
with your scary-ass chickens.
- Did you call him?
- I called you. Several times. Yeah, me.
Swipe. Me, me.
Okay, great.
That's what I'm saying.
You're always the worst
with your fucking phone.
I'll take the bag.
Nephew!
Oh, Kai.
You outta school? Huh? Hmm?
What's that mean, chicken time?
Where were you?
What?
Wow, the air is thick
around here, huh?
I'm saying
it's worth looking at.
And they have a class.
Excuse me, Jake.
I am sorry to interrupt.
We do have breaking news.
Hey, Merrick-Stern
just went down.
Guessing that's bad, huh?
They're one of the biggest
brokers on Wall Street.
- It's worse than bad.
- If you got money.
Hey, you're not on Wall Street.
Just unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
I... I've just
never seen a collapse this bad.
2008 was nothing
compared to this.
Oh, Stan,
take a look at these...
Is he okay?
Bird got out.
What is it? Huh?
What's wrong?
What's...
Fuck!
- Greg.
- The fence is electric.
- Since when?
- Now, see, that's some bullshit.
All right, come on. I want you to move away.
I'll get him.
All right, everybody
stay away from the fence.
You need to go talk to them.
Them who?
Uh, the assholes
who hotwired your fence.
You don't know who lives there?
The seller said they were quiet.
They never met him before.
Yeah, they're obviously
fucking crazy.
Don't worry, he'll be back.
He'll fly back in.
Look at me.
Sweetie, you'll see.
He'll be back.
All right, come on.
He'll be back. Come on.
- What you see coming in?
- Nothing strange.
I spent half the trip
trying to stay out of the way
of people who were driving
like maniacs.
And the other half of the trip
wondering why these fools
acting like it's their first
time ever hearing bad news.
I'm scared.
How are we gonna get
what we need?
Babe.
People overreact.
They did the same thing
when COVID hit.
I got a text, what, 20 times
that the president
was gonna declare martial law
and the country was gonna go
into lockdown.
And the country
went into lockdown.
The country went to "Stay home."
Well, since we all gonna
be stuck at home,
maybe you can get our neighbor
to cut off his fence.
You ain't got but one
neighbor for ten or 15 miles.
You might want to know
who they are.
Huh. Well, who's your neighbor?
Oh,
there's a lot of people
live next door to me, Mr. Shade.
I thought we were friends.
Hmm.
Look, I will drive up the road
to see if I can find
the entrance to the property.
Entrance? How big is the place?
I don't know.
Dry your hands before
you get electrocuted again.
Ah, yeah.
Oh, shall we, me chérie?
I'm nursing.
And you're pumping.
Get over yourself.
One glass won't hurt.
Oh,
talking about a curfew.
Mom, can I watch TV
in your room?
Stay off my bed.
I don't want to be on your bed.
Just thinking about
what goes on there. Ugh.
Nothing goes on there.
Which is why you want me
to stay off of it.
Nothing goes on there?
- Is that your business?
- It's not my business.
I don't want it to be.
Who else am I supposed
to talk to?
Think it rhymes with therapist.
He's the one who should...
Oh, God, see.
You got your man back.
That's the win.
Plus you got your baby.
I thought I was done.
The minute you stop trying is
when you actually get pregnant.
- Karma.
- Hmm. Sex.
I wish.
He doesn't want it?
- He tries.
- Oh. He's here, Helen.
It was an affair,
not the Titanic.
If you want your man,
you better act like it.
Why is it on me?
You want to be happy,
so get happy.
You want to trade?
I want the man I married.
I want my husband.
No, you want a time machine.
You set these impossible
expectations
that no one can keep,
including yourself.
When it comes time for you
to do one little thing...
- It's not little.
- Well, then I'm happy for you.
'Cause size matters.
You better use it or lose it.
- I hate you.
- You love me.
You just don't know
how to show it.
Did you talk to him?
All I saw was a rundown stable
and an old trailer.
- There's nobody there.
- They just issued a curfew.
Yeah, I should probably go.
No, stay.
- I mean, you've been drinking.
- I've been sipping and it's fine.
It's only 30 minutes away.
I'll be at my house
before you guys
turn off all these lights.
Okay, you want me
to take you home?
I'll bring your car
in the morning.
No. Nothing exciting
happens on my street
except finding a place to park.
And besides, I have a life.
Call me tomorrow.
Okay. Bye!
...secretary is saying
with the market's recent
collapse, that we can expect...
You see him?
Ah, he's gone.
I can't imagine he's
gonna last very long out there.
Maybe. Maybe not.
I mean, if you think about it,
it's weird
how long a bird survives
inside of a coop.
Is that what
you're gonna tell Kai?
His bird is better off
without him?
I don't know
who that guy thinks he is.
All the schools are shut down.
There's a bunch of armored cars
in the city.
I need you to check on Brooke.
I called, I text.
She hasn't answered me.
It's getting bad out there.
I don't think I should
leave you guys alone.
We'll be fine.
...unemployment
as high as it is.
Uh. William Calverts here
with a little update.
To your point, you know,
who are they gonna pay
these loans back to?
It would take a major disruption
to prompt a suspension
of civil liberties.
General Brennan,
is Senator McKinney's
assessment optimistic?
The nation is essentially
under martial law right now.
In the midst
of ever rising chaos,
we're gonna go to Lisa
on the street
to give us more details.
What do you see out there?
Jan, Ken,
I'm out here on the streets.
I am trying to get
to some shelter here.
Uh, there are shots
being fired...
Hey!
I don't, I don't know
where they're coming from.
Greg?
Brooke.
Thank God. We've been calling
you all morning. Come on.
They're sending in
the National Guard.
Okay, I'm coming.
Kai. We're not going
to school today. Come on.
Oh, my God.
You okay? Okay, stay right here.
I'm gonna go get Mom,
all right? Mom.
Mom. Kai got stung by a bee.
Have you seen his pen?
- No.
- Go look in your father's office.
Hey.
- Kai got stung by a bee. We need a pen.
- Get out of the way!
I thought you got one.
Just tell Brooke to bring hers.
All right.
Hey. Kai got stung by a bee.
Do you have a pen?
Yeah, I think so. Uh,
just let me go back upstairs.
Can you look in my car
for my phone? I can't find it.
Mom. I found it.
Hey, here. Here.
- Did you find my phone?
- No.
- Fuck.
- Look, we got to go.
Give me a second.
I need my phone.
Brooke, we got to go!
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
Just let me look one more time.
Come on, Brooke.
Geez.
What are these guys doing?
Are they jacking cars?
- Come on. Look for a ride.
- Here we go.
No. No. No, no. Shit.
Shit!
Brooke!
- No, leave me alone.
- Come on, open it!
Hey!
Brooke!
Where's Brooke?
I got you.
Greg. You haven't
answered my question.
How could you just leave?
Babe, I tried.
Yeah, that's what you do.
Helen.
- Listen, I...
- When are you gonna do more than fucking try, Greg?
You always try.
The man had a gun.
- So?
- So, you want me dead? I got... I got kids.
I got you!
Oh. So now
you're worried about me?
- Oh. Don't even...
- Don't what?
Don't cry? Don't hurt?
Don't scream?
What do you not want me to do
so you can fucking feel good
for yourself?
- There ain't nothing...
- Just tell me. Tell me what it is. I'll do it.
There's nothing... There was
nothing else for me to do.
I know.
You tried.
...in an
attempt to quell the violence,
they have set up checkpoints,
and at this point,
no one is being allowed
in or out of the city
after another night of violence
has left at least 60...
Can I help you?
You Helen?
Yes.
Ma'am, could you come with me,
please?
And who are you?
Amber sent me.
She met you at the store.
Is she okay?
I just need you to come
if you can.
- Let me grab my bag.
- Wait, come where?
I'm sorry, sir. Just her.
No, she's not going anywhere.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not.
Be right back.
Wait.
Put these on.
No.
- I have to.
- Uh-uh.
I'm not letting my wife
walk off blindfolded
- with some white boy.
- Greg. That's not necessary.
Look, man, we can leave.
Well, this way.
To your right.
Told you to blindfold them.
They wouldn't put 'em on.
I didn't ask for you.
Matty, take her in.
Yes, sir.
Hey. Have a seat.
Okay.
Do you have any cramps or
contractions with the bleeding?
No.
Matty! Come here.
- There it is. That's the heartbeat.
- Oh.
Very good.
How about that? All right.
I'm going to have to
examine you.
All right.
How old are you?
- What is it?
- Well,
it looks like
a subchorionic hematoma.
And she's gonna need
attention for it
if it gets worse.
What do you mean worse?
Well, it might be a sign
of placental abruption.
Might.
Might not.
Well, is that how you want
to handle this?
Next time, you come alone.
That's not your decision.
She can either come alone
or leave alone.
Okay? Your choice.
My son got a shock
when he touched the fence
up against our property.
Fence is there for a reason.
Maybe you should put a sign up.
Maybe you should keep
an eye on your boy.
- Matty, take 'em home.
- Yes, sir.
The kitchen
looks pretty stocked.
Just grab all the food.
Find anything else of value.
All right, man.
Go get the baby. Yeah.
Okay. Come on.
Take this one.
Yo, I found two more.
Right here.
That's it.
Grab 'em both.
All right, I got one.
Shit. Upstairs. Go.
I don't know.
Come on.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go.
The kids are in the car.
Helen...
what are we doing?
We have no food.
They took everything.
We have to go.
You have to leave.
We need your help.
Can't help you.
- Can't or you won't?
- You're trespassing.
Somebody broke into our house.
And how do I know
you're not bringing them
- to break into mine?
- We would never do that.
How do I know that?
You help us, we can help you.
I don't need you.
What about Amber?
You give a damn about that baby,
she's gonna need somebody.
So if you're saying you'll
take your chances, then...
we'll take ours.
- Let's go.
- Matty.
I'm here.
How many are they?
The two you saw,
plus three younger.
One's a baby.
Put the car in the stable.
All right.
Thank you.
How old are you?
- His name is Kai. He is about...
- He can speak for himself.
He doesn't talk.
But you do.
Zoe. Mind your manners.
Can she use your bathroom?
Matty.
Follow me.
Sub chorionic hematoma?
"These blood clots
are rarely problematic."
"They usually result
in a onetime bleed
once the clot has passed."
The bleeding stopped.
- You think I'm stupid?
- I don't.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
- You lied to me.
- I was being cautious.
The only reason you're here
is because she wants you.
You lie to me again,
we got nothing else
to talk about.
Let's go get your stuff.
Go.
- I'll check on Zoe.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Protect your mom.
- Did you change your pad?
- Yeah.
Where'd you put it?
- In the trash can. Why?
- Okay, good.
No, never mind.
- Go check your brother.
- Okay.
She has to stay on bed
rest. She's still bleeding.
Is the baby in trouble?
Could be.
Something is aggravating
her condition.
- What has she been doing?
- Nothing out of the ordinary.
Besides living in a bunker.
Let her stay, Winter.
Please? Just...
Okay, just... just
give me a second.
All right, hon?
With third trimester bleeding,
the chances of her having
a complicated delivery
are significantly higher.
You know, we could be dealing
with placenta previa,
placental abruption,
incompetent cervix.
There's really no way to know,
given the lack of prenatal care.
I've been taking care
of this family for years.
Yeah, well, this baby is coming.
She going to need help.
You're going to need help.
I'm not gonna need help
from all of you.
But you can't get it without us.
I don't think you know
what's been going on out there.
Why do you think I'm in here?
The girl and my boy
will have the sofa bed
in the living room.
You all are here.
Uh-uh. My daughter's
not sharing a bed with your son.
It's okay.
I can sleep on the floor.
- No, it's okay.
- It's fine.
Lights shut off at 9:00,
come back on at 6:00.
- And the hatch stays locked.
- Why?
'Cause that's what we do.
So, how come I never
seen you around before?
Like at school and stuff?
Uh, the school system is, um...
Uh, my dad doesn't
believe in it.
So, you're homeschooled?
I guess
you could call it that.
What's wrong with your brother?
Nothing.
I mean,
he's actually really smart.
He's adopted.
- For real?
- Yeah.
We got him
when he was about five.
We know his birth mother died
when he was a baby,
but... other than that,
we don't know
what trauma he suffered.
I mean, my mom got him tested
for everything.
He just doesn't talk.
They said it's like
a coping mechanism.
Yeah, well,
not having a mom sucks.
Where's your mom?
She's, uh... she got into
a lot of bad stuff, that's all.
Like what?
Oh,
just about everything.
Drugs, alcohol, you name it.
But she got into it
'cause of this guy.
My dad...
he didn't know about it,
but when he found out...
...it was too late.
Where is she?
She OD'd.
- I'm sorry.
- It's not a big deal.
Are we safe here?
Yeah.
Get some sleep.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Hey, hey.
What do you think you're doing?
Look at me
when I'm talking to you!
Put that down, boy!
God!
Hey, man, what's going on?
These cans were stored
by expiration date!
Now everything's out of order!
Hey, you don't have
to yell at him.
Jesus.
You have everything.
There's enough in here for mine.
You all being here one month
uses up six months of supplies!
You don't know that.
You can't just take from us.
Everybody's got to bring
something to the table!
All right, do me a favor, okay?
When you talk about me,
talk to me.
Dear Lord,
please bless this food
we are about to receive.
Watch over Amber
as she prepares to bring
a precious life into this world.
Pray for my guests.
Bless their Kai...
so that he may be
one day healed and...
and speak your good word.
In Jesus' name, we pray. Amen.
- Amen.
Why didn't you say "Amen"?
That's kind of a... personal
question, don't you think?
I like to know what kind of
man's sitting at my table.
Amen to that.
There's nothing wrong with Kai.
What's that?
You said bless Kai
so he can speak.
- He can speak. He just doesn't.
- Zoe.
I'm just saying
what you told me to say
when people treat Kai like
he's different. He's not.
He's fine.
Amen to that.
Hmm.
We spoke to Kai
about touching your things.
And that won't happen again.
Appreciate that.
You, uh...
you want to pour.
You got to let it sit.
Wipe it off.
And drop 'em in.
Think you can handle that?
Pour, let it sit,
wipe it off and drop it in?
- I think so.
- Yeah, okay.
And pour.
You got to let it sit
for a second.
Wipe it off.
There you go.
Okay. You keep doing this.
That's fine.
Man should know how to shoot.
Uh, mm-mm. "A rifle these hands
will never fire."
"History will look upon the Act
depriving a whole nation
of arms as the blackest."
Ah. You know your Gandhi.
That quote is out of context.
He wasn't arguing for more guns.
He was arguing for the repeal
of the Arms Act of 1878.
Well, it would've been
a more convincing argument
if he had a gun.
Where'd you study?
Library mostly.
Iraq, Afghanistan.
Hmm.
W.E.B. Du Bois believed that
without a proper education,
anything that the Black man
was working to get
could be taken away from him.
Booker T. Washington
believed a man
should not use
an education to avoid labor.
He was Black, too, right?
Yes, he was.
Well, I believe it's best
to have an education
than to need one.
How do you expect
to protect your family?
There are other ways.
Not here.
Go ahead.
I guess,
I guess you were right.
You just got...
Yeah, you got to cock it.
Oh, my gosh, he ordered
the same thing every time.
It was eggs over hard
with extra bacon.
And mind you, this is at
three o'clock in the morning.
He never said
more than two words to me,
until one night,
I left my lights on
and he jumpstarted my car.
Next time he came in,
I offered to comp his meal,
but no, no, no,
he wanted the bill.
When I came
back to his empty table,
I thought, "He must've left me
his number."
But you know what he wrote
on the receipt?
"You left your
lights on again."
I know.
What's that fabric?
Oh, that's...
Winter got that overseas.
He calls it a, um...
a du... something.
- Dupatta.
- That's right.
- Yes, dupatta. You're right.
Excellent.
Whoo. It's beautiful.
- It's nice.
- Mm.
You don't like it?
He thinks I don't know,
but he...
It was for his wife.
Then he gave it to me and it
still had the card inside,
so I just didn't feel right
wearing it.
Looks really pretty on you.
Get up!
Get up! Matty, we got a breach!
- What's all this?
- What's going on?
Sons of bitches
rammed the gate.
- How many?
- Four.
Here, take it.
Wait, you're taking your son
out there?
Uh-uh. I'm taking you.
Go get dressed.
- Dad, no.
- Amber.
Baby. Bed rest, baby.
Get in bed.
What do they want?
Not what they're about to get.
Don't shoot unless
you have a shot.
- But if you have a shot, take it.
- Look, I didn't come here for all this.
This is not a negotiation.
You're either an asset
or liability,
and I don't have time
to guess.
I'm not a liability.
- Over there.
- This way.
Stay down.
Damn!
Stay.
You take the shot, you move.
You don't want to be
where the shot came from.
Stay low. Be quiet.
Helen.
Oh.
Okay. All right, Amber.
You're okay.
Let's get you back on the bed.
Fuck.
Put your feet close
to the bottom as you can.
Matthew!
Put that down.
Go get me some towels.
This baby wants
to come out, all right?
Come on!
Okay.
Push!
Thanks.
Everything okay?
Greg?
Greg.
Um...
Greg, come on!
Get a move on!
The shoes.
So, I'm screaming and crying
and yelling, and Kai is sitting
there with me, holding my hand.
He's really, he's such
a sweet boy.
He is.
You did a great job.
Now, listen.
I want to call him Daniel.
That's a good name.
- It is.
- Virtue. Integrity.
- A man of God.
- Hmm.
- Here's to blessings.
- Mm.
Amen.
I can't. I'm still nursing.
Ah. Yeah.
What's wrong?
- Greg told me he killed a man.
- He did what needed to be done.
Needed?
The first time you take a life,
it haunts you.
Second time, it thrills you,
you know?
Eventually, it just numbs you.
Maybe it's like
delivering babies.
You do it enough, it gets old.
Bringing life into the world...
that never gets old.
I delivered a baby once.
Afghanistan.
We're in this canyon
taking fire from a bunch
of 12-year-olds. Right?
And I see this little
mud brick house, okay?
So, I shimmy over to it,
you know, take cover.
And inside there's this girl,
scared to death,
with a baby's head
halfway out of her.
So, I go over to her.
And she's pushing,
and out pops this baby,
a little boy,
right into my hands.
And I knew right then
that I needed to get home.
But you come back,
it's like...
It's like I was frozen in time
but my life kept moving.
And I found out my wife slept
with somebody, you know.
- She left you?
- I left her.
But, you know, this guy,
he was no good for her.
I knew that, but I wasn't there.
And she had...
she had this laugh.
Had pretty red hair.
Auburn, she liked to call it.
I loved her.
I really did.
I'm sorry.
Your husband...
he's got a spirit in him.
It's only so long
before it comes out again,
and when it does,
I don't want it coming at me.
That's not gonna end well.
I think you and your family
need to figure out
what you're gonna do.
- Winter...
- I'll give you a week.
- When?
- A week.
To stay, we have
to prove our value.
What, killing a man
is not enough?
You did what needed to be done.
When did he tell you that?
Another one of your
breakout sessions?
Greg, don't you question me.
- You have no right to question me.
- I'm asking you.
Okay? I'm asking you.
You're my wife.
Yeah. Don't I know it.
Helen, I'm trying to understand
what's happening here.
All right, let me recap for you.
Winter wants to throw us out,
and you're worried about me
talking to him,
instead of trying to figure
out what we gonna do.
Okay, so now it's okay
for me to try.
So, what do you want?
I want you
to not have to ask me that.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
How old were you when you had
your first girlfriend?
I was about your age.
Um...
maybe a little bit younger.
I wasn't the macho type,
but I could talk.
Girls like that.
The girls I knew anyway.
I'm not much of a talker.
Is it Zo?
No. No, no, she, uh...
No, you don't even
have to explain.
I mean, is this the first time
you've been around a girl?
Let me ask you a question.
Okay.
How long... you guys been here?
Like, you know, in the bunker?
Not too long. Couple months.
We were living in the trailer
up front.
- Oh.
- I liked it a lot better.
Then my... my dad
started hearing about
all this stuff on the news
about everything,
and, uh, he said
we needed to get ready.
Need to get back to work.
No, this is so hard.
- This is so hard.
- No, no, but you can do it. You can do it.
Now, take your right hand
and get your breast.
His nose a little tickle
with the nipple.
You know,
he's ready to latch.
He's ready to latch, so get
his head right on the tip.
Oh. Ow, God, that hurts!
Get him off!
Get him off, please!
Get him off, get him off!
Come on, Amber!
You got to try, Amber!
Just try! The boy needs to eat.
- No, no, no, no, no. Okay...
- You got to try. The boy's...
Listen, unlatch him
or you're gonna do more damage.
Helen, I can't do this. I can't
do this. You make it look...
Watch your tone, Amber.
Let's switch to the other side.
Come on.
All right. There you go.
Let's try now. Lift his mouth
right on the tip.
Mom, I thought
you were supposed to...
Is it normal
for it to hurt this bad?
No, this... this...
Ow! No, this...
it cannot be normal
- for it to hurt this bad. It cannot be normal...
- Just relax.
- ...for it to hurt this bad!
- Relax.
Lord, Lord,
just give me strength!
Lord, give me strength.
No. This is impossible.
Listen.
Listen. Amber's falling apart.
Her nipples are a bloody mess.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, this may be
a more complicated issue.
Her nipples could be inverted.
Daniel could be tongue-tied.
What do...
what do you mean?
Daniel's losing weight.
I mean, we've got to start
thinking about formula.
You did think to stock up
on formula?
I mean, after all,
you bought popcorn.
Breastfeeding was supposed
to be healthy and free.
No one knew
how challenging this would be.
But we've got
to get Daniel some milk.
She doesn't look so good.
It'll be okay, man.
My dad will check on her, okay?
You need to try harder.
You think I don't know that?
And what the fuck is she doing?
She's taking care of your child.
And you're okay with that?
I'm not gonna let her
replace me.
She ain't the one
trying to replace you.
- What was that about?
- Um. Nothing to worry about.
Come on, Dad,
don't do this to me.
Don't do to me
what you do to Mom.
- Come on, be straight up.
- Zo, Zo, please.
I'm telling you
everything is okay.
No, everything is not okay.
- I'm not stupid.
- What are you talking about?
- You think I don't know what's going on?
- Okay, what's going on?
I know about you
and that woman.
- That's between me and your mom.
- It's not just between you and her. It's not.
She's feeding that man's baby
right now.
And all she's saying
is trust her,
- but you're not even saying anything.
- Zo, listen, I'm your father.
- Okay?
- And this is your fault.
The fucking world is collapsing.
That's not my fault.
Look, I know you're scared.
So are we.
Your mother and I are trying
to figure this thing out.
It don't look like it.
You can't let him do this
to our family.
You just can't.
I think I'm ready to try again.
Are you sure?
It can take a few weeks
for you to heal,
and the last thing
you want to do
is... hurt yourself even more.
Well, she said
she wanted to try.
You ought to...
You ought to watch
where you put your hands.
Hey. You need to eat that.
We don't let food go to waste
around here.
We eat what we make.
- I'm not hungry.
- Won't keep.
You can warm it up later.
There's a lot going on.
She just needs a little rest.
Okay.
Amber, will you
please fix me a bowl?
Kai.
Finish your dinner, Kai.
Now is not the time.
The boy's inspired.
Let him embrace God's good Word.
Doesn't the Word tell him
to honor his mom and his father?
Your father's telling you
to eat your dinner.
Hey, Dad.
Uh, one of the hens...
she doesn't look too good.
Don't beat around the bush.
The bird's about to die,
just say so.
Either an asset or a liability.
Chickens, people,
all the same to you, hmm?
Chickens are more dependable.
Greg.
Time to wake up, Greg.
- Greg.
- Hey.
- Greg has a surprise for everybody.
Right, Greg? Hmm?
What were you planning, Greg?
- What's...
- What's going on?
Get up.
Go!
Kai, get Mia.
Come on.
- Get in there. Get in there!
- Greg! Stay here!
- What's going on?
- Please stop!
- Stop!
- Hey, Dad!
Dad!
Stop!
- What's going on? Zoe!
- Winter!
Guys! Come on.
- Dad!
- Kai, get back.
- Wait.
Dad, please! Put...
Oh, my God.
Dad.
- Oh, my God.
- Look at me!
Look at me.
Please, don't.
See,
this is what happens, Greg,
when you try and take
what's mine.
I'm trying to take what's yours?
You should be thanking me.
Everybody here contributes!
But you, all you do is take!
Right? You take!
You live inside your head,
while people like me...
- end up with that...
- Please.
protecting people like you.
I took you in, Greg.
- I fed you!
- Mom, make him stop.
Your family! Helen! I provided
for you! I protected you!
And you can't protect her!
You can't protect her, Greg!
Not like I can!
You don't have to do this.
- He goes.
- What?
- The boy goes, too.
- No!
Mm. This is good.
Zoe. Come on, have some.
Why?
- Oh, I know you're upset.
- Because you won't let us leave?
The new normal.
"New normal"?
That what you said? What?
There's no such thing
as "new normal."
No, baby,
anybody who believes in that
got conned.
Now...
while we're scraping by
down here,
I guarantee you there's somebody
up there living like a king.
Right, Matty?
That's not new.
That's normal.
Oh, we are blessed.
We can live under the open sky
the way the Lord intended.
We grow our own food.
Now, you don't put poison
in your body.
Your body can heal itself.
You don't need drugs.
Don't need pills.
We don't have to answer
to some corrupt politicians,
robbing us blind,
sending good men
to far away...
...places to do bad things.
Y'all answer to me.
I answer to the Almighty.
Where'd you find that?
Hey, Brooke.
I was thinking about
what you said.
It still hurts, you know?
Maybe you don't.
I love Greg, and I know
he loves me. I just...
He made me feel like
I was in this alone.
Maybe I made him
feel like that, too.
It's just hard.
Anyway, I love you.
Call me when you get home.
I'll be out in a few minutes.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not.
Good.
You are...
You are a beautiful woman.
Decent.
You're a good mother,
strong-willed.
This man...
wants you.
This man, he needs you.
I've waited for this.
I know.
Tell me you want this.
It's not that simple.
You being here is no accident.
Winter, I'm married.
He's gone.
- He's not coming back.
- Maybe.
Remember what it felt like.
You loved a woman.
When you left, she betrayed you.
No, baby, this is different.
Is it?
What are you gonna think of me
when you realize
I'm the type of woman
that wouldn't wait a day
after claiming to love...
love a man?
Her husband?
The father of her children?
Is that the type of woman
you want?
You need me, Helen.
Not like this.
It has to be right.
Helen.
Let it be right.
Don't move, okay?
I know you're scared,
but I got to go get your mom,
Zoe and Mia. I'll be back.
Dad!
Geez.
Get down, Matty!
Amber, get back in your room!
Everybody, Helen, Helen,
get down! Get down!
- I'm coming with you.
- You stay with the women.
Hatch stays locked.
The bedrooms are safe.
Get in the bedrooms!
- You can't leave us down here.
- Stay low.
Okay, Amber, close that door.
Close it!
Winter!
Amber, take the baby
in the other room.
Give me that!
There's got to be another key!
Where is it?
- My dad told me not to say anything.
- Come on, boy!
Come on.
Oh, it was here.
Uh-uh-uh-uh. Stay down.
Though I walk
through the valley
of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for you are with me.
Your rod and staff,
they comfort me.
You prepare a table before me
in the presence of my enemies.
Ma!
No, no, Greg.
Okay, Greg.
Step on out.
I got ya.
Oh, Greg. I see you.
Come on, take it like
a man. Come on out.
Get back. Get back.
I can see you.
Come on out.
Move!
- Come on out.
- Winter!
Put it down.
- Put it down.
- Helen.
- What? Helen.
- Don't you say my name.
Baby.
Honey, you don't know
what you're doing. Come on.
Oh, I do.
I do. Trust me. Put it down.
Put it down!
You know I...
I can't. I can't do that.
You know I can't do that.
How you gonna make it?
You can't make it
out here without me.
How you gonna... you're not
that type of woman.
You don't know shit about me.
You wouldn't.
Ah. You wouldn't do that.
Daniel's not my son.
And you aren't my husband!
Dad!
That's fine.
Ah, my hand!
Chickens have
a survival instinct
just like we do.
Theirs tell them
to find a high roost
before nightfall
to avoid predators.
Ours tells us
that we have a choice...
...to run, to hide
or to fight.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
Within the flock,
the pecking order remains.
If you remove the aggressor,
the hierarchy resets...
Hey, look!
...and everyone finds
their place again.
But the flock will always
need a leader.
And sometimes
the one who emerges
is the one you least expect.