Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[lively jazz piano music]
♪ ♪
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
- Hi, it's us.
It's Molly.
Ha! Look at the first one.
[vocalizing]
- We're at Garde Robe,
where Sarah Jessica
stores her archives.
And no human hand
has touched anything.
I want to figure out
what's worthy to reintroduce
in the reboot.
Super fragile and iconic.
[laughs]
This is the, you know,
Staten Island ferry shoe.
She must have the entire
Staten Island--
I mean, if she's got the dress.
[gasps]
She does not.
She has the whole
Staten Island outfit.
- I lost my choo.
Hello.
At one time, this was
the most expensive dress...
- I had no intention
of going in.
- We ever bought her.
It was in the window at Dior.
And Pat said,
"I want that dress for her."
I cannot believe
this is in here.
I cannot. I can't, I can't.
- Come on, Granny.
I'll take you
to the early bird special.
- Custom made for her
by Alexander McQueen.
Seriously, fashion museum
in a hanging bag.
- We're gonna have to come get
some of this, you know,
for closet scenes and you know,
so people can have little
treats in the background.
Incredible.
[soft jazz music]
♪ ♪
- We just did hair
and makeup tests.
Even 23 years in--
well, maybe more so important
when we're 23 years in
if you know what I mean.
And then of course,
standing with your colleagues
side by side to see
the three of us,
to see Cynthia and Kristin
and myself standing together,
which was
definitely the highlight.
And there's typically no sound
so it's like a silent movie.
♪ ♪
- Um...
She was like someone
I hadn't seen in a while.
To me, that character
is present like some--
anybody that I've spent
10, 12, 14 years with
who I really love.
You know, if I see something
that's memorable
or uniquely New York,
I-I think I'm seeing it
for her as well or with her.
- Just getting it right.
Just every day.
There's just so much--
so much work ahead of us.
There's just so much work.
And--but I'm excited.
Terrified and excited,
which is always where I am.
[discordant piano notes]
[indistinct chatter]
[camera shutters
snapping rapidly]
- Mask off, mask off!
We're rolling!
Background! Check!
- Background!
- That's a nice blend
of polemics and farts.
[camera shutters
snapping rapidly]
[indistinct chatter]
- Somebody said today, I think
they described it so well.
They were like, "Does it feel
like it was just a hiatus?"
- Right. It's, like, a week.
Then Willie said, like, a week.
- Yeah.
- And this is--I think is
partly because we're in touch.
I'm in L.A.
That's what you know.
- Look how much we love
you regardless.
- Oh!
- [laughing]
- We care about life
on the West Coast.
- They forgive me for being
a West Coaster.
- Yeah.
- Well, tomorrow.
- Tomorrow, yeah.
Tomorrow's a special day.
- Tomorrow, we have big scenes
and the very,
very first scenes in the show,
so that's exciting.
- And some new friends.
- And some new friends
and some old friends.
- Oh, do you have a schedule
on your phone?
- I do.
- Wow.
- Did you put it in there?
- I did.
- Well, 'cause I can't
print anything.
- Do you remember when you put
everything in your PalmPilot?
- My--my BlackBerry.
- Your BlackBerry,
and you'd say,
"Betty Ann! Betty Ann!" and
then you'd go like this, wait.
I still have a BlackBerry,
but let me say one thing.
- I know.
That's where I wanted you.
Did you think that we were
going to be quiet
and you could ask us questions?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Please forgive us.
- No, it's my turn.
- Okay.
- I just ran into LTW
in the ladies' room!
I understand.
- Welcome.
- ♪ Welcome! ♪
- Welcome!
- ♪ To Nicole, whoo ♪
- Oh, my God, it's amazing.
It's kind of surreal, actually,
you know,
to be talking to the people
that I used to talk to
through the TV.
- These are
my very best friends
in the world,
Miranda and Carrie.
- Hi, I'm Lisa.
So nice to meet you both.
- Nicole Ari Parker
is playing LTW,
who is a mother of three,
a documentarian,
a humanitarian,
and on the "Vogue"
International
Best Dressed List,
which is all we ever
wanted to do
with any significant character
on the show.
Show someone
who is more than one thing.
- She has gotten
so much flack,
and I feel so bad
for that part,
but she's handled it
really beautifully
because we're not
replacing Samantha.
We would not replace Samantha.
It doesn't really make sense
to replace Samantha.
- You know, it's weird.
Can I have one?
- It was very important to me
that LTW sit down,
but I didn't want to tell
the audience one,
two, three, fourth,
she's the new Samantha.
- All right,
I'm going to be late.
- So I had Carrie and Miranda
get up and leave,
and she sits at the table.
And at first everybody,
including the network
was like, "Ah, ah, ah!
Where--what happened?
Where's Carrie and Miranda?"
And I was like,
"Gotta pump the brakes."
- Where's the fourth musketeer?
Where's Samantha?
- The energy changes.
- Oh.
Um, uh.
Samantha's no longer with us.
There is a storyline
about Samantha
that I think is great
and I think is very true.
It seems very true to me that
friends sometimes grow apart.
- Who's it even from?
[soft sentimental music]
♪ ♪
They can stay.
I think it's handled
really nicely,
and it's very gently peppered.
What did I say?
- Um.
Well, you told
the diaphragm story,
and--and you--you--oh, Lord.
- Oh, it happens all the time.
It doesn't matter.
They have a mind of their own.
- They do. Please stay.
- Sometimes they walk me
straight down the avenue.
You tell them to.
- Okay. Okay.
So back--back--back
to what we're talking about.
You told the diaphragm story,
- I did.
- Yes.
And you used Samantha's name.
[soft percussive music]
- Go.
And I just had my nails done.
- I knew Kim had moved on
from playing Samantha.
I realized,
"Oh, we can have them
"mirror a split that people
already know,
"but make it really
Carrie and Samantha
and heartfelt
the way you lose friends."
[sentimental music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- No, someone's in here!
- Oh, my God! Oh! Oh!
- So you want me to come here
and stand, like, right here?
- Yeah.
- I appreciate that,
but we're okay.
It's all in the past.
- I've only ever seen
every episode once.
We never got to do any scenes
together since one.
I mean, not like
sitting and talking.
You're chasing, running.
- Carrie. I see you. Wait!
- The--the luncheon, remember?
You interrupted my luncheon.
- Oh, my God, that's right.
- My teeth.
This tooth is still a different
color than this tooth.
- Having to find out
where you were having--
- 'Cause you're a stalker,
clearly.
[both laugh]
Professional stalker.
I'm gonna scream.
- Please don't.
I'm only gonna stay a minute.
David Eigenberg, we've never
had a scene together.
Steve?
- What you want?
- I think we have.
- We did.
We--I know we did one
on the stair.
- Yeah, and it was about what?
- We're sitting on the stair.
- I was sitting on the stoop.
- I was sad.
I was getting beat up again.
By that woman.
[laughs]
It's Miranda, right?
She doesn't want me
calling so much, right?
It's fine. Whatever.
- And it wasn't about Aidan?
Maybe it was about both.
- It might've been about Aidan.
- How does Aidan feel about me?
- Aw, jeez.
- Might've been about both.
- The age of Aidan.
- That--that woman and Aidan.
- That would then--
- Maybe they--
there were storylines
that called for compatriots.
- Yeah. Is that--
- Can you open that?
Sorry. No one can.
Can you believe it?
- Miranda!
[laughter]
- God bless. Thank you.
- She's--she empty--she--she
emptied the hard drive.
- Did we kiss
on the Eagle Justice?
- Yes.
[both laughing]
I mean...
We had bed scenes.
She's gonna forget
this entire thing happened.
[both laugh]
- Tomorrow, I'm gonna say,
"When should we do
our interview?"
- Are you coming with me
when I go to check...
Willie Garson and Mario
and make sure they got
their underwear on right?
Hi, can you grab anybody
that can bring me the Roger?
- This was Pat's idea,
was you should try
to get Molly.
And it would--you know, it's
the right and perfect handoff
because Molly was there
with us from the beginning.
- I came to New York in 1984,
and the first person I met
on Friday the 13th, 1984--
it was very witchy--
was Pat, Pat Field.
We did season one through six,
both movies.
In between one
of those movies,
we did
"The Devil Wears Prada."
So it's been a real
fashion career alongside Pat
and now on the reboot
with Danny.
It's kind of a natural--
it feels
natural progression to me.
- Molly coming back
to do this show
was incredibly necessary.
- Do you have any berets, dear?
- Packing hats
for the black event.
- Background.
- Listen, MPK is supposedly
coming here
to go through and approve
or kill fittings that
we have spent two days doing.
- Molly, at some point,
needs a villain,
and it's me coming down
and going, "No."
She goes,
"He's going to ruin our day."
And I love it
because it's partly true
and not at all true.
- Okay. Thank you for coming.
- Oh, my God, are you kidding?
- We need you.
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
No!
- What?
[laughter]
- One of my favorite,
most favorite
processes in the show
is Molly and me and Danny
and them saying,
"Here's the pictures."
And I'm like, "Why are they
all wearing turbans?"
Great.
- Okay.
There's no surprises,
but there is a hat
being made for her
that you haven't seen yet.
- All right.
- It's funny 'cause I wanna
have the hat call conversation.
- Okay.
- It's color restraint.
I can't look out there and see
"Ascot Gavotte"
from "My Fair Lady."
It cannot be Danny.
[laughter]
- Blame the gays
whenever you can.
- You know what it's gonna be.
Hmm, and a huh, and a huh.
This isn't a peacock walk.
This is a--
- Somber.
- Sombery tasteful
business people event.
It's about where we tip into...
- Okay.
- Mocking a funeral.
Just don't make them fall
in love with the hats
or style the hair
around the hat.
So if I take the hats off--
- Then you're--
- We're in a hole.
- Okay.
[gasps]
Oh, my--Andy.
- There's more, there's more.
There's more.
- [gasps] Oh, my God.
- Okay.
- Let me find something great
before Danny gets here.
Hurry. Hurry.
What's the best thing?
[gasps]
What?
- Vivienne Westwood.
- Get out.
- Missing a belt,
but it's still good.
- I've only got
one fall episode.
Miranda all day long.
- This is 1981 Yohji Yamamoto.
- [gasps]
Didn't I tell you?
He's like a mad scientist.
- This is years of collecting.
This is '70s Saint Laurent.
Just travels.
You know, people's homes.
Maybe some eBay, but I'm not
gonna say that publicly.
Probably, like, 10,000.
- Danny.
- Yes, ma'am.
- There's a lot to see.
- Mm-kay.
- Andy, you--you know
I can't buy all this
until I try it on SJ, right?
Right?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- Okay.
And I won't
abuse the privilege.
- I know.
- Danny! Ezzeddine.
- I know, I pulled that out
to look at the color.
- ♪ You're taking the color
out of the show ♪
- Yeah.
- We'll put something
neon under it.
[inhales sharply]
Bergdorfs.
- Mm-hmm.
Isn't that beautiful?
- Gaultier '96 or '97.
- I think it's great.
It's cool.
- So cool.
- But look how pretty
'cause its back--
the back is open on it,
so it's sexy.
- What do you think?
- I love it.
- I know you love it,
but there's no way
she's gonna wear that color.
Do we have anybody?
Do we have someone
that works at Sachs
and comes up to her
and is like, "Hi!"
Let's try.
This belongs on our show.
- The institutional
knowledge is here.
It's being protected by
the very person who should be.
- So this is new.
- Okay.
- Normally, you start with new
and we talk about it.
- Let's do that.
We need tank tops,
that's your point.
- We just saw 'em.
We liked them. We grabbed them.
- Great. Were they expensive?
- No.
- Okay.
- There.
- Vintage Gucci.
- I mean, that is so good.
Not helpful.
This is unbelievable.
Unbelievable!
Oh, my God, is this
an old Brownie uniform?
- It's Gaultier.
- It's like a kitchen in 1979.
- Yes, it is.
- But it's unbelievable.
[lively piano music]
Yeah, but don't do that.
Let's just let that be
for a minute,
and you'll just do the back.
Okay. So wow.
It's so good.
My physical therapy outfit.
We have to wear this
for something.
And then we'll have to just
take care of some business
'cause we want it to fit
a little better
than it's fitting now.
But this is so good.
I mean, it's hideous. Hideous.
- You know, you need to step
outside your comfort zone,
which is what this show
is famous for
as far as a television show
and its fashion.
And we did it,
and we had fun styling it
and using it in the scene.
- Like, this is the kind
of thing you want on a shelf,
like, on her bookshelf
in her house.
- Yeah.
- Like, this is literally
on a shelf for no reason.
- I know you keep putting
that egg in front of it.
Egg that outfit.
- Egg!
- Every time.
- Someone's gonna get
knocked out.
[laughter]
Closer. Much closer.
There.
We don't happen to have
a gingham belt, do we?
Like a--like a crazy,
amazing belt?
Where's the belt that I think
is a piece of art?
That should be hanging
in Carrie's apartment.
- Oh, God, isn't that great?
- Kinda great.
- Okay.
- Thanks, Loughlin.
- It's almost too much,
but it's beautiful.
- What are we gonna do
with a big coat like that?
- Oh, we don't care.
We highlight it.
Try to make sure the camera
focuses on it.
Safe to come in?
[laughter]
- And you wear that open?
- Yes.
- And what do you want to do
with those ties?
Do them off the cuffs?
- Yeah, maybe.
- Or is that too...
- We'll just leave 'em.
- Leave them?
Let them--I'm going to look
for a handbag.
- Let 'em live.
- Okay.
That's so pretty coming--
- That's so pretty.
- Okay, and then
you go downtown...
- We need a shoe.
- There's that too.
- Maybe Molly mends that.
- Maybe?
- Pretty good.
- Yeah.
- That's gorgeous.
- That is so beautiful.
- Yeah.
- That looks so pretty.
- What's the bag, do you think?
- I'm looking.
So beautiful.
- Is that good?
- Perfect. Time for a cocktail.
- We have vodka here
and tequila and...
- What?
- If you want a shot.
- And you waited until freaking
10:00 to tell me that?
- Someone. Whoo!
[laughs]
[lively percussive music]
- I am the still photographer.
You're documenting
everything they shoot.
You're almost shooting
your own movie in stills.
I did the pilot,
did the first season,
survived that, surprisingly.
- Action.
- And then did
all the seasons,
all the movies,
and I'm still standing
and no one's more surprised
than I am.
- Oh, nice touch, Cassette.
- We're just setting up.
- All the background drinks
right now.
I mean, we can't have people
getting drunk on camera, right?
Uh, the tequila
can go way too long.
No, we use juices
and do coloring of water
and, you know, other secrets.
- Cassette, Cassette!
[overlapping chatter]
- Whenever actors
are interacting
with all these other props.
- You take my soul. Help.
Help, someone.
Don't you see what she's doing?
- Sarita, can you be--
in this part could be
a little bit to your left.
I'm the cinematographer.
Michael and I wanted
to be true to--
to the original series
but also give it a new look,
and I think we've managed
to sort of update it,
present the women in the most
realistic yet beautiful way.
- I am the gaffer on the set.
The gaffer
is responsible
for the lighting.
I work with the director
of photography,
Tim Norman, and Gary Martone,
the key grip,
and we try to get things done.
- I'm the key grip.
We're responsible
for camera movement.
How the camera gets
from point A to point B.
We also control the lights.
- Believe it or not,
I did--I was the gaffer
on the pilot.
However many years ago
that was.
- Uh, 24.
- Yes.
- My station.
I'm just trying to get
the best sound,
and it's tricky
because the fashion has
definitely been challenging.
- Naughty, naughty Mike.
- I wanna twirl like this too.
[chain jangles]
- Wow.
Picture Charles
and the sound department.
I'd have to be still
in a scene, right?
He would--he would kill me.
He would kill me.
- All right.
Good morning, friends.
Happy Wednesday?
Jeez, it's only Wednesday.
- Did you see Cynthia?
She might not recognize you
with the mask.
- Luca.
- Luca!
- I assigned all
the scene numbers
and keep track
of which takes are good
and which takes are bad.
I make sure that the actors
say their lines correctly.
- Luca, is it
exceptionally pretty?
- On a shelf in my closet.
Got it, got, got it.
- Last time we were single.
- Who?
[laughter]
- One at a time, Luca.
- One at a time.
- Don't ask for the moon.
- I'm on the turn.
It's like we get there,
and as SJ starts to go,
even then, we're pushing.
- Be nice to see you
in more than just the red.
- Pebbles, you okay?
- Pebbles.
- Pebbles told me to do that.
- That's a good question.
Maybe because it's fun
to scream Pebbles.
I don't know.
[all saying "Pebbles"]
- Pebbles, let me know.
- We're set.
[all saying "Pebbles"]
- And action.
- They scream my name often
because I'm sort of a bridge
between the director
and the DP
and the actors and the camera
and how all of that's
working together.
- Oh, Pebbles.
Hiding behind the plants.
- This is
"And Just Like That..."
episode 106, "Diwali,"
written by Rachna Fruchbom
and directed by Cynthia Nixon.
[all cheering]
- We knew from the beginning.
Michael Patrick and I
had talked about that
before she even
signed on as Miranda.
- I knew Cynthia
was the director
because I'd seen plays
that she's done.
And I knew that
she had that in her.
- The cue should be for SJ.
- Feel her.
- And then you feel S--
when you feel SJ, you turn.
Cut.
When you're an actor,
you're very loved,
and you're very included,
but at a certain time,
it's 9:00,
and you've got to go to bed.
And you know that the grownups
are still out there
having a cocktail and chatting.
And it's sort of like
turning 18 or something,
and it's like
other people go to bed,
but you're allowed to stay.
- I'm really excited to see
how this all--how we--
- Yeah, show you
how the sausage is made.
I guess my question to you
is this--in your--in your head,
this particular episode,
just thinking purely of tone,
do you--do you see this episode
as different in tone?
- I am fully confident
you know the tone
of what we've been doing
for the last 23 years
and how it needs to evolve
and change
depending on who we are.
I'm very confident
or we wouldn't be sitting here.
- It was really hard for me
to know how prepare.
Like, there
were certain scenes that
they really wanted a shot list
from me early on
before we had ever rehearsed
or anything.
My thought was, right?
They come in here
and pause for a minute.
- Okay, what is the goal
for today?
- They walk down
to the middle aisle,
and then they kind of
gather their strength,
and then Carrie
gets overwhelmed.
- Oh, shit.
- And then Carrie
notices the pan.
- Okay, now can go.
- I'm a very decisive person.
And I think that's a good thing
in a director
because people are constantly
coming up to you
and asking you what you want
or what your--
what your preference is,
and you need to have one.
Or if you don't have one,
it's good to say
"I don't know."
- And the question
I have for you is,
do you want this dishwasher
on this so she's facing this,
or do you want the dishwasher
that she's facing that way?
You know what I mean?
- Right.
- That's something to--
- Yeah, I don't know.
- A few.
- [chuckles]
- I probably asked more than
I answered, though.
- And when in doubt, say yes.
- Say yes.
- When in doubt, just yes.
- We're the--we're the
anti-Nancy Reagan.
Just say yes.
- Yes.
- Sorry, if you could just
come this way, okay.
My first strength is,
of course,
the actors and understanding
and scene
and working with them.
- I know. They were so lovely.
- Ten. Background!
- Whoo.
- It's exciting.
- Action.
- What? What? Action?
Wow. Oh. Hey. Wow.
Um, yeah, 15 years gone.
I love that scene.
She and Charlotte
were having a thing.
Like, a real thing.
My character was like,
"Ooh, wait."
- Say something.
- Cheese?
- She gave me a really
good note in the middle of it
to the point where I was like,
"Oh, I forgot
that you were directing."
And then also that's
an excellent note
because she knows us so well,
you know what I mean?
And she knows acting
so brilliantly.
You brought it up,
and we talk about everything,
so you can't suddenly
just change the rules.
I had to really,
"Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!"
which is hard for me sometimes.
You know, Charlotte's like,
"Ooh-do-do, do-do-do."
Not like, "Blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah."
You are married to a man.
And now you're just suddenly
having non-binary sex.
I mean, why can't people
just stay who they are?
- Ask me again.
- Why does everyone have to
suddenly change who they are?
- I was going like a train,
right?
So then in the middle of it,
Cynthia very quietly said,
you know, "Make your point."
You are not progressive enough
for this
[overlapping chatter]
[cheers and applause]
- The best part
is when she's in a scene,
and then she says, "Cut."
That's my favorite.
I love that.
- She's really great,
just as we suspected.
- Yes.
Also, she told me to be
like a fawn in the episode,
which possible is
my favorite direction ever.
- Aw.
- [laughs]
- And I was like, "Uh.
That's gonna take
a lot of work."
And she's like,
"I added eyelashes."
[both laugh]
- We're on the subway
for the first time
on "Sex and the City" history.
Technically,
we're at the Bowery Station.
Shh. Don't tell anyone.
But story-wise,
we're at 116th street
up in Columbia and Broadway.
We've been wanting to get
our gals on the subway,
I would say, well,
now it's more than 20 years
we've been trying,
and we made it.
[soft jazz music]
- Just getting to know
our new cast members
has just been like one gift
after another gift
after another gift.
And we all have something new
brought to us by them.
[overlapping chatter]
- Just wearing a pink pussy hat
wasn't gonna cut it anymore!
- I'm super proud of that.
And that's Nya!
[laughs]
What I think I didn't expect
the camaraderie
and the real sisterhood
and, you know, that experience
and the laughter and the funny.
Like, it's as funny
behind the scenes
as it is in front
of the camera.
- You did make
a 7:30 reservation.
- Thank you.
- At our San Francisco
location.
- Should I call them
and tell them
we're gonna be
a little bit late?
- Nya was there
to be many things.
She's a leader,
she's the teacher,
and then she's the student
with Miranda.
- Miranda Hobbs,
are you about to tell me
that motherhood isn't worth it?
- Um...it depends on the day.
- Miranda, who's always had
a ambivalence to motherhood.
It almost--Brady was
almost an abortion.
- Charlotte, I didn't do it.
I'm keeping the baby.
- That's amazing.
- Dan, shut up!
- Start rolling. Oh, my God.
More later!
- So originally, when Michael
was sort of trying to think
about what would happen
in our season,
he talked about Nya, you know,
Miranda's professor,
being the
romantic relationship.
You--you're the professor?
- Yeah.
- You're Nya Wallace?
- [laughs] Yes.
Why do you seem so surprised?
- Nya was a straight character,
and Miranda's
a straight character,
and I was like, that doesn't
sound very sexy at all.
Do you know what I mean?
To women who've gotten
to this age
and are now just sort of
fumbling around,
that doesn't seem great.
And--and I was like,
why couldn't it be, you know,
why couldn't it be
this butch person
that you're talking about
having for Carrie?
- I am Che Diaz,
your host and queer
non-binary Mexican-Irish diva
representing everyone else
outside these two
boring genders.
"Sex and the City"
was really inspiring to me
and empowering around exploring
my own sexuality
and my own just empowerment
as a person
who is not a man in the world.
Look at me, listen to me.
Are you listening to me?
- I am.
- I can't give you
anything traditional.
- We built that character
for them
based on their
gender identifications.
- You need to dialogue
with us more.
That's the last time
to try them.
- You need to dialogue
with us more, ding.
Okay, so I--and I said--
I said, I really
want this working.
- It's like it's missing.
- And I say this with love.
- Good. Okay, thank you.
That's great.
I say this with love.
You better step your pussy up.
- Oh, okay.
I've got a bunch
of stuff with Sara,
which has been great
and really fun.
The podcast stuff
is so much fun.
And included in that is
Bobby Lee, who is heaven sent.
- You still with us?
- I'm in the scene.
I'm doing a fucking scene
on the show.
[laughter]
God.
- This kind of dollop
of something.
Oh, I've never tasted that
bef--you know, like.
- You gotta stroke it, Lee.
- This is the longest day.
[laughing]
- Seema was brought into
the show to be another version
of somebody
we haven't seen in the show,
a South Asian woman
from Queens,
first-generation daughter
of immigrants.
- It's such a pretty name.
- It means "boundary" in Hindi.
- Oh.
- Which is hilarious
because I have none.
- She comes in
as a real estate mogul.
She owns her own business.
She even has a license plate
that says SEEMA NYC.
I mean, you don't need more
than that to say, "Baller."
And then we have Sarita,
who is the most quiet baller
in the entire world.
- 4-16, take one.
A-mark.
And action.
- It's gorgeous.
It's all gotta go.
- Try--I think
a harder version
and then punctuate it.
- Okay.
It's gorgeous.
It's all gotta go.
- She's a very interesting,
quiet kind of stealth
way about her
that's really cool to see.
- You staged me
like an apartment?
When?
- Valentine's Day
on my lunch break.
Nobody buys real estate
in the winter, so I listed you.
I know those scenes
at the table.
And then when they told me
I was in a scene at the table,
by then I'd shot a lot,
so I was at ease
with doing the show.
But that day was different.
- Nice and quiet, please!
Let's hold for...
- There was something
about the table and that scene
that was so iconic
that to enter into it,
it was not
a normal human feeling.
- What?
- Yes.
- Oh, Sarita!
- And she lives to tell.
- Welcome to the table.
- I was very nervous.
They're super nice.
I survived them.
- And you know, we asked Sarita
what she was drinking,
or Seema what she was drinking,
and she's drinking
her own version of a Cosmo.
- Oh, my God.
- I didn't realize.
- It's a new day.
- With mint.
- Whoo.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
- Back to work. Come on.
- Nine, ten.
- Action.
- [sighs]
[gasps]
- Cut.
[bell rings]
- The great thing
about Sarah Jessica is,
she just keeps going.
- Where's his wallet stuff?
Where's that--all the stuff
in the wallet?
- That's all in the wallet.
- Wouldn't it able to be--
- It can all be
wherever you want it.
- Yeah, like the picture
and the Pinkberry, and...
- Yeah, it's all here.
- And a Pinkberry punch card
is on the walk to here.
- Yeah.
- Okay, so just roll the--
the punch card's over there.
- And here's my wallet.
That's his wallet.
- Okay, perfect.
Until I really figure it out,
it doesn't feel like
it can be real on screen.
Like, I almost
have to be super technical
over and over again.
So then I've gotta find her
on Instagram, right?
- Yeah, that's on your phone.
- Lord have mercy.
If you're not living
in the apartment
and you're not handling
the food or looking at a phone
or dealing with a plastic bag
or waking your computer up.
Oh, I-I-I-I found
her Instagram.
I'm gonna send her a--
I'm gonna DM her.
Just, you know, in case
she didn't get the email.
- I say let's give her
another day.
All right, I'm gonna change.
It's gonna be a long one.
- All right.
- And action.
- Did you know that Big had
a dog named Gogi?
I have been spiraling all--
I've been spiraling all day
about him and Natasha.
Damn it! Son of a bitch.
I know. I know. You're scared.
[laughter]
[voice muffled]
It's a cashmere something.
She blocked me on Instagram.
- Okay, the woman
is a total bitch.
- Oh, what a mess.
- I think maybe 'cause
I wasn't formally trained,
I can't count on a class
or a masterclass or a teacher,
so you look to others.
I remember being in a theater
with both Mary McDonnell
and Claire Bloom,
and they were, like...
Involved in everything.
Hi, what do you do?
- I'm an assistant
set director.
- Oh, nice to meet you.
Why are you guys hiding?
I can get closer to being
whole and alive and real
if I am head to toe
a living person.
You know,
and if this is here...
Whatever it is
that makes you feel like
you're in an active tableau
when someone yells action,
I just feel more whole.
I wanna definitely do this
with Molly, you know,
so I don't mess up
stuff of Molly's.
I just--it--we can't ha--
this looks like an ad.
You know, I want it
with the bad stuff too
and broken things
and, you know.
We've got literally every label
under the sun in here.
It just feels like...
♪ Ah! ♪
Hey, Molly.
- Hi.
- I feel like we have to be
really thoughtful
about what we're saying
about her.
You know, and get some
of the old stuff in here.
And I know that's
a huge undertaking.
- So is too store-looking?
- Yeah.
I have tons of her shoes here
and stuffed in between
is, like, some CDs,
you know what I mean?
Like, kr-kr-kr-kr!
I'm scared if we don't
bring Carrie here...
- Yeah.
- That we are--
people are going to be like,
"Well, where's all
her old junk?"
- It's a fine line
between the eye candy for...
- Correct.
- Viewers and the tone of it.
I agree.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Okay. We got our--
we got our marching orders.
Let's rock.
Those are good notes.
She's smart.
[upbeat jazz music]
- So let me--
- Yeah. I'll let you do that.
Sarah Jessica is so tactile.
She needs to feel like
she lives in her house.
That's why all of a sudden,
we're throwing stuff
all over the set--
because it makes her feel
not like a set.
It makes her feel
like she lives there,
and that's necessary
because Carrie is true to her
and true to the audience,
which is why we're back.
- I think we should stuff
shoe bags in her now.
She needs. I do that.
Old shoe bag in this row.
- That makes me happy.
- Mm-hmm.
- All right, let's go.
- All this stuff
but--but different rejects.
- Rejects?
[indistinct chatter]
- I'm always trying
to be careful
and polite and gracious,
but sometimes,
they're going to call action,
and we've got to get
a detail right
'cause it really matters.
- Those are from your store.
- Kevin,
who's our set deck guy,
and, you know, who I love,
but, you know, we didn't
know each other at first.
And it was--
it's a lot to let me,
like, barge
into his department,
but he's been super gracious
and generous, and he's great.
- I've never learned so much
about Chanel in my life.
[indistinct chatter]
- I would venture to say that
one of the reasons we're here
is because I missed him.
- [laughs]
Okay, so tell me where
to start, and I'll work on a--
- Start right here.
[heartfelt music]
- [sighs]
Hello, lovers.
♪ ♪
[upbeat jazz music]
- When I wrote episode four,
one of the things that
I put in the episode
is the scene
where you have a dinner party
that's predominantly
African American,
and there's a conversation
about art.
- So you know art.
- Yes, and so, um,
it was really just--
what kind of a collection
would this couple have?
And that was
the direction I got,
and I was like, "Got it."
I know that couple.
- I can't think of
a better investment
than what Lisa has chosen here.
- We started out
with Gordon Parks...
- You also have
Deborah Roberts.
- We have Derrick Adams...
- Which is like owning early
sheet music by Beethoven.
- And Barkley Hendricks...
- And my personal favorite,
if I am allowed
to choose a favorite,
which would be
the Mickalene Thomas in there.
She did the very first portrait
of First Lady Michelle Obama.
- I loved her book.
- I think it would be silly
to pretend that
we haven't been
what we've been,
you know, for a long time.
The Wexleys can't be the only
Black couple at the dinner.
They're gonna think we don't
have any Black friends.
So I think it's nice here
that we can show that,
you know, her world
gets expanded in particular
by Lisa Todd Wexley,
Nicole's character,
and then it--she shines a light
on the rest of her world
and is like, "I need
to expand and be better."
Gwen.
Gwen, hi!
I haven't seen you
since Leo moved to Dalton.
- I'm not Gwen, but I know
who you're talking about.
- It's about Charlotte
trying to be perfect
when she's completely flawed.
Even in a editing process,
people were like,
"I'm uncomfortable with that."
- It's terrible. It's terrible.
- And I called up Kelly,
and I was like,
"Kelly, why is that
in the show again?
Just remind me, just remind me
why we put it in."
She goes, "Because every
dinner party I go to
"where there's white people,
they always think
I'm the other fancy
Black writer that they know."
- This picture in particular,
really,
to me so encapsulated
everything we're trying to do
with these characters
in this episode, right?
We know that so many people
in our audience
who may not consider
themselves art experts
are gonna see this photograph,
and it's gonna be
meaningful for them.
Awesome! Thank you!
- This is Carrie Bradshaw's
famous apartment.
There's a lot of her
original furniture
that Sarah Jessica
had in storage.
This is original.
This table, original.
The famous chaise.
Who doesn't know the chaise?
- You have to promise
not to judge.
- Do I judge?
- We all judge,
that's our hobby.
- God's honest truth,
it's like,
when I'm in that apartment,
I'm always like,
I don't remember
a lot of other people
in that apartment
except for Willie.
Who is it?
- Mr. Right.
Have you seen "The New York
Times" Style section?
- For some reason, in my head,
that was Stanford's place.
- You know,
the last time I saw Willie
and most of us saw Willie,
maybe all of us saw Willie,
was at that Mr. Big's funeral.
Sarah Jessica was
the only person
who knew that he was ill.
- At one point, Sarah knew
and the rest of us didn't
because
he didn't want us to know
because he didn't want it
to be about that.
- If he could have stayed
one more day, two more hours,
three more weeks,
he would have summoned
the strength and pushed away
the p--the terrible pain
that he was in.
I mean, pain.
Like, physical pain.
- You know, it was a shock.
It was unexpected.
- The week before,
I had spent hours and hours
with him shooting this scene,
and he was so funny and silly
and--and full of energy,
seemingly.
- It's slightly more natural.
- Oh, I don't get olives?
- Well, you didn't ask
for them.
- Twist. You know, twist.
- A twist.
- Twist.
- And action.
- Shouldn't they have
called her first?
- I would think.
- Stanford?
- Where?
- Sorry, I went back
for my martini.
I-I told you
I'm not a good hider.
- He came first.
You know, he was
the original gay on the show.
You know, and at that time,
sometimes there's only room
for one gay character.
We were gonna get to see
their turbulent
yet dependent
and loving marriage.
And it was--it was really,
really a tough thing
'cause just losing him
and not having him around.
- It's straight love
that's become closeted.
- Stanford Blatch was
one of my closest friends.
- God, I can't believe
I can't call Willie.
I cannot--I cannot believe
I can't call him.
I just...
I just can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
Oh, my God, I love this song.
- Me too.
- Oh, thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- And he would always tell me
that he was the most
popular character on the show,
and he was not making a joke.
He was quite serious.
I was like, "If you say so."
It turned out
he might have been right.
- ♪ Biggest part of me ♪
[Chicago's
"If You Leave Me Now"]
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, no,
baby, please don't go ♪
- This is my best prom ever.
- Aw.
- Thank you for coming.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Look right here.
- They're just making it.
- Oh, my God.
[apprehensive music]
This is a walk and talk
with Cynthia Nixon.
I just didn't want
your hardware
getting too close
to his software.
Remember this?
This is "Vogue" magazine
with the black
big beaded necklace.
I realized I would have
to change my lifestyle.
This is the one
that got thrown out the window.
Here. Put this on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Look, look, look. DBF.
- And he's got no money,
no savings, no nothing.
- [gasps]
Okay, you gorgeous Russian.
I'm off.
- Oh, here's Heidi.
- There's Heidi. Oh, my God.
Maybe you should just
face the fact
that you're attracted
to angry guys.
- The most notorious dress
ever on the show.
- Why are you putting freckles
on your face for this scene?
[laughter]
Because I want to.
- That's notorious.
- I mean...
- I remember that.
I'm like, "That's LA."
- We were ready for a night
on the town.
[upbeat music]
- This is Dolce Gabbana.
- Are you gonna--
- Wait and see.
♪ ♪
- I knew you had an idea!
I was hoping you would.
[laughter]
[crowd gasps]
- Fuck me hard.
[laughter]
- Now you bet, okay?
- Oh, my God,
she's fashion roadkill.
- Good times.
- [groans]
[laughter]
[playful woodwind melody]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- I'm gonna try that at first.
- Okay.
- Forgot about her.
- She's beautiful.
No one can come through here.
- No. No.
- Yes.
- No.
- Yes. Yes.
- But how did it
even fit in there?
Is that a closet
or the wardrobe from Narnia?
- Oh, no, no, no, you--
you can't smoke in here.
- But I feel like
I just had sex.
[laughter]
- I know. I'm so sorry.
Ten hours later...
[somber music]
All dressed up
and no Petrovsky to go.
[laughter]
- That was surreal to see you
sitting in this dress again.
- 20 years later!
They got the dress back out!
- I got 1979 on my face.
- 1979.
Can we make tweaks, Pebbles?
Molly just needs
to make some stuff.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- One more. Okay.
- One more rehearsal.
- Okay.
- There's just a lot
of gray right here.
- Oh!
[indistinct chatter]
- Not at all!
♪ ♪
And just like that, I realized
there are some things
that should never be put
into storage.
- Charlotte has hot flashes.
Is that how we wanted
to start this?
- No.
- How do you want to start it?
- I want to start it with,
is she with the girls--
- At the lunch.
- Like how do you start it?
- I think you start it
just by--well...
- Do you remember how I was
still getting my period
every month
very regularly for years
after you had stopped
getting yours?
- I haven't had
my period now for--
- Six months.
- Four months,
maybe three months,
four months, I think it's gone.
- I haven't got my period
in four months,
so I think
I'm finally in menopause.
- There was a rule established.
Do you know this rule?
- Mm-hmm.
- Nothing that is ever depicted
as story points,
it can't be illustrated
on the show
if it didn't happen
to someone in the room.
- You had a lot of sweats,
right?
Like, I--tell me again--
- Yeah, 'cause I'm still at
the exact same internal temp.
- Right. That's steady.
- And you also--
you gained some weight.
- I think.
[laughter]
- Welcome to the club.
Prepare to be sweaty.
- Actually, it's funny.
I haven't had any hot flashes
or tender breasts
or--or brain fog
or any of the awful symptoms
you guys had.
- How do we get
smug Charlotte in?
'Cause that's the whole reason
to do the show.
- I mean, that--all of that.
- I think it's gonna
be with Lily
when she's like, "Listen."
- No, no, no, no.
The only reason
I wanna do smug Charlotte
is that when Carrie and Miranda
just say, "Oh, smug Charlotte."
- It has been so long
since we've heard
from smug Charlotte.
I thought that perhaps
she'd retired.
- Either Lily is gonna
pull her aside
and say, "Mom!"
- Wait, Mom!
- Or maybe LTW.
- It has to be someone
more embarrassing than her kid.
- Yes, LTW-like.
- And then has to be like--
- Charlotte, come. Come here.
both: Charlotte. Charlotte.
- Come here, quick.
- It's her walking away
and Lily seeing
and being like, "Mom."
She's like, "No, I'm done."
- I am ready.
- Rattle her.
- Just when I was finally done
with my periods and now,
I still have to deal
with this shit.
- You--you may not be
as done as you think.
- Its flash period
is as you're coming out--
as you're entering menopause,
you get these--
- Unexpected.
- You go, like,
five, six months,
and then all of a sudden.
- And that is the entry
to menopause
or that's just something
that randomly happens
when you're in menopause?
- I think it's on the way to--
- On the road, yeah.
- Okay.
- I think you got
a flash period.
- I did?
What--what--what the hell
is that?
- It--it happened to me once,
months after
I thought I was done.
I was arguing a case in court,
and the opposing counsel
literally signaled
to me to look at my ass.
- And then we turn into--
- Why?
- Walk. Gently walk.
- Cut.
- We've all seen hot flashes.
We've all seen stereotypical
representations of menopause.
I had gone through something
that I have never seen
and I didn't know--
I never heard about
before it happened to me.
- I'm doing a lot
of Elisa's stories!
The tennis story is Elisa,
the flash period is Elisa,
I know, I'm Elisa now.
[soft jazz music]
- So you tried to step here
and then that.
You can't do that.
- Don't do that. Don't do that.
- So do you play tennis?
- Mm-hmm.
- I like her.
- Just thinking
about everything,
you push through it again.
- Tennis.
Tennis was fun to learn.
I had my sweet coach, Matty.
- You're gonna stay back
and your time is good,
but then once the ball
gets up in the air...
- I'm panicked.
I know, I'm panicked.
I'm panicked.
- Just a little back
behind you, that's all right.
- At least I had
a little time to learn.
Nicole's husband and her son
are, like, pro level, right?
So I'm like,
"Are they helping you?"
And she's like, "No."
And then apparently
from what I understand,
I didn't ask him personally,
but Chris Jackson,
I think, is probably the best.
So Evan, I was like,
"Can you play?"
He was like, "Oh yeah,
I played the other day."
And I was like, "Okay."
Anyone who knows me
knows that yeah,
not the kind of thing I do.
But we're gonna change that.
[upbeat jazz music]
[gibbers]
Oh, Lord. What do I do?
What do I do?
[yelps] Yes!
- Nice!
- [laughs]
- Now! Beautiful.
Now. Yes! Yes!
[humming]
- We just got a lot of
variations of different things.
- Good.
- Accordion.
That is so flat.
- Very cute.
Very cute like the one in here.
- Is this a one piece
that you were
theoretically just gonna
play tennis in?
Molly, did you see
this crazy one piece?
- There's a bunch there
that's good.
- Right, what if you need a
little zip jacket
on top of one?
- Okay.
I think I may have some trouble
based on my one lesson
playing--playing
in a zip jacket, I don't know.
It's gonna have
to be a soft zip jacket.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- You gotta go like Molly.
Do you know
what I learned today?
Look, look,
you have to start down,
and you have to go
all the way back.
- Like a golf swing?
- Yeah!
Kinda.
- Are you gonna serve?
You better serve--
- He told me that I was.
I'm scared. So scared.
- Well, this would be fun
and very Charlotte.
- Oh, my God. It's amazing!
- It looks great.
- And it's very long.
- What do we have to do?
A visor. A matching speaker.
Are we gonna get wrecked
'cause she's in the dress?
- Don't tell anyone
I'm in a dress.
Say it's a Gucci tennis outfit.
Shh.
- What are you gonna do
with your hair?
- Well, I think I have to
have it in a ponytail.
- Good answer. Go.
- Boosh! Wait, hold on. Boosh!
[soft jazz music]
♪ ♪
- Me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, my God, I'm calling
my husband right now.
He's my--I live
in a tennis house.
Tennis balls, tennis rackets,
son plays, husband plays,
daughter can hit the ball.
I think I'm just trying to,
like, fit in at home.
- I'd rather be
a professional athlete,
except they work a lot harder
than I do, so it's nice.
I'm--I'm good with it.
- I know--I know some friends
who know how to play tennis
and they're not gonna think
that I look very good.
Put maybe people who--
who'd never played before,
I look maybe--
maybe I look good.
♪ ♪
- We're just talking about
how they can almost pull it off
without the stunt doubles.
It's just editing
and the right energy.
Their game, Evan and--
Evan and Chris Jackson
are great, and Nicole's great,
and Kristin's game.
And you put the camera on here,
all of a sudden,
everybody gets better,
- Action.
Nice.
- Nice.
Thanks, babe.
Even though it was
a very long day,
the fact that
it wasn't all talking
was really nice, right?
We could get out there
and do something physical.
It was fun.
I got it!
[both grunt]
- Oh, no!
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat jazz music]
♪ ♪
[laughs]
- I'm--I'm elated.
I'm ecstatic.
It's really exciting.
I can't wait
for people to see it.
- It is magical that we're
even back here doing this.
After all these years,
it's just fantastic.
A million girls would kill.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
And Sunday?
- Sunday we're open.
- I can look here, right?
- Of course you can.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
It's a lot, yeah.
- I'm just looking for things
I like,
or now that I read nine
and ten,
I know we don't have
many scenes,
you know, that I need for.
[knock at door]
They go to a nightclub.
- Do you have your dress?
And they don't get in.
- Was I just canceled
by a doorman?
- Mm-hmm.
- Cut.
- And she'll let me try
this one tomorrow.
- Yes.
- And it'll.
[imitating cracking]
Thank you so much.
- Thank you, my dear.
- I've heard so many
wonderful things.
I had to come here first.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
- What a beautiful day.
Caw, caw! MPK!
- What?
[laughs]
- This would make Magnolia,
like, a little less...
Prancy fancy ladies that lunch.
- Then you're stuck
with it, though.
Paris is about a dream.
It's about a return.
- Bonjour.
- The name of the episode
is "Seeing the Light."
It's about light, but really,
it's about returning
to the most magical place
in her...
Aside from New York.
- SJP.
Come up.
There's tea.
When do you want me?
- All right, I'm gonna go
before she--
- No.
- Oh, yeah.
- Why?
- Yeah, this is church.
She has to come to church
by herself.
I'll come down later.
- Okay, what's the best thing
to do?
- I would like to ask you
the first easiest thing to do.
- Look at this. Look at these.
- Wait to do this dress
till the end,
or could you do this?
- Okay.
- I think this is..
- That's a no-brainer, right?
- Heaven on earth.
It's kinda great.
- Could that be bat mitzvah
with the Dior skirt?
- Yes! Yes.
Forget I said
anything about Paris.
- That's a beautiful shoe.
- So these are may--maybes.
- Maybes.
- But I could squeeze
if I had to.
- Okay. Gotcha.
- It's a nice height.
You know, it's old school
Italian movie.
- Totally.
- That's beautiful.
Wow. You guys scored here.
- That is a great color
for Magnolia.
- She stays. Frenchie.
- Mm-hmm.
- I think, you know...
- So far, these kind of--
- Are sturdy in height.
- Especially because
Vivienne Paris.
- Right, right.
- France. Oh, look at this.
Oh, my God. What is this?
- Chez Sarah.
- [chuckles]
- I mean...
- What in the hell...
- Are we gonna do?
- Well, this would be good with
the Magnolias, to be honest.
- Okay.
- Ooh.
- I know. It's a problem.
[laughter]
- She has issues.
- I just think it's so weird
and mess--
oh, it's a--it's a wreck
and it's beautiful
and it's dangling death.
- Bringing in the couture.
- It's so happening!
- Bonjour, bonjour.
Ca va?
- Oh, my God.
It's a better color
than I remembered, Molly.
The Valentino couture dress
is the only one
she's ever considered
or looked at, which is amazing.
We didn't have to show 20.
She saw it. That's the one.
- I also have to be able
to open it, which I can.
Good luck getting in there.
Yeah.
It's actually--it works,
the bag.
I think these shoes are great.
- Oh, my gosh, I feel so lucky,
and now that
we're shooting here, like,
it's all been such a--
it's all been so theoretical
and so kind of--
what's the word?
What's that word? I'm sorry.
It's been so sort of abstract.
Like an idea that we were--
I don't know
that we ever really felt
confident we would get here.
I'm so excited.
I feel so lucky
that we're here.
I can't even believe it.
I can't believe we're here.
Now, Carrie necklace.
No Carrie necklace?
What you guys think?
- Well, we were
talking about it.
- What you think?
Juvenile.
- It's--it's hard to do it.
- I know. It don't feel right.
- And it's long.
- Why don't I just put it
in my purse where it was?
Where I found it?
- Okay.
- Oh!
And that'll just be for us.
They'll tell us when
they're ready I think, Elaine.
- Yeah, Scott can do lunch now.
[indistinct chatter]
- [laughs]
Whoo!
No, I think that's going to--
that one's gonna hurt.
- This one on the back?
- Yeah.
- Still?
- No, keep going.
Got pass the pain.
♪ Having good time
for the pain ♪
- This guy?
- I thought he was talking
about me.
That's gonna be me next year.
[laughter]
- That is--it was just waiting
to be recognized.
Yeah. Perfect.
- It's not going anywhere?
- No. No.
And I think we just
almost hairspray the lace.
Maybe it will stay.
[knock at door]
Yeah.
- Come in.
- Come in. Ready?
- Yes, please.
- Yay.
- Let's go play in Paris.
♪ ♪
[engine rumbling]
- Bonsoir. Bonsoir.
- He's gonna say he didn't
say this, but he did.
He said, "What do you get
when you add a E to hat?"
[laughs]
He's a hat hater.
- I was, like, electrocuted.
I was like,
"This is a bad situation
because now Sarah Jessica
loves the hat."
As she showed,
it was a phenomenal look
for one scene
but not for many.
So now I have
to become the studio.
I have to become the monster,
the guy who slams the door
on the soufflé--pff!
- Now I'm incomplete.
Like, I feel like
I have a dangling sentence.
- He didn't like it.
I would have
made different choice--
like, I'm incomplete now.
Like, I didn't choose this,
or I chose a purse because of--
you know what I mean?
It's like this weird thing
where I feel like...
It's very painful
to feel that I'm not
producing something
that he imagines.
It's very weird to be
in somebody's head,
to put your--try to be
in somebody's head the way
they imagine or, you know,
a disagreement about a hat,
but it's when it happens,
where it happens, and how.
And then it--it's, like,
it really affects me
because of how
I feel about him.
- Just the idea that
I had to take that hat off her
was really uncomfortable.
It was bad.
- Hat killer.
You know, I wrote a poem
about it.
You want me to read it?
[laughs]
"'Where is his body,'
they ask me,
"but I will never tell.
"It's under Carrie's closet
until it starts to smell.
"It's fun at the wrap party,
"but no one can find MPK.
"I'm at the bar toasting.
"Why couldn't he ha--
let that hat stay?
"I buried him
with his favorite thing.
"I've really said my piece.
"I bury him with a hat
from France.
I'm sure he'll rest in peace."
- He laughed his ass off.
[soft piano music]
♪ ♪
- Yeah. Yeah.
Maybe we have different way
of parenting sometimes.
Obviously, Darren Star
is kind of the birth mother,
you know what I mean?
But I think
we have been parenting,
and--and like most parents,
we are primarily
aligned philosophically,
and we both feel
very protective,
not just of Carrie but of the,
you know,
the animal that it is.
Like, the living,
breathing thing.
- All right,
here's a rehearsal.
Let's all clear back.
- Carrie Bradshaw
is real to me
even though
I know she's not real.
It's a thought process
that is born
of Sarah Jessica doing Carrie
and then me sort of giving her
more to do based on that.
So it's this
very intertwined creation.
- Action.
- In my head, that seems
like an aria with no words.
There's no libretto
or song or even,
like, poetry or anything.
There's nothing.
[motorcycle engine revving]
- Cut.
- I'm covered in ashes.
- It's everything.
We're here in Paris.
The dress, the hair, her,
the purse, the emotions.
It's a big deal.
She can carry that.
It's unbelievable
how she was not upstaged
by that building behind.
[rigging rattling]
And it's--it's moving.
- See you on Thursday.
Bright and early.
[imitates rooster crowing]
- Thank you very much.
- I'll see you
on the flip side.
- You made it.
- Thank you so much.
Have super safe flight home.
- Oh, you too.
- Goodbye.
Thank you to all
the Parisian crew.
Thank you thank you.
Merci beaucoup.
Thank you all so much.
[somber jazz music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
I think this is
our last time together.
[all mock sobbing]
- I know.
Travel safe.
- Love you, ladies.
both:
Love you too.
- Thank you for coming back.
- Yeah.
- They're playing characters
from 35 to 55.
It's unique,
and it's a testament
to these three actresses...
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- Till December 8th.
[indistinct chatter]
- Oh, that's right!
That's right, which is
right around the corner.
That's right.
- Make sure
you don't wear pink.
[all laughing]
Just kidding.
- I'm not sure who all will
understand that, but we will.
- We do. We do.
- We should--
- Talk to you guys tomorrow.
[laughter]
- Cut. That's a gig.
- Cut!
[all cheering]
- On a good day,
that's a picture wrap
on the best crew
in New York city.
[cheers and applause]
- You know, the miracle
is not that we're back.
The miracle is that
we found all of you to join us.
That's the miracle.
'Cause it's just words
on a page without you all.
Just typing,
and you made it life.
So thank you,
every single person.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪