Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[upbeat music playing]
-[upbeat music continues]
-♪ GI, let's go! ♪
♪ Welcome, welcome
It's the biggest party of the year ♪
♪ Round 3 and drinks for free ♪
♪ It's a bright summer day
Wonku' muntu's been paid ♪
♪ Bring your crew
Please, ladies, don't delay ♪
♪ It's been a long time
Since we partied this way ♪
♪ Make way, GI is here to stay ♪
♪ It's been long overdue
Pop a glass, pop two ♪
♪ Let loose, what you do is up to you ♪
♪ Join the party campaign
Pop some French champagne ♪
♪ Put your glasses in the air
And let us make your day ♪
♪ Ay, mami
Don't be shy, lovely ♪
♪ Get on the dance floor
And just let loose, please ♪
♪ Leave all your worries
Woz’ojaiva nathi tonight ♪
♪ We dance all night, dance all night ♪
♪ Dance till the morning sun ♪
♪ We gonna dance all night
Dance all night ♪
♪ Dance till the morning sun ♪
♪ I see you dressed up
In your dancing shoes ♪
♪ Who, me? ♪
♪ And making you dance
Is what we came here to do ♪
♪ You're looking so good
Making me say, "Ooh!" ♪
♪ Forget your troubles
This is no time to be blue ♪
♪ We gonna dance all night
Dance all night ♪
♪ Dance till the morning sun ♪
-[music continues]
-[people whooping]
♪ Leave all your worries
Woz’ojaiva nathi tonight ♪
[whooping continues]
[speaking Afrikaans]
Tina!
Focus!
[man exclaims]
[in Afrikaans] Yes, that one.
Yes, it's a very nice one. Good morning.
How are you? Yes, there's a fish for you.
♪ Dance all night
Dance till the morning sun ♪
♪ We gonna dance all night
Dance all night ♪
♪ Dance till the morning sun ♪
[upbeat music fading]
[Tina in English]
Angie, the fish is on the table.
[Angeliena] For yesterday,
today…
and tomorrow.
[humming indistinctly]
[grunts]
Soon. I promise.
[bright music playing]
-[woman] Adrianus, did you pack lunch?
-[Adrianus] Um, I don't know.
[woman] You didn't pack it?
No, man, you must have packed it.
[indistinct chatter on radio]
[boy] What's this boot doing here?
-It stinks.
-[woman] Mine.
[sighs heavily]
[muttering] Ugh.
No, I don't have any today.
Sorry, I don't have any.
[kids clamoring]
Go ask the car behind. Please, just go.
-No, ma'am!
-[kids talking indistinctly]
-[honking loudly]
-[kids screaming]
-Asshole.
-[both] Asshole!
Asshole.
-[car backfires]
-[woman yelps]
[boy] That one really hurted.
[steam hissing]
Oh.
No, no, no.
[coughing]
Get back in, get back in.
-[upbeat music playing]
-Morning! Morning!
[laughing]
There we go.
Morning! Morning!
[muttering happily]
Hey.
-Good morning, sir. Good morning!
-[man] Morning. Morning.
[Angeliena exclaims]
That's for you.
Special today! Special today!
You go to casualty, go to casualty.
Go around, go around, go around.
This way, this way.
And then you can park right there.
Morning, morning, morning!
Romantic for you.
[muttering happily]
Yes, yes.
Been saying it for years,
this is an abomination.
This. Her.
[upbeat music continues on radio]
For God's sake,
it's about first impressions.
Your father still gave her the job.
My father's dead.
These… charities of his
have cost me and this hospital enough.
That's why the fucking world
needs more Trumps.
[honking loudly]
[honking continues]
[muttering]
No, take more time!
I've got all the time in the world!
Me too.
[sighing]
[sighs contentedly]
You know what?
Find out from the traffic department
what it will take to put
an automated parking machine in here.
[Angeliena] Fuckin' bast…
Bloody fool.
[exclaims]
Sorry.
-Oh! Now you care.
-Of course I care!
He's just…
He's just not really good with words.
Sometimes things come out wrong.
The only thing that came out wrong is him.
[muttering]
I'll come visit soon, okay?
Tell Auntie Dot
to keep a snoek ready for me.
Tell her yourself.
Hey, Ang.
-Last touch.
-Hey!
Last touch.
[bicycle bell ringing]
Captain, my captain!
-Morning, morning, captain! Morning!
-Morning, Angeliena!
[Angeliena] Here we go, we go. Yeah.
-Ha!
-[man] Ah.
Eh.
[man exclaims]
I'm so sorry, Angeliena.
What has happened all over you?
A story for another lifetime.
-Beggars can't be choosers.
-[exclaims]
Don't talk like that, Angeliena.
Your subconscious,
she doesn't have the sense for humor.
-Her thoughts become your things.
-Ah!
Man, it's not even Sunday
and you preaching.
[Angeliena mutters]
Have I got a surprise for you!
-A surprise?
-You must wait for lunchtime.
Go park your Suzuki.
I want you to see something.
Ah.
[muttering]
[ethereal music playing]
I… finished the last bit the weekend.
[ethereal music continues]
Oh, Angeliena.
It is good. It's good.
It's good. It's great, Angeliena!
[Angeliena exclaims]
So, which picture
rings your bell the most?
Ah…
Um…
Every day for the last 20 years,
Angeliena's pictures takes me
to a new hakuna matata.
[laughing heartily]
All Majaba has to do
is come stand right here
and see how he gets to go over the water.
And while he's looking,
he's waiting for the day that his
Angeliena sends him the postcards from…
one of all these places.
That's the nicest picture
this captain will like the most.
Ah, man, there's no…
rush.
Angeliena.
You must go to a doctor.
This thing of yours is getting worse.
-I'll see you at tea time.
-Take care.
Hey! Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
-Let me do this.
-Ah!
A video? Yeah.
[bittersweet music playing]
Yes!
-Let me see, let me see!
-Okay, you want to see?
[Angeliena exclaims]
You can look,
but you can't touch!
Not until you see the doctor.
[sighs heavily]
Y'all need some help?
[sensually] Yes… lots.
And a mechanic!
All right.
And a mechanic.
[car parking and door opening]
[angelic music playing]
[angelic music continues]
[choral music swelling]
[in Xhosa] Wow.
Legend, we welcome you.
[Angeliena exclaiming and laughing]
-[in English] Angie!
-Doccie!
It's so good to see you.
-[laughing]
-Angie, it's good to be back!
And look what you've done
with this place. It looks like Wonderland.
-It's my place!
-[Doctor] It's amazing.
How long has it been? 16, 17 years?
Uh, uh, 17 years, six months,
and three days to be exact.
You missed me that much?
You better believe it!
I missed you too, Angie. I missed you too.
-[Angeliena] You remembered!
-Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Statue of Liberty.
How could I forget?
You're obsessed about traveling.
-Did you ever get a chance--
-[Angeliena] Hey.
Hey! Debbie.
[muttering]
Debbie,
Doctor Alasa.
The doccie was chosen by Mitchell Sr, eh?
To go and study some medical stuff
way overseas in America. Right, doccie?
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Something, something like that.
-Yeah.
-In fact, that's why I'm back.
I'm trying to finish off what he started.
Oh!
-Yeah, it's the least I could do.
-Yes.
And besides, I missed you guys too much.
I missed you too.
-[exclaiming] Welcome back!
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much, Angie.
-Nice to see you! Nice!
It's good to see you. Thank you.
-Yes!
-Yeah…
Thank you, doctor.
[muttering]
Stay good. I'll see you around then.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
-Oh, my goodness. Doccie?
-Yeah?
Remember.
[both] Tea time!
[both laughing]
-[Alasa] Good to see you, Angie!
-Yeah, man!
[angelic music playing]
[angelic music continues]
-Hey. Clothes for the children.
-[angelic music stops]
Ah! America, the land of the free.
Ah, so nice.
You didn't have to.
That's a pleasure, my darling.
It's a pleasure.
[man clears throat]
My father gave you that, didn't he?
It's getting too much sun.
Mmm-mmm. Looks happy to me.
Your father, he teached me a lot
of things, and he said it needed sun.
It's "taught."
-Get back to work.
-[exclaims]
You know, legit scientists
have proved that people who have issues
with grammatical errors
have less agreeable personality types
than those who just let them slide.
-"Legit scientists"?
-Mmm-hmm.
What are you, her bodyguard?
He can't help that he was born
with an extra asshole.
[Debbie chuckles]
What did you say to me?
She said it's not her fault that
you were born with an extra asshole.
[scoffs]
[Debbie titters]
[in Afrikaans] Fuck, I love you!
Don't worry, just watch.
Breakfast.
-[in English] Last touch.
-Last touch.
-[laughing] See you later.
-[Debbie] Bye!
[upbeat music playing]
-[upbeat music continues]
-[clicking tongue]
[laughing softly]
[exclaims softly]
Angeliena.
Hey!
Captain Majaba.
[laughing]
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
[exclaims]
Hey!
Angeliena!
[in Xhosa] Thank you for the snoek!
I love it so much. It's very nice.
Mmm!
Angeliena.
Angeliena!
Uh…
Angeliena.
[softly] Angeliena.
[in English] Oh, not again, Angeliena.
Please wake up. Please wake up, Angeliena!
Oh, no. Help! Please! Help!
[elevator bell dings]
[Angeliena mutters groggily]
[Angeliena] That's a serious-looking
bouquet.
A serious bouquet
for a serious-sounding situation.
[mutters] Yeah.
This parking machine talk.
That's a serious situation.
Why don't you give me the lowdown on that?
You heard about the parking machine?
I might be ugly, but I'm not deaf.
Ugh, Ang, his bark is worse than his bite.
And… you're not ugly.
Don't talk to yourself like that.
How about when people show you
their bark, believe them?
You promised me you'd study your thingie.
And I've been trying
but Mitchell controls our finances.
He'll hear nothing about it,
let alone pay for it.
Pay for what, Lily, darling?
"Pray," not "pay."
You don't… You don't really pray.
-I'm a God-fearing man.
-[titters]
-[sighs]
-[Mitchell] But yeah.
No need to pray at present.
I already have everything I want.
Don't I?
[clicks tongue]
-Cheers.
[knock on door]
Yes?
How can I help?
[in Sotho] Rolihlahla.
Father of all, Dr. Majaba.
[laughs]
[in English] I was hoping
you'd still be here,
but obviously
under different circumstances.
[both laughing]
You left a boy.
And now here you are a man, a Dr. Alasa.
In the flesh. In the flesh.
-[Alasa laughing]
-[Majaba exclaiming]
Ah, Dr. Majaba.
Angeliena.
[Alasa] Yeah.
How bad is it?
I'm actually about to go see her now.
[speaking Sotho]
-[Majaba in Sotho] Yeah.
-Dr. Majaba, you've surprised me!
[both speaking Sotho]
[Majaba] Rolihlahla. Rolihlahla.
When did you get back?
-[in English] Doccie?
-Mmm?
I don't know what news you've got for me,
but I've got news for you.
It's my monthly gathering soon.
And I haven't missed one,
and I'm not planning to, so…
So you want to tell me a little bit more
about these gatherings?
Our activities,
our events, our inner workings
and membership,
are clear to us
but concealed from non-members. Capisce?
First rule of the Gathering Club…
you do not talk about the Gathering Club.
All right, and the second rule,
Dr. Majaba, is you
do not talk about the Gathering Club.
-Capisce?
-[both laughing]
-Doccie?
-[Alasa] Yeah.
Give it to me straighter than
The Fast and Furious Vin Diesel.
When? How?
Why? And how long?
[Alasa sighs]
You suffer from a rare,
but treatable disease.
And I'm afraid it's very much
a fast and a furious strain, Angie.
[somber music playing]
As you may know,
life-prolonging treatment is very much
my field of interest.
The only thing missing
while Mitchell signs is a trial patient.
And it seems to me
I've found one.
Who?
You.
Me?
But of course, Angie. Absolutely.
Wait, wait, just back up.
[speaking Afrikaans]
All this talk of life-prolonging stuff.
Am I chopping off?
I just want you to focus on
getting yourself some rest, okay?
You can clock out of here tomorrow
if you want to as long as you promise me
that you're gonna go home,
and you're gonna go straight to bed,
and get some rest, okay?
At least until I can get you
on this medication.
But what about my job?
The people, my plants!
Don't worry about your plants.
I will water your plants.
Captain,
I haven't missed a day since I started
this job and I'm not planning to.
You're not gonna be able to stand
for hours on end.
All right? It will spread the already
progressive disease even faster,
and we cannot have that.
You are not alone.
I'll be with you.
Every step of the way.
We all are, Angeliena.
Promise.
Oh, a pinky promise.
[somber music continues]
Promise.
I'll even cross my heart and hope to die.
[muttering]
-That's my job, apparently.
-[both chuckling]
-[Alasa] Good night, Angie.
-[Angeliena] Captain.
First, corona, now this.
[woman] Angeliena, come.
It's getting dark, baby.
Come.
[woman exclaims]
For me?
It's pretty.
[coughing]
[sighs]
They're giving me an appointment,
they're going to fix me.
Really?
Come lie down.
[woman singing softly in Afrikaans]
[both singing softly]
[Angeliena singing by herself]
[Angeliena singing]
Mommy?
Mommy!
Mommy, please, wake up.
Wake up!
[wind gusting]
[ethereal music playing]
[Alasa] Mitchell?
[clears throat]
I need that grant's paperwork signed.
It was supposed to be done
before I left the States. You know that.
Yeah, well, you're on Africa time now.
Get used to it.
[Alasa sighs]
[singing] ♪ Yeah, there's this girl ♪
♪ Angeliena
Call her, Angeliena ♪
♪ If you want to see the sun ♪
♪ This girl ♪
♪ From Khayamandi ♪
♪ Ekhaya Khayamandi ♪
♪ Khaya, let me go home ♪
[Angeliena] "A group of progressive
neurological disorders
that destroy the cells that control
essential, voluntary muscle activity,
such as speaking,
walking, breathing, and swallowing."
"Some are not fatal and progress slowly."
"Others such as… my one…
are fatal."
[ethereal twinkling]
[voice breaking] Captain…
I'm not scared to die.
But I'm not ready yet.
♪ Hey, girl ♪
♪ Angeliena ♪
♪ Is it true that your rivers run ♪
♪ Beneath the sky? ♪
♪ Hey, girl ♪
♪ Angeliena ♪
♪ I'd love to see ♪
♪ Your rainbow in the African sky ♪
[mystical music playing]
-[mystical music continues]
-[Auntie Dot muttering]
[snorting]
[muttering]
[muttering continues]
[snorting]
[sputtering and muttering]
Forty-three. Forty-three.
Hmm. Oh.
[exclaims]
[mystical music continues]
[kissing]
-Damn.
-[Lily laughs softly]
You smell as good as you look.
It's not too late to change your mind.
Come with me.
You know this is my once a month, my love.
Just don't get too comfortable
in those roots of yours again.
There's no space for them
in the real world.
Yeah?
Can I at least drop you off?
Um… I'll Uber, thank you.
Suit yourself.
Love you.
[quietly] Love you.
I mean, by doing many more operations,
getting the people through.
-And your timing…
-[waitress] Can I top you up, doctor?
-No, thank you.
-[Mitchell] So less time in beds.
Less time in beds, absolutely.
Make sure they move through.
Sir, your table is ready.
Well, cheers to Lawrence,
who once again kicked all our asses and…
[Mitchell laughing]
…came out tops
with record-breaking profits.
-Cheers, Lawrence. Cheers, buddy.
-[all] Cheers.
-[glasses tinkling]
-[man chuckling]
How the hell do you do that?
Hospital business is
as much of a business as…
wall business, property business,
show business.
-[man] Absolutely.
-[Mitchell] Money is money.
Money is money.
[woman] We all know money is money.
But money with heart, that's legacy.
And if I recall correctly,
that's something
your dad always used to say.
And my dad never achieved
this kind of financial success.
I'm busy breaking records
with my profit margins.
I'm making the hospital business
great again.
-Ah!
-[woman] That might be so.
But I hear that profitable hospitals
might be using local monopoly
to overcharge insurers and patients.
I'm bringing traditional values back.
Free market capitalism,
a bit of deregulation where needed.
Some internal social conservative policies
and restrictions.
Just look at the turnaround already!
All there.
Another round for my colleagues, please.
And a shot of your best tequila
for the faithless on my right.
Hakuna tequila, Doctor Vundla,
it means no worries
for the rest of your night.
[man laughing]
I don't drink tequila.
Well, we can't all be perfect, can we?
[all] Cheers!
[all laughing and whooping]
[speaking Afrikaans]
There.
Huh?
[Angeliena laughing]
Always forgetting.
-Forever. Mmm.
-[Spaghetti Western music playing]
Angeliena, cards.
[Spaghetti Western music continues]
-Snap! Snap! Snap!
-[all exclaiming]
[Lily] Again?
[Angeliena] I win again!
I win again! Ha-ha!
[all laughing]
Attacking my nerves.
-[alarm beeping]
-[yelps]
My lotto results.
Ah, here we go again. How…
-Auntie, man, please.
-[Auntie Dot muttering]
Leave Auntie Dot and her dream.
And while you're at it, leave mine.
Those dreams, they don't discriminate.
-Unlike you, Tina.
-[Tina] "Discriminate"?
How long has Auntie Dot
been playing the lotto?
And how long have we been living
in this Ocean View?
Clue.
Ask your husband's people.
And did you not hear
about Angeliena's diagnosis?
And now this,
after everything that she's been through.
Don't you think she's been through enough?
We've all been through enough?
And then this?
So, no, it's not discrimination.
It's annihilation.
But you're a good one to judge, Lily.
'Cause you married up.
Hey. Who's discriminating now, eh?
Okay, let me ask you, since when do
people like us go over the seas anyway?
[Auntie Dot scoffs]
[Tina] Or win the lotto?
It can still happen.
Some of us are late bloomers.
-Do you even have a passport?
-Tina!
Just drop it, Tina.
So it was a stupid dream.
Some of us make mistakes, you know.
Like coming here.
-Angie, don't go.
-[Auntie Dot mutters]
[Tina] Don't… don't go, Angeliena.
[Angeliena in Afrikaans] Leave me alone!
[Tina in English] Sorry, Angeliena.
I'm just sick and tired
of seeing us always come last.
[Angeliena] Don't make
your problems mine again!
No, man, please, Angie. Stay, Angeliena.
[speaking Afrikaans]
Take my name out of your mouth
and fuck off!
[laughing]
But I'm not the one
that invested in a new MRI machine!
Not just one, my friend.
-Two.
-[Mitchell] Oh, my God.
And I budgeted only for one!
-[woman] Mr. Mitchell.
-Don't worry, they'll pay for themselves.
-Mr. Mitchell.
-In 20 years.
Mr. Mitchell!
Doctor Mitchell.
The one and only.
Can I have a word with you?
Word away.
There seems to be a problem
with your card.
[card clatters]
[scoffs]
[men laughing]
-That's probably just a glitch.
-He made all the profits.
Exactly. Thank you, thank you.
I must say, my hospital,
like others sitting at this table,
barely broke even this year.
So Dr. Mitchell,
thank you very much.
I'll leave this one
in your profitable hands.
-Dr. Botha.
-Joan.
-You're on your way.
-I am indeed.
-Drive safe.
-Will do.
-Good night.
-Bye.
[Botha sighs]
Mitch, buddy, let me see if I can help.
-Mmm-mmm. I've got it, really.
-No, let me see.
What is the damage here? Ah…
Fuck. Thanks for a nice evening.
[both laughing]
Swipe it again.
-[baby cooing]
-Code zero-five.
No funds.
-Let me speak to the manager.
-Speaking.
-Let me talk to the owner, then.
-Talking.
[laughs]
You've gotta be fucking kidding me.
Nope. Comedy…
not my thing.
I'll do an EFT from another account.
I'll wait.
[muttering in Afrikaans]
-[mutters]
-[computer chimes]
-[chimes]
-[exclaims]
[yawns]
[smooth jazz music playing]
[jazz music continues]
-[jazz music stops]
-[record skipping]
[banging on door]
[banging continues]
[man] Miss Kruiper.
I'm Sergeant van der Merwe.
This is Sergeant Zulu.
It's regarding a Mr. Majaba.
His neighbors gave your address
as the other next of kin.
I'm sorry to tell you, but…
Mr. Majaba passed away in his sleep
last night.
It's natural causes.
His body has been taken to the morgue.
But there's still his personal belongings,
and we'll need you
to come sign for his body
to be transported
back to the Eastern Cape.
Condolences, ma'am.
I'm so sorry, Ms. Kruiper.
[door closing]
-[crying softly]
-[somber music playing]
[sobbing] Captain.
Captain.
-["The Lighthouse" by Majozi playing]
-♪ When it's dark ♪
♪ And cold outside ♪
♪ I will never ever ever need to hide ♪
♪ As long as I know you're alive ♪
♪ And that you're always by my side ♪
♪ I gave you my hand
And I gave you my heart ♪
♪ I wasn't worthy of you from the start ♪
♪ You are a lighthouse
That shines on the sea ♪
♪ Came down from Heaven and rescued me ♪
♪ When it's dark and cold outside ♪
♪ I will never ever ever need to hide ♪
♪ As long as I know you're alive ♪
♪ And that you're always by my side ♪
♪ I gave you my hand
And I gave you my heart ♪
♪ I wasn't worthy of you from the start ♪
♪ You are a lighthouse
That shines on the sea ♪
♪ Came down from Heaven and rescued me ♪
[song fading]
Hi, sorry. Sorry.
Angeliena Kruiper.
[laughs]
Sorry.
[chuckles]
Kruiper, Kruiper.
Kruiper.
Hmm.
[mutters]
Just sign… Sign there.
[laughs]
I'm sorry about your captain.
Yeah.
Actually, just in time, sister.
[laughs]
In time for what?
You see,
Mitchell sold all
of these refrigeration storage chambers.
All of them.
They're coming…
they're coming to pick them up tomorrow.
Including
all the dead bodies inside of them,
the unclaimed ones.
For real?
[whispers] Fuck! What the fuck?
I mean, check, check, check.
Check for yourself. Check for yourself.
It's this one, right here.
Mitchell, Mitchell.
Mitchell.
[chuckles softly]
-He signed all of this?
-All of it.
Fucking bastard.
What the hell?
There's all… all types of orders in here.
Okay.
Now…
How much for this, huh?
Take it.
[laughs]
For real, for real?
For real, take it!
Bloody fool. That bastard.
[speaking Afrikaans]
[downbeat music playing]
-[wistful music playing]
-[crying softly]
Captain.
My captain.
-[grunts]
-[monitor turning on]
[Majaba on video] Now… action!
-[triumphant music playing]
-Just imagine their faces
when this Angeliena is really going to go
to her pictures
with the aeroplane!
Come, Angeliena, let's go!
[shouting] Angeliena!
We're going to the airport!
[all cheering and whistling]
Yeah!
-[triumphant music continues]
-Rrrr-a! Rrrr-a!
[triumphant music continues]
[Majaba] It's good! It's good!
It's good! It's easy, Angeliena!
It always seems impossible
until it is done!
[all] Yeah!
[turns off]
Okay, my captain.
Okay.
I promise.
[exclaims softly]
Next.
Ma'am, please take your headscarf off.
It's just procedure.
They gotta see your hair.
No scarfs, no hats, no earrings.
They've got no style.
Now, straight into the camera,
and say,
"Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious."
-[upbeat music playing]
-[camera flashing]
[upbeat music continues]
[whistling]
Irie, sister, one love.
How much to
skip the line kind of passport, huh?
The clock is ticking, man.
How much you have, sister?
Money.
[struggling]
[mutters]
My sister.
Please don't take me for a Bushman.
[in Afrikaans] Come on, how do you see me?
[in English] Open it, man.
[speaking Afrikaans]
Fuck.
Christmas box.
My passport.
Irie?
Irie, my sister.
Irie, irie. Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
I's all right. Yeah.
Yeah, it's okay. It's okay.
[both in Afrikaans] She's gonna fly!
She's gonna fly!
[Tina in English] Look, she did it!
-[upbeat music continues]
-[phone chiming]
[whistling]
[somber music playing]
[scoffs] You've gotta be kidding me.
A fucking bum doing EFTs?
How did she even afford this?
You've disrespected me.
Again.
We spoke about this.
And I was going to transfer it back to her
during lunch break.
[whispers] Excuse me.
[angrily] I thought we were clear
on this matter!
And we are.
I swear.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
[exhales]
[somber music playing]
[Lily clears throat]
[phone dialing]
[woman on speakerphone]
Welcome to the traffic department.
If you know the extension of your call,
please dial it now.
Alternatively,
please hold for the operator.
-[dials]
-Lawrence…
Angeliena's dying. Please have a heart.
Desiree. Dr. Lawrence Mitchell,
Grand Freedom Hospital.
How are you?
Fine. Fine, thanks.
How are your little ones?
That's good.
Oh, nothing. I…
[laughing]
Yes.
That's correct.
I, uh… I wanted to know when the council
was planning on putting in
the proposed automatic parking machine.
Uh-huh.
Hmm! Wonderful.
Good news, then.
No, no, that's it.
Yup. Always lovely hearing your voice.
Okay, all right.
Bye-bye, now.
[Alasa] Mitchell.
Mitchell!
Mitchell, hold up a second.
What?
If you don't sign that grant,
they will pull the funding
and they will give it to someone else.
Your father spent years on this.
I did not come all this way for nothing.
No one forced you to do anything.
You're gambling with people's lives here.
I'm gonna report this to the board, your
behavior will not be my problem anymore!
You shouldn't shit on another man's
doorstep if you know nothing of his home.
-This is my home!
-Was your home!
You left,
and now you're back when it suits you to
save the day like some big fucking hero.
Well, good luck. Join the queue.
And if the race card is next,
that queue is even longer.
I had to leave.
Who wouldn't for such an opportunity?
Someone needs to step up
and finish what your dad started.
"Step up"?
Step up.
[laughing]
Trust my dad's little pet project
to stamp his feet where they don't belong.
I'll sign that grant
when I'm presented with
a suitable trial patient.
Suitable.
As in someone who's earned the right
to stay alive.
Who contributes to society
and the face of this hospital,
not some fucking oxygen thief.
Why don't you just go back
where you came from,
before this hospital
breaks your heart too.
[somber music playing]
[exclaims]
Let's travel.
I'm Angeliena Kruiper,
and I want to book
a ticket around the world
that you've been advertising.
Mmm.
Ah.
Nice to meet you, Miss Kruiper.
I'm Brandt, and nothing will give me
greater pleasure
than to book
that around the world trip for you.
As long as you remember
that there is no change policy to the
ticket because of the special price.
-So, dates are locked, yes?
-Yeah, yeah.
[typing]
Payment?
Hello.
[clears throat]
Let's make it happen.
[typing]
Away.
[upbeat music playing]
What are you doing?
Get out. Get out.
Get out.
I don't have any change.
I'm not looking for money.
Then what do you want?
Suitcases.
[chuckles]
Traveling, are we?
Nationally or internationally?
Internationally.
[scoffs] Do you have any idea
the distances one has to cover
while transferring
at an international airport?
No? Well, let me tell you.
King Khalid International Airport
is 780 square kilometers.
That's bigger than
its neighboring country, Bahrain.
And Heathrow Airport processes
75,000,000 people per annum
last time they counted.
So…
[chuckles]
Good luck to you schlepping that bag
across an international airport.
The modern-day traveler's suitcase needs…
stamina.
Chutzpah.
Built-in combination locks.
And wheels.
Okay.
All right.
Then I'll take all of the three pink ones.
[laughing]
No, no, no. Don't… don't you hurt me.
I have children.
I'm not gonna hurt you!
Yo…
There. For your children.
Make it your grandchildren…
[Angeliena muttering in Afrikaans]
[bell tolling]
Turnover every half hour,
that's plus-minus…
200 cars a day at least.
Ka-ching!
-[man whistling]
-[Mitchell] Right.
Yeah. No, no, no.
Thanks again for bringing this gold mine
under our attention.
From the old South Africa to the new,
the paperwork must have got lost.
Indeed, what had become a parking lot,
is in fact, our land.
[man] Ya, and I always say,
it's good to know there's still some good,
honest people out there, doctor.
[speaking Afrikaans]
Um, are you sure you don't want to
go after this parking attendant, though?
You know, operating
illegally like that for so long.
She must have pocketed a cent or two.
I can probably get the details for you.
Ugh. No, don't worry. I mean…
honestly,
how much can a bum actually make?
Well…
We only worry about
big money.
Ya, and anyway, I must go now.
Okay. It's my lunch break, and every
second that I spend here talking to you
is eating into that break time,
and I must go on eating now, so…
Stay safe on the roads, eh?
I'm just… I'm glad to be of help.
You know, one man's trash
is another man's treasure.
One man's trash is…
That's a bloody nice quote.
Thank you for sharing.
Ta-ta.
Bon appétit, I guess.
He's always hungry.
What are you doing here, Lily?
What are you doing here?
I thought I'd look into
that course you keep talking about.
Everything I do for you lately
seems to be making you unhappy.
I thought, I don't know,
maybe this would make you happy.
I don't…
I don't want to lose you.
I'm right here, Lawrence.
I'll sign that grant.
Okay?
Yeah. Ask…
Angeliena to come into the office,
get the paperwork out of the way,
get her on the program.
Thank you.
Do what you please with the course.
You do what you please anyway.
[somber music playing]
-[knock on door]
-[Auntie Dot] Angeliena?
What's this? We got the message.
Are you sick?
[Tina] Are you fine? Are you okay?
Don't, man… Don't worry.
Just look.
Look, you are going to get us all killed
with this over the water nonsense.
[Auntie Dot] Please, Angeliena,
you've got to keep yourself still.
[scoffing] There.
Are you joking?
She bought the fucking tickets!
-[Auntie Dot] Huh?
-With what?
[exclaiming]
Man.
I'm going overseas
whether you believe it or not.
Ciao bella.
[speaking Afrikaans]
-[phone chiming]
-Ah…
[exclaims softly]
Mmm. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[sighs contentedly]
-[ominous music playing]
-[machinery thudding]
-[ominous music continues]
-[tools clanking]
[wailing] Stop!
[sobbing] Stop it!
[crying hysterically]
You bastard!
You fucking bastard!
-My flowers!
-[Mitchell] Come!
-You guys! Get this shit off my property!
-[Angeliena] You bastard!
Here! Come, come, come!
[hysterically] You bastard!
-[wailing incoherently]
-That's it!
[Angeliena sobbing]
Look what he's done to my house!
You bastard!
No! No!
[screaming hysterically]
[screaming] You bastard!
[wailing hysterically] No!
[wailing continues]
Look what he's done to my stuff!
[sobbing] My stuff…
My plants.
[melancholy music playing]
[music continues]
So, where to, ladies?
-[Lily] Excuse me.
-[Angeliena] What are you doing?
[Angeliena nervously] What?
The closest visa agency, please,
but we need to pick up a few people
on the way.
[music continues faintly on radio]
Are you drunk?
-Not yet. Come here. I'm sorry. Come on.
-[Angeliena sniffling]
-[Angeliena crying]
-I know.
I'm sorry, Ang.
[melancholy music continues]
[music fading]
[woman] Welcome, ladies.
My assistant by day
and daughter by night when…
the day nurse can't come.
So…
-Where are we going to this morning?
-Oh, no, it's not for me, it's for…
[slowly with difficulty] Uh, I…
I… want a visa…
for…
a trip around the world.
Please.
Uh, apologies.
How exciting!
I've always wanted to do it,
but I just never had the guts.
[laughs]
[clears throat]
Your ticket and passport, please.
Okay, so…
you'll need about
five visas in total,
and get away with a Schengen visa for…
for Europe.
[muttering indistinctly]
The only other thing I'll need from you
before we get started on your application
is a medical certificate
that deems you fit for travel.
I know. Corporate and companies,
they are so strict about
liabilities.
From the airlines to border control,
they all seem to have this bee
in their bonnet about it these days.
But she's paid for her ticket in full
and there's no change policy
on her ticket.
She doesn't have time to wait anymore.
Can't you see?
I can see that and that is the problem.
Because they will see it as well.
I'm on your side here.
As soon as I get the certificate,
I will put it right through.
And I… we will…
work through my lunch breaks if I have to.
This…
is my direct line.
-I knew it, I knew it.
-Shh, Tina.
[both speaking Afrikaans]
[softly] No, no, my girlie.
No.
[slowly] Don't feel sorry for me.
You…
You go
and make your life spectacular.
-Promise?
-Promise.
Pinky promise?
Pinky promise.
I'll be okay. I'll… I'll be fine.
[sniffling]
[both speaking Afrikaans]
[Tina] What's with the suitcases?
Oh, shut up! Next!
What is… What's going on? Eh?
This is next.
Now, you might not want to meet next,
but next wants to meet you.
Tina?
At number one we have a Huisgenoot.
[Lily] Mmm!
Read one of these and you will realize
that no story is as bad as
the ones that they write in here.
Not even yours.
And, secondly,
the best of Ben &amp; Jerry's,
ice cream recipe book.
Because it's always the answer,
no matter what the question is.
And…
-Hit it, Auntie Dot!
-Yes, sir! Table!
[all humming and singing]
[Auntie Dot laughing]
Ta-da!
[slowly] It's nice.
It's very beautiful.
-Pleasure.
-And, lastly.
A candle.
Because you, my dear,
are the light at the end of the tunnel.
Light?
[slowly with difficulty] There's no light
at the end of my tunnel.
I didn't even know
what suitcases to buy.
And I didn't even know
how big Heathrow Airport is.
Hey, Ang.
You have more light in you
than all the lights
in all the tunnels put together.
[Angeliena clicks tongue]
-Come.
-[Auntie Dot] Come.
-[Angeliena] What? What's happening? What?
-Come on, come on, come on.
-That's right.
-Come on.
[in Afrikaans] Tina, open that door!
-[in English] What's going on? What?
-[Auntie Dot muttering]
Look at this place.
-Outside. Go. You stay.
-What? What's happening?
-What's happening?
-Stay!
You stay.
What's…
[dance music playing]
[all cheering]
[all] Surprise!
-[all cheering and clapping]
-[dance music continues]
Oh, my goodness!
Danny boy! The boy! Attaboy!
-[music continues]
-[Angeliena exclaiming]
[music stops]
-Speech!
-[all] Speech! Speech!
Speech! Speech! Speech!
[chanting and clapping continues]
Uh…
[slurs indistinctly]
[indistinct]
[Auntie Dot muttering]
Yeah.
[both muttering]
She says, "Thank you!"
[all cheering]
[upbeat music playing]
[music stops]
-[Debbie] Careful. Stand back.
-[Alasa] Somebody call an ambulance!
-[Debbie] Stand back.
-Angie?
-Are you all right?
-[Debbie] I'm getting the bag.
All right, thank you.
Debbie, she's got a faint pulse.
-We're gonna need to stabilize her.
-Just hold on.
[Alasa] You're gonna be okay. All right.
There we go. Angie.
Angie.
All right, Debbie.
We're gonna stabilize you.
[siren wailing]
[Debbie] Come on.
I'll meet you at the hospital.
[Debbie sighs]
-[Tina] English, please.
-[Debbie] Sorry.
[Tina] No fancy talk.
[speaking Xhosa]
[sighs]
Right, um…
With this type of disease,
there will be some good days
and there will be some bad days.
We can… we can work with that.
That's good, because the bad days
will be more than the good days.
That's what we've got for now.
If you'll excuse me, um,
I need to get back to Angeliena.
[somber music playing]
[indistinct chatter on radio]
[woman on radio] Truth Coffee.
Visit truthcoffee.com to experience
the joy of the extraordinary.
[upbeat jingle playing on radio]
[reporter on radio] The sudden, unexpected
auction of the Grand Freedom Hospital
brings communities to their knees.
-Instant job losses face hundreds.
-Fuck. Bastard.
The future for its groundbreaking
MND clinic seems even darker.
Today, we have with us in the studio
Dr. Lawrence Mitchell,
son of the late Dr. Mitchell Senior
of the Grand Freedom Hospital.
Bastard!
Despite the challenges, Dr. Mitchell's
leadership and accomplishments
-ensure he is the right--
-[radio turns off]
[Angeliena mutters]
[straining]
[yelling in frustration]
Fuck!
[Majaba on video] You know
how much this old gogo
wanted to see his Madiba's house.
-[faint upbeat music playing]
-Now, he's here.
-[upbeat music continues]
-You see?
Ahh!
Seeing it
is believing it.
Now,
my Angeliena,
she's coming too.
Just look at our Nelson.
[upbeat music playing]
Your playing small
does not serve the world.
If your dreams
don't scare you,
they're not big enough.
Come on, Angeliena…
yours is good…
is good,
is good.
-It's…
-[snaps fingers]
…great, my Angeliena.
[inhales deeply]
Okay.
Okay, my captain.
All right.
[upbeat music continues softly]
Number.
[slowly with difficulty] Hello?
I want to know
how far my voice box thingie is.
Ah.
Y… Yes.
Cash on delivery.
I'll wait. Okay.
[upbeat music continues softly]
[sighs]
[car approaching]
You sure about this?
You do know, if they accept your bid,
there's going to be nothing left?
As in not a cent. Nada.
[over voice box] I finally know
what it feels like to be sure.
Okay.
Do you know someone in the fraud unit?
Oh…
This is so bad.
[laughing]
God, another dishonest prick.
But, Angeliena,
why did you wait this long to act on it?
Especially after everything he's done.
It was never about him.
Lily.
Friendship is more important than revenge.
And the money?
You had it all this time.
But why the wait? Why the secrecy?
Stuff.
Here. Here.
And I've been given a serious deadline.
[cane clacking]
What the hell?
And who the hell are you?
I'm representing my client,
Ms. Angeliena Kruiper.
Did you really think
that the union was gonna scare me?
I'm her lawyer.
Just get the hell out of my office.
[over voice box]
It's not your office anymore.
You're right.
The hospital sold at auction yesterday
for a small fortune.
I know.
Detective?
[lawyer speaking Afrikaans]
Detective Angelov, Fraud Unit.
Cuff him.
Twenty years of car guarding
is a much more financially sound trade.
And the misappropriations of funds, not.
[Angeliena] Mitchell.
Bullies don't scare me.
Not anymore.
Thank you. Thank you.
-We'll be in touch.
-[Lawyer] Thank you, detective.
We did it! We did it!
You did it.
-[imitates explosion]
-[laughing]
[upbeat music playing]
[mellow music playing]
[muttering indistinctly]
[muttering continues]
[groans]
[speaking Afrikaans]
[muttering]
[muttering in disbelief]
[speaking Afrikaans]
Tina? Tina!
Tina! Tina! Tina!
Tina!
[triumphant music playing]
[Auntie Dot] Knock, knock.
[Tina] Knock, knock.
[over voice box] And this?
Auntie,
don't take me for a--
Open it.
♪ Guess who won the lotto? ♪
It's people like us who won the lotto!
[laughing]
Auntie?
For me?
A trip around the world?
Bon voyage!
[mellow music playing]
[Angeliena] Sweet dreams,
Desmond Frank Majaba.
[mellow music continues]
♪ There's this girl, Angeliena ♪
♪ Call on Angeliena
If you want to see the sun ♪
♪ This girl… ♪
[Angeliena] Sometimes it just takes
a while to keep a promise.
♪ Let me go home ♪
♪ Hey, girl, Angeliena ♪
♪ Is it true that your rivers run
And meet the sky? Hey, girl… ♪
[Angeliena] Annihilate.
[chuckles]
♪ Love to see your rainbow
In the African sky ♪
[Angeliena] Thank you, Auntie.
Waiting on the other side.
♪ Why the birds of love ♪
♪ Keep dancing in the summer rain ♪
♪ It's a feeling ♪
♪ Feels like Africa… ♪
For you, boss.
♪ I want to try ♪
[Angeliena] Yeah.
It always seems impossible
until it's done.
♪ Always remember ♪
♪ That you're the beauty of Africa ♪
♪ There's this girl ♪
♪ Kwezi ♪
♪ Call on Kwezi
Kwezi is the movement, she's the earth ♪
♪ Hey, girl, Kwezi ♪
♪ Teach me all the secrets
Of the rhythm in your ground ♪
♪ Hey, girl ♪
♪ Kwezi ♪
♪ You remind me of Madiba
You unite us in your dance ♪
♪ Hey, girl ♪
♪ Kwezi ♪
♪ I think Kwezi is the rhythm
Of the African drum ♪
♪ I want to know ♪
♪ Why the birds of love ♪
♪ Keep dancing in the summer rain ♪
♪ It's a feeling ♪
♪ Feels like Africa ♪
♪ I want to try ♪
♪ Like the rivers in your sky ♪
♪ To water the soil when it's dry ♪
♪ Always remember ♪
♪ You're the beauty of Africa ♪
♪ Minjani, tsakane ♪
♪ Tsaki brings us joy
In everlasting love ♪
♪ Nako randza, Tsaki ♪
♪ You're the love that healed my people
And by you I'll stand ♪
♪ But I want to know ♪
♪ Why the birds of love ♪
♪ Keep dancing in the summer rain ♪
♪ It's a feeling ♪
♪ That feels like Africa ♪
♪ I want to try ♪
♪ Like the rivers in your sky ♪
♪ To water the soil when it's dry ♪
♪ Always remember ♪
♪ That you're the beauty of Africa ♪
♪ Africa ♪