[eerie music playing]
[rumbling]
[ Y2flix.cc - Watch Movies and TV Shows Online for Free ]
[Riya] Who's there? Who am I?
What's happening?
- [indistinct whispering]
- [Riya] What is this place?
- [shrieks]
- [Riya] It's your fault.
- [voices] There's nothing they
can say!
- [Riya] Did I do this?
I can't think straight.
- [indistinct whispering]
- [woman] Do it.
[machine whirring]
[facility beeping]
[facility] Abnormal activity
detected.
[machine whirring]
[Riya sighs]
[Riya groans]
[thundering]
[groans]
- [facility beeping]
- [groans]
[facility] System failure.
Reboot to activate
standby power.
[pants]
[groans]
- [groans]
- [machine whirring]
- [button beeps]
- [gasps]
[facility beeping]
[facility] System failure.
Reboot to activate
standby power.
[Riya] Hello?
[gasps]
[machine whirring]
- [suspenseful music playing]
- [Riya] Hello?
[electricity crackling]
[facility beeping]
Security system breach.
[Riya gasps]
[facility beeping]
[facility] Abnormal activity
detected.
[eerie music playing]
- [machine whirring]
- [facility beeping]
[facility] System Failure.
Reboot to activate
standby power.
[computer stuttering]
[Riya gasps]
[Riya] Hey.
[eerie music playing]
[computer stuttering]
[facility] Reboot to activate
standby power.
[facility powering up]
- [upbeat music playing]
- [facility beeping]
[facility]
Station standby power activated.
[door hissing]
[eerie music playing]
[thundering]
[soft music playing]
Hello?!
[thundering]
Hello?
[soft music playing]
[thundering]
[coughs]
Where am I?
[grunts]
[wonderment music]
[thundering]
[Riya] Brion.
[chokes, gasps]
[coughs]
[retches]
[gasps]
[coughs]
[coughs, gasps]
[gasps]
[thundering]
[facility beeping]
[facility]
Vital oxygen levels compromised.
[pants]
[Clarke] Riya.
[screams]
[shrieks]
[upbeat music playing]
Pass.
- [crowd chuckles]
- [chuckles] Oh, come on.
- Someone's gotta say something.
- Uh. [clears throat]
How about...
we will prosper here. Huh?
- [chuckles]
- [Kevin] What?
- [Audie] Yeah, yeah.
- [Kevin chuckles] What?
- [Riya] "We will prosper here."
- [Kevin] Right?
- What the hell does that even
mean?
- What are you, the queen?
- I think it's nice.
- Nah?
- Nice? Nice is fucking boring.
All right, folks, here we go.
In honour of our dear friend in
the Orbital,
five delicious bowls
of Brion's boiled beans.
- [Clarke grunts]
- To Brion.
- Hmm.
- [Clarke] To Brion.
- To Brion.
- Yeah.
- So, Clarke, you, uh...
you think you got
something better?
- [Audie] Hmm.
- No.
Ask Riya.
Chances are she's gonna be
the first one out.
[Kevin chuckling]
- I am?
- [Clarke chuckling]
- Don't look at me.
- [Kevin chuckling]
- [Clarke] Nah, come on, guys.
- How about you, Cap?
[Kevin] Yeah, let's go, Cap.
Come on.
I say
we should focus on our mission.
- Oh!
- [Kevin] This guy.
Captain Syed Audie,
first man to set foot
- on planet K.O.I.-442...
- [Kevin] Mm-hmm.
...and his famous first
words were...
- [Audie farts]
- [all laugh]
- [Clarke] Delicious.
- Guys.
- Shit.
- [Davis] Fucking savory.
Let's say it's you, then.
What is it?
You're one small step.
- [Davis] Come on.
- [Clarke chuckling]
You really think
we're gonna head out soon?
Yeah, probably.
I mean, uh, this planet, like...
The fact that the atmosphere is
almost breathable already,
like, I-- I would be shocked
if any of the others found
something
even close to this viable.
You know what you're doing?
- You're doing your little thing.
- No. No.
- She's good.
- [Clarke] Oh!
- I know.
- I see it. I see it.
- [all chant] Riya. Riya. Riya.
- Guys, okay.
- [all chant] Riya. Ri...
- Okay, guys, guys. Okay.
- Oh God. I hate you.
- Come on, you love us.
- [sighs] Okay.
- [Clarke chuckles]
[Kevin] Come on.
- Um.
- Yep?
I'm thinking-- I'm thinking,
um...
How about...
let's not fuck it up this time.
[chuckles] Yeah.
- Wow
- What?
Kind of a downer?
Come on, guys,
I don't even want to do this.
Cheers.
[electricity crackling]
[computer stuttering]
[inhales]
- [patch beeping]
- [sighs]
- [soft music playing]
- [pants]
[winces]
[shower pattering]
[Riya] Who am I?
[suspenseful music playing]
[bell chiming]
[Riya reading] "Oxygen
saturation."
"Cabin pressure"
- [airlock banging]
- [gasps]
[facility beeping]
[facility] Movement detected
at Zone One.
[facility] Exterior airlock.
[airlock banging]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [airlock banging]
- [facility beeping]
[facility] Movement detected
at Zone One.
[facility] Exterior airlock.
[airlock banging]
[thundering]
[wind howling]
[airlock banging]
[airlock hissing, opening]
[footsteps receding]
- [Riya grunts]
- [Brion groans]
- [Brion groans, pants]
- [Ria grunts]
- [groans]
- Who are you?
- Riya!
- What the fuck?
- [pants]
[Brion pants]
[grunts]
It's me.
Brion.
Brion Cargyle.
Here. Look.
I'm Seven-F.
We're on the same crew. Okay?
I'm orbital monitoring.
- Brion?
- That's right.
Brion.
Brion's boiled beans.
[chuckles]
Boiled beans.
Yeah. That's me.
You sent me a distress call.
An SOS.
Said that Clarke had
some sort of psychotic break.
Turned on the crew.
Is she the one that did
this to you?
Davis too?
I'm sorry.
When-- when I woke up...
everything had already happened.
What had already happened?
[suspenseful music playing]
What do you remember?
Um...
Just...
moments.
Images.
A woman.
- Attacking us. I...
- Clarke.
Any idea where she might be?
No. When I woke up,
there was no one left.
That's all you remember?
I'm sorry. I... [clears throat]
[sighs] It's just everything
that is going on.
I don't know where I am.
I don't know who I am.
[soft music playing]
Wait here.
- [thundering]
- [soft music playing]
- [button beeps]
- [Medbot powering up]
- Welcome to Medbot.
- Yes.
[Riya] You said Seven-F.
[Medbot repeats welcome in
Japanese]
- What does it mean?
- [Medbot beeping]
Mission and vessel.
Wait.
Do you not remember Earth?
At all?
No.
- [sighs]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[Medbot beeping]
Medbot is now scanning,
please remain calm.
Missions one through six failed.
Seven's our final hope.
Half a dozen vessels
spread across the galaxy.
Targeting viable Earth-sized
planets.
- Mission Seven. Vessel F.
- Mm-hmm.
That's us.
And we have the great honor of
calling K.O.I.-442 our home.
Or Ash.
As Kev used to call it.
[Medbot beeping]
[gasps]
- [Riya panting] -Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
I know, it's weird.
Just-- just try to stay calm.
You okay?
[Riya] Yeah.
Yeah.
How come you were able to stay
in orbit.
[Brion] That's how it works.
For the first year, at least.
One of us has to stay up there.
To establish comms with
home base.
Or, well,
if anything goes wrong.
[Riya] I think I saw you.
A light across the sky.
- Is that the Orbital?
- That's the one.
- Every couple days we line-up.
- [Medbot beeping]
[Medbot] Next phase beginning,
please remain calm.
- [Riya groans] -[Medbot repeats
itself in Japanese]
- [Riya pants] -[Medbot] Thank
you for using Medbot.
[Medbot repeats itself in
Japanese]
Hey, have you been experiencing
any fever spikes?
Uh, yeah. Actually,
just right before you got here.
I found something in
the emergency kit.
- I just put it on. It was
a patch. -[Medbot beeping]
All right. All done.
[Medbot beeping]
Anything stand out?
Nothing major.
There's some swelling in
the brain.
Most likely caused by
blunt force trauma.
But fever, memory loss.
It says here they're all side
effects of the swelling.
But I'll remember everything
eventually, right?
You should still have
your technical memory
and all the skills that you've
learned.
No.
I-- I mean...
about me.
Who I am.
What happened here.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
[suspenseful music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Brion] A while back on the way
out here.
You and I. We were talking about
why we joined the program?
There's something about the way
you spoke.
Like, it wasn't about making
a sacrifice.
It was about needing answers.
Like what was out there.
Wasn't enough for you.
See, you don't remember
who you are.
But somehow you're still exactly
the same.
Get some rest.
[door opens]
[gasps]
[shrieks]
[suspenseful music playing]
[spacesuit whirring]
[sombre music playing]
What are you looking at?
[thundering]
[Riya] I can't imagine her
still being out there.
If she is, she's got to be
running low on oxygen by now.
She may have tried to find
shelter.
Sandstorms out here are
no jokes.
Maybe we can find her.
I saw a drone somewhere.
[Brion] Which you're planning
to pilot how?
[Riya] Yeah.
Shit.
What if she needs our help?
Maybe she got infected
by something out there.
Lost her mind. Killed everyone.
[Brion] We need to forget
about Clarke.
Listen,
the station is on standby.
Running basic life support
systems only.
We're running out of oxygen.
So what's the plan after this?
[Brion] We need to get off this
planet as soon as possible.
That is our priority.
Everything else, including...
trying to figure out
what the fuck happened here,
has to come second.
Talking big picture.
[Brion] Big picture.
First, we got to get back up to
the Orbital.
Which ain't easy.
Our rotation and satellite's
orbit have to line-up exactly.
- Next line-up is in 12 hours.
- [pants]
Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
I just need a second. [pants]
- [suspenseful music playing]
- [gasps]
[Brion] Riya.
Riya?
[pants]
- [door closes]
- [Riya grunts]
[Brion] You cool?
Yeah, I'm cool.
You don't seem cool.
Hey, I'm fine. I'm just...
I'm tired. That's all.
I haven't slept that well.
It's your patch. It's out of
juice. If you want, I can go--
I just need you to give me
fucking space.
I'm sorry.
I'm just tired. That's all.
[sombre music playing]
[cacophony of indistinct
whispering]
[footsteps approaching]
[shudders]
[grunts]
[indistinct whispering]
[door lock beeping]
- [somber music playing]
- [pants]
[patch beeping]
- [patch beeping]
- [pants]
What's happening? [echoes]
What is happening?
[suspenseful music playing]
[wind howling]
I'm sorry about earlier.
Hey, man. It's cool. I get it.
We're all dealing with some
pretty meteoric shit right now.
- [thundering]
- You know...
I've started to remember things.
Yeah?
Like what?
- [sighs]
- This is about Kev?
- Yeah.
- [wind howling]
How do I know if it's true?
If this is about the two of
you being a...
a thing, then yeah.
It's true.
[indistinct screaming]
[station thudding]
[Brion] This station's about to
handle much worse than this.
[alarm blaring]
[facility] Hull breach.
Oxygen levels critical.
[upbeat music playing]
[facility] Hull breach.
Oxygen levels critical.
Where is it?
[Brion] There's gotta be a hole
in the structure somewhere.
[Riya] Brion, in here.
- Why is this open?
- [Brion] Oh, shit.
[facility]
Vital oxygen levels compromised.
[Riya] How much time do we have?
[Brion] Every minute we don't
fix this,
we lose ten hours of
breathable air.
[Riya] Okay, I'm going in.
[facility] Pressure loss
imminent.
[Riya] It's tight in here.
So small.
[facility] Oxygen levels in all
sectors at critical level.
Someone's been in here?
[Brion] Yeah, probably tried
some sort of manual fix
for the system failure.
Just hit 75.
[metal clanging]
I can hear something.
[Brion] It's gotta be just
ahead of you.
I hear some noise coming through
the back.
[Brion] Hey, what's going on?
Brion, I need to get off comms.
It's too tight.
[Brion] Work fast, Ri.
You're practically breathing
poison in there.
Riya?
[metal clanging]
[grunts]
- [metal clanging]
- [grunts]
[metal clanging]
[Riya] There you are.
- [gasps]
- [high pitch squealing]
[shrieks]
[pants]
[Riya grunts]
[footsteps approaching]
Alright.
So, we are going off the theory,
and correct me if I'm wrong,
that Clarke came into contact
- with some sort of--
- A pathogen, yes.
Somewhere out there.
And it triggered
some sort of psychotic break.
[muffled] Right?
[low drone]
Right. Yeah. Yeah.
Alright,
so maybe this infection...
is changing her.
- Like rabies, or-- -[Riya] Yeah.
I mean, I don't know. Yes.
Yeah, maybe, but...
It's just something is not
adding up.
Yeah, well,
it's not gonna add up.
I mean, not for a while.
You know, we're still missing
most of the picture here.
Well, we fill it in.
That's what we're gonna do
the next few days, right?
[sighs]
What?
What? Say it.
We just lost 30% of our oxygen.
We don't have time to fill
anything in.
Okay, we have to take
the next line-up in five hours.
We have no answers. We have more
questions. We can't--
Riya! You are not listening to
me, okay?
It is tonight, or we die.
All right? We suffocate.
And all of this,
all of this was for nothing.
We're just gonna leave
her behind.
We're gonna leave Clarke
behind?
We don't have a choice, Ri.
Not with the time frame
that we are working with. Okay?
We still have to make it back to
my lander,
and that's 25 minutes easy.
Okay? And we still don't even
know what the fuck
is going on with Clarke.
Okay? She is not worth the risk.
Okay.
Hey, hey.
[sighs]
Riya, we will get to the bottom
of this. I promise.
You good?
Yes. I'm good.
[soft music playing]
[thundering]
[Kevin] Sometimes I feel like
I could close my eyes
and be back on Earth.
But being here is the start of
something.
Not a reminder of what
we've done.
We're finally here.
- [inhales]
- [sombre music playing]
[bells chiming]
[drone whirring]
[soft music playing]
[birds shrieking]
[drone whirring]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[suspenseful music playing]
[high pitched droning]
[Kevin] Riya.
It hurts. [echoes]
[birds chirping]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [Riya gasps]
- [shrieks]
[pants]
[upbeat music playing]
[computer stuttering]
[Medbot beeping]
[Kevin] Now, I know
there's not a lot out there,
but I'm not really missing
Earth much.
This place is amazing.
[Clarke] You'd leave
in a heartbeat for a pizza.
- [crowd chuckling]
- [Kevin] Okay.
[Riya] I don't think I'll ever
get used to these views.
[Clarke] Mm, mm.
[Kevin] I like the view of you
in that space suit.
[indistinct chatter]
- [Kevin chuckles]
- [Clarke] You really said that.
- [Clarke chuckles]
- Shut up.
[Davis] My room
is right next to both of theirs.
- [Clarke] Oh, I know!
- [Davis laughing]
- [Riya] Stop, guys. -[Davis]
Just imagine the sounds.
- [Riya] Guys, focus, come on.
- [Clarke] I can hear it too.
- They can't help themselves.
- [crowd chuckling]
- [Clarke groaning]
- [Davis] My man is terrible.
[Kevin] Guys, I think we're
getting closer.
It's got to be here.
[Riya] Are you sure?
Because if you're not...
You're going to cook dinner
tonight.
[Clarke] That's a fucking no.
[Davis] Yeah, no. Yeah,
please no.
- [Davis] Please no.
- [Kevin] Oh, you're what?
[Riya] What are you guys talking
about?
All we have is beans and rice.
- [Davis] I need no more of
that shit. -[crowd chuckling]
[Kevin] Hey, guys,
I think we're here.
This is the exact spot
that Brion
pinpointed the emissions to.
[Riya] Really?
[Kevin] It's just past
these rocks.
- [Clarke] Are you sure?
- [Kevin] Yeah.
[Kevin] Can you believe it?
- [Riya] Holy shit. Look at this.
- [Kevin] This is insane.
[Clarke] Oh my God.
[Kevin] Kevin. Home.
- [Davis] Dude, I knew it.
- [Kevin] They were right.
- [Davis] It's fucking
manufactured.
- [Kevin] This is amazing.
The whole atmosphere is
manufactured. They made it.
[Clarke chuckles]
How many of these are there?
[Kevin] Across the whole planet?
Dozens, maybe hundreds,
maybe more.
At least to the extent
that Brion could observe it.
Emission signatures,
they get a little diffused
by the time they reach orbit.
I mean, this is it.
- We did it, guys. We did it.
- [Clarke] Holy shit!
[Kevin exclaiming] Let's go.
- [Riya] How deep is it?
- [Clarke] Whoa!
[Davis] Hang on,
let me find out.
[Clarke] Just-- just be careful,
all right?
[Davis] Oh, you guys, come on.
I can handle it.
One. Two.
Three. Four. Five.
Whoa.
[Davis] Hang on, guys.
I think I see--
- [eerie music playing]
- [gasps]
[Kevin] Davis!
[Kevin] No!
[Clarke] Oh my God!
[Riya] Careful! Careful!
[Kevin] Guys! Guys!
[Kevin] What's happening?
[Kevin] We gotta get out
of here.
[Kevin] What are we doing here.
Let's go!
- [Brion] What's this?
- [gasps]
You knew.
What are you talking about?
[sighs]
[sniffles]
You can explain, right?
Listen to me.
I didn't know.
[Brion] Not for sure.
[Brion] I knew that you went on
a mission, but you went dark.
The entire station went
dark, okay?
I didn't know that this was
how-- how Dav--
You knew why we were out there.
You knew.
Kevin talks about it in
the fucking video.
[Riya] This entire time you saw
me go around in fucking circles
over and over trying to decipher
what the fuck had happened
to Kevin, to Clarke, to Audie,
to Davis.
I was going fucking crazy
when the entire time you knew
this planet was being
terraformed.
There was a window.
Okay, I had a mission
and a window,
and the only way to
fulfill the mission
was to keep things under
control during--
To keep me
under control! Me!
Because I know you, okay?
I know how you are.
You may have lost your memory,
but you haven't changed at all.
Okay, why can't you just let
it go? For once.
For once, until we are up there.
Until we are safe.
Because I killed them.
What?
What'd you--
I killed Kev.
I killed Audie, and I...
I just don't know...
I don't know why I did it.
I don't.
I just...
If we leave this station,
I'm never gonna know.
I-- I-- I need to know.
- Brion, I need to know.
I can't leave. -Hey, hey, hey.
What are you saying to me?
I don't...
I don't know why I did it.
These patches...
When they're fading, I've...
I start having more memories.
I can remember everything,
and it comes back faster.
Maybe-- maybe we can...
we can wait for two more hours.
They've been coming quicker and
quicker.
[Brion] Not a chance.
Not a chance.
- Why not?!
- Because I don't trust you!
Okay?!
[scoffs] All right,
listen to me.
I...
I trust you. I just don't know
the person that did this.
Okay? And I don't know
who you would become
if you stopped using these
things.
We were gonna go up there.
What if I...
- if I don't remember?
- Then you don't remember.
And you live with it.
[Brion] Riya.
Listen to me.
You and I...
we have a purpose.
Okay?
We sacrificed our lives on Earth
to come out here for a reason.
This.
This is about our species.
The big picture.
Okay? What we have
uncovered here,
proof of alien intelligence
somewhere out there.
There is technology to mold
planets.
This could change the fate
of our entire existence.
Our priority has to be about
the preservation of our mission.
Do you understand this?
Riya.
Tell me that you get this.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues
playing]
I just want to make sure
that we're...
we're good.
Yeah, we're good.
I'm just getting ready.
How long till line-up?
Lander takes off
in two hours and 39 minutes.
A couple clicks east of here.
You all patched up?
Yes.
Put one 30 minutes ago.
Is that enough?
You said they're getting less
effective.
[patch rustling]
Come on.
- [patch beeping]
- [Brion] There we go.
That's good as new.
[Brion exhales deeply]
I'll come get you when it's
time to...
[muffled] head out.
[indistinct whispering]
[lights flickering]
Brion I...
[eerie music playing]
- [Riya grunts]
- [Audie grunts]
[Riya grunts] Audie, no!
[Riya grunts]
- [Riya grunts]
- [Audie groans]
- [Audie grunts]
[Riya] No! [grunts]
[Riya grunts]
- [Riya grunts]
- [Audie groans]
[Riya] Audie, no.
[Riya] Stop! [grunts]
- [Audie grunts]
- [Riya grunts, groans]
[Riya groans]
[Riya groans] No! [grunts]
[Riya grunts]
[Riya grunts, pants]
[Riya pants]
[Riya grunts]
[Riya grunting, crying]
[shrieks]
[gasps, pants]
[lights flickering]
[groans]
[metal clattering]
Brion?
It wasn't just Clarke.
- [metal clattering]
- [Riya] They're all infected.
- [suspenseful music playing]
- [gasps]
[sombre music playing]
Brion?
[gasps]
- [suspenseful music playing]
- [Riya grunts]
[grunts]
[Riya grunts]
- [spacesuit whirring]
- [groans]
[eerie music playing]
[Riya pants, grunts]
[Riya grunts]
[Riya groans]
[shower pattering]
- [spacesuit whirring]
- [Clarke chokes]
- [Riya grunts]
[screams]
- [Clarke chokes]
[Riya pants]
[sombre music playing]
[Medbot beeping]
Welcome to Medbot.
[Medbot repeats itself in
Japanese]
- [groans]
- [Medbot beeping]
Medbot is now scanning,
please remain calm.
[Medbot repeats itself in
Japanese]
Medbot scan completed.
[Medbot repeats itself in
Japanese]
[Medbot beeping]
[somber music playing over
Medbot]
What?
No.
[Medbot beeping]
No, no, there has to be
something else.
There has to be something else.
[Medbot beeping]
Fuck!
[somber music playing]
[facility beeping]
[facility] Orbital line-up
window is now open.
Orbital line-up window is
now open.
[hopeful music plays]
[hatch opens]
[hatch closes]
[pants]
[upbeat music playing]
[buttons beeping]
- Come on.
- [buttons beeping]
- [computer stuttering]
- No. No. No.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Oh fuck.
Fuck. Fuck!
[sighs]
[upbeat music continues playing]
[patch beeping]
[Medbot] Welcome to Medbot.
[Medbot repeats itself in
Japanese]
[Medbot beeping]
[upbeat music playing]
[grunts, pants]
[Medbot whirring]
[Medbot beeping] Medbot scan
completed.
[Medbot repeats itself in
Japanese]
[Medbot beeping]
- [somber music playing over]
- [Riya] Fifty-one hours ago.
What is going on?
What is happening?
It's your fault.
[cacophony of indistinct
whispering]
[facility beeping]
[facility] Abnormal activity
detected.
[metal clanging]
[facility beeping]
[facility] Unusual life form
detected.
Hello?
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues
playing]
[soft music playing]
[shudders]
[footsteps approaching]
[Riya] What are you?
[quick breathing]
[Riya] You used me.
You used me to kill her.
- [gasps]
- [eerie music playing]
You...
you are...
the infection.
A part of you.
You...
will understand.
[eerie music playing]
Let me show you.
- [hatch opens]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[Kevin] What the hell is
that thing?
[Kevin] How long's it been here?
[Audie] Maybe it came
back with you.
[computer stuttering]
[Brion] Orbital to ground
station.
Ground station, do you copy?
The data transfer's interrupted.
Please respond.
Ground station, do you copy?
This is the Orbital.
Ground station, please respond.
[thundering]
[computer stuttering]
- [Kevin] Riya, step back.
- [Audie] It's everywhere.
[Riya] Take a sample.
Bring it to the lab.
[facility beeping]
[facility]
Movement detected at Zone One.
Exterior airlock.
[wind howling]
[airlock closes]
[thundering]
What the fuck happened to Davis?
It seems like it attached itself
to our mainframe.
Yeah, it spread from there.
I dug a hole in the wall to see
how far.
And it's-- it's mostly isolated
- to the airlock and the control
room. -For now.
What if it's been studying us
ever since we landed?
Exactly. Waiting for the right
moment to shut us down.
[Audie] When's the next line-up?
[soft music playing]
Huh?
The next line-up. When is it?
[stutters]
- Thirteen hours.
- [Kevin] Got it.
- I'll pack up the lab and I'll
meet you... -No, no, wait.
- We're leaving.
- Riya, we're following protocol.
Fuck the protocol.
- This is what we've been
waiting-- -No!
Protocol exists for a reason.
We need to get out of here
before that thing spreads.
- Protect the mission. -The
mission? This is the mission.
Do you guys remember why
we signed up?
All of us.
Everything we sacrificed.
That the best case scenario, we
would grow old light years away
from everything we've
ever known.
It's out there.
Right now.
An actual solution. The
technology to create a new world
where we don't get poisoned
by the air we're breathing.
[thundering]
[door opens]
[Riya] Self-replicating
technology.
[Audie] What are you doing?
Audie...
Audie, this could be our answer.
[squelches]
Back the fuck up!
[grunts]
- Audie!
- [grunts]
[grunts, groans]
Audie!
- [groans]
- [parasite screeching]
[groans]
No. No. No.
[parasite growling]
[Riya] Audie?
[high pitched frequency]
[Clarke] What the fuck?! Riya!
- [Riya pants]
- [Kevin] Whoa! Whoa!
- Riya.
- [Clarke] What the fuck?
[facility] Abnormal activity
detected.
- Riya, what have you done?
- [Riya panting]
- [intense music playing]
- Oh shit!
- [Audie grunts]
- [Kevin groans]
- [Kevin chokes]
- [Clarke grunts]
- [Riya grunts]
- [Kevin grunts]
[grunts, groans]
[Kevin grunts]
[Kevin groans]
- [Riya grunts, groans]
- [Audie grunts]
- [grunts, groans]
- [Kevin grunts, groans]
[Kevin groans]
- Throw me!
- [Riya groans]
- [Audie grunts]
- [Kevin groans]
[Audie grunts]
[Riya groans]
- [Riya] Kevin.
- [Kevin grunts]
Kevin?
- [groans]
- [grunts]
- [screams]
[grunts]
[groans] Riya!
- [parasite shrieking]
- [screams]
- [Riya grunts]
- [shrieks]
[Riya grunts]
[groans]
- [Riya groans]
- [Kevin growls]
[Riya groans]
- [Riya groans]
[Kevin growls]
- [Kevin growls]
[gasps]
[Kevin growls]
[eerie music playing]
- [Clarke grunts]
- [facility beeping]
[facility] Abnormal activity
detected.
- You okay?
- [alarm blaring]
- Riya!
- Clarke.
Come on, we gotta
get the fuck out of here!
Go.
- [Kevin growls]
- [Clarke] Riya! [grunts]
Clarke!
[Clarke grunts, groans]
[facility beeping]
[facility] Abnormal activity
detected.
[helmet thudding]
- [screams, groans]
- [helmet thudding]
- Help her.
- [Clarke groaning]
- [upbeat music playing]
- [Clarke groans]
[growls]
Fuck.
[Kevin growls]
Oh fuck.
[grunts] Clarke.
[grunts]
[Kevin growls]
- [Clarke groans]
- Clarke.
- [Riya grunts]
- [pants]
[Riya grunts]
You gotta go.
Go to the lander.
I have to stay. [grunts]
- [Riya grunts]
- [Clarke grunts]
- [Kevin growls]
- [Brion groans]
- [grunts]
[sombre music playing]
[pants]
- [Kevin growls]
- [Brion grunts]
[growls]
[pants]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [Kevin] Riya.
- [gasps]
[Kevin] It's me.
- [Riya gasps]
- [eerie music playing]
[whispers] Kevin.
[Riya pants]
Did I do this?
[Kevin] It's okay.
- [shushes]
- [Riya] It's all my fault.
[Riya shudders]
It's okay.
- [Riya stutters]
- [Kevin shushes]
[mumbles] You can say it.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Remember.
It's okay.
[grunts]
- [Kevin growls]
- [Riya shudders]
- [groans]
- [parasite shrieks]
[shudders]
[parasite shrieks]
[screams]
[eerie music playing]
[soft music playing]
[facility beeping]
[facility] Abnormal activity
detected.
[gasps]
[eerie music playing]
[Riya] Take it, Riya.
[Riya] You're all alone.
You're gonna die.
You didn't do this.
You killed them all. I'm scared.
Am I crazy?
[indistinct whispering]
[thundering]
[facility beeping]
[facility] Unusual parasitic
activity detected.
[parasite]
[eerie music playing]
I don't want
More.
[parasite growls]
[parasite]
Fuck your existence.
[groans]
[sighs]
[eerie music playing]
[facility beeping]
[facility] Oxygen levels in all
sectors at critical level.
[facility beeping]
[facility]
Vital oxygen levels compromised.
- [Medbot beeping]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[Medbot] Welcome to Medbot.
- [Medbot repeats itself in
Japanese] -[sighs]
Medbot is now scanning,
please remain calm.
[Medbot repeats itself in
Japanese]
Scanning completed.
[Medbot repeats itself in
Japanese]
- [Medbot beeping]
- [pants]
[Medbot] Next phase beginning,
please remain calm.
[Medbot repeats itself in
Japanese]
[groans]
[winces]
[flatline tone]
[soft music playing]
[gasps]
[intense music playing]
[groans]
[parasite shrieking]
[Medbot beeping]
[triumphant music playing
over Medbot]
- [crowd applauding over Medbot]
- [Medbot beeping]
[parasite squelching]
- [parasite squelching]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
[growls]
[parasite grunts]
[Riya groans]
- [parasite growls]
- [Riya groans]
- [Riya chokes]
- [parasite growls]
- [Riya choking]
- [Riya grunts]
- [parasite growls]
- [Riya groans]
- [Riya grunts]
- [parasite growls]
- [parasite groans]
[Riya grunts]
[parasite growls]
[Riya groans]
- [Riya grunts]
- [parasite groans]
- [parasite growls]
- [Riya grunts]
- [parasite groans]
[parasite growls]
- [Riya grunts]
- [parasite groans]
[parasite growls]
- What the--
- [parasite growls]
- [Riya grunts]
- [parasite groans]
- [Riya screams]
[Riya grunts]
[parasite groans]
- [Riya screams]
- [parasite groans]
[alarm blaring]
Fuck you!
[tranquil music playing]
[buttons beeping]
[computer beeping, powering up]
Come on. Come on.
[computer beeping]
[lander powering up]
[chuckles]
[buttons beeping]
[lander engines revving]
[soft music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[all cheering]
[soft instrumental music
playing]
[song playing]
♪ A host ♪
♪ I claim you ♪
♪ As my own ♪
♪ Even if some ♪
♪ Wanted to ♪
♪ Obey ♪
♪ In your dreams ♪
♪ I, I saw ♪
♪ Sweet dream ♪
♪ In your head ♪
♪ My dreams ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Keep ♪
[woman vocalizing]
[piano playing]
[parasite growling]
[flatlining tone]