Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Ah!
Huh? Aah!
Dad, look!
My hair's gone
back to normal again!
I swear it was a top knot
last night.
Hmm.
A shame. That hairstyle
looked rather good on you.
Huh?
Moments ago,
a warning was issued
for a Yakuza Hurricane
approaching Gotham City.
A low-pressure system
is currently building
- to the southeast.
- Uh...what did she say?
A Yakuza Hurricane.
- Let's get to work.
- Strong rain and winds are expected...
- Right.
- ...along with a large number
- of yakuza falling from the sky.
Damian, after we got back
from feudal Japan yesterday,
I needed to know if we
prevented history from changing.
I went to search for deviations
in modern-day Japan,
but as you can clearly see...
Japan is gone?
Yes, the islands of Japan
have disappeared.
And just like your hair,
something is wrong.
Hm.
Alfred, have you made contact
with the Watchtower?
Well, Master Bruce...
I'm afraid the Watchtower
does not exist.
- Huh?
- It gets worse.
It would seem that Superman,
Wonder Woman, Aquaman,
Green Lantern, and Flash
have also disappeared.
So we now find ourselves
without a Justice League.
It makes sense
that there'd be no Watchtower.
Okay, then does this mean
we're on a different Earth or something?
No. I already verified
the multiverse frequency.
We are definitely standing
on the right planet.
Which tells us one thing:
That history has been changed.
Hm!
I am transmitting
the forecasted coordinates
of the Yakuza Hurricane
to you now.
The yakuza?
How does the Japanese mob
fit into this?
I sure hope
something makes sense soon.
Here we go.
Let's do it!
Ahh.
Now give 'em hell!
Huh?
Hello, Batman. Good to see you.
I guess they weren't kidding
about it raining yakuza.
Well, yeah, of course.
It's raining men,
just like it always does.
What the huh?
What's wrong?
We just did the same thing
yesterday.
Hyah!
The only way this makes any sense
is if we've swapped--
- Ha!
- Swapped?
When we returned
from feudal Japan yesterday,
we must have swapped places.
The versions of us who fought
the yakuza in this timeline
must be somewhere else.
You make it sound simple,
- but isn't that kind of a huge deal?
- You're next, kid! Oof!
Huh?
You really should learn
to watch your back, Robin.
Oh, mind your own business.
I was just about
to wipe the floor with that guy.
Oh, you were, huh?
I thought all that time in the past
would have straightened you out,
but, no, you're right back
to being the same little brat.
Come on!
What's with the hairdo?
- A wig?
- No!
It just grew back overnight.
Yeah, whatever you say.
Arrest the lot of 'em!
That crazy weather alert
got me off the couch.
Someone care to explain?
Exactly what it looks like.
In this Gotham,
yakuza rain from the skies.
- Huh?
- Yeah.
Everything's all out of whack.
The islands of Japan are all gone,
and the Justice League
doesn't exist anymore.
Really?
But if there's no Japan,
how are yakuza falling from the sky?
- Huh?
- Mm?
Holy cow!
Is that really Japan?
Floating directly over Gotham.
What are you looking at up there?
Can you not see the huge island?
An island?
Okay, then.
I guess now we know where
the yakuza are coming from.
I can't find anything about the island.
And it would seem the four of us
are the only ones who can see it.
I'm going up to investigate.
- The rest of you deal with the yakuza.
- Wait! Me too!
Ah!
- Hey!
- Better get busy.
Somebody's gotta take care
of that mess.
Master Bruce,
there is a strange energy signature
coming from the anomaly in the sky.
Sending you the data now.
It looks like the Quake Engine.
Yes.
Or at least something very similar to it.
The Quake Engine?
Isn't that what sent us
through time before?
This is fallout from using the engine.
Japan has been removed
from the space-time continuum.
Even though it looks
like it's floating in the sky,
it's actually drifting
through a fissure in space-time.
So maybe the reason
only we can see it
is because we went through time too.
Right. And we don't belong
in this timeline.
We have been displaced in time,
just like that island has.
We need to recover the Quake Engine
and then use it to return
space-time back to normal.
We're entering the fissure.
Brace yourself!
♪ Traveled through time ♪
♪ Traveled through space ♪
♪ I found that I was lost
and far from home ♪
♪ Trouble ♪
♪ My life is all, all about trouble ♪
♪ Won't you come face my fantasy? ♪
♪ Drowning the night away ♪
- ♪ Battle these crimes ♪
- ♪ Battle ♪
- ♪ Battle through time ♪
♪ I sacrifice my life all for justice ♪
It doesn't quite look like
feudal Japan, does it?
There's a signal near the Tokyo area.
Thanks, I see it.
It's enemy territory.
Going radio silent for a while.
Noted, Master Bruce.
Is that Green Lantern?
I commend you for making it
as far as you have,
but it was foolish.
You have entered an area
controlled by the Hagane Family,
and I'll be damned
if you encroach any further,
for I am Zeshika the Emerald Ray.
Is that Jessica Cruz?
Not exactly.
This woman's dressed
in a kimono.
Oh, no, you don't!
Hang on! Aquaman, too?!
I'm second-in-command
to the Hagane Family,
Ahsa the Aqua Dragon!
Now get a taste of the spinning blades
from the trident of
the ruler of the waves!
First a Yakuza Hurricane.
Now a yakuza tornado?
Sorta.
Tornadoes form on the ground
and pull things upwards.
Since this is coming from the skies,
it would technically be
a yakuza downburst.
I didn't ask if you were a weatherman.
Hmm?
- What is that?
- Huh?
Invisible to the eyes,
unheard by the ears,
a red blur that comes
and goes like lightning.
Known to be the fastest man
in the Hagane Family,
but I'm the fastest man alive!
I'm the Fleet of Foot, Bari!
It's Flash!
I see you've been giving
my boys here some trouble,
so I'm here to put you in your place!
Hyah!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Where are you going?
We have orders from the oyabun
to eliminate trespassers.
It's nothing personal,
just how we do business.
Now, say goodbye!
Aah! Oof!
That's quite enough
out of you for today.
Daiana.
Carved upon this burnished skin
and polished in the Inokashira waters
for reasons only the gods could know...
a gold eagle soars through the skies,
and as the woman who leads her clan
by turning brutes and thugs
into warriors...
I am the Eagle Goddess, Daiana.
You should know
not to underestimate me.
to stay out of this!
Back off, Daiana!
Hyah!
You're in Kichijoji,
and it belongs to the Amazone Family.
Oh! Oof!
Those men are
my guests in our land,
and allowing you
to lay a finger on them
would disrespect the name
of Daiana, the Eagle Goddess.
And I won't have it!
Ha!
Your life is on the line.
I suggest you think about
if these two are worth it.
Are you smart enough to know
when to back down, Aqua Dragon?
Beepity-beep! Honky-honk!
Comin' through!
Your attention please!
Guess who's here, kids!
I hail from the wonderful whirling
cesspool of grime and greed, Gotham!
I fell for a clown prince of a man
and started to play pretend
I'm a psycho hoodlum.
Then I met the badass warrior babe Daiana,
and started kicking ass for her.
I'm Harin the Wild Jester!
It's a pleasure for you to meet me.
Now let's dance!
Hyah!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Yeah!
What's wrong?
Having a difficult time?
Well, yeah. We're dealing
with a speedy fella.
We need a way to slow him down.
Hmm.
Come on, come on, bring it!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Aah!
I'm running out of energy.
Zeshika, we're leaving.
What are you talking about?
The oyabun won't be happy.
I'm the one in charge,
so I call the shots.
Do what I say.
Consider yourselves lucky.
You boys have done it now.
You look hungry.
Huh?
Damn you.
Think you're so clever.
Now I'm hungry as hell
and thirsty.
I need to save enough stamina
for the trip back,
so this will have to wait.
I'll be back!
And next time,
you'll get what's coming to ya!
Somebody wanna explain
why Flash is all messed up?
A lot's messed up.
Batman's up there trying to figure it out.
So you're telling me
the world is still out of whack?
Looks like it.
Welcome back, Madam Daiana.
A country of nothing but yakuza?
Yes.
For a very long time now,
Hinomoto has been divided
into different yakuza families,
with clashes happening
almost daily.
Ultimately, it gave rise
to a great war for territory
known as the "Yakuzageddon."
So in order to survive,
everyone was forced
to join one of the syndicates,
and now yakuza families
are all that exist.
There is no government
nor law enforcement.
It's yakuza rule over yakuza,
a place of total anarchy.
Those guys from earlier
were talking about
something called the Hagane Family.
Hagane is the dominant syndicate
that rules over most of Japan now.
They are the worst of the worst
who will resort
to any tactic
they feel necessary to win...
...and their reach runs far
and wide across the land.
My Amazone Family
and the Doomuzu Family
are the only ones with
the strength to oppose them.
But their leader, Deio,
was recently killed
and his syndicate fell apart.
As of now, the only family who
still respects the Ninkyo way is mine,
the Amazone Family.
The Ninkyo way?
We will fight for what's right
in the face of death,
never at the detriment
to those living honestly.
And that is the spirit
of the Ninkyo code.
So your people are more than
just your typical villains, aren't they?
That's Wonder Woman for ya.
Wonder what?
Uh, no. Never mind.
In the Hagane Family,
is there a man who can
run with incredible speed
and a flying man who possesses
superhuman strength?
Yes. In fact, there are.
One of their most trusted soldiers
is Bari, the Fleet Foot.
He can outrun
even the speed of sound.
Then there is the man faster
than a speeding bullet,
more powerful than a locomotive,
and he is able to leap tall buildings
in a single bound.
He is their leader.
Kuraku the Man of Steel.
That's Flash and Superman.
And we've already seen
Green Lantern and Aquaman,
plus Wonder Woman, of course.
So all the heroes that went missing
in our world are now over here.
Their Justice League is
more like the Yakuza League.
This is no laughing matter.
I take it that is
your world up above us.
We refer to it as Amatsukuni.
What does it mean?
"The land in the sky."
It was about a month ago
when it first appeared in our atmosphere.
A month ago, huh?
That must be right
when time started to diverge.
The Hagane Family wants
to rule more than Hinomoto.
They've already attacked your lands
in efforts to expand their territory.
They've figured out a way
to reach Amatsukuni
by having Bari the Fleet Foot
create a tornado.
Let me get this straight.
Flash can use his speed
to spin up a tunnel
through the fissure in space-time?
Unless someone stops them,
the Hagane Family
will overrun Amatsukuni
and eventually take it over.
I cannot turn a blind eye
to such a thing.
We battle injustice and help the weak.
The righteous do not deserve
these horrible actions.
It goes against the Ninkyo way.
This is Lake Inokashira.
In the middle is Nyogogashima,
the Isle of Women.
It is also where the
god Benzaiten resides.
Legends say
that when calamity befalls us,
an incarnation of Benzaiten
will arise to save all of Japan.
I was bestowed a fraction
of Benzaiten's powers
and then dispatched here.
I have a mission--
protecting Hinomoto
and the Ninkyo spirit--
and I will do that with my life.
Kinda seems
like Wonder Woman's personality
is more intact than the others.
This version of Japan
has its own reality,
isolated from the rest
of the space-time continuum.
Some form of convergent evolution.
The heroes have likely had
some evolutionary changes
due to the ecology of this world.
So did all of this happen
because of our battle
back in feudal Japan?
No. It's doubtful
for so many elements
to line up by mere coincidence.
It's more likely
that someone had a hand in it.
Yeah, I guess so.
Can you point me in the direction
where we crashed earlier?
I would like to repair the Batwing.
Of course. Follow me.
We have already recovered
your airplane.
Don't worry. The Hagane Family
cannot attack you here.
How did you get it here?
I had my wards carry it.
Thank you.
Must have taken some work.
Oh, no.
They've managed much worse.
That said...
hauling back two in one day
did prove a little taxing.
That plane.
It belongs to Harley Quinn.
Aw, you got me!
You are the same Harley
I know from Gotham, aren't you?
Yeah. It's me.
Unlike you dorks,
I blended in nice and easy.
Then I met
this beautiful boss lady.
I mean, this chick
can command a room, am I right?
So I stuck around and she let me stay.
Hold on.
You haven't been here for more
than half a day longer than we have.
Acclimated incredibly fast.
- I'm cool like that.
- Uh, 'kay, so...
how can you be
the real Harley Quinn?
I thought we left you in the
custody of the cops last night.
Hello! Newsflash!
Gotham PD ain't too smart.
- Did Joker escape too?
- Who knows? Oop!
Spill it!
What did you come here for?
Because it looked like
a total blast.
I mean, a freaking
giant Japan floating in the sky?
How could I possibly resist?
I don't trust you.
Tell me, where the hell is The Joker?
I dunno.
We're not joined at the hip,
you know.
Don't lie to me!
That is enough.
I do not know your relationship,
but the two of you
are guests in my home...
so please refrain from fighting
while you're here.
Hmph.
"Lift up the honor of others."
The pathway to respect.
I'm glad that you
understand our customs.
There. See? Mm-hmm!
Really?
When it comes to the samurai,
one's honor is cherished even
more so than their own lives.
I can appreciate that, ma'am.
A wealth of knowledge.
I knew you were more than ordinary.
Despite the dark mask you wear
to cover up your face,
you must be a reputable oyabun
where you're from.
Oyabun?
No. I am no leader.
Whatever.
He heads up
the whole Bat Family.
Everybody in the underworld
knows all about that freak
and hates his guts too!
Right, Batty Man?
The Bat Family?
I'm not surprised you
would have a syndicate.
Harley, you need to keep
your mouth shut.
The oyabun of the Bat cartel.
- Interesting.
- It's not like that.
I don't know, man.
Sounds kinda rad.
Be quiet.
- Where are you going?
- So sorry, Daiana.
Appreciate all ya done for me,
but there's no way I can be on
the same squad as those losers.
You mind if I park the plane here?
Thanks! Bye-bye!
Shouldn't we go after her?
No. Repairs take priority.
We'll return to the Batcave.
I've had plans in place
to defeat the Justice League.
Huh?
I've always been prepared in case
I ever needed to take them down.
Turning on your own allies.
That is so you.
All finished with your repairs?
Yes. Thank you for your help.
- We'll return soon...
- Huh?
...and I will put a stop
to the Hagane tyranny.
Aw.
We're approaching
the space-time fissure.
Something is closing
in on the Batwing.
Oh, and pretty fast too.
I figured he'd show up sooner
or later.
You've got quite the audacity
to trespass into my territory
and not come say hello.
And who are you?
Kuraku, the Man of Steel.
I am in charge
of protecting the Hagane Family.
What are you planning
to do with us?
Come along, Robin!
The Great Oyabun would like
to have a word.
- You're not the boss?
- Hard to imagine someone above you.
Yes.
The Great Oyabun is the one
who has led us down this path.
Do not resist.
I have orders to eliminate you
if you try to make things difficult.
I must ask, how does
your Great Oyabun refer to me?
You are the Detective,
the worthless trash who
collects dirt on other people.
There you have it.
That tells me pretty much
everything I need to know.
You think so?
Yeah.
It looks like we're
dealing with Ra's al Ghul.
Hm?
Still as sharp
as ever, Detective.
Of course it's you.
But it seems you figured it out
a little too late.
I even had enough time to
hack into the Bat-Tech of your vehicle.
Now, come, grandson,
I need to talk to you.
Looks like you're in it
pretty deep, Batty Man!
The Joker!
Now let's get this party started!
Stay out of my way!
You kidding me?!
Getting in the way
is my favorite pastime.
Besides, the only one
who gets the pleasure
of killing the Batman is me!
No way in hell some phony
super fella gets to do it.
The Great Oyabun
gave me an order,
- and I will follow through!
- Aah! Aah!
- Wahoo!
- Damian!
- Excellent work, Kuraku.
- Hey! Put me back!
- I'll see you soon.
- Aah!
No, no, no,
don't just throw me!
You never should have come here,
you rotten piece of trash!
Harley! I'll let you
duke it out with the big guy.
What?!
Are you freaking kidding me?!
Oh, don't worry.
I'm sure you'll be fine. You got this.
- Huh?
- Love you, boo! Have fun!
Uh...
It's time for the good little
Bat birdies to go on home!
You wanna get back to Gotham,
don't you?
Well, I'm feeling I could do
you a wee favor today, Bats.
- Mwah!
- And just abandon Harley?
Abandon her? Don't be silly.
I'm giving her the spotlight.
Ain't that right, baby?
What?!
I'm just your chopper fodder!
This is your stupidest prank
ever, Joker!
Wha!
Time for you to die!
Aah! Aah! Oof!
Mind your own business,
Amazone wench.
This girl is my personal guest.
I don't care which family you work for.
I won't let you lay a finger on her.
I caught the kid.
He's safe and sound.
Okay. Good work.
We all live within
the underbelly of society.
Only the strongest survive.
It's simply
how the yakuza world works.
Our path in life is forged
through crime and violence.
Along that path,
hell is all that awaits you.
Demons and yakuza
are both the same.
You'll find soon enough
when I take your head off.
Lucky for me,
I've got a strong neck,
so you're going to
have to work for it.
Hm.
You still alive?
Yeah, more or less.
Uh, why'd you save me?
It's like I said:
I will not let anyone be rude
to my guests.
I refuse to watch a girl suffer,
especially one caught
in the crossfire between men.
The Amazone Family
is a refuge for women,
as well as their tears.
Not sure what
that's supposed to mean,
but I can say
I appreciate the sentiment.
That's just fine.
The Ninkyo way is about heart,
mine and yours.
Mm-hmm.
Ah, here we are,
back in good ol' Gotham proper.
Joker, why are you doing this?
I'd like to preserve the
pleasure of killing you myself.
And I don't know if I could
stomach the thought of
some know-it-all super sucker
having all the fun.
Especially if that old fart
Ra's is pulling the strings.
So you rescued me to kill me?
That's dumb.
- No need to thank me, buddy!
- You're always up to something.
Oh, come on!
You and I go back.
You can trust me.
When have I ever led you astray?
Smell ya later, Batty!
Don't get into much trouble!
- Batman!
- Ah.
Irasshai. Come in.
Zeshika, very well done.
You may go.
Yes, sir.
Your seared salmon, sir.
- Can I get a California roll?
- Nice.
Are you familiar
with "oral seasoning"?
Can't say that I am.
With sushi rice,
you can pair an endless amount
of combinations,
and all those infinite
possibilities eventually become
a singular phenomenon
for each individual.
Interesting, yes?
What are you talking about,
old man?
The Japanese people are masters
at layering these wondrous
flavors together
to create a new universe
within every meal.
So you're trying to tell me something
about this whole new Japan thing?
- Ubu, turn on the television.
- Sir.
What am I looking at?
The moment just before
you were all sent to feudal Japan.
I had already received word
of Gorilla Grodd's plans
to develop the Quake Engine
and use it to warp space-time.
Okay, so this place
was created by the Quake Engine.
That's what we figured.
Oh, it's far more advanced
than that.
I improved upon its design
to allow the engine
to shift space-time itself.
The idea was to stack
multiple worlds over each other
and change their shape.
I could conjure an entirely new world
by simply overlaying different scenarios,
and this yakuza version
of Japan was ultimately born.
So, what if an alien from Krypton
who was meant to end up in America
instead landed in Japan and
was raised by a yakuza family?
What if there was an island of women
in the middle of Lake Inokashira?
And what if a descendant
of the gods was born there?
And what if there was
a species of aquatic people
living at the bottom of Lake Inokashira,
and their queen fell in love
with a yakuza gangster
and gave birth to a son
who grew up to become
ruler of the aquatic race
and a yakuza lieutenant as well?
I feel like you cut that short.
What if a low-level yakuza thug
got struck by lightning
while in a hot spring,
and obtained the ability to run
even faster than a thunderbolt?
What if a gambler found herself
in trouble and on the run,
and just so happened to stumble
across a hidden power ring
and its energy supply?
By folding and overlapping
all these various scenarios,
one can form them into an
entirely new thing altogether,
like shaping a crane out of
a single sheet of paper.
The Four-Dimensional Origami System...
That is what I have chosen
to call my brilliant new device.
Now there is a country ruled
entirely by violent gangsters,
my very own army of assassins.
All I have to do is send them
to attack Amatsukuni,
and the earth will be rid
of the plague of humanity.
It's beautifully ironic.
It won't be the Justice League
but a Yakuza League
that will restore peace
and harmony back to the world.
Rather amusing,
wouldn't you say?
Sounds like you went to
a whole lot of trouble, Grandpa.
Does my mom know about this?
Talia?
She has no part in any of this, no.
It's my plan, and mine alone.
So then, Damian,
all you have to do is ask
and I will gladly hand over
my rule to you.
I was sure to make the inflection point
where history changed
a month prior to your return
from feudal Japan.
Everything is in place.
The order can be given at any time,
and the yakuza of these lands
will lead a purge of the old world.
You want me to be like
your successor or something?
Yeah, that's a hard pass.
Still not interested, are you?
This is a wonderful opportunity.
Such a waste.
You can ask all you want,
but I'm not changing my mind.
And, like,
what are we even doing here
if none of your big master plan
involves sushi?
I don't get why you feel like you
have to put on some dramatic show
to get your point across.
I just like the sushi here
and thought it would be nice
for you to experience a little culture,
but all you ate were
those awful California rolls,
disgusting pig vomit.
Well, my taste buds say,
"Screw you, old man."
Alright, we are done here.
Aah!
Mm-hmm.
This seaweed reeks!
You just stay there
and watch my yakuza army
cleanse the world
of all the human filth.
Feel free to enjoy some California rolls
while you're at it.
You are seriously
like the worst grandpa ever!
Hold up.
So you're saying it was The Joker
who actually saved your butt?
It's never simple with him.
I'm sure it must be part
of some bigger scheme.
Well, we can't just let
him run loose, can we?
No, but dealing with the
yakuza takes priority right now.
Especially given
who's behind all this.
Ra's is insane.
So we have yakuza versions
of Superman,
Green Lantern, Aquaman, and Flash?
While I'm glad
Wonder Woman is on our side,
it still won't be easy.
Wrong.
This should be a simple win.
We already know the extent
of their abilities better than anyone.
So what?
The Yakuza League is like the
proverbial frog born in a well.
They know nothing outside
the world in which they live.
They lack practical combat experience,
and that's a weakness
we can take advantage of.
I get it.
They don't know what it's like to fight
against the most cunning badass
of all time.
At the time when
we returned from feudal Japan,
we were exposed to an energy,
a space-time pulse,
that was being emitted
from the Quake Engine.
That's why we can see Japan
in the sky,
as well as travel safely through
the fissure in space-time.
And the same goes for whatever
we're holding on to as well.
Which means we can take all of
our Bat-gear with us to Yakuza Land, too.
I like the sound of that.
I have something prepared
for you, gentlemen.
♪ Did you see that?
Those are the wings that cut down evil ♪
♪ Yes, he cloaks his identity in shadow
and fights for justice ♪
♪ Even in the face of death ♪
♪ He seeks eternal peace ♪
♪ By using all manner of
scientific knowledge ♪
♪ He'll get it done ♪
♪ Soar high, Bat-Phoenix!
Combine your powers together ♪
♪ Did you see that? In the form of a bat,
but somehow a phoenix ♪
♪ Fight on, Bat-Phoenix!
Use the power of friendship ♪
♪ Fly beyond the horizon
in the azure skies, Batman! ♪
I do hope you enjoyed
my presentation.
Yes, um... thank you, Alfred.
Huh? Hmm.
Fine job extinguishing
the Doomuzu-gumi.
It was hardly a challenge at all.
That leaves the Amazone Family.
She is the only one among you
who failed to embrace the
yakuza's ruthless way of life.
Perhaps overlapping
the different dimensions
didn't go as smoothly as I thought.
She's been a thorn in our side.
I'll deal with her.
Yes...
and once Hinomoto is brought
under a single banner,
next will be Amatsukuni.
Invading and conquering the
obnoxious blight in our skies
should be quick work for you.
Yesterday, some of the yakuza
from Amatsukuni stirred up trouble.
They were dressed in ridiculous
bat and clown outfits.
Judging by their actions,
they are nothing but fools
with no respect for our ways.
As you have said,
leaving them alive will not prove useful
to us in any way.
Exactly right.
And also, you said
their world is like ours,
filled with a rabble
of yakuza thugs?
- Yes.
- Then I will crush them without mercy.
The weak shall perish
and the strong thrive
as the rule of all yakuza rings true.
I trust you will not fail.
Rest assured Amatsukuni
will crumble
and fall under a hailstorm
of our warriors.
Then see to it.
- Ubu.
- Yes, sir.
- The sushi.
- Hm!
Make sure Bari has a full stomach.
He'll be happy with that.
My lady, may I have a moment?
Quietly, please.
Our guest is still asleep.
There is a turtle at the gates.
A turtle?
Right.
An oracle bone script.
Such an antiquated way
of sending a message.
Ma'am,
it's from the aquatic people.
Very well.
Tell Ahsa I accept the request.
I have been challenged to a duel.
Ahsa the Aqua Dragon
wants to settle things.
♪ Suppose that there
were no tears in this world ♪
♪ Suppose that there was
no anger in my soul ♪
♪ Suppose that I never learned
how to love ♪
♪ All I think about are
those possibilities, however ♪
♪ The warped threads of
destiny overlap and intertwine ♪
♪ Going against the maelstrom
to take a stand ♪
♪ An unrealized dream
hidden behind a blade ♪
♪ I shall walk alone down
the path of carnage ♪
♪ Yes, down this path
without a single regret ♪
♪ All alone, just me, walking on ♪
Always I--
H-Hey!
I thought I was clear
when I said one-on-one.
She is here to be a witness.
Aw.
Daiana, I will first ask if you'd agree
to join the Hagane Family.
We've known each other
since we were young.
I can put in a good word for you.
You two were friendsies?
We once played together
in the waters of Lake Inokashira.
I don't want to hurt you.
Oh, don't flatter yourself.
How did you get dragged
into this yakuza mess, anyway?
The Great Oyabun of your gang
is from Amatsukuni.
I hope it was worth
throwing away your pride.
I want to rule...
the skyward sea.
The sea?
It's a strange thing.
I've known nothing but
the waters of this lake my whole life,
but whenever I look up to the sea,
it feeds a fire deep within my soul.
As though there's
another world out there,
one where I live
as king of the great ocean.
There are days it's all I think about.
I will make that sea my territory.
And to have it, I will submit
to Ra's as Great Oyabun.
Ahsa, you act as though
you're some pillar of society,
but that's just your ego talking.
Living underwater
has swollen your head.
I'd expect you
to say something like that.
Hmm?
Huh?
Don't you worry.
I'll drain that big head of yours.
You're so cool!
You're out of your depth!
Huh!
Hyah!
Prepare to meet your maker, Ahsa!
Huh?
You've got some real fight
in you, Daiana.
My girls!
Zeshika...
There's no way that Daiana,
the surrogate mommy
with the heart of gold,
can just sit back and
watch her precious children die.
Forget about us!
Destroy her, Oyabun!
- Keep fighting! Take her down!
- We're here for you!
- Pay us no mind!
- Well, if you guys
aren't gonna fight fair,
then you won't mind
if I join in too.
Bleh!
Hyah!
I have a duty
to see this through,
so please forgive me, ladies.
Aah!
Hyah!
Hmph. You haven't changed at all
since you were a kid, have you?
Even if you think
you've got it all figured out,
there is still doubt in your heart.
You're not the man you once were.
It's time
to say your prayers, Daiana.
Hyah! Hee!
Jumpity-jump, jumpity-jump,
jumpity-jump, jumpity-jump!
Quit jump-jump-jumping
all over the place!
Now feel my fury!
Kanzashi Fl--
Hello!
Kanzashi Flasher!
- Nightwing, you take Zeshika.
- I'm on it.
Red Hood, Red Robin,
you two head for the Yakuza Tower.
- Got it.
- Roger that.
Wahoo!
Splash!
I'm glad we made it in time.
You came back.
Ha!
Huh? Aah!
When the hell did you do that?!
Aah! Oof!
I have sent Doomuzu Deio to his death!
The Hagane-gumi ended
Yakuzageddon as victors!
Now it's time to extend our rule
by taking control of Amatsukuni.
You will find no one
more ruthless than us.
You will eradicate these intruders
with the full force of our strength.
Teach them a lesson!
The Hagane-gumi reigns over all.
We have nothing to fear!
Hunt down every last piece
of trash from Amatsukuni,
and crush their very spines!
You're a fool!
Fighting me under water
is a death sentence!
Hyah!
You can't defeat me!
Take this!
Dice of Hell, The Devil's Bones!
Ha!
Yeah!
The operation to take over
Amatsukuni has begun!
You are all ammunition! Bullets!
Right!
What the heck is that?
You can fly?!
Oof! Gah!
- Huh?
- Hyah!
Come on! Don't tell me
you're already done.
'Kay, funny man.
You are going to regret
getting cocky with me.
Nobody can beat me under the waves!
The water is my home,
and it's always on my side!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Huh? Oh?
Aah!
That's an ultrasonic shield.
You're not going anywhere.
Gah! Aah!
Bad idea!
Gah!
- Aah!
- This fight is over!
Aah!
Don't you get it?
This is what happens when you face
the might of the Emerald Ray.
- Hey.
Huh?
Science Ninja Technique: Decoy Body.
When did you do that?
I was never inside to begin with.
Hm.
Sweet dreams.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
You can't hold me!
Hm?
Daiana!
Damn you!
Ahsa, I believe you said
the water is always on your side,
but the tide can be turned
against you.
What?!
Running electric currents through water
splits it into hydrogen and oxygen.
Aah!
And when you recombine
the two again,
they can become highly explosive.
Science Ninja Technique:
Electrolysis.
Take it from me,
there is no bigger threat
than having a friend turn foe.
Thanks for getting me
out of that sticky situation.
Same to you. I appreciate it.
I am grateful you returned
with your henchmen.
They seem very capable.
Since the Hagane-ikka launched
an attack on my family,
it means that they must be ready
to unleash their full-scale invasion
on Amatsukuni.
As I thought.
That's precisely why we came here.
- Batman.
- Huh?
We found the Quake Engine.
It's in the heart
of the Yakuza Tower.
What is the Quake Engine?
It's a machine that's
been keeping this country stable
by connecting it
to an interdimensional fissure.
But once we destroy it,
Hinomoto should go back to being
part of its original world.
So you're saying
it's something like an anchor,
and once we cut it loose,
we're free?
That about sums it up.
Huh?
- Nightwing, let's get moving.
- Right.
I'm going with you.
I'm a native of Hinomoto,
and we should clean up our own mess.
That is exactly what
I'd expect from you.
Yeah, you're not too different
from the person I know.
The one called Wonder Woman, right?
Robin mentioned her before.
Yes. That's correct.
I've always had this feeling
that I wasn't alone,
that there was someone like me
out there somewhere.
Ahsa seemed to share
the same sentiment.
- Yeah?
- I shall not bring shame to her
by living below her standards.
Perhaps she's the reason
I protect the Ninkyo
and why I keep its spirit alive.
I wouldn't worry about that.
You're exactly how
you should be, wherever you are.
Hop on in.
No.
I tend to get carsick.
Ha!
Huh. Go figure.
Let's go.
Within the ranks
of the Japanese yakuza
are sacrificial assassins sent to kill
the bosses of rival syndicates.
They are like human bullets.
And now those men will quite literally
be fired straight into Gotham,
willing to pay the ultimate price.
Alright!
Now give 'em hell!
Huh? This is so dumb.
You guys are
out of your damn minds.
It's like a damn Yakuza Tornado,
and it's about to hit Gotham!
Very good.
It's building up from the ground,
just like a real tornado.
Not like a downburst.
Huh?
There seemed to be
some confusion earlier.
What are you, a weatherman?
We gotta stop it.
Yeah, yeah. Hang on.
We need to amplify the
space-time pulse that's within us
and block the Speed Force
from crossing dimensions.
Science Ninja Technique:
Tornado Canceler!
Oyabun!
Those jerks from Amatsukuni
are attacking!
Do they think
we're screwing around?
Beat them to a bloody pulp!
Yes, sir!
Come, Detective, meet your end.
Bat-Phoenix,
going into cloaking mode.
Step on it, Jason.
Alright!
Get back here, now!
Here comes our boy!
Flash in a funny hat!
Why don't you stop talking
and focus?
Ha!
Hyah!
You won't get away from me
that easily!
Yeah? We'll see.
Okay, that's not bad.
But watch this!
Ha!
Hyah!
Huh? Huh? Hyah!
You may be the fastest man alive,
but you're still a man.
Huh?
Hmph.
What?!
I don't think so.
I ain't falling for that again!
Then try this on for size!
Try again!
Hyah!
Tim!
Go that way!
Huh?
Hyah!
Aah!
That's not good.
We can't fit on the road!
No, check this out!
Hyah!
You won't escape. Hyah!
Damn it!
No way!
I should be faster
than these chumps
because nobody beats
the fastest man in the world.
Nobody beats me!
Huh?
That's not possible!
What...
the hell is this?!
You dare pull this kind of crap
with me?
I am done screwing around!
You hear me?
You and your cheap tricks.
I hate your stupid city
and all you losers!
Bunch of damn punks.
I'll run them down
and pull their guts out
and throw 'em in the in the street.
Just wait, you little turds.
Huh?
Science Ninja Technique:
Vending Machine.
After running
at such high speeds for a while,
you're bound to get hungry
and thirsty...
like any man would.
Enjoy your nap time.
It went off without a hitch.
Way to go, Jason.
You know, this
doesn't really feel like a win.
Aw, come on.
You know this would
have been much more difficult
if that were the real Flash.
Now that is a super huge problem.
You've got some guts to make
a mockery of my henchmen,
but it's the last thing you'll do.
Hmph!
You must be joking.
Ha!
Hyah!
Huh? Aah!
You cannot win.
You are going to pay
for defying us
by spending the rest
of your lives in pain.
Ah!
Child's play.
Hmm?
Hmph.
It's about time you showed up,
bat fiend.
I'm here to get Robin back.
I'm sure you love your son.
Sadly, your other sidekicks
are already dead.
Hm?
I've got bad news for you, Kuraku.
Daiana.
Ahsa...
I should have known he wouldn't
be able to handle the job.
Get in!
All of you, go to secure the
Quake Engine and find Robin.
Come on!
Hyah!
Zeshika has been defeated.
You're the only member
of the Hagane Family standing.
Yes, well, that is hardly a problem.
Not with me around.
Ha!
I am the Man of Steel,
master of the underworld.
Kuraku will show you no mercy!
And as long as I live,
the Hagane-gumi will never die!
All of Hinomoto and Amatsukuni
will both be under my control.
Hm!
The power you wield,
why do you not use it
to help other people?
To help others?
That's what I'm doing.
This is humanity's true nature.
They have a desire
to hurt each other
and rule from the moment of birth.
The only way to govern this world
is to suppress their evil tendencies
with an even greater evil!
Hm?
Aah!
Daiana, you should
head for Yakuza Tower, too.
Yes, but--
Stopping the Quake Engine
is our top priority right now.
I'll handle things here myself.
You think all that fancy machinery
will be enough to stop me?
You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
This is where the Quake Engine is.
Can we take the elevator?
They could just stop it
and screw us over.
We can run up the stairs.
Oh, yay.
Aah!
Hyah!
So much for your little toy.
I knew you were
nothing more than a fraud.
There's only one fraud here,
and that would be you.
Hmph.
Die.
Ha!
What's wrong?
Got something in your eye?
Hya--
What?!
Aah!
What'd you do?
You're not from here.
You were born
on a different planet.
The only way you have
such incredible powers
is when you're exposed
to the sun rays here on Earth,
your superhuman strength
and your body of steel,
your power to fly,
and your ability to shoot
heat vision from your eyes.
However...
when exposed to the red sun rays
from your birth planet,
then you become just like
any other normal human being.
That's not possible.
Hm?
Huh?
You did this?
Yes. That's right.
You didn't destroy my machine.
You helped me arrange it
into the proper positions.
By configuring this collection
of crystals into a filter,
I turned the Earth's yellow sunlight
into the exact same type of light
found on your birth planet.
Science Ninja Technique:
Spectral Conversion!
Damn you!
You feel that?
That's what we humans call pain.
You never knew what it felt like
because you've always
lived with incredible strength.
Hurts, doesn't it?
This is the pain of all the people
you're trying to tyrannize.
Everyone living normal lives
in Amatsukuni.
Normal?
There's nothing normal
about the yakuza.
Yakuza?
Yeah, that's right!
I know that Amatsukuni
is the same as Hinomoto.
It's filled with nothing but yakuza.
Unbelievable.
You never gave a second thought
to all that crap Ra's al Ghul fed you.
You mean he lied?
Most people living in
Amatsukuni are average citizens.
Or as a friend once put it,
"good, honest people."
The whole reason I fight
is to protect those people
from criminals like the yakuza.
You don't expect me to
believe that nonsense, do you?
Oh, no, you don't have to
take my word for it.
Your arrogance will be your end!
Is that all you've got, Kuraku?
What's the matter?
Are you afraid of me?
I know a man who is
remarkably similar to you.
Except...
losing his superpowers wasn't enough
to stop him from having a heart of steel.
He kept on fighting
through sheer willpower
and did whatever it took to save lives.
If I'm enough to strike fear in you,
then you're nothing compared to him.
And you never will be.
You'll never amount to anything.
Ha!
They're back.
I can feel all my powers
returning to me.
Now I'm going to make you regret
ever talking to me like that.
Die!
Just as expected.
Hyah!
Kryptonite!
Your weakness.
It nullifies the powers
of Kryptonians like you.
This was entrusted to me by
the very man I told you about.
He wanted me to use it to stop him
if he ever lost control
and went on a rampage.
You two may look the same
on the outside,
but you don't even have a fraction
of his pride or his heart.
I'm coming for you next, Ra's.
I never expected Kuraku to lose.
Hm.
Wha--
Aw, man. This was supposed to be
my time to shine.
Your father asked me
to come help you out.
Your friends are here as well.
Are they your older brothers?
You all look pretty similar.
You've got to be kidding.
They're just posers
who think they came first.
Ra's the Great Oyabun,
your family is finished.
The leader of the Bat Family
has defeated them all.
Ha! Your big plan has failed,
Grandpa.
You won't be able to send
your stupid goons
- over to Gotham anymore.
- Hm.
Very well, then.
I guess it's time for plan B.
So glad you could make it,
Detective.
But once again,
you're a little too late.
He's got
the space-time converter.
What is that?
I can only guess it's the key part
of his time travel machine.
Dear God. What is that?
What have you done? Ra's?!
I deactivated the energy modulator,
sending the Four-Dimensional
Origami System out of control.
Now nothing holds Hinomoto in place,
which will cause the Tokyo area
to rematerialize in the other world.
Gotham City will be crushed.
- Ra's, no!
- That is going to impact
far more than Gotham!
The shockwave alone
will bring a global disaster.
This cannot be what you want.
Oh, well, you don't need
to worry about a thing.
The shockwave will
be absorbed within the fissure,
so it won't be like a meteor
or anything that exciting.
In fact, I would consider
it an improvement.
This nation of yakuza will purge
and purify all the rotten filth.
Eh, sounds kinda overboard
to me.
Hm! Ha!
Hya--
It's gone.
Mm.
Batman!
Where's the Quake Engine?
Yeah, so, uh...
it sort of disappeared.
It did what?!
The Bat Family makes
its grand entrance.
But unfortunately for you,
your superior numbers
make no difference here.
Since the Four-Dimensional
Origami System no longer has limits,
it is now operating while sliding through
multiple space-time continuums,
which means anyone
within this part of space-time
won't even be able to touch it.
That can't be.
What is this lunatic
even talking about?!
It's like he's gambling
and cheating at the table.
He's hidden the dice that
are supposed to be in the cup,
and now nobody gets a roll.
Ridiculous.
Then it's not even a game!
Huh? Ah!
Yes, exactly.
I've no intention
of taking a gamble with you.
- Well, in that case...
- Huh?
- Hmm?
...then why don't I
do the gambling?
There it is!
What?
Our bodies have been exposed
to a space-time pulse
emitted from the Quake Engine.
It may be possible for us to
focus that energy on the device
as it fluctuates through space-time
and then anchor it to this continuum.
That's the gamble
I'm willing to take.
Sounds cool. I'm in!
We'll join, too!
No, you won't!
Hyah!
Get the space-time converter
away from him!
Consider it done.
Did it work?
Not yet. We need more energy.
Five of us isn't enough?
Huh?
Wha...
How can that be?
Losing his superpowers wasn't
enough to stop him from having a heart of steel.
He kept on fighting
through sheer willpower
and did whatever it took
to save lives.
If I'm enough to strike fear in you,
then you're nothing compared to him.
You'll never amount to anything.
Daiana!
What's wrong?!
It must be recoil
from the Origami System.
Batman, this thing's starting
to disappear!
You worthless piece of trash!
Ha!
It's time to die!
Gah!
Daiana!
Hm.
Evacuate everyone from the city.
Right now!
That looks bad.
What is happening?
Tokyo has physically manifested
itself outside of the fissure
and is now being affected
by Earth's gravity.
And there is nothing you can do
to stop it.
Yes, there is.
I can still take back the
space-time converter from you
and then stop the device.
Mm. That's a valid point.
Right.
Then let's complicate things.
What the hell have you done?!
I've detonated the base
of the structure.
Even if this tower is the
only thing to fall on Gotham,
it's still enough
to raze the city to the ground!
You're a damn monster!
Farewell, then, Detective!
Now you and your little Bat Family
can go back to Gotham...
as a pile of bloody corpses.
Aah!
At last, a signal!
Master Bruce, can you hear me?
Copy, Alfred. What's going on?
The fine ladies and gentlemen of
the Yakuza League are protecting Gotham.
Ha!
- Aah!
- Ha!
- Oh!
Hyah!
Huh?
Arise!
Kuraku and the others.
- What the...?
- Master Ra's! It's him!
Hmm?
How is he doing that?
You're not getting away, Ra's!
Aah!
Damn you, Detective!
I have the space-time converter.
- You got it back!
- Whoa!
We have to hurry!
The tower is about to crash into the city!
It didn't work!
I don't think we have
enough pulse energy!
Is that you, Daiana?
So what made you change your mind?
I saw the man,
the other version of me.
He risked his life to protect the innocent
and vulnerable people in his world.
That is when I realized...
he and I are the same,
both in heart and soul.
And I see the same is true
for them as well.
Yes. That's right.
It's the Ninkyo spirit.
I suppose it is.
We must hang on.
The Bat Oyabun will find
a way out of this...
with a little help from a friend.
Having yourself
some trouble there, B-man?
Harley? What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm just gonna leave
if you use your mean voice.
Be nice, and I might
just lend you a hand.
Daiana gave me a call.
She said you would need
some saving.
And how could I turn down
a request from her?
Daiana sent you?
I see.
When she disappeared,
she was actually going to get you.
Exactamundo!
Well, we need to move quickly!
I know even you don't want to
see Gotham destroyed.
Eh.
Wha!
Ha!
Alright!
Hmph!
Hmm?
Take the Four-Dimensional
Origami System back to Hinomoto
and destroy it there.
That will enable the island to
slip out of the space-time fissure
and return your world to normal.
And that will be the end?
Yes.
The connection between
our two worlds will be severed.
Good. Then we'll take
this whole tower back with us.
Wouldn't want it
to land here on your fine city.
I'll help you.
No, this is our mess to clean up.
Ahsa, Zeshika, Bari!
Do your thing!
Right!
Hyah!
Bleh! Wha!
Enjoy this spectacle.
It won't happen again.
A Hagane technique.
The Rising Dragon of Valor.
Impressive.
Thanks for everything you've done,
Oyabun of the Bat Family.
We will never forget
all your kind efforts.
Once you return, your world will
no longer be a land filled with yakuza.
The honorable and the innocent
will live there now as well.
Sounds much better to me.
Did I hear that correctly?
You've come around to
the ways of the Ninkyo spirit?
I saw the real thing...
and so did they.
Good. Glad to hear.
Alright then. Let's go!
Make way! I'm gonna be first!
I think I'll stick with lake water.
Turns out the ocean is really salty.
You're seriously
just figuring that out?
Better late than never.
Goodbye, Miss Thang!
That was a heck of a punch
you gave me.
I'm gonna feel it for a while.
Now then, if you'll excuse us...
What was that?
A space-time pulse wave.
The Four-Dimensional Origami
System has been destroyed.
Does that mean
we fixed history or whatever?
Yeah. We're good.
Everything's back to normal.
At least according to hairstyle.
Looks great.
Mm? Huh?
Aah! Aw, not again!
I can't be seen out in public
like this!
Where are you, Batman?
You're late.
Yeah.
It's time for the weekly meeting.
Come on, quit goofing around.
We know you just got back
from your big time-traveling
adventure yesterday,
but that's no excuse.
Get moving.
We're all here waiting on you.
You okay, Bruce?
Is there a problem?
Sorry.
I'll be right there.
Master Damian,
would you care to try wearing a wig?
I believe it would suit you quite well
and provide a less ostentatious look.
Alfred, leave me alone!