Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
You coming?
-Hi, Evelyn.
-Hey.
Alex, college selection seminar
at00
in the guidance office.
-Don't forget.
-I'll be there.
I didn't see your name
on the list for the seminar.
You got a special in
with the guidance counselor
-or something?
-Mom...
Besides, I already know
where I'm applying.
Really?
What's the lucky school?
Harvard, Princeton, Oxford?
Uh, CalArts.
-CalArts.
-Yeah, is something wrong
-with that?
-Nothing's wrong with CalArts.
You mean, nothing's wrong
with CalArts for Breanna.
I didn't say that,
I just think you should try
for the best school you can.
And with your grades
and achievements,
that could be
almost anywhere.
I wanna be with Breanna in LA.
Sweetie, I know it's been
hard for you, making friends,
and I am so glad
you met someone
you get along with so well
like Breanna, but...
You don't understand.
I'll see you later!
So yesterday,
we talked about
the two authors
that I have listed here.
Would it be surprising to learn
that both of these authors
are one person?
They're the exact same person.
Why would an author do
something like this? Yes.
Hello.
Evelyn, you're needed
in the front office.
Okay, okay.
But--but yes,
they are the exact same...
Breanna McMillen!
Hello, Ms. Walsh.
Why aren't you in class?
Uh, I was actually
just about to go,
-but I really have to--
-She's helping me!
College week,
my mom needed help
posting more flyers,
and Breanna was nice enough
to volunteer.
Well, keep it quiet.
Class is in session.
-Yeah, sorry, Ms. Walsh.
-Sorry.
And drop a few by my class.
-I'm all out.
-Yeah, yeah, of course.
Come on!
What--what's this?
A bike.
If my mom finds out about...
...you lying about
putting up flyers, you mean?
Let's go.
Let's go!
Where are you going?
Bree, we can't!
Come on!
You can write about it
in your diary.
It's not a diary,
it's a memoir.
Let's go!
So what's your memoir about?
It's about you and me
and the things we love.
Red roses and lipstick,
movies, Hollywood.
-Norma Jean?
-Of course!
There you go.
It's cool, right?
-What's wrong?
-I don't like heights.
Okay, that settles it,
you're jumping.
Um, no.
Fear is an ugly emotion.
I'm not jumping.
We can do it together,
-take my hand.
-No, I'm not jumping!
All right.
What are you doing?
Imperfection is beauty,
madness is genius,
and it's better
to be absolutely ridiculous
than absolutely boring.
Breanna!
Bree?
Breanna?
Breanna!
Bree?
Bree...oh my God.
Bree!
Bree.
Bree, Bree!
Oh my God, Bree!
Bree, Bree...
Bree?
-You shoulda seen your face!
-I thought you were dead!
-I was kidding!
-Why did you do that?
I--I guess I just wanted to see
how far you'd go for me.
To see if you're
really my best friend.
I'm sorry I scared you,
okay?
I got you something.
Here, you get the black.
Look at the back.
-Help me put it on?
-Mm-hm.
Let's never go back.
-Bree...
-I'm serious.
We should go to LA now, today.
-We don't have to wait.
-What are you talking about?
Do you ever...
close your eyes and...
wish that everything
were different?
Hey.
I thought I could help
get you started on your packing.
Look, I know it's hard
moving to a new city
for everybody.
Yeah. Thanks.
I remember from just
two years ago.
But you got through it.
And you're doing
better than ever.
Your grades are up
and you're making new friends.
What's the point
of making friends
when you'll just
make us move again?
This is a really great
opportunity for us.
No.
This is a really great
opportunity for you.
I thought we were gonna
try to work things out.
This isn't up for debate, Greg.
North Carolina Park Services
are offering me
30 percent over
what I make now
and I'll be a supervisor.
And how about moving
three states away?
How's your daughter
gonna feel about that?
You do not get to act
like you care about Breanna,
-not after what you did.
-I never did anything!
I told you!
-Whatever Breanna told you--
-She wasn't the one who told me.
She even tried
to cover for you.
Don't you think
I know my own daughter
-better than that?
-I think Breanna is very good
at convincing people
to think and do what she wants,
and if she got someone
to lie for her--
I said this wasn't
up for debate.
It is over, Greg.
-But--
-Goodbye.
What are you doing?
I bought unbleached cake flour.
Thought we could make
those scones we saw
-on Battle of the Bakers.
-Okay, great.
-That's pretty.
-Oh, thanks.
Bree gave it to me.
Breanna?
Breanna, what's wrong?
Tell me what happened.
It's my mom
she's--she's dead!
Stay here, Evelyn.
-Here you go, Breanna.
-Thank you.
This is Detective Kent.
Okay, Breanna.
I'm gonna need you
to go over your story with me
just one more time, okay?
Okay.
Um...
I got up about
the usual time
and got ready for school,
and I went into the kitchen
for breakfast,
and my mom wasn't there.
And at this time,
had you seen
anything unusual?
No, just that it was quiet.
Mom always has
the coffee going
before I come down, but...
this morning,
there wasn't any,
-because...
-I understand.
Then what happened?
I thought she overslept
or something, so...
I went into her room,
and that's when I found her.
I saw her on the floor
and I thought
I could help her, but...
as soon as I touched her,
I knew.
I know this isn't easy to hear,
but we know your mom was killed
with tranquilizer darts,
and apparently, they were
taken from her own work bag.
Were you home last night
all night?
Yes.
And when was the last time
you actually saw your mom?
Um...about00?
Did you hear anything
after you saw your mom
at00?
No.
I had my headphones on
and my music was up, I--
I didn't hear anything.
Okay.
Can you think of anyone,
anyone at all,
that would want to hurt
your mom?
Um...no.
Well...there's Greg,
Greg Olson.
That's Mom's boyfriend--
or ex-boyfriend.
He was really mad
when they broke up.
I heard them fighting.
Well, thank you, Breanna,
you've been a really big help.
I'm sure you can use your rest.
Can you let my office know
where she'll be staying?
I--I'm afraid not.
Your mom didn't fill out
the emergency contact person
on your paperwork.
It's easy to miss,
especially when
there's so much to fill out.
Who's your nearest relative?
You mean I can't stay here?
At the school?
No, I mean...
I don't have any relatives.
-None at all?
-My mom has a cousin,
Sarah-Louise, but...
I-I can't go to her.
She lives hours away
and I hardly know her.
Do you have her number?
No.
Okay.
I'll contact Family Services.
They'll be able to set you up
with a foster family
-or a group home--
-No! I can't go to foster care.
Ms. Hayden, please.
I-I can't go
to a bunch of strangers, okay?
-Not now, please.
-I'm sorry.
I'm afraid that foster care
or a group home
is your only options.
No they're not!
You can stay with us.
I'm sure we can get you
a temporary custody order
under the circumstances.
Mom?
Okay.
Um, at least until
we find this cousin,
and then we will
reassess things.
It'll be okay.
It'll be just like
you talked about.
Best friends forever.
Forever and ever.
You know where everything is,
right?
I'm sure Evelyn can
lend you some clothes.
Thank you, Ms. Hayden.
I don't wanna be any trouble.
Oh, Breanna, you're not.
Please never think that.
Hey, thank you
for letting Bree stay here.
-You're the best.
-I'm proud of you
for caring so much
and being such a good friend.
Thanks.
I'll do everything I can
for her.
Detective Kent!
Is everything all right?
Yeah, yeah, I just thought
Breanna might need
a few things from home.
-Come on in.
-Thank you.
Thank you,
that's so thoughtful.
I had one of the female officers
do the packing.
I don't have much of an idea
what a teenage girl would need.
I'm surprised Breanna has
anything left at home.
She spends so much time here
and the girls are always
trading clothes.
-Well, here we go.
-Thank you.
-Would you like to come in?
-All right.
They seem close.
Ever since they met
in summer school
a couple years ago.
Evelyn's always been shy
and had trouble making friends,
but her issues got worse
after her father passed away.
She missed
quite a bit of school.
I'll bet they didn't have a lot
of other college-track kids in
with the summer slackers,
did they?
Just the two of them.
It's been that way ever since.
You didn't happen to find
Breanna's mom's cell phone
at her house, did you?
Nah, it was smashed pretty bad.
I was hoping it would have
her cousin's contact info.
Maybe Mindy's boyfriend
might know?
I'd be happy to ask,
if we can find him.
He seems to have taken off.
-Is that suspicious?
-Mm-hm.
You don't think he'll
come for Breanna?
We don't even know
if he's our guy.
Look, whoever the killer is,
if he wanted Breanna, he could
have done it last night.
I guess you're right.
I don't wanna take
any more of your time.
Thank you again.
-I'll show you out?
-Of course.
...get an apartment,
and it'll be right by
the Hollywood sign, right?
It'll be just like
you talked about.
It's perfect!
Hi, girls.
Breanna, Detective Kent had
some of your things sent over.
He though you might need these.
Oh, thanks!
Breanna, do you know if
your mom had an address book
or a planner,
anything like that?
Uh, I don't know.
Maybe. Why?
I'm hoping it would have
her cousin's number.
Do you know where
she might have kept it?
Probably in her room,
but I'm not sure.
Hey, Mom, we kinda need
to be alone.
Okay.
Let me know if there's
anything you girls need.
Yeah. Thanks.
-Anyways...yes, red walls.
-Yes.
-Flowers, maybe.
-Roses everywhere.
Yeah, thank you.
Hi, Breanna.
I thought you might like these.
I'm sorry about your--
I mean...
I know what it's like.
Both of my parents
are dead, too.
I didn't know.
Um...
Would you like
to sit with us?
You sure?
Yeah.
Thanks.
They're really pretty,
thank you.
It was a long time ago.
"S" for Sarah-Louise.
Hello?
Is someone there?
I mean, she just called me
and she, like,
sprained her ankle falling.
-Mom.
-Ms. Hayden.
Evie, take her bags.
You girls are sweet.
I'm fine.
The doctor said I can walk,
as long as I don't overdo it.
God.
Oh. The tea.
I just put it on.
Lemon and one sugar?
-Yes.
-Okay.
I should probably
go help her.
Hold on.
-Mom--
-I'm sure Breanna can make tea
on her own just fine.
What did you mean
when you said,
"It will be just like
you talked about" to Breanna?
You said it in my office
and I overheard you
say it again yesterday.
So I'm not
the only eavesdropper?
-It's no big deal.
-Then you won't mind
telling me about it.
I just meant
it'll be like
when Bree talks about us
rooming together at college.
Honey, we don't
even know how long
she's gonna be staying with us.
Her cousin may want her
to come stay with her.
-She lives hours away.
-She's also her family.
I'm sure that's what
her mom would have wanted.
Who cares what her mom
would have wanted?
It's not like she was
such a great mom anyways.
-Evelyn!
-She was making Bree move away!
You knew about that?
Why didn't you say anything?
What's the point?
It's not like talking
would have changed anything.
That's really mature of you
I'm really--
Okay, that's not
the only thing she did.
She was always dating
these gross, creepy guys,
like that Greg.
What was gross and creepy
about Greg Olson?
Uh, he was always
hanging around Bree,
trying to talk to her,
wanting to touch her.
Like, totally hitting on her.
And when Mrs. McMillen
found out,
that's when
she broke up with him.
Look.
All I'm saying is
let's not borrow trouble.
Breanna has suffered
a big loss, and...
you have to expect
big changes to come from that
sooner or later.
Here we are.
And I just baked
some cookies.
Do you need a blanket?
-No, I'm--
-Evie, get the red afghan
-in the room.
-It's really not necessary.
This is all very sweet,
but you don't have to do this.
But you've been so good
letting me stay here.
Well, I wanna think
about something else,
even if just
for a little while?
Is that all it is?
You can tell me.
My mom and I,
we had a fight
the night she...
It was stupid, but...
I was so mad at her.
But now she's...
I feel so bad about it,
but there's nothing
I can do,
because I--
I can't see her
or talk to her or anything.
Not ever again.
Breanna, your mom knows
you love her,
no matter where she is.
And she knows you didn't mean
anything you said in anger.
Your mom never stopped
loving you.
Not even for a second.
How do you know?
Because even if they
don't like their actions,
moms always love their kids.
You know I'm always here
for you, okay?
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
You know...
Breanna, hey.
How are you holding up?
She's okay.
Thanks for asking.
Okay.
What's up?
-Not much, how are you?
-Good.
-What are you reading?
-Oh, it's Huckleberry Finn.
Ooh!
I had a friend in college,
and every time
she got a new boyfriend,
I wouldn't see her
for two weeks.
But she always
came back around,
and it always gave me a chance
to meet some new people.
And Jenna Ryder
is really friendly
and there's room
at her table.
I'm not mad about that,
it's just...
-Are you sure?
-It's Alex Tyler.
He doesn't actually like her,
he's just using her
to get attention,
to be popular.
-Sweetie, I don't think--
-I gotta go.
I'm gonna be late for class.
Lucy?
This came for you
to the office.
Thank you.
I asked Breanna McMillen's
last school to send over
her file.
I'm still looking
for the contact info
for her mom's cousin.
Still nothing.
I guess it's hard to imagine
that the worst
will ever actually happen.
-That's a pretty thick file.
-You're right.
-What is it?
-It looks like Breanna
didn't change schools
because they moved.
She was expelled.
She broke
another student's nose.
I can't even...
Breanna McMillen's been
in and out of my house
almost every day
for the last year and a half.
I've never seen anything
like this from her,
especially not
anything violent.
Well, just goes to show,
you can never really know
another person.
It says that her problem started
after her dad died.
Maybe she just needed
a fresh start.
I wouldn't be so sure
about that.
I-I didn't just come here
to play Pony Express.
There's something serious
I need to talk to you about.
Breanna McMillen handed this in
to Mr. Drew for English.
He showed it to me because
he thought it was very good,
very insightful.
"Joseph Conrad's
Heart of Darkness
has at its center
Commander Kurtz,
a man driven by his
environment and circumstances
to commit evil deeds."
He's right. I didn't realize
she could write this well.
That's the problem.
She can't.
"Joseph Conrad's
Heart of Darkness
has at its center
Commander Kurtz,
a man driven by his environment
and circumstances..."
I see.
I assigned that same book
to my AP English class
last year.
I kept a copy of this
because it was so good.
This was Evelyn's essay.
I haven't shown it
to Mr. Drew yet.
I wanted to give her
the benefit of the doubt.
And Evelyn's worked so hard
after her little bit of trouble.
Thank you.
I appreciate you
coming to me first.
Will you just let me
talk to the girls
and get their side
of the story?
Yes, go ahead, I...
I know it hasn't been
easy for you
raising Evelyn by yourself.
Especially when
she struggled so much.
Thank you.
But I would get that Breanna
out of your house.
It would be a shame
if her bad influence
rubbed off on Evelyn.
Who are you?
What do you want?
I'm Greg Olson.
Hey!
Hey, stop!
I need to talk to you.
I need to--
Hey, I just wanna
talk to you, that's it.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Well, you're not really
giving me much of a choice.
I didn't kill Mindy.
You're not doing a very good job
of acting like an innocent man.
I was home
the night she was murdered.
I wanted to be with her,
I loved her.
I would never hurt her,
not ever.
Tell it to the police.
You think the boyfriend--
ex-boyfriend--
isn't always
the prime suspect?
Especially one who has
a couple DUIs on his record?
What's to stop them
from pinning it all on me,
go for an easy conviction,
get the case off the books?
Make everyone look
like a rock star...
except me.
How 'bout the truth?
That's what I'm hoping for.
I'm a victim here too.
I know what it looks like,
but I'm a good guy.
Not a bad guy,
but you hit on your
girlfriend's teenage daughter?
That little brat!
Is that what she told you?
I never did that.
The only time
I ever touched her
was the day that I shook her
hand when Mindy introduced us.
That's clearly not
what Mindy thought.
Because Breanna lied.
She saw we were getting close
and didn't want a stepdad.
Why wouldn't Breanna
want a stepdad?
I wasn't falling for
her little lost girl act.
I wasn't gonna, you know,
tolerate her manipulation
and lies.
Why are you telling me all this?
Mindy was killed
with a hypodermic needle
filled with animal tranquilizer.
And her dart gun is missing.
And who had
the most access to it?
So you think Breanna
killed her own mother.
Tell that to the boys in blue.
Okay, you know what?
I just wanna make sure
I get all this.
I wanna write this down, so.
You little...
Lay down and close your eyes.
Just do it.
Okay.
Okay. On three, we'll open.
-Okay?
-Okay.
One, two, three.
Wow.
It's perfect.
Evelyn? Breanna?
-Do you like it?
-Remember I told you our plan?
-It's the midnight sky.
-Remember I told you
to hold off on redecorating?
-Evelyn, I was clear--
-Mom, it's my room.
Okay, we will
address this later.
Breanna, something very serious
has been brought to my attention
and we need to discuss it.
It's very serious, it's about
your essay for Mr. Drew.
-What about it?
-We know that
you didn't write it.
Not really.
-What?
-Don't you realize
you could've gotten Evelyn
into a lot of trouble?
Evelyn...what's she got to do
with my essay?
Mr. Drew showed it
to Mrs. Walsh
and she recognized it
as one too similar
to one that she had
received last year.
I don't understand
what you're saying.
I haven't even
turned in my essay yet.
-What?
-I'm still working on it.
He gave me an extension
until Monday, I...
I have my notes and my outline
on my laptop.
Mr. Drew received this essay
with your name on it.
I've never seen this
before in my life.
Breanna, please don't try
to lie and cover this up.
You're only going
to make it worse.
I'm not lying.
Why don't you believe me?
I saw a copy of the records
from your last school.
We know all about the fight
and you getting expelled.
I didn't want anyone
to know about that.
I knew they'd judge me for it.
It does make it very hard
to believe you now,
especially when I have
the proof in my own hands.
Okay, I got into some trouble.
But even at my old school,
I never cheated,
-I would never do that.
-It was me.
What?
I turned in the essay
with Breanna's name on it.
I-I put it in his mailbox
this morning,
but she didn't have
anything to do with it,
-I swear.
-Evie, what were you thinking?
I coulda got
into so much trouble.
But I didn't know Mr. Drew
would show it to Ms. Walsh.
I was just trying to help.
You're my best friend.
Right? Best friends would do
anything for each other.
I have a very hard time
believing that you did this
entirely without
prompting from Breanna.
See what you did?
Now everybody thinks
I'm a liar and a cheat.
-But I did it for you--
-No.
I don't wanna hear it.
I can't believe
you'd do this to me.
-Evie...
-Let her go.
She'll come back
when she calms down.
You hate me now?
I don't hate you.
Even if Evelyn gets in trouble
for trying to help me?
It's okay.
You're not my mom.
You don't have to love me
even when you don't love
my actions.
Breanna, I just--
Can I get back to work now,
please?
Finally.
Hello?
Hi, uh, you don't know me,
but my name's Lucy Hayden.
I-I'm looking for
Mindy McMillen's cousin.
That's me. Why?
Is anything wrong?
Um, I'm afraid so.
Mindy's dead.
-She was murdered.
-Oh, I can't believe this.
Breanna.
Is Breanna okay?
She's fine. In fact,
she's staying with me
and my daughter, Evelyn,
the girls are best friends,
while we tried to reach you.
Tried to?
I don't understand.
Well, I'll text you
the number of the detective
in charge of Mindy's case.
He'll be able to explain
more to you than I can.
Thank you, and thank you
for letting me know.
I'm sorry, I don't even know
where it is that you live.
-Fort Pierce.
-Oh.
That's only 90 minutes away.
I'd be happy to come to you
to discuss everything with her.
-Would Sunday be too soon?
-No, the sooner the better.
Thank you for taking care
of Breanna.
-Poor child.
-Again, I'm so sorry
for your loss.
Goodbye.
Ow.
Who's out there?
I'm gonna call the police.
Oh, seriously?
Show yourself.
I'm calling the police.
-Hey, is everything okay?
-Someone's out there.
Get inside.
It's probably just
the neighbor's cat.
He cuts through
the yard sometimes.
Ms. Hayden.
Did you get locked out?
I thought I heard knocking.
I'm sorry.
I'm really tired.
Um, it's been a long day,
we could all use some rest.
Hey.
Talk to you in the morning.
Bree?
Can you forgive me?
Yes. Of course.
It's been a terrible week.
A terrible, terrible week, okay?
-I'm so sorry.
-No, of course.
I--I'm sorry too.
You know you mean
everything to me, right?
Best friends forever.
Forever and ever.
Oh, good, there's coffee.
Hold on.
You owe me a talk.
Mom, Bree's coffee
is gonna get cold,
-and she hates cold coffee.
-Bree can make herself
some more coffee.
Do you realize
how much trouble
you could have gotten into
for that essay stunt?
What made you think
of doing such a thing?
Bree was really worried
about getting kicked off
the college track.
She said she might
not even be able
to get into state then.
So she asked you
to help her.
No, it wasn't like that.
She didn't have to.
She knows how much going to
college together means to you.
She just had to make you
think there was a chance
she couldn't go and let you
draw your own conclusions.
Mom, she didn't
make me do anything.
Look, I know you think
she's your friend,
but she is manipulating you.
You have to ask yourself
if her words and actions
-are those of a true friend.
-She didn't make me
do anything, I swear.
Fine.
I believe you.
I'll--I'll tell Mr. Drew
it was just a misunderstanding.
Breanna can turn in
her essay on Monday.
And no more helping.
From here on out,
Breanna has to do
all her work on her own.
Your future
depends on this, Evelyn.
Okay, fine.
Can I go now?
Hey, can I have a hug first?
-Hey, what's up?
-Oh, God!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
It is okay. I will
just change my shirt.
Uh, I'll pick up some pizza
for dinner tonight.
-See you girls tonight.
-Thanks, Mom.
Oh, Bree doesn't
like mushrooms.
-Hey, Ms. Hayden.
-Jenna.
What brings you into school
on a Saturday?
Band practice
for the spring musical.
I was hoping maybe
Evelyn would reconsider
coming back
this year.
We could really use
an oboe player.
Our reed section
is a little thin.
I think the girls
decided against
the school musical
this year,
but I'll be sure
to bring up your invitation
-to Evelyn and Breanna.
-Not Breanna.
I mean, we have
a pianist already.
Okay, well,
I will just tell Evelyn,
but if I were you
I'd keep up the oboe search.
Do you know why Evelyn
doesn't like us?
The other band kids, I mean.
Did we do something
to offend her or something?
What? No.
I'm sure that's not true.
What would make you
ask that?
Last year, we kept asking her
to hang out and do stuff
after rehearsals.
We invited Breanna,
too, of course,
but they just wanted
to be together.
Even if Breanna had something
to do with her mom or whatever,
Evelyn wouldn't hang out
with us.
-Did she say why not?
-She said something like,
"Breanna wouldn't like it."
Well, I will bring
this up to Evelyn,
and we'll just have to see
if she'll reconsider
when things
settle down a bit.
Thanks, Ms. Hayden.
Hello.
I come bearing pizza,
mushroom-free.
What are you doing out here?
Come on, don't tell me
that Breanna changed her mind
-about mushrooms.
-No.
-What's up?
-Nothing.
Would that nothing
be named Breanna?
No.
Where is she?
She's finishing her essay.
Good.
I'm glad
she's taking it seriously.
Yeah, well,
she would have been done by now
if she hadn't
been gone all day.
Gone? Where'd she go?
I don't know.
She wouldn't tell me.
She wouldn't let me
go with her either.
You know, even best friends
need some time apart.
Jenna stopped by
my office today
to see if maybe you wanted
to join the band
for the school musical
after all?
No, they just need
an oboe player.
She said that,
but she's also afraid
that you don't like her
and the other band kids.
I think she really wants
to be your friend.
Why don't you give her
a chance?
I know that
you still struggle
with your shyness
and anxiety,
but you can talk to me.
And if you want, I can make you
another appointment.
God, Mom, I don't want
to talk to anybody, okay?
I don't need other friends,
I have--I have Bree.
Nobody understands.
I couldn't tell
anybody this.
-Ever.
-Breanna?
Sh, I have to go.
Breanna, what are you doing up?
It's the middle
of the night.
-I couldn't sleep.
-Who are you talking to?
-No one.
-Breanna.
-It's private.
-That's not
an acceptable answer.
Evelyn said
you were gone all day
without letting me know
where you were.
I just went to the mall.
You still should have told me.
Let me see your phone.
No.
I don't have to show you.
You're not my mom.
I know.
But you're under my roof
and I'm responsible for you.
That means that I get
to set rules and boundaries,
including knowing
who you're speaking to.
But I would never
try to replace your mom.
Well, that's good.
What are moms
good for anyway?
They jerk you around
from place to place.
They date whoever
they want.
Even if you hate them.
They don't care
about how you feel
or what you need.
I never want a mom again.
I know that you're going
through a hard time, but--
You don't know
anything about me.
I'm glad you're not my mom.
-I wish I never had one.
-Breanna!
Breanna.
Sarah-Louise?
It's Lucy Hayden.
This was a wasted trip.
Lucy?
Detective Kent,
what are you doing here?
Well, they called me in
since the victim's connected
to one of mine.
I just don't understand
why someone would do
something like this.
Yeah, it's a hard thing to wrap
your head around, but...
At least we know one thing.
Sarah-Louise wasn't killed
by Greg Olson.
-How do you know that?
-Well, 'cause he was in
my station when she died.
So you finally ran him down?
It's more like
he came to his senses.
Walked in on his own.
And he doesn't
look too good
for Mindy McMillen's
death either.
Neighbor swears
she saw him sleeping
in his living room
with all the lights still on.
She was out
walking her dog
right around
the same time she died.
So we have no idea
who killed Mindy either?
I--it's gotta be someone
who knew about the dart gun,
someone who had access to it.
Unfortunately,
a lot of people
knew about her work as a vet.
But did they know
where she kept the gun?
What are you saying?
Excuse me, I'm gonna
go see what they want.
I'll be back.
Hey, Mom, where are you?
It's a long story,
I'll tell you when I get home.
Are you okay?
Maybe you should tell me now.
Was that a police siren?
I'll tell you
when I get back.
Is Breanna there?
Um, yeah, she's here.
She's working on her essay.
She would have
had it done by now
if I could have just
helped her a little bit.
Not now, Evelyn.
Put me on speaker.
Okay.
Can you girls hear me?
This is very important.
I need you to lock the doors
and stay in the house.
No going out,
no guests over.
Don't even open the door,
even if you know the person.
Especially you, Breanna,
do you understand?
-Yes, Mom.
-Yes, Ms. Hayden.
Good, I--
I don't mean
to scare you girls,
but I need you
to take this seriously.
I'll be home in about
an hour and a half.
I love you girls.
-Love you. Bye.
-Bye.
Your mom said
she loved me.
Yeah, why wouldn't she?
She was so mad about
the phone call last night.
Well, she gets mad
all the time.
It never lasts.
Yeah, my mom
was like that too.
Do you miss her?
Maybe that's why this essay
is taking forever.
Maybe you need
a study break.
We could make some popcorn
and watch a movie.
Niagara or
Don't Bother to Knock.
I--I really shouldn't.
It's due tomorrow
and it has to be
at least as good
as the one you turned in.
I could help you.
-I don't know.
-Just with, like,
grammar and spellcheck.
That's not cheating.
That's something
you can do online.
I guess that'd be okay.
Actually, I need you to do
something for me first.
Anything.
Tell me where
you were yesterday.
Why do you want
to know that?
Because...
if we're best friends,
we should tell
each other everything.
We can't keep secrets
between us.
Okay, but you can't tell anyone.
-Ever.
-Yeah, okay.
I mean it.
Especially not your mom.
Cross my heart.
Detective Kent?
Detective?
Are you girls okay?
Yeah, Mom, we're fine.
We'll be down in a second.
I'll wait down here for you.
What now?
I swear, Evelyn,
if I find
one more red lipstick
melted in this dryer.
Hello?
Detective Kent, I just
found a tranquilizer dart
in Breanna's clothes.
Evelyn said she went off
by herself yesterday
and--and wouldn't say
where she went,
but we know she knows
where Sarah-Louise lives.
-That's not all.
-What?
The neighbors reported seeing
a strange car in the area
right around the same time
Sarah-Louise was killed.
It matches Mindy's car.
Lucy, would--would
Breanna have a key?
No, I--I borrowed
Mindy's keys
when I went to grab
her address book.
I have 'em right here.
They're not in my purse.
I just had them.
I caught Breanna making a phone
call to someone last night,
and we got in an argument
and she said--
she said she wished
she never had a mom.
Here's what you're gonna do.
Call Child Protection Services
and tell 'em
you're surrendering custody
of Breanna immediately.
They'll send
somebody to get her.
Evelyn's gonna be heartbroken.
Well, she'll have you
to get her through it, okay?
Call me if you need anything.
Okay, thank you.
Hi, I am looking for
Child Protection Services.
I need to surrender
my temporary custody
of a minor.
Her name's Breanna McMillen.
Do you have her file?
Okay, good.
How soon can you send
someone to pick her up?
Okay, great.
Thank you so much.
Yes, I--
-Mom, what are you doing?
-Evelyn, I'm sorry.
But she cannot stay here.
I know how much
you care about her,
but it is not safe.
Evelyn, you have
to trust me here.
I have your best interest
in heart.
-Sweetie, it's not safe.
-Not safe, not safe.
Mom, what are you
talking about?
Why did you make us
stay inside?
Hi.
Breanna.
Your tea's ready.
Thank you.
We were just talking
about you, actually.
All good things?
Yes, of course.
Care to share?
-Ow!
-Bree!
Are you okay?
Mm-hm.
It's not that deep.
Looks like you need a Band-Aid.
-Here, I'll help.
-Nope. Breanna's got it.
The Band-Aids are in the
bathroom medicine cabinet,
top shelf.
Breanna.
The knife.
Right, here you go.
Mindy's cousin is dead.
That's why you made us
stay inside?
That doesn't mean
someone wants to kill Breanna.
Who would want
to kill Breanna?
That's not what I mean.
There are signs,
evidence even,
that Breanna
might be involved.
No.
No, Bree wouldn't
kill anybody.
I don't know that.
She might be sick,
she might need help,
but if she's dangerous,
she can't stay here.
We can't send her away,
not now.
Not after everything
we've been through.
I'm sorry, I know this is hard,
but I need to keep you safe.
You are the most important thing
in the world to me.
You can't do this!
You know what she means to me!
We're best friends.
I'm--I'm nothing without her.
She's made you feel that way
so she can use you.
No.
If she's going,
I'm going too.
Evelyn, she is not your friend.
You're wrong.
She's my best friend forever.
Forever and ever.
Bree!
It's gonna be okay, okay?
Evelyn.
Hey.
CPS is gonna be here soon,
so I'm gonna go help Breanna
-gather up her things.
-No, I should be the one
-to tell her.
-Nope.
-You're gonna stay here.
-No, she's my friend.
Stay here.
Breanna, are you okay?
I need to talk to you.
Where is she?
Where'd she go?
"Dear Ms. Hayden,
I didn't tell you
how to contact
my mom's cousin
because I wanted to stay
with you and Evelyn
and not have to move away
and start over again.
You said you loved me,
but now you're sending me away.
I was right about
never wanting a mom again.
I'm leaving.
You'll never see me again.
Breanna."
Sh--she's gone?
I'll have to call
CPS and the police.
They're gonna go
have to look for her.
She--she left me?
No, I don't believe it.
We're best friends,
she said so.
Evelyn.
This is all your fault.
What? No.
I'm never gonna see my best
friend again because of you!
I need her!
I'm nothing without her.
-Evelyn, it's gonna be--
-No!
-Evelyn.
-I'm sorry.
Evelyn. Evelyn,
we need to talk about this.
-It won't happen again.
-No, I don't care about that.
-I need to be alone right now.
-I don't think that's a good--
I need to be alone!
Okay, well, I have
some calls to make.
You promise me
you're gonna be okay?
And do you promise you're
gonna stay in this room?
I'll be fine.
Give me your phone.
Hey, there's gonna be
a little change of plans.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
Sure, sure,
whatever you need.
Hey.
Yesterday was really amazing.
I, um, I've never
done that before.
It--yeah, it was--
it was amazing.
And I haven't either.
Ever.
So...
I love you.
Don't say that.
Please.
-But what I--
-Just...don't.
Okay?
Everyone that says
they love me leaves me.
Or they die.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah,
whatever you want.
We need to get
to Long Leaf Drive.
No problem.
She needs time.
Just give her time.
What's going on
in that head of yours?
Hello?
Who's out there?
Lucy, it's Detective Kent,
let me in.
Lucy?
Detective Kent, what is it?
Did you find Breanna?
No, but we found a boy
from her high school.
His name is Alex.
Alex Tyler?
Yeah, he's dead.
And we found this
in his hand.
I didn't want
to believe it, but...
It's worse than that.
Turn it over.
Th--this is Evelyn's pendant.
Evelyn never takes it off.
-Yeah. Where is she now?
-She's upstairs.
We had a fight and--
oh God.
Evelyn?
Evelyn? Evelyn?
Are you in there?
Open this door!
Here, let me.
I would have seen her
if she left.
I've--I've had her phone
the whole time.
Been downstairs
the whole time and--
She could have used
the email app on the computer.
She must have gone over
the railing.
Yeah.
It's a straight drop.
Evelyn's terrified
of heights.
Well, she must have really
wanted to go to Breanna.
So, Breanna enticed Evelyn
out to kidnap her?
But why?
I don't understand.
I don't know either.
All I know is,
Alex's car is missing,
presume Breanna took it.
Lucy, do you have any idea
where they could be?
I don't know.
I mean...
Breanna could have
tried to go home.
I already sent people
over there.
Said the place was dark.
There's no sign of anybody.
Look, we'll keep
everybody updated
and we'll keep looking,
okay?
-I'm going out, too.
-No, you're not.
Breanna is disturbed,
a very dangerous girl.
I can't just sit here
and wait.
I'm sorry, it's too dangerous.
You need to stay here
and let us handle this.
You'll call me
as soon as you hear anything.
Yeah, I will.
Thank you, Detective.
Breanna!
Detective Kent, leave a message.
Detective Kent,
I'm at the McMillens'.
I drove by
and the lights are on.
I think that Breanna is here.
Please.
Please hurry.
Breanna?
Evelyn, Evelyn, Evelyn.
Evelyn, I'm gonna get you
out of here, sweetie,
don't worry.
Don't worry,
don't worry!
I'm gonna get you
out of here.
Breanna!
Breanna, you don't
have to do this!
What? What?
-What happened?
-I'm covered in gasoline.
We have to get out of here.
I don't under--what happened?
I don't understand.
I don't know.
Evie messaged me
on the app and said
she figured out a way
I didn't have to go
and needed to see me,
so I had Alex take me
to where she said to meet.
She was so mad I was with him,
she shot him.
What? I--I don't know.
How could--how could
she do this?
I don't know.
It takes a smart brunette
to play a dumb blonde.
Evelyn!
You can't be here.
You shouldn't be here.
I know that
you're scared, sweetie.
I just--I want to help you.
Put that down.
You don't want to help me.
You want to keep us apart.
You and everyone
wants to keep us apart.
Ms. McMillen
and then Sarah-Louise
and then Alex
and now you.
I just want you
to be happy, sweetie.
If you wanted me to be happy,
you wouldn't try
to take Bree from me.
I need her.
I'm nothing without her.
Nothing!
Bree.
I'll make sure that we'll
never be apart ever again.
It'll be like
you always talked about.
Evie, please don't do this.
With the clouds
all around and...
and the stars up above.
First you and then me.
And then we'll always
be together.
What--what are you saying?
It's just like
you always said, Bree.
We are all of us stars.
We deserve to twinkle.
Best friends.
Forever and ever.
Evelyn, no!
Evelyn.
I never wanted any of this.
I know, I'm sorry
I thought it was you.
I have been so blind.
I should have known,
I should have seen.
-I didn't see it either.
-Lucy!
Lucy, are you okay?
It was Evelyn--
she confessed.
She's alive.
Call for an ambulance
right now.
It's gonna be okay, Evie.
We're gonna get you
all the help you need.
I promise.
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Excuse me, do you know
where I can find Evelyn Hayden?
I believe she's over there.
The doctors say
you're doing really well.
Seems like you've made
a lot of friends.
Oh, but I'm not--I mean, I--
I like them all the same.
Except maybe Tyler.
-You like Tyler more?
-No, less.
He--he can be annoying,
but only sometimes.
I think that's
more than fair.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I--
I did such terrible things.
And I don't even--
I didn't even want to, really,
I just--I don't--
I don't know why I did.
I'm sorry too.
I should have known.
I should have seen it.
I don't know how I missed it.
I guess I just wanted
to think that...
But I should have
made you get help.
And I know now
I'm gonna do everything
I can to help you.
I'm still here for you
and I still love you
just the same.
How?
After everything I did.
Moms always love their kids.
Always.
-I'm sorry.
-Oh, sweetie.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
-I love you.
-It's gonna be okay.
-I'm sorry.
I love you.
So what do you want to do?
Um, let's go ride bikes.
-Yes.
-Yeah?
Oh, I'll be right back.
Hi.
Uh, how's Evelyn doing?
She's doing better, much better.
The doctors are really pleased
with her progress.
That's good.
Um...
I can't help but feel like
part of this was my fault.
You can't blame yourself.
Evelyn's disorder progressed
incredibly quickly,
turning a normal friendship
into an obsession
in a matter of weeks,
maybe even days.
They--they said
we couldn't have expected
or predicted any of this.
Thank you.
I--I think I really
needed to hear that.
I better go, but I'll see you
later, okay?
Thank you for everything.
I got you something.
What is it?
You're gonna really like it.
-Show me!
-Okay.
Oh my gosh, Breanna.
It's perfect.
-I love it so much.
-You like it?
It's my favorite colors.
I know, I know you.
Thank you.
This is so sweet.
Of course.