[birds chirping]
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[suspenseful music]
[whimpers]
[screams]
[princess moans]
[groans]
[electricity crackling]
[distant clatter]
Hey. Darling.
Darling.
Did you hear that?
[distant clatter]
I think someone's
in the house.
[sighs]
I don't hear anything, Ray.
- You're imagining.
- I'm not.
Then go check.
- Me?
- Yeah.
Chicken.
Oh, baby.
[distant clattering continues]
I'm gonna go check.
Yeah, you do that.
[camera beeps]
[light clattering]
She's not even there.
When you open your eyes,
nothing's gonna be there.
Just gonna go to bed.
You are the chosen one.
[animal growls]
Maiden...
[sighs]
mother...
crow...
[hummingbird chirps]
Cannot believe
they're making this crap.
Found footage.
That's never been done before.
I bet it's based
on true events too.
Yep.
Right there on the front.
"Based on true events."
It's ridiculous.
Absolutely ridiculous.
You know, how come the
found footage is always edited?
Lilly.
You are so salty.
Grammar alone is infantile.
[sighs]
I'm getting paid.
Yeah, I hope so.
I'm getting paid a bonus too.
Bonus?
Yeah. Well, if I go viral,
I get a bonus.
You know, someone should really
teach them the difference
between "there" "their"
and "they are."
Shh. Honey,
I am trying to focus.
No, I mean, look at this.
Your character's a medium,
right?
A medium and a dominatrix.
Yeah. Who cons some
poor old man with tarot cards.
He is a real life ghost
in the South.
I'm thinking
about channeling him.
And then, on page ten,
needless to say you hardly
know each other at that point,
what's with the bondage?
[sighs]
Are you jealous?
Seems gratuitous.
[sighs] I don't buy the whole
past life thing either.
Then why do you jump out of bed
in the middle of the night
like you see ghosts?
Cry.
That shit's not real.
My subconscious
goes crazy when I sleep,
and dreams may occur.
May occur?
How the hell you gonna
physically sleep
with a ghost anyways?
They're already dead.
"T-H-E-Y"
apostrophe "R-E" dead.
You're an asshole.
Y-O-U apostrophe
R-E an asshole.
What? I--
Yo, yo, yo, yo, my girl.
This is about to be the best
of all the possession movies.
Like, "The Exorcist"
or some shit.
And I'm telling you right now,
it ain't gonna be none
of that remake bullshit
that Hollywood's into,
'cause I hate that shit.
I'm so excited.
You got another box.
I'm chatting
with the director.
Hey.
Sup, boss man?
Honey, you're going to be on
my fan-site video for the movie.
Chaz is recording us right now.
Eh, me out.
Sorry, Ray
just likes his privacy,
but he's just cranky,
Mr. Cranky Pants,
because he was up
all night writing.
Drinking, more like it.
[laughs]
I hope there ain't going to be
no problems with this Ray cat.
- Know what I'm saying?
- No. Why?
I don't know, you know.
You just said, like...
that we could film you
at my crib and shit
when we cast you.
Like this behind the scenes
look at a professional actress.
Yeah, of course.
By the way,
your house is amazing.
You know that when
you sign that contract,
there's this little section that
says "any and all footage--"
Ray will be fine.
No problemo.
I see you got my package.
Oh, I did.
Oh, my God.
What is it?
Unfiltered, baby.
[laughs]
Can you dig it?
I have to warn you,
I'm like, totally method now.
Like, Ray thinks I can be
a little scary and weird.
Shit, scary and weird?
That's our business.
See that right there,
that's what the horror fans--
that's what they wanna see,
baby.
Well, I mean,
I have a fan base,
but it could so be better.
It will after this movie,
baby.
You gonna be a movie star.
Say it with me.
Movie star.
Yay. Thank you.
I am so excited.
And you going viral.
Honey, do you hear that?
♪ I'm gonna go viral
- ♪ I'm gonna go viral
- ♪ Gonna go viral
♪ Gonna go viral
Hey.
Skin is a scream queen's
necessity, yo.
I promise Ray
will bare it all for you.
[laughs]
Shit.
You is funny, girl.
But, for real, like, I don't
wanna have to recast you.
Like, if your videos
ain't getting watched,
and, like, people aren't
liking that shit...
Oh, God. Really?
I'm just playing with you.
I ain't gonna recast your ass.
- You.
- [laughs]
You should have seen
your face, though.
Thanks again for this fab cam
and cool statue.
I will totally do a bitchin'
unboxing video later for you.
Hey, guys,
it's Box Girl Lilly.
So I just got this
awesome new huge box
I can't wait to open
for you guys.
It's from my director.
It says, "Lilly, you're
the next big scream queen.
Sincerely, Chaz."
What is that?
Oh, this is hot.
What do you guys think?
Should I try it on?
This looks tight.
It is tight.
Whoa. Cool, right?
Super weird.
You and me, we're going
to make a masterpiece together.
[ominous music]
What up, my paranormalists?
It's time
for your favorite podcast,
"Beyond Paranormal."
I am your host and fellow freak
Juice McDaniels.
Our special guest this month is
world renowned quantum physicist
Dr. Ulrich von Strauss.
And today we will be asking
the question
"Is time travel possible?"
Better question,
do you travel in time
or does time travel to you?
Time and space can
be manipulated,
fused together
and then displaced
to create a window to
a completely different reality.
Realities are what we make.
Ain't that right, Doc?
Some of us live in between
realities and dimensions.
You think
we are not alone?
Oh, absolutely
we're not alone.
We've been visited
by many alien life forms...
many alien life forms...
[laughs]
I'm writing.
Did you sign
the release form yet?
Don't worry,
I'll get him to sign.
These "ver" glasses are like
looking into another dimension.
This is my first...
ASMR video.
Robert, thank you so much
for the bear.
Oh, he's so cute
and so fluffy,
like a little white cloud.
I'm going to sleep with him
right now.
Oh, yeah, I can't "bear"
to sleep without him.
Don't be jealous, Ray.
Oh, shoot.
Well, that's not good.
Hey, everybody,
it's Box Girl Lilly.
Welcome to Lilly vloggin'
the vlog.
[clears throat]
Okay.
Hey, guys, Lilly here again.
So this is harder
than I thought.
Um...
But you guys will
totally dig the next video,
and don't forget
to hit the like button.
"Don't forget to tune in
and hit the like button."
Hit the like button,
people.
Hey, guys,
are you ready?
[groans] Babe, will you
scratch my back, please?
[sighs] This novel
is driving me crazy.
Ugh. It's like
I'm writing in circles.
Mm-hmm.
What's with the creepy statue?
Oh, I know.
Cool, right?
Yeah.
If by "cool"
you mean super creepy.
Yeah, it's cool.
It's really cool. [sighs]
Can you please not
bring evil shit in the house
that may have
evil shit attached to it?
[moans]
Like what?
Like,
you know what I mean.
- Stuff.
- What stuff?
Evil shit
can attach to things,
and those things
can attach to us.
Like bedbugs.
I'm serious.
I promise,
no evil parasitic juju.
This isn't a joke.
Ow!
Is that real bone?
My director thought
it would inspire creativity,
Speaking of creativity,
I think my brain's
been sucked all of mine.
Oh, you're bleeding.
You just need to relax.
You know I need to write.
Is this house not the best
writing retreat ever?
It's okay.
Have you seen
the hot tub?
Hello.
I can't bring the computer
into the hot tub.
You're so cranky.
What? My editor's
breathing down my neck.
I mean, my advance
is almost gone,
and as soon
as we get back home,
we're gonna have a stack
of bills waiting for us.
Honey, my website Patreon
is killing it right now,
and I'm making a movie,
so don't worry about money.
That's easy for you to say.
I know what you need
for inspiration.
[laughs]
What are you--
- Mm.
- [sighs]
Oh, that's...
so...
[ominous music]
That's...
Oh, God, that's good.
What is that?
Uh, a camera.
Is it on?
Mm-hmm.
You want me to stop?
- Uh, yes.
- Yeah?
- Ah. No.
- No?
- No.
- Stop?
Ugh.
how do I turn it off?
[breathing heavily]
Oh, God,
where's the off button?
Oh, babe,
how do I shut it off?
Oh.
[ominous music]
Babe.
Did you see that light?
You're sleepwalking.
No, I'm not sleepwalk--
Lilly. Lilly.
There's someone
standing over you.
- You're dreaming.
- No, I am not dreaming.
Where?
Shit.
I must be dreaming.
Geek it down
a little bit here, fellas.
I gotta call
my girl anyway, so...
get the fuck out of here.
Why bother?
I can just hack
into her webcam
and you can
remotely broadcast.
Word?
Shit, that's like some
big brother shit right there.
[laughs]
Now we in your house
and you don't even know it.
[laughs]
Read 'em and weep, boys.
That's what I'm talking
about, girl. [laughs]
Oh, hello.
I didn't know anyone
was there.
Hey, how'd you get him to sign
the release form, Lilly?
Never underestimate a woman.
Baby girl,
I knew you would deliver,
and I got to say,
you and your man boy
make some pretty great pixels.
Thank you.
That's so sweet.
But I'm just-- I'm worried
because not too many people
have watched.
Girl, people gonna watch
the shit if it's scary.
And guess what?
Might be a little extra
bonus pay for you if it's hot.
[laughs]
Feel me?
Oh, it will be.
By the way, how am I doing
with the camera?
Fantastic, Lilly.
You're broadcasting
as we speak.
So when can I see
some footage?
Oh, shit, girl,
I'ma show you the footage.
I know, I just-- I feel like
I'm, like, I don't know.
I'm, just, like,
this insecure artist.
I'm like...
I'm crazy. So...
what can I do to help?
Know what? I got it.
You gonna take the red light
on the camera,
and you gonna mark it out
and then you won't know
when we filming and when
we not filming.
That's genius.
[laughs]
Sometimes it happens that way.
I-- I can't control the shit.
Well, I have to tell you I can't
video-chat with you anymore
because my character
wouldn't do that.
'Cause you method and shit.
That's why I hired you, mama.
I like it. I like it a lot.
[groans]
Lilly isn't here anymore...
minion.
My name is Roxanne.
Now and how.
Just kidding.
All right, guys. See ya.
Thank you. Bye bye.
[ominous music]
What up,
my conspiracy realists?
I am your host,
Juice McDaniels.
It's Beyond Paranormal.
Look, let's just dive
right into it, flat Earthers.
You ever sleep
with your eyes open?
Do you see things
that don't exist?
Or perhaps you find yourself
lying on the floor.
[Lilly singing indistinct]
And I'm not talking about
partying the night before.
Maybe, just maybe you're
a vessel for traveling
into another dimension.
Babe,
I'm trying to concentrate.
Juice: Today we will look
into outer body experiences
and the dangers
that lurk in your--
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
Come on. You gotta
be freaking kidding me.
Babe,
did you touch anything?
[Lilly exhales]
Lilly meditates to thrust
herself into character.
You know, babe, I--
I might have figured out my
inciting incident for my book.
[sighs]
[Southern accent]
What you whinin' about?
Ain't no thing
but a chicken wing.
You got taters
in your ears?
Oh, baby.
- [hisses]
- [groans]
This is Lilly
really getting into character.
Who are you this time, babe?
You got anything to drink?
I'm so God dang thirsty
right now.
You know we're out of milk.
You got some browns?
Excuse me.
My daddy used to say,
"Stay away from them browns,"
but I sure
do like them.
Browns.
Bourbon.
Brown liquor.
Oh. Yeah.
[slurps]
Why is this thing always--?
Where's that fine piece of ass
you got around here, hmm?
Pardon me?
Brunette.
Perfect little titties
made from God.
- Right.
- Ass of a teenager.
Mm-hmm.
You must mean Lilly.
- That your girl?
- Sometimes.
No, that ain't her.
Got anything to eat?
Oh.
Then you must mean
Miss Roxanne.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's the bitch.
She got one tight satchel.
I been waiting a long time
to tap that...
Oh, maybe youse put in
a good word, huh?
Yeah, I'll do that.
What's that thing?
Camera.
How about you
shut that shit off?
I mean, technically, I'm really
not supposed to 'cause...
How's about I take that camera
from your hand, boy,
and I shove it up
your God dang ass.
That's not funny, Lilly.
Done. I'm done.
Oh, shit.
Swear, this novel
is trying to kill me.
Now and how, minion.
Lie down or I'll
scratch it till it bleeds.
That's some outfit.
Do you like it?
My director picked it out.
[sighs]
Of course he did.
Silence.
You've been a bad little boy.
Babe, with the creepy statue?
It really freaks me out.
Ray, you said
you wouldn't be so judgey.
What's with the scotch?
Helps me write.
Shut up, bed slave.
Now and how.
I'm so fucked right now.
My publisher wants pages.
You should have seen
the email.
It's totally preposterous.
She wants the first
150 pages.
Ah. God.
Please, God, give me
a sign I should be a writer.
[sighs]
Hey, I thought we both agreed
no filming bedroom stuff.
Relax, baby.
It isn't on.
Do you need your muse?
Yeah, where's she at?
Shut your mouth,
my love slave.
Now and how.
- Now and how?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
"Okay" what?
Okay...
Roxanne.
- Aah.
- Miss Roxanne.
Miss Roxanne.
Isn't my dominatrix name
so cool?
Yeah,
more like nymphomaniac.
I read the script.
Not super excited about
all the explicit sex stuff.
It's totally superfluous.
Who copulates with a corpse?
It's a metaphor.
A metaphor.
In a horror movie.
Totally absurd.
Are you doing nudity
in this film?
Sex sells.
You know that, Ray.
[groans]
What--
What are you doing?
I'm going to make my little Ray
rise from the dead.
Little Ray.
I'm a grower, not a shower.
You know that.
Okay. Well, let's see
how much little Ray--
I mean "big Ray," can grow.
Lilly--
Miss Roxanne.
Yes, my love slave?
- Now and how.
- Now?
I'm really tired.
Fine.
- I thought you said it wasn't--
- [camera beeps]
And don't you dare wake me up
with one of your stupid dreams.
Little help.
[chanting]
What a whackadoodle.
Traveling astrally
has been dated back
to the oldest of books.
Do you think it's possible
to meditate across the state?
I had the craziest
dream last...
With the right incantation,
people have been able
to travel in time,
space,
even across galaxies
with other worlds
and other species.
Oh, brother.
I have a collection of mantras
you can use
for such a journey.
Oh, thank you.
Like, so generous.
You got any snake oil
for purchase?
Remember,
traveling can be dangerous.
Evil horn dwellers
can attach themselves
to the wandering soul.
Evil horn dwellers.
Why would you--
Attach to who now?
Don't mind him.
No, see,
this is exactly the kind
of paranormal shit
I was talking about.
- Angela, meet...
- Raymond.
Have we met?
Ah, no. Lilly must have
told me your name.
Hello, Ray.
I need to write.
Ray!
Yo, this girl's stupid,
but she mad good, though.
Yo, IT, while you're down there,
I could use a little release.
[laughs]
- We're all fixed.
- Hey, what?
Both: Must have been
a power surge.
So we up?
Camera is live, bitches.
[laughs]
We live.
All right, let's see
how much little Ray--
I mean "big Ray," can grow.
Ray:
Oh, Miss Roxanne.
What?
What else
do I have to do?
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
[growls]
Jeez!
Oh.
You scared the hell
out of me.
[growls softly]
I'm just meditating, babe.
Trying to give me
a heart attack.
[sighs]
Will you relax?
If I wanted to scare you,
it'd be easy.
Next time you meditate,
could you please keep
the covers on me?
It's hot in here.
Only it's not hot.
It's freezing.
I'm hot!
[Lilly moans softly]
Come on now.
You know you want it.
Now and how.
I'm so hot...
you could fry an egg
on the hood of my ride.
Feel that heat
coming from my chassis.
Oh, yeah. Just--
Let's just kinda--
Oh, my radiator's so hot.
My thermostat's about to pop.
[moans]
All right, Roxanne,
let's do this.
[both moaning]
Oh, now... now...
Oh, now. Now!
Now! Aah!
And how!
Oh! Oh, God.
[moans]
Oh, you came really fast.
Sure could use a release.
[thunder rumbling]
[baby crying]
Shh.
[baby continues crying]
[speaks foreign language]
[gasps]
Had the weirdest dream
last night.
[ominous music]
Oh, yeah?
What about?
Nothin'.
Welcome back,
my comrades in conspiracy.
Today,
significant spirit animals
and how it relates
to your life.
Now, personally,
I like to gravitate
towards more being...
[hisses]
Embody me with
all the light and darkness.
Invade my soul with
the gift of life everlasting.
I am your vessel.
Yeah, it's the spirit animal.
Many powerful women
in arts and literature.
[inhales sharply]
The only animal
that moves its wings
in a figure-eight pattern...
...and other magical gifts
include healing
and the manipulation of time.
What-- What do you mean
the manipulation of time?
Well, it has the innate ability
to pause and move forward
and even back in time.
And on the spiritual side,
the tiny wing blossom dancer
reminds us to cherish the day.
Remember to hover
in the moment,
my tortured tin-foil hatters.
I think we all could learn
to appreciate the day...
- Ugh.
- Stop and smell the roses.
[groans]
Let's all drink deeply
in the nectar of life.
Signing off.
[indistinct
computerized voices]
Hey, babe?
You hear that?
[computerized voices continue]
Hello?
[loud ringing]
Aah! What the fuck?
[groans]
Ray?
What's that?
Never mind.
Are you okay?
Maybe you should take a break.
Earth to Ray.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
What were you saying?
Maybe you
should take a break?
You don't look so good.
And if you don't get out
of this black hole,
we might never get out.
Right. Yeah.
That's probably a good idea.
Great, 'cause I have
to show you something cool.
But I'm gonna change first.
Cool like the statue?
[groans]
I'll be there in a minute.
[muttering]
I do not believe
what I just wrote.
What is that?
Tarot cards.
Not those. That.
A Ouija board.
Why? Why are you trying
to freak me out?
Let me read your cards,
Ray.
I'm good.
Please, Ray.
Fine.
How about you
read your own cards?
But can you read the meanings
for the camera?
[sighs]
They call this
a six-card lay.
[laughs]
You said "lay."
- Maybe later if you're good.
- 'Kay.
Maybe I'll get to finish
this time.
And now you know
how I feel.
The first card
is the inner child.
The Fool.
"The Fool represents
a free spirit of spontaneity."
The next three cards
represent consciousness.
Flip the next one.
The fifth card
is subconscious.
The Devil? That's what's
in your subconscious?
Read the meaning
in the book, Ray.
All right. It says the Devil
card represents bondage,
sexuality, and addiction.
Oh, my God.
That totally means that
I am thinking in character.
That's amazeballs.
Amazeballs?
Where'd you get that one?
Acting class?
Yeah, how'd you know?
All right. Flip over
the last one, Miss Roxanne.
I gotta get back to writing.
This card represents my future.
Holy shit.
The Empress.
What the hell
does that mean?
The Empress card. The Empress
card is the card of fertility.
Oh.
Oh shit.
Are we having a baby?
No, no.
No. Not with my career
skyrocketing the way that it is.
Babe, nuh-uh. We are not
having sex ever again.
You keep that in your pants.
It's staying over there.
All right, just calm down.
Hey, calm down.
We're not having a baby.
Oh, God.
I feel nauseous.
- It's okay.
- Oh, I really do.
- I feel nauseous.
- Look, we're not
having a baby.
That's a sign, isn't it?
- [breathing heavily]
- It's okay.
Look, I'll tell you what.
Hey.
Let's read my cards.
I'm sure they won't
even be close to the truth.
Come on.
This is a three-card lay.
The final card, slave,
is your future.
See? No, see, I told you
not to bring evil shit
in the house.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was just kidding.
Honey, it was a joke.
I stacked the deck.
Oh, great.
Real funny.
Now I'm not going to be able
to sleep tonight.
That's really funny.
It's not funny.
No, but, babe,
I was just kidding.
By the way, there'll be
no sex in this house.
Lilly.
You and or Miss Roxanne
need to chill.
All right.
Balls are gonna need
an ice pack.
Lilly.
There's someone out here.
Lilly. Lilly.
Lilly.
Lilly?
Are you hungry?
[animal growls]
Oh...
not the giblets, babe.
You don't-- You don't want...
[hisses]
Ugh.
Uh, babe...
[groans]
Oh, shit.
Did you make coffee?
No milk.
I don't feel well.
Morning sickness.
Oh, ha ha.
- Maybe if you didn't
keep me up all night.
- What do you mean?
- I said no sex.
- We didn't have sex.
Well, then who was between
my legs last night?
Grew up, Ray?
I-- I didn't do that.
Oh, of course you didn't,
because that would mean
you're having fun.
I am fun5.
I'm going to shower.
You've no sense of humor.
I'm fun. Try me.
Tell me I'm not fun.
You're not fun.
I'm a lot of fun.
[shower running]
We'll see if you find it
amusing when I scare the shit
out of you for once.
Boo!
Lilly?
Lilly, you okay?
[speaking foreign language
in demonic voice]
Lilly.
- [hisses]
- [shouts]
Aah!
What the hell?
[laughs]
Oh, I got-- I got you.
You know I hate clowns.
It's a clown
from outer space.
It's not funny.
Boo. Rah!
- I'm gonna go work.
- You're such a pussy.
Hold on a second.
You're telling us that the
lunar lander from Apollo 13
didn't burn up
in the atmosphere?
That's correct.
And the technology was used
to travel back in time?
Not back. Forward.
How did the lander reach Earth
without blowing up?
Well, the theory is
is that Aquarius was swept
into a time continuum,
a black hole
without the destruction,
and it was recovered by
a primitive civilization.
At that point,
they were guided by outsiders
to create a machine
that could transport
to another time and place.
Outsiders, Doc?
Oh, you mean like aliens?
Wow.
Now a word from our sponsors,
my tortured tinfoil hatters.
"Click a seer if you want
to be seen and have a session."
There we go.
Ah, nice to see you.
Come into my den.
We will talk.
- Must be a Jesus sale.
- Come.
I have a special
right now just for you.
Welcome to Mystic Mama.
- Look who it is.
- My friend,
I see dark and stormy nights
in your future.
You want
to change your luck?
Give me a call.
Mystic Mama at your services.
[laughs]
God, that chick's freaky.
This is the exact moment
I should not be here.
Shh.
We are here to travel
across the great divide.
Oh, brother.
We will travel through
the needle of time,
space and dimension.
It's inconceivable,
theoretically impossible.
Raymond,
you should join us.
It's Ray.
And I'm good over here.
The power of three
is a safer energy.
Yeah, see,
I'm the camera guy.
Ray.
Okay. All right, fine.
When I have bad dreams tonight
and can't write tomorrow,
somebody is getting
their ass kicked.
Are you drunk?
No. You're drunk.
You have bad dreams?
We have to sleep
with a nightlight on.
I have a vivid imagination.
It makes me a better writer.
Oh, does it?
Sometimes I dream
with my eyes ajar
and they
play mischief on me.
Night light helps.
There, I said it.
He dreams of horned people
watching him while he sleeps.
Why do they watch you?
Oh, can we keep this
about Lilly please?
Her acting job.
So we just put our fingers
on the oracle like this?
That is correct, Lilly.
Ray.
Close your eyes,
take a deep breath,
let go of the tension
of the day.
What about the tension
of the night?
Shut the fuck up.
Deep breathing.
Release control as we control
nothing in this universe
and we are but
an existential leaf
floating in the wind
of time.
Breathe in and out.
Ray,
why did you let go?
- Did you move it?
- No.
What about you, Yoga?
Raymond, it's normal
to feel awkward
in times of enlightenment.
Did you fucking
move it or not?
Ray, be nice.
I can assure you the oracle
glided without my influence.
Okay, I'm out.
- Ray!
- No, don't "Ray" me.
I didn't sign up
for incantations
or spiritual channeling,
whatever the hell that is.
If you let go now,
we may not be able
to control the portal.
So?
If we can't control the portal,
anything can pass through.
Evil can make its way.
No, Ray.
Okay, fine.
Can we just hurry up and
close the door or whatever.
Put your hands on the oracle.
We will close the portal.
Whoa, Lilly,
hands on the thing.
Aah!
[bones cracking]
[Southern accent]
You should have thought
of that before I caught you.
Who are you?
Who am I, witch?
What can we do for you?
Shut your mouth.
This is none of your business.
[laughs]
Time to pay the piper.
The what now?
[gasps]
Come here, boy, I'm gonna
split your skull in two.
[bones cracking]
[screams]
Jesus, Lilly.
Lilly!
Are you okay?
Oh...
What happened?
You okay?
I'm fine.
I think
you're overdoing it.
You're working too hard.
Just get some rest, okay?
Our baby needs sleep.
You're a jerk.
I got a bit
of writing to do.
My book needs nursing.
[sighs]
Besides, who can sleep now?
I love you.
"His long journey
into the wild
would have been
all for naught
if it wasn't for
his sole surviving wife
and unborn child
that carries on
in light of his stead."
"That carry...
carry on..."
[mutters]
"Carries on..."
"His wife..."
"Unborn child..."
[muttering]
[ominous music]
[computerized voices
speaking indistinct]
[animal growls]
[Lilly moans]
Lilly, wake up!
I think someone's
in the house.
She's not even there.
You can open your eyes.
No one's going to be there.
You're just gonna go to bed.
My love,
the moon and stars.
[demonic voice]
You will surrender your seed.
You will surrender
your seed.
[animal growls]
Camera man:
Damn, she's super hot.
Chaz:
Mm-hmm.
Hey, yo, by the way, that
hidden camera statue thing,
that shit's dope.
For real. Well done.
Where'd you get that shit?
Oh, my girl got it
from a flea market.
Hmm. Word.
It's, like, some weird, like,
indigenous shit, huh?
What'd I miss?
Where's my candy?
- Tony "C" says hi.
- Mm.
Did you tell him
what the camera can do?
Oh, yeah,
so it's motion activated.
It tilts. It pans.
Both:
It can even zoom.
Yo, whatever the fuck that is,
that need to stop right now.
Both:
Okay.
See if we can't find
our superstar.
[urinating]
[gasps]
Get out!
Can I have
some privacy please?
You told me
to record everything.
Get out!
Okay.
Lilly on computer:
So, guys, I'm off to the Con.
Don't forget to get your tees
and your selfies
with your favorite
Box Girl Lilly
at booth 323.
[exhales]
Okay. Here we go.
Yeah! Oh, my God.
Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Okay.
What are you doing?
What does it look like
I'm doing?
And you call me
the crazy one.
What?
You back to normal now?
What the hell
are you talking about?
Really?
Look, I've got
character work to do,
so kill your bugs.
Especially the ones
inside your head.
And please have the camera
ready to roll in ten minutes.
Mm-mm. I'm done.
What?
I can't do it anymore.
My followers are coming back,
Ray.
They're responding
to my content.
No.
All this social media stuff,
whatever,
it's making you crazy, okay?
And I'm not gonna be
a part of it anymore.
My director says that
this could be my big break.
Please.
Okay.
Dr. Ulrich:
They were guided by outsiders
to create a machine
that could transport
to another time and place.
Juice: I always wanted
to travel back in time.
But this future
doesn't look so bright.
Dr. Ulrich:
The cost of traveling from
one dimension to another
comes at a price.
Juice:
Like a blood sacrifice.
Well, glyphs indicate
that only their death
allows a rebirth.
Juice: You hear that,
paranormalists?
Rebirth.
[static]
[thunder rumbling]
[baby crying]
Aah!
I don't know
what the hell happened.
I was writing
and the juices were flowing,
and the next thing I remember,
I wake up on the floor.
Is this thing
really necessary?
It's to catch bad dreams.
It's for your protection.
Carrying the statue
to the bathroom with you now?
That's what we're doing?
It's my inspiration, Ray.
Well, speaking of inspiration,
I got some pages done.
- You wanna read 'em?
- Not now.
I see. So it's okay
for you to be creative,
but as soon as I wanna show you
some of my stuff, it's...
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's going on? Hey.
Hey.
What's up?
What's happening?
[sniffs]
I'm losing fans.
They're gonna
demonetize my site.
And I'm gonna be cut
from the cast.
No. Babe, no. Hey.
You're doing great.
You're amazing.
No. Baby.
Now, look, don't worry
about reading my stuff.
You can read it whenever.
I'm sure it's good.
Thanks.
I need you
to film everything, Ray.
I mean, no matter what.
I need you
to keep the camera rolling.
Okay-- Hey, I'll--
I'll film everything.
- Everything?
- Yeah. I promise.
Okay?
But you gotta
keep me out of it.
All right?
Just the camera guy.
Great, because, well,
Angela's coming tomorrow
for another session,
so make sure the camera's
fully charged.
Angela.
Fantastic.
May the darkest journeys
turn bright.
Cannot believe I let you
talk me into this again.
Oh, my God.
It tastes like fecal matter.
We would like to give thanks
for this special night.
We open our arms
to the mystics.
to the unknown.
We open our hearts
freely to contact you,
the all-present, everywhere
spirit of the night.
Spirit, who do you seek?
R... A... Y.
Okay.
Ray, it wants you.
Yeah, well, tell whoever it is
Ray's not home.
[hisses]
[groans]
[screaming, bones cracking]
[Southern accent]
Get inside my gut, Ray.
What is your name, spirit?
Silence.
Come here, boy.
Babe, I love you,
but you're really
freaking me out right now.
Maybe I can help.
What is it that you want
from Ray?
[cracks neck]
Okay. All right. Look, babe,
you're taking this method shit
way too far.
Shut your mouth, cunt.
You're the blackwater leech
that feeds off people
without a memory of doing so.
And he finished
his Earthly...
with an ungrateful
swig of content.
Ow! Lilly, what the hell?
Hell? Not exactly, boy.
That really hurt.
Could you please stop
slapping me?
[groans]
You like being slapped,
don't you, clown?
No, I don't like
being smacked.
Yeehaw! I think
the catfish likes it.
You like it,
bottom feeder?
[bones crack]
[screams]
[normal voice]
Ray-- Ray--
Who's that bitch trying
to get inside my God dang--
[bones crack]
Ray.
Ray. Ray...
[grunts]
Lilly. Lilly.
Angela, help!
[snarls]
[screams]
[laughing]
[roaring]
Ray.
Ray,
I want to eat your heart.
[laughs]
Lilly:
Ray...
Lilly?
Angela?
Just close your eyes.
Open them, and you're
gonna be back in bed.
[laughs]
Just close your eyes,
and when you open them,
you're gonna be back in bed.
[wood knocking, clattering]
You feel that?
Aah!
[knocking continues]
Oh, God.
Aah!
It's not there.
It's not there. It's not there.
It's not--
[cracking]
[animal growls]
[gasps]
Why you leaving it there?
Well, good morning.
How you feel?
'Cause I feel like shit.
Would have been nice to know
that we were gonna trip
on cosmic tea last night.
What, nothing?
You just get to drug me
with some strange woman
and I'm supposed to be
okay with this shit?
Something's been
going on here too,
and don't tell me
I'm dreaming.
I'm not dreaming.
Got these bites
all over my back.
Shit's itchy as hell.
You know, every time you start
to do this method acting shit,
you get all bipolar
and crazy on me.
I don't appreciate it.
There is a long list
predating the pyramids.
Dr. Ulrich:
And I'm not talking Egypt.
Juice: You're talking
south of the border.
You know, there's evidence
to suggest that--
that time and space travel
had been integrated
into the spirit world.
Juice: You hear that,
paranormalists?
Aliens and ghosts
travel in time.
[ominous music]
Hey, babe.
Need any organs lately?
Some wild stuff today.
Think you got this charac--
Oh, characters, down.
You're amazing.
You know that?
I know-- I know it's been
a crazy week, but...
I just wanna let you know
that I'm proud of you.
Well, goodnight,
whoever you are.
[ominous music]
[papers rustling]
[Ray sighs]
You're all a bunch of assholes.
You know that?
Mm. Yeah, Lilly bird.
[phone rings]
Hey, Lilly?
Think your director's calling.
[ringing continues]
Roxanne?
Babe, you want me
to draw you a bath?
Maybe it'll make you
feel better?
[speaking indistinct]
- Mm.
- No.
I'm just gonna put it over there
so it doesn't get wet.
- [hisses]
- Oh. Oh. Okay.
I'm just gonna put it
right there
so it doesn't get wet,
okay?
Come here.
There. See? It's fine.
It's fine.
It's okay. Here, let's get in.
Let's get you in.
Okay.
Let's get in.
[phone rings]
[beeps]
Yeah.
What up, Raymond?
[laughs]
How's it hangin', brah?
You're watching, aren't you?
She won't talk.
Just want to say aces
with the camera work, son.
Look, tell me something.
Have you noticed anything...
odd with Lilly?
What you talking about,
Willis?
Like, she won't go anywhere
without that damn statue.
Yo, you being kind of
aggressive and shit, Ray.
Okay. Yeah--
Have you seen any footage
that's out of the ordinary?
A phantasm.
A demon.
[laughs]
Demon?
Why would you say that?
[water dripping]
Okay. Something that's...
possessing her.
[bones cracking]
I ain't seen nothin'
beyond paranormal, brah.
Yo, Lilly bird is okay.
It's you who we worried about.
[man speaks
on Walkie Talkie indistinct]
Yeah, I'll be there
in a minute, a'ight?
Mm.
Yo, Ray, Iotta be honest
with you, brah.
We in preproduction hell
right now.
Like, agents be callin' me
and shit,
wanting their clients
to be paid more.
We ain't got the money.
You know what I'm saying?
The shit's Hollywood.
You feel me?
Ray, I ain't even seen
the footage myself.
[Ray moans]
You haven't watched any--
Great.
Babe,
how do I shut it off?
Could you please just let me
know if you see something?
I'm really--
I'm really worried about her.
I gotta fly, Ray. Peace.
[computer beeps]
You're a dickhead, bro.
Y-O-U apostrophe R-E
a dickhead.
[gasps]
You would not believe what
a douchebag your director is.
Lilly.
[sighs]
"In order to travel,
they would sacrifice
a being of one world to take
the host of another world."
"The Sun and Moon Goddess
is a traveler of space and time.
She prays upon
the weak and desperate.
She occupies vessels
with her enslaved warrior.
They impregnate their way
into the lives of their victims
through pleasure and pain."
"It's their only way
to survive,
travel of time and space."
"The warrior takes a direct
approach to his female victims."
"The Serpent Goddess first
inseminates her praised soul
with her life force."
"She then
devours their hearts...
for a strong offspring.
After consummation,
she sometimes removes
the host's skull
as a souvenir."
Jesus. Why?
Why are you reading this?
What are you doing?
[crickets chirping]
[breathing heavily]
Did you see that?
Oh...
Okay.
Oh, I like that.
Don't stop.
Lilly:
Oh, hey.
[moans]
- [speaks foreign language]
- [moaning]
Lilly: Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Harder.
[moaning loudly]
Oh, yeah.
No, wait. Don't stop.
Oh, don't stop.
Where are you going?
Oh, come back.
- [laughs]
- Oh, yeah.
- Wait. No, wait.
- [animal growls]
That doesn't feel good.
No, that doesn't feel good.
- [laughter continues]
- Stop!
[gagging]
Hey, Lilly, Lilly, Lilly.
Are you okay?
- [laughter continues]
- [Lilly speaking
foreign language]
Ray: Lilly!
Lilly, Lilly! Lilly...
Wake up!
Lilly, wake up! Wake up!
Wake up. Wake up. Wake up.
Look, it's me.
- It's me. It's just Ray.
- Don't touch me!
It's just Ray.
It's just Ray. It's okay.
Hey, wake up.
Wake up. Come on.
Tell him to stop, Ray.
Tell him to stop.
It's okay.
No, it's over. It's okay.
It's okay. It's all right.
It's just a dream.
You were just dreaming.
It's okay.
Ray, it's not okay.
[gasps]
They're after me.
What's after you?
They're after us.
Who?
[whimpers]
Baby, it's okay. Hey.
What?
Damn it!
[screams]
[laughs]
- Lilly: Damn it!
- Maybe you're going too far.
Bitch, great things happen
when you hit rock bottom.
You Kubricked
the shit out of her.
Ugh!
You're not worried?
A desperate artist
is a hungry artist.
A hungry artist
works harder, yo.
- Word.
- [laughs]
That girl's a fuckin' earner.
You gonna be famous, Chaz.
[laughs]
[Ray groans softly]
Lilly?
Lilly, will you please
come look at this please?
Look, babe, I thought
it was bug bites--
Ugh.
[doorbell rings]
- Hmm.
- You want some?
Angela:
I'm fine.
All right, suit yourself.
On the phone, you said
he has not been herself.
Yeah. I don't-- yeah, ever--
ever since she's been meditating
with that stupid statue.
This statue
is the God of Fertility.
Fertility. No, no,
the internet said it was
the God of, uh, Space Travel.
But not in the sense
that you think.
It is the exploration
of traveling one's being
into another
between time and space.
Angela:
As if you were being born
into another.
Then the traveler impregnates
their soul's energy
into the vessel.
- The vessel.
- The person.
B-But what happens
to the person then?
- Their life force is expunged.
- Expunged?
However, it takes a while
before complete reproduction.
What do you mean, takes--
So how long?
It depends on the will
and the openness of the host.
There's gotta be a way--
Like, is there a way to stop it?
At any moment,
the surrogate's totality
can reverse
the transposition or possession.
Okay. Come again?
It can be stopped
at any time.
Okay, then, yeah, stop it.
I cannot.
Well, why the fuck not?
It's up to the person
closest to her.
So I-- Okay, great.
So what can I do
to stop it?
Do normal things.
Alter her path
back to commonality.
Then once the person
refutes the foreign entity,
it can go back
to a normal life.
Okay.
However,
most are mentally too forgone
to make the distinction
unless it's from
an outside force.
Outside force?
You, my friend.
Right.
Made your favorite.
You know I'm not very good
in the kitchen,
but I followed your recipe,
so hope it's okay.
Did you try the... wine?
Well...
Come on, babe.
Your fans are watching.
You gotta eat something.
You know, you're always
trying to get in my pants.
Well, now's your chance.
Who's in there?
Is it Miss Roxanne?
Huh?
Ow. Ow.
Hope you guys
enjoyed that one.
I got so carried away
the other night.
It was all for theater.
And the fans.
[whispers] And the fans.
No doubt.
How's social media treating you?
Like the mob that kills if they
don't get what they want.
That seance was the bomb.
I'm getting killer fans.
Well, at least one of us
will get the bonus.
And that chair and table trick
worked perfectly.
I know!
All we have to do is stick
these furniture pads on.
Aah!
Amazeballs.
[cracking]
Ooh, that's gross.
Sound is a powerful tool.
To fool.
[laughs]
- How much time do we have?
- Two hours.
Ooh.
So during the seance I want you
to scare the hell out of him.
Yes.
You're gonna grab one
of these fizzy tablets,
bend over,
pop it in your mouth,
let the fizz do the work.
Oh, that was so fun.
I know.
I think we went a little far
with the psychedelic tea.
Eh, whatever.
Ray will get over it.
He's a little paranoid.
This shit's gotta stop.
You need to get
the heck out of here
and leave Lilly alone.
Understand each other?
Good.
[distant thud]
[camera beeps]
[static on computer]
Oh, girl, those
stacked cups and plates?
That was an accident
waiting to happen.
Uh, what stacked cups
and plates?
Oh, shit.
Here he comes.
Hello?
[ominous music]
Hey, were you
talking to someone?
I thought I heard voices.
Hearing drums, too.
Here, you should drink
some water.
Damn it.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Hold on.
I swore I heard somebody.
I'm not going crazy.
Maybe I am going crazy.
[Lilly crying]
Oh, babe. Oh.
Hey, don't cry.
Hey.
You're gonna be great.
And you're gonna get
so many fans from this.
And, you know, your director's
really lucky to have you.
- [laughs, cries]
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- You just--
You just get some sleep.
I think... we all just need
to get some sleep.
I'm losing my mind.
[exhales]
[shoes thud on floor]
[electricity crackling]
[bones cracking]
Aah!
[laughs]
[animal growls]
[breathing heavily]
[heart beating]
[animal growls]
[laughs]
Okay, Ray, I'm off to set.
Despite my fanbase,
they still want me.
So, well, I must have
done something right.
[groans]
Ew, that doesn't feel right.
I better not get my period.
Ray. Honey.
Ray. Don't pout.
I love you.
- [doorbell rings]
- Lilly: Coming.
That's my co-star
and my driver.
I will call you
when I get to my trailer.
[groans]
You know, maybe you should
go outside, get some sun.
Bye, babe.
- Hi.
- Hey, Angie.
- Are you ready for this?
- Oh, honey.
Lilly: Ugh.
Thanks for everything.
Angela:
Of course.
Lilly:
Girl, I don't feel good.
Like, I don't-- I haven't
gotten my period yet.
I don't know what it is.
But it's all right.
Oh, hey.
I'm so excited.
Angela: [Southern accent]
Why, hello, Sheriff.
What can we do for you?
Lilly: [Southern accent]
Yes, what can we do
for you, Sheriff?
Sheriff:
[clears throat]
Sorry for showing up
unannounced and all,
but there's been
some complaints in town
about strange happenings
at your place at night.
Angela:
What kinda strange things?
Lilly: Would you care
for some tea?
Sheriff:
Something about an out of towner
staying with you ladies.
Uh, heard a little thing.
Angela:
I see.
Talks of witchcraft
and blood sacrifices.
Lilly:
Witchcraft?
Angela:
Blood sacrifices?
[coughs]
Whoa.
That's got some kick.
[laughs]
Best tea in all of Texas.
He is so sweet to Nina.
[gurgles]
[laughs]
You like that?
Yeah.
Yeah, it looked good.
[laughs]
I'm a master.
Angela: ...An ungrateful swig
of content.
Hey, yo, add Lilly's likes
back to her page.
Tell her there was
some sort of, like,
computer glitch or some shit
that we fixed, you know?
- Yo.
- [sniffs]
Done.
Oh, are you okay?
Can I get you something?
Yo, boss.
I need some water.
She preggy, yo.
Lilly, baby.
- [ominous music]
- [Chaz gagging]
Chaz, you all right?
- [Lilly screams]
- [Chaz groans]
[groans]
- Shit.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Oh!
Oh, my God, I think--
I think
I'm having a baby.
- Please--
- Are you okay?
Get it out! I want it out.
Please help me.
[Lilly groans]
[screams]
How can I help you?
- [bones crack]
- [screams]
[gags]
[growls]
[laughs]
[speaks foreign language]
Aah!
[screams]
[baby snarling]
No! No! No!
[screaming]
No!
Dr. Ulrich: Time and space
can be manipulated...
fused together
and then displaced
to create a window into
an entirely new reality.
Juice:
You think we are not alone.
We've been visited
by many alien life forms.
And now that Texas tea
turns to blood.
Cuzut.
That shit was fire.
Fuck yeah.
Hey, yo, little
Pippi Longstockings,
you a movie star!
[laughs]
Angela:
What about me?
You, Daisy Dukes?
You're a'ight too.
All right, listen.
So, you two, I want you
to come in my double-wide.
You been
in my double-wide yet?
- Not yet.
- A'ight.
I'ma show y'all around.
And, you, uh, you can get
the fuck out of here,
'cause you fired.
I don't know
what the fuck you doin'.
She's my ride.
Shut the fuck up.
Hey, you get that shit
on camera?
Guess what?
You fired too.
And, you, IT guy.
[sniffs]
- Give me some more cocaine.
- Right on.
A'ight.
♪ You wanna get down
♪ Down tonight