Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
-BRUNELLE: Stop the music!
-
What was that?
Glissade assemblé, sissonne...
You are a dancer...
-not a horse.
-I’m sorry.
I don’t speak French.
I took Spanish
’cause my dad said
it would be more useful,
but honestly,
French would be really useful...
-Why are you here?
-Um...
I’ve placed first
in every competition
in the States
for the past two years.
A-All my teachers
recommended that I...
Mademoiselle Sanders,
as a scholarship recipient,
I expect a real answer.
I’ll ask you one more time.
Why have you come here?
I’m here to win the prize.
CELINE:
Marine!
I told you, you’re not allowed
to touch anything in this room.
You said you wanted to win
the prize for Ollie.
I do.
Then what are you still
doing here?
VALENTINE: Training will be
rigorous and begins before dawn.
The lowest-ranked rats
may be sent home
at the discretion
of Madame Brunelle.
Five girls and five boys
will be dancing
in the final presentation.
And from this,
only one girl and one boy
will be awarded the prize:
a contract to join the company
of the Paris Opera Ballet.
CLAIRE:
Who is she?
LUC: Apparently she only started
dancing five years ago.
Before that she
played basketball.
-Basketball?
-Oui.
CLAIRE: She’s too awkward
to be a ballerina.
LUC:
Oh, fuck.
What are you doing back?
Had nothing better to do.
What’s new?
After you left last fall,
Gia took number one.
She’s the favorite.
You’re back?
Nice to see you, too.
You broke out
of the mental hospital?
You flatter me.
Felipe... you’re up, baby.
How do my leftovers taste?
Like victory.
Hetero dancers are such sluts.
Cover my tattoos so the devil
doesn’t shit her Spanx.
CLAIRE:
Felipe’s so good.
LUC:
He’s the best.
If Ollie were here,
he’d be better.
No one is better than Felipe.
Ollie was always number one.
Who’s Ollie?
Who are you?
I’m Kate.
Hi.
I’m the one from Virginia.
GIA:
She’s here to take your place.
Oh, Ollie.
Yes, he was the dancer who...
He jumped off a bridge, right?
What’d you say?
M, stop...
-Uh...
-What the fuck did you say?
-I...
-He didn’t jump.
Sorry. I read a post that
he jumped off a bridge.
-
-DANCER: Oh, my God.
-DANCER 2: Stop!
MARINE
Putain, putain.
-
I’m gonna kill you!
I’m gonna fucking kill you!
FRANCIS:
Absolute perfection, Felipe.
Thank you.
He was the last rat?
-
So you decided
to join us after all.
Your parents made quite the case
for your return.
I’m not doing it for them.
I’m doing it for Ollie.
I’m Luc.
I’m Claire.
I don’t get it.
What did I do?
Ollie-- he was her brother.
He was her twin.
The other half of her soul.
Oh.
Just because
you were number one once
does not mean you will be again.
I will be number one.
You are dismissed, rat.
Two Americans?
One too many.
We won’t have two for long.
VALENTINE: Your appearance today
was unacceptable.
You’re extra-large, right?
Let me see if I can find
something that big.
That will be a hundred euros.
-Well, I’m on scholarship.
-Yes.
You have a scholarship
to attend as a foreign student.
It does not include
the expenses.
They didn’t tell me that.
Look.
You can jump very high
and move very strong.
This might make you
a sensation in America...
...but this is Paris.
Romance traditionnelle.
They want ballerinas
to be light and graceful.
They want girls to be girls
and boys to be boys,
and if you don’t fit
into that mold...
...they’ll simply
find somebody who does.
Trust me, I know.
You’re 18, yes?
Sign your consent here.
And your mobile phone please.
KATE:
It’s going well.
Everyone’s super French.
SCOTT
Yeah.
You making any friends?
Uh... yeah.
Yeah.
People are... nice.
SCOTT:
Well, good. Good.
Billy Elliot says bonjour.
Bonjour, Billy.
The house feels empty
without you.
Well...
Hey, at least now you get to,
you know, get some sleep.
Not paying for my classes
and all that working so late.
Ah, I always sleep well.
Know why?
I go to bed with
a clean conscience.
You got that?
Got it.
SCOTT:
Where do stars come from?
KATE:
Rebel’s heart. Will of steel.
SCOTT:
Eyes set on true north.
I love you, Little Bird.
I love you, too, Dad.
What are you doing here?
MARINE:
I’m in my room.
No one said anything to me
about a roommate.
Well, this has been my room
since I was eight.
-Look.
-Oh.
Well, what are
we supposed to do?
There’s only one bed.
I know we got off
to kind of a rough start.
I honestly had no idea, and I’m
really sorry about your brother.
Okay? I really... didn’t...
Are you really gonna
smoke in here?
Yes.
Okay.
Isn’t that against the rules?
Yes.
Do you always follow the rules?
No.
Prove it.
20 euro.
BOUNCER:
Twenty.
Uh, no, thank you.
No one enters without the worm.
MARINE:
Want to play a game?
LUC
Is she okay?
CLAIRE: Are you sure
this is a good idea?
MARINE:
She’s a big girl.
What kind of game?
Whoever stops dancing first
drops out.
-Of school?
-Yes.
Of school.
Oh.
You in or not?
I’m in.
Good.
-
My heart is on fire.
I think I might die.
You give up?
Never.
You?
Fuck no.
So what do we do?
We keep dancing.
-Fine.
We could both stop
at the exact same moment.
Nice try.
What?
You’ll just tell me to stop
and then you’d let me stop.
I would never do that.
Why should I trust you?
I’m gonna count to three.
And we’re gonna both stop
exactly... at three.
Not before.
Not after.
One.
Two.
Three.
What about tomorrow?
What about it?
Are we friends?
Tomorrow is tomorrow.
-
-Hey.
Why didn’t you wake me?
Set an alarm.
What’s that?
It’s for luck. A charm.
LUC:
Claire never dances without it.
BRUNELLE:
The pas de deux...
...is chemistry made flesh.
The heart of ballet.
Dance is a ritual
of seduction, no?
Up, everybody.
Felipe...
...today you will pair with...
...Claire.
But, madame, I’ve been
his partner for three months.
He wouldn’t be able to lift you
with all the weight you gained
over Christmas.
Marine, Luc.
And Virginia
with... Jean Paul.
Try to relax.
I’m fine.
I’m a drug dealer.
If you need drugs,
I’ll deal them to you.
-Sorry.
-BRUNELLE: Heavy, Virginia.
Light. Be light.
And down.
You look like a sack
of potatoes.
Madame Brunelle
is just testing you.
That’s why we call her
Le Diable.
She plays us off each other.
Anyone who partners with Felipe
will be the better dancer.
He’s the key to the prize.
She’ll assign final partners
based on chemistry.
In the meantime,
she’s torturing me, too.
Le diable obtient
ce qui lui est dû.
What does that mean?
The Devil gets her due.
BRUNELLE:
You’re currently ranking last.
I think it’s better
to send you home now.
KATE:
No. I know I can do better.
BRUNELLE: Let me tell you
something, Virginia.
Kate.
My name is Kate.
And I can’t go back.
I’ve given up everything
to be here.
Now we’re getting somewhere.
Let me tell you something, Kate.
This rat was caught in one of
our traps in the basement.
I never use wire traps.
Do you know why?
Tonight I plan to take it home
and feed it to my cat.
She prefers her meat fresh.
You just press this button here,
and it releases a gas
that gently...
puts the rat to death.
Painless.
Clean.
I’m not a monster.
If we don’t get rid of the rats,
then the school will be overrun
and it will be worthless.
Greatness has a price.
Do you agree?
Yes.
Good.
Then do the honors.
You want me... to push the...
Please. Push the button.
Show me that you have
what it takes to win the prize.
The devil pulled the rat trick
on Kate.
Really?
CLAIRE: The button
is so obviously fake.
I believed it.
She brought Ollie and I into
her office when we were nine
and did the same thing.
Which one of you
pushed the button?
Oh, neither of us.
Don’t tell me you pushed it.
Of course not.
76 euro?
Such a rip off.
They know we have to buy new
shoes each week. It’s extortion.
I bet the devil gets kickbacks
from this fucking store.
Ballet Mafia.
Aren’t you getting any?
Uh, no. My shoes are fine.
CLAIRE:
M...
-MARINE: Come over here.
-
Are you okay?
It’s not easy competing with
a bunch of skinny white girls.
For me, every little mistake
gets noticed.
I have to dance miracles
just to be the exception.
I do what it takes.
Good luck with your shoes.
Oh.
-Oh.
-Sorry.
Um, I was wondering, um,
if maybe...
you could dance with me
sometime.
I know I’m, like, really tall,
but you’re tall
and appear strong and--
I don’t know.
Um, maybe you could help me
with some stuff.
Like partnering and stuff.
Okay. Come in.
Like right now?
Okay, lay down.
Do you want my help?
Keep your hips even.
Floating.
To be a star
you have to be soft.
Your form is very strict.
Very controlled.
Okay, so get up
and à la seconde.
Arabesque and face the door.
Ballet is precision
and perfection.
But so what?
Nobody pays to see perfection.
They pay to see romance.
Desire, dominance.
Bodies touching bodies.
What makes a perfect
prima ballerina
is total submission.
Allow yourself to be possessed.
Okay, fall back.
No thinking. Breathe.
You’re beautiful.
Is something wrong?
Don’t tell M.
Where are you going?
MARINE:
Embassy party.
That’s cool.
MARINE:
I’d skip it, but I have to go.
I’m the ambassador’s daughter.
KATE:
Which ambassador?
The American ambassador.
Your dad is the
American ambassador to France?
My mom is
the American ambassador.
How come you never told me this?
It never came up.
What does your dad do?
Businessman.
We should talk about
gender expectations.
What type of businessman?
Mostly milks.
Why is that funny?
Milks?
Macadamia, soy, coconut,
almond, cashews.
Squeezable nuts.
Your mom is
the American ambassador
and your dad is
a nut milk tycoon.
So?
My dad pours concrete
in Wakefield.
MARINE:
What about your mom?
KATE:
It’s just me and my dad.
It’s nothing.
That one’s nice.
Will you help me
with the buttons?
Sure.
What does this mean?
"Never mind."
Okay.
No, it-it means...
"never mind."
Oh.
Ça ne fait rien.
I like it.
You never answered my question
about your mom.
She was a dancer, actually.
Yeah.
She died when I was little.
MARINE:
She’s beautiful.
KATE:
Yeah.
My dad refuses
to talk about her.
I think it hurts too much.
But when I quit basketball
and started dancing...
...I could tell it meant a lot.
It’s stupid, but, um...
...when I dance...
it feels like...
I can feel her.
You know? Like she’s with me.
"How are your classes?"
Oh, they’re-they’re good.
"Any new friends?"
Well, my roommate--
she’s American.
-She’s fun.
-E-Enough.
Katherine Sanders.
You know her?
She’s the recipient of
the scholarship we established
in your brother’s honor.
How come you-you didn’t tell me?
I hear she may be
sent home soon.
Can’t you just talk
to the school?
Isn’t she supposed to be
your competition?
If we’d known they were
gonna give the money
to a female dancer, we would
never have sent the check.
She’s my friend.
Boundaries, Marine.
-
Marine, can I see you please?
Your daughter is
quite... fascinating.
Spirited.
You’ll excuse me, I’m sure.
What is this?
Oh, this, uh...
this charade
you invited me to perform
where we pretend to be
a happy family.
You listen to me very carefully.
Tonight is not an obligation
which is subject to your moods.
WOMAN:
Look at you, Marine.
Ambassador Durand,
your daughter has grown.
Just about.
Oh, Marine is
quite the dancer now.
She’s on track to join
the Paris Opera Ballet.
-If all goes well.
-Wow.
Well, we’d love
to see you dance sometime.
I’m sure she’d be happy to.
N’est-ce pas, Marine?
Sure.
For your bloody feet.
I’d offer to wash them for you,
but I think that might sound
a little creepy.
A little?
S-Sorry. That was so dumb.
-I’ll leave you alone.
-No, no, I, uh...
I just don’t let boys
look at or touch my feet.
It’s a dancer thing.
And I strongly prefer
women in socks.
It’s a drummer thing.
My name’s Jamal.
M.
Just M?
Short for Marine,
but I never liked that.
My brother used to call me
Marionette.
Like the puppet.
And so... should I call you
Marionette?
Close your eyes.
JAMAL:
Do they hurt?
MARINE: Let me tell you a
little secret about ballerinas.
We are warriors of pain.
Oh, shit.
Why do you do it?
Because if I stop, then, um...
someone I love will be gone.
Your brother?
It was always supposed to be
the two of us.
My mom put us in ballet class
as soon as we could walk.
It’s who I am.
You must think
I’m really fucked-up.
I think you’re sad.
And funny.
And a very good dancer.
Are you with an embassy?
No, I...
I’m with the band.
Well, that’s good because, uh...
um...
then we won’t
see each other again,
and we can just pretend this...
never happened.
The problem is
I want to see you again.
That’s a bad idea.
I have poor judgment.
I don’t have any time.
Then we better move fast.
SCOTT
Scott Sanders.
-You know what to do.
-
KATE:
Hey, Dad.
Sorry I keep missing your calls.
Um, everything’s good here.
Things are going really well.
Yeah.
-I love you.
-
Hey.
How was it?
I acted out,
as my therapist would say.
Mm.
What’s wrong?
I just keep thinking about
this story
my dad used to tell me
when I was a kid.
I was afraid of the dark.
Will you tell it to me?
You really want to hear it?
Okay.
The animals were behaving badly.
So the gods decided
to cover the entire Earth
with a blanket,
blocking out the sun.
It was so dark.
So dark.
The animals were afraid.
But the gods did not answer
their prayers.
But then...
this one brave little bird
flew up to the sky.
Faster and faster.
Her heart was beating so fast
she thought it might burst.
But she just kept going.
Rebel’s heart.
Will of steel.
Eyes set on true north.
Until finally...
...she pierced the blanket
with her beak,
and a tiny ray of light
shone through.
The little bird flew back up
again and again,
poking holes in the blanket,
defying the will of the gods.
But the gods were not mad.
The gods were so moved
by her courage
they decided they were
only going to cover the Earth
for half of the day.
And so, this blanket,
full of these tiny holes
became the night sky.
And that’s how
the stars were formed.
I don’t want to win if...
if it means you lose.
I’ll help you.
And we’ll both dance so well...
...they won’t have a choice.
And they’ll have to
make an exception.
And we’ll both get the prize.
I like that.
Give me your earring.
-Is this real?
-Mm-hmm.
-I can’t take this.
-I don’t care. Come on.
Let’s make a pact.
Repeat after me.
-This is our sacred oath.
To always be there
for each other.
To always be
there for each other.
To help each other out
every step of the way.
To help each other
out every step of the way.
And to win the prize together...
or not at all.
you’ve got to say to me
-
to hear the truth
at all, you see...
Thank you.
You’re a bigfoot, Virginia.
What were you and Gia
talking about?
Oh, nothing.
She’s still pissed at me
because Felipe dumped her.
KATE:
Mm-hmm.
She needs to get over it.
CLAIRE: M, telephone.
Some guy named Jamal.
-KATE: The drummer?
-MARINE: Mm-hmm.
CLAIRE:
I see the way you look at her.
You should be careful.
She’ll make you think
that you’re her new twin.
But when it comes
to competition,
you get the knife in the back.
for you
Still so boyish.
yesterday
from the start
that I could claim the same
you held my heart...
What is this?
Modifying the choreography.
Who does she think she is?
-Stop.
I’m sorry.
I wanted to show you
my own ideas.
I can see that.
Had you not, you would have been
ranked number one today.
So please.
What happened?
Just until your rank goes up.
I meant what I said.
Both of us or none at all.
Claire, à toi.
What’s wrong?
My ribbon-- I can’t find it.
Her ribbon.
Don’t panic. We’ll help find it.
Are you sure
you checked in your bag?
Of course I looked there!
Well, check again.
Claire,
we won’t wait any longer.
Look at me.
You are a great dancer,
with or without your ribbon.
Go.
I know it was you.
What did she say?
Nothing.
Why have you not come
to see me, Marionette?
-Don’t call me that.
-Why not?
You know why.
-
MARINE:
Dead rats.
It’s a fight for survival now.
JEAN PAUL:
Hello, American girl.
I knew you would come to see me.
Pink’s for up
and blue’s for down.
I don’t need drugs to dance.
Well, you are the exception.
Everyone else does.
You can ask your friend M.
She hasn’t come to see me
since she’s back.
That’s why her rank
is not as good as before.
Hey, there’s no testing
in ballet.
No one will ask you
to pee in a cup.
I thee endow
God’s holy ordinance
your consent
with blessings
until death do us part
Good, Ms. Sanders.
Go for it.
Good. That’s almost it.
There you go, lighter. Good.
with blessings
-
until death do us part
VALENTINE:
Marine, wake up.
Where’s your head?
until death do us part
for better, for worse
JAMAL:
What are you thinking?
That I should go.
Says who?
You make me happy.
It’s dangerous.
You’re right.
I am very dangerous.
What are you doing?
What are you...
Ah, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
I’m not gonna look.
I won’t look, I promise.
I just want to...
You can look.
These feet belong to a dancer,
not a marionette.
There’s more to you
than just ballet.
I’ve seen it.
You’re an artist, not a puppet.
Shoulders down.
Look at you. That’s good.
Come closer.
KATE:
I’m finally up to number two.
And Madame Brunelle,
the one who doesn’t like me,
well, she finally paired me with
the best dancer in the school.
She saw we have chemistry
and, well,
we’re basically unstoppable.
SCOTT: You do your best.
You do the right thing.
That’s all I care about.
Katie, I’ve got to
tell you something.
What?
I moved into an apartment
closer to town.
What about the house?
I sold it.
You sold our house?
-Without telling me?
-
I didn’t want to upset you.
We both got a lot
to worry about, Kate.
The house, the dog--
it’s a lot for me, okay?
Well, I guess
I better win, right?
It’s not like there’s any home
to come back to.
-KATE: Hey.
-Hey.
Do you have something
you want to tell me?
Mm, what do you mean?
Why do you have Claire’s ribbon?
I saw it on the ground, and I...
...I just...
picked it up.
I was going to give it
back to her.
She just got so upset; I didn’t
want her to think I stole it.
You should have
said something to me.
I know.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean
for her to get hurt.
It’s the worst thing
I’ve ever done.
Are you gonna turn me in?
I’m sorry
I went through your bag.
It’s fine.
I thought you were taking pills.
You seem on edge lately.
And I know what that’s like.
I had a dream about
the story you told me.
About the little bird.
She fell from the sky.
Her body was broken.
She was in so much pain.
But then another bird appeared.
She helped her fly again.
That’s going to be you one day.
Giselle, my love!
-Don’t go.
-I must leave you.
My heart will ache
for all of eternity!
GIA:
Shut the fuck up!
-People are trying to sleep!
Sorry!
Good night, Gia. Sleep well.
Sleep well, Gia.
GIA:
Fuck off!
-I have an idea.
-What?
-You have a phone?
-I gave them a burner.
-Come here.
-Ah, genius.
KATE:
What? What are you doing?
Wait, is that Benjamin Benjamin?
Like, Benjamin,
star of the ballet
-that we just saw, Benjamin?
-Mm-hmm.
Holy fuck.
Oh, my God, he’s typing.
MARINE:
Come on.
Oh, we see you.
We know you’re there.
-
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. -Be cool.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
BENJAMIN
Hi there. Do I know you?
You look familiar.
You need a hint?
You’re the Durand daughter.
"The Durand daughter."
This is my friend Kate.
She dances at the academy
with me.
Hi. Uh, Kate.
You were amazing.
I can’t believe
I’m talking to you.
Benjamin, are you
going to be the judge
-for the prize again this year?
-Yes, I am.
Have two girls ever won before?
Nope. Tradition.
And traditions are
meant to be broken.
You never know.
-Good night, girls.
-Good night.
Bonne nuit.
-
How do you have
his phone number?
-
CELINE:
He’ll be here in a moment.
Have they assigned
final partners?
KATE:
Not yet.
We think they’ll announce it
in the next couple of weeks
once they’ve narrowed it down
to the top five.
Will Marine make the cut?
I hear she’s right on the edge.
Of course she will.
When Marine danced with Ollie,
they were always number one.
Ollie would’ve been
the next Nureyev.
-He was that good.
-He wasn’t the next Nureyev.
How would you know?
You’re not even on track
to be the next member
of the corps de ballet.
I don’t feel well.
KATE: I wanted to say thank you
for the scholarship.
I know it’s supposed
to be anonymous,
so I wasn’t
going to say anything.
Um...
but M told me.
It means everything.
I just wanted to say
it means even more to me
to know that
it’s in Ollie’s name.
I know how close he and M were.
Yes.
But now she has you.
This is our sacred oath.
To always be there
for each other.
To help each other
every step of the way.
To win the prize together
or not at all.
She hates me.
No.
I don’t blame her.
It was my fault.
-It wasn’t your fault.
-You don’t know that.
Ollie and I-- we were like...
the same person.
My mom...
What?
Hey.
You can tell me anything.
Anything.
I promise.
We were home on summer holiday.
Ollie and I.
We were just rehearsing
in the living room.
We’d moved all the furniture
to the side
like we used to do
when we were little.
And she, um...
She walked in.
We didn’t know she was home.
And she screamed.
So loud.
And she pulled us apart...
and she slapped me.
And then she told my dad
what she saw--
what she thought she saw.
He didn’t believe her.
She wouldn’t listen to anyone.
We were just dancing, but...
...my mom couldn’t look at
either of us after that.
Ollie...
...he...
...he-- we’d...
we had taken pills to dance.
But after that, he just...
he started taking everything.
Whatever he could find.
And the night it happened...
...he called me.
And I d...
I d... I didn’t answer.
I didn’t answer.
OLLIE
What happened to our promise?
Never mind, right?
Okay. Never mind.
Ça ne fait rien.
What happened to our promise?
Never mind, right?
Okay. Never mind.
Ça ne fait rien.
KATE: I have something
to tell you, too.
MARINE
I already know.
You do?
MARINE:
Felipe told me.
Thought it would
make me jealous.
Were you?
MARINE:
At first.
And then I realized
it wasn’t because
you were with Felipe, but...
...because Felipe was with you.
KATE:
He thinks he has all the power.
That we’re all in love with him.
KATE: I just want to know
what it feels like.
MARINE:
What?
KATE:
To be you.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I don’t know.
You just stopped
answering my calls.
And now I kind of
feel like a stalker.
Maybe you are one.
So that’s it?
I went by your house.
I didn’t know
how else to contact you.
I talked to your mom.
Do you know what she said?
She said
your idea of love was sick,
that you were disturbed
and that I should stay away.
She’s right.
Good luck with your prize.
-KATE: Dad, guess what.
-SCOTT: What?
KATE:
I made the top five.
SCOTT:
Of course you did.
Aw, that’s wonderful, Katie.
BRUNELLE: Felipe,
today you will pair with...
KATE: I mean, honestly,
the way that things are going,
I think they’re gonna
make Felipe my partner
for the prize dance.
KATE:
Bonjour.
I need new shoes.
I’m done helping you.
There are only five of us left.
You’re on your own now.
My shoes.
Shoes.
Your shoes. I know.
There’s only one prize.
I was nice.
FRANCIS:
Félicitation.
You have made it
to the top five.
The partner you are
paired with today has been
carefully assigned
by Madame Brunelle
to be your final partner
for the prize dance.
Together you will choose an
excerpt from Romeo and Juliet.
What’s wrong?
This is such bullshit.
It’s like they want me to lose.
We’re gonna figure it out.
We’re not gonna let anything
or anyone come between us.
We’re not gonna give up
on the pact.
KATE:
I know.
It’s just...
you wouldn’t understand.
This is my one chance.
Okay.
-
BRUNELLE: The prize dance
is on the horizon,
and nothing should
distract you from that.
However, it’s come
to my attention
that there is a good opportunity
for the right ballerina.
We are looking for an understudy
for Sarah.
It is a more
contemporary project.
It would be...
an honor to work...
with you two.
Good luck.
BRUNELLE:
Don’t be nervous.
Just show us what you can do.
BRUNELLE:
Virginia,
let’s not waste any more
of Sarah and Benjamin’s time.
Shall we?
MARINE:
I’m happy they picked you.
KATE:
You don’t seem happy.
MARINE:
I am.
You deserve it.
Thanks.
I mean, it’s not the prize, but
it’s still pretty cool, I guess.
Where is your earring?
KATE:
Oh, um...
I don’t know.
-It must’ve fallen out.
-
I’ll give you another one.
Oh, no, no, no,
don’t worry about it.
Don’t worry,
it’s just a shiny rock.
I don’t want another one.
We need to talk.
-About the pact.
-Are you serious?
-You don’t want to keep the pact
-
now that you’re ranked
higher than me,
but you were fine with it
when you were at the bottom.
It’s not about that.
I’m just trying to be realistic.
Since when?
You think you can
fuck your way to stardom
and that’s gonna make you
high-class.
BENJAMIN:
Kate Sanders, you’re up.
We need to rehearse.
What did you expect?
KATE:
It doesn’t matter.
Benjamin’s gonna be a judge
at the final evaluation.
-He knows what I can do.
-
It does matter.
This is so unfair to me.
-Did you think of this?
-
KATE:
Luc’s refusing to dance with me.
I can’t be expected to rehearse
for Benjamin’s project
and the academy
at the same time.
Well, that’s exactly
what you are expected to do.
The understudy role doesn’t mean
that you’re gonna get
a contract...
or win the prize.
It doesn’t mean anything.
You’ve never liked me.
You have never given me
a real chance.
Do you think I don’t see you?
If I didn’t like you,
I’d just let you fail.
-
Oh, thank you.
-You look great.
-
SARAH:
We are gathered here today
to celebrate the birth
of this obscenely talented brat
that I’m very proud to call
my collaborator and friend.
Let’s be honest, Benjamin.
This toast wouldn’t be possible
if not for all those rich people
you convince
to empty their pockets
for the sake of our art form.
So, may you continue
to pander to their demands.
-Long live Benjamin.
-Long live ballet.
Long live ballet.
-OTHERS: Long live ballet!
-
What did she mean by
"pander to their demands"?
Hmm.
She’s just poking fun at me,
because it was a donor who
insisted that she would be cast
at the beginning of her career.
What do you mean?
Well, they gave
a bunch of money to ballet
so they could strongly suggest
their favorite to be cast.
And you agreed to this?
She was terrific.
KATE:
But not the best?
She became the best
with my guidance.
-But...
-But what, ma chérie?
It’s never been
an even playing field.
It’s always been about
sex, blood, money.
It’s all that matters.
SCOTT
Katie?
Are you okay?
I need you to tell me the truth.
Why did you sell the house?
They said...
the Durand family had a change
of heart, whatever that means.
The bastards
revoked your scholarship.
What’s wrong?
You’re scaring me.
I know what you did.
You used me.
Made me think
we were actually friends.
And then you had
your parents intervene
to cancel my scholarship.
Why would you do that to me?
I-I s-- I swear, I didn’t...
I didn’t.
I didn’t know.
You’re such a liar!
I swear on my life, I would
never purposely hurt you.
We’re best friends.
We’re sisters.
You would have a threesome
with your sister?
Oh, that’s right.
You probably would.
-
MARINE:
Kate!
Can we talk?
Please.
What’s going on?
LUC:
Is it true?
Is what true?
You and Ollie.
Everyone is saying that
your mother
caught you guys fucking,
and that’s why
he killed himself.
No, it’s not... it’s not true.
That’s not true.
-You know that’s not true.
-Don’t fucking touch me.
You disgust me.
Hi.
I was just
a few years older than you.
I was dancing Swan Lake.
Main stage.
One day, I noticed
that I was gaining weight.
It didn’t make any sense.
-What’d you do?
-Nothing.
I kept dancing.
Harder than I had before.
Whatever life was inside me
bled out a few weeks later.
You cannot change the past.
You cannot.
All you can do is
learn to accept your grief,
your shame,
your regret.
It’s a heavy rock
we carry around.
And one that we can
never put down.
But...
...I have learned...
...to love my rock.
Instead of...
of weighing me down...
...it’s made me stronger.
Blessed is she who falls.
Blessed is she who rises again.
So you’re dancing a solo.
Yes.
Madame Brunelle says, because
you decided to dance alone,
she’s reassigning Felipe to me.
Isn’t that what you wanted?
FRANCIS:
Welcome, friends,
family.
Thank you for being here
to witness
these ten extraordinary
young dancers...
...a contract with
the Paris Opera Ballet.
-Thank you.
just wants to break you
that look inside your eye
it only makes you stronger?
to run and hide
just wants to trick you
that look inside their eyes?
pain can make you stronger?
into their lies
-
the nights are getting longer
you’re only getting stronger
when they call.
-
That took courage.
I didn’t know you could
choreograph like that.
I would love to dance for you
one day.
It would be an honor.
Thank you for your patience,
everybody.
You have made me...
very proud, petits rats.
If I call your name, I will have
to ask you to leave the stage...
...and to pursue opportunities
elsewhere.
Natasha.
Peter.
Isabelle.
Jean Paul.
Roman.
Luc.
Felipe,
we award the prize
for best male dancer to you.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
BRUNELLE: And now
to our talented ballerinas,
a subject of much debate.
Gia.
You haven’t won the prize today.
But we would like to offer you
an apprenticeship
with the Paris Opera Ballet.
Merci.
Bravo.
The time has come
for which ballerina
will win the prize.
The winner of the contract
for the Paris Opera Ballet is...
MARINE:
Wait.
I don’t want it.
What are you doing?
What about Ollie’s prize?
If you leave now,
you are on your own.
You have no idea how to fend
for yourself in the real world.
You will be cut off.
Do you understand?
I do.
Marine!
BRUNELLE:
Mademoiselle Sanders,
the prize belongs to you.
Congratulations, Virginia.
I know you would have
picked her.
I saw you with her father.
I know he paid you to pick her.
The family revoked
your scholarship.
I was trying to reverse that.
I picked the best dancer.
KATE:
So who was it?
Me or M?
Please.
I need to know.
Kate!
Hi.
I saw the show.
You were really good.
Thanks.
How are you?
Actually really good.
Great, even.
It took me a long time to be
able to say that, but, um...
...it’s true.
You still dancing?
Mostly at the Jungle.
That place still exists?
You should come by sometime
if you ever feel like it.
I just finished
choreographing this new piece.
I came by to say thank you.
For what?
You really forced me
to face myself.
And I feel free now.
I hope you find that, too.
Hey!
Hi.
-What the fuck was that?
-What do you mean?
What kind of fucked-up game
are you trying to play?
-I’m not...
-Bullshit!
You should be mad at me!
You should fucking hate me!
Why don’t you hate me?
I’m sorry.
Sorry.
You have no idea
how much I wish
I could take back
everything that happened,
everything I did.
I’m sorry.
MARINE:
Virginia.
Blessed is she who falls.
Blessed is she who rises again.
MARINE:
The animals were behaving badly.
So the gods put a blanket over
the Earth to block out the sun.
Until one little bird
flew higher
than any bird
had ever flown before,
so high she poked a hole
in the blanket.
-
KATE:
The fall nearly broke her.
But she embraced the pain
she could no longer escape...
...and opened her heart
once more to the sky.
to be in love
what some people don’t
until they explode
doesn’t seem to shine