Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[Light orchestral music]
[Guests chattering]
- [Narrator] In this life,
Savannah had only
encountered two phenomena
with unequivocal
rarity and beauty.
The first was the magical
glow of the blue moon,
so named for its scarcity.
It appeared only once or
twice every two or three years.
And the other was love,
an even rarer occurrence,
ignited by the passion
of a man named linden.
[Crickets chirping]
However, even
the truest devotion
can be threatened by ambition,
and for Savannah, this
coursed through her veins
like a fire that refuse to dim.
- I love you.
- On the strike of midnight,
it would be time
for her to choose...
[Bell tolls]
Between her heart's
comfort or destiny unknown.
[Bell tolling]
She could have
one but never both.
As she disappeared
into the night
to the sound of pounding
hooves on cobblestone,
Savannah pulls off
her heels and she turns
for one last glimpse
of her true love.
[Book slams cover]
Now that's how you finish a
book! Wouldn't you say, grace?
- I know! I did it
once, I can do it again.
- Uh-uh! Hello!
Where's the fire? Come
on, I'm not feeling it!
- Maybe I have nothing
left to say about love.
It's not like romance is
the only genre out there.
Mysteries are always popular.
- Your deadline is in 10 days,
and we're paying you for
the third book in this trilogy,
so you better find something
worth saying about romance.
I'm gonna be frank.
Your book sales have
dropped significantly
in the last quarter.
If this book doesn't
hit the bestseller list,
we won't be extending
your contract.
- I'll get the pages
out to you, okay?
I'll force them out
one way or another.
- No, you're not
gonna force anything.
You're gonna weave a
tapestry of love and passion
that ends this trilogy
was such fierce emotion
people are gonna be buying
your book for the next 10 years.
- Fierce emotions. Gotcha.
- Yes!
You know, get a
change of scenery.
Ask someone on a date.
- Wanna go on a date?
- Not me, but I
like the confidence.
- Ooh! How 'bout him?
- How'd you even
know that was in there?
[Both grunting]
- Do you think I would have
forgotten about your muse
when you, a lowly,
unpublished writer
approached me with the
most heartfelt manuscript
I'd ever set my eyes on?
- Sean's irrelevant. He
broke up with me, remember?
- No, you broke up with him
because he was being distant.
- Same thing!
He's probably often in
Europe researching catacombs
or imagining the
next Eiffel Tower.
- What's this?
- What?
- [Grace] The blue moon ball.
- Um...
It's just a hometown event
that happens every few years.
Flyer I used to think
was meaningful.
[Paper crumples]
- Used to?
Sounds quaint.
- Ancient history now.
- Grace, stop waiting for
the moment's stars to align.
Take action in your life!
Fight for your love!
I need you to think about
where your heart was
when you first met Sean,
when you first fell
in love with him.
Go there and write.
Okay?
[Grace sighs]
- My book signing!
[Upbeat instrumental music]
- Hey.
- Hi!
So nice to meet a
fellow rom reader.
- Actually, I'm just looking
for some books on isometrics.
- [Grace] Oh.
[Quirky music]
[Phone beeps]
[Books tumbling]
- Oh!
[Grace shrieks]
- I am so sorry!
Are you all right?
- [Grace] I'm fine.
- I am such a klutz. Hopefully
my patients never find out.
[Soft piano music]
Um...
I'm really sorry, again.
Have a good evening.
- Um, I mean, I
am a little bruised.
[Chuckles]
Nothing a book
sale wouldn't fix.
- Well, I can't say I've
ever read a romance novel.
Is this one any good?
- Only if you like
your passion red hot.
- Sounds like I could get
burned if I'm not careful.
- So you're a doctor?
- Resident currently,
so I'm good with burns.
[Both laughing]
- Well, what do you
residents like to do for fun?
- Fun hasn't come
up much lately.
We do enjoy an
occasional brunch.
- Me too!
Maybe the author
of "river romance"
would be open to
discussing her novel
over mimosas some time?
- She might be.
- James.
- James?
- Strong name.
- Thank you.
- I'll just...
Give you my number.
- Ciao.
- That was a hot tamale!
Nicely done, dear!
- Okay.
- It's quite nippy
out there tonight.
Keeping people inside, I think.
Leaving already?
- Yes.
Thank you you so much for
letting me use your store, ester.
- Nevermind about the turnout.
You're a great writer!
- Thank you.
- I want you to come back
here for your next book launch.
- If I have one.
- You will!
Just don't give up.
That's the secret to
anything worthwhile,
because, you know,
everyone loves a happy ending.
- Me too.
[Gentle instrumental music]
[Grace screams]
What?
[Grace grunts]
- Oh!
[Woman laughing]
- Pinch me! I'm dreaming!
- Hi, mom.
- I can't believe
you're really here!
And just in time!
How serendipitous.
- It was kind of a
last-minute decision.
- Well, I'll take it.
Come on, let's get
you in the house.
- I miss this place.
I wish I could
transplant it back to la.
[Mom chuckles]
- Well, la may have
skyscrapers and strip malls,
but it doesn't have
the blue moon ball.
[Grace chuckles]
- Please, that's so far away,
it's the last thing on my mind.
- What do you mean?
I assumed you knew the
blue moon is this Friday.
[Grace chokes]
- It can't be!
It's supposed to be
another five years
until the next blue moon.
- That's how long
you've been away.
- Really?
It feels like no time at all.
- Well, the good
news is you're back,
and this is gonna be
a very special year,
where the blue moon
falls on the same night
as the harvest moon.
I thought you knew.
- I'm sorry I've been
away for so long.
But I'm really happy
I'm not missing this.
- You work too hard
in that career of yours.
You have always been
single-minded, and I am so glad
that you finally took
some time for yourself.
But if you didn't
know about the ball,
what brought you back home?
- My agent suggested
it. [Chuckles]
He wanted me to
return to the place
where I first
learned about love.
- Back to your mom,
who's the person who loves
you the most in the world.
[Grace chuckles]
- Exactly.
Well, I should get to bed.
I've got a full day
of work tomorrow.
- Okay.
I'm gonna make this
trip extra inspirational.
- Thanks, mom.
- I'm gonna start with baking.
- Yes!
- Okay.
[Mom chuckles]
Goodnight.
[Relaxed banjo and vocal music]
♪ Wheels rusting over too
♪ time is running out on you
♪ just the way
your love is new ♪
♪ so Autumn fell
and let you lose ♪
♪ when summer's
warm embrace eludes ♪
♪ scared of what
you'll say or do ♪
♪ in a winter too
cold to tell the truth ♪
♪ come on around
come on around ♪
♪ I won't let me
let you down oh ♪
♪ come on around
come on around ♪
[Mom laughing]
Don't tell me your an FBI agent.
I was just getting used to
the intense writer phase.
- Hilarious!
I'm going the old
mansion to write,
and I didn't want
anyone to recognize me.
- People are gonna think
you're there to mug them.
- Maybe they'll
keep their distance.
[Soft instrumental music]
- Maybe the mansion
isn't the best...
Idea.
♪ Gonna get up there
and take what's mine ♪
♪ gonna say goodbye
and make this desert blue ♪
♪ I've been running
for way too long ♪
♪ all directions wrong
♪ now all of a
sudden I can see ♪
♪ I'm so bored of the ordinary
♪ it's time for me to
change the story now ♪
♪ I'm gonna show
my face to the world ♪
♪ and stop and stare at it all
♪ I've seen too many days
without light to stay in the dark ♪
♪ I'm gonna show
my face to the world ♪
♪ because I'm not
scared anymore ♪
♪ I'm telling you right now
I'm making it mine now ♪
♪ I'm gonna show
my face to the world ♪
♪ Quit this life girl
to get enough ♪
♪ don't need this
stuff gonna cut out ♪
- Are my eyes deceiving
me, or is that grace montague?
[Woman laughing]
- Heather.
Hey.
- Grace!
Grace, grace,
grace, grace, grace
girl, did I ever miss you!
- I missed you too.
So much missing.
[Gasps]
- See my truck on your way in?
I just got new mud tires on her.
Can you believe it?
- Wow.
That must've cost
you an arm and a leg.
- Boyfriend's leg, not mine.
I'm so glad to see that you
made it back, just in time, too.
- I know. For the ball, right?
- Oh, sure. If that
even happens,
they'll probably
have the permits
to tear this old heap
of timber down by then.
- Tear it down?
- Yeah, for the new
shopping complex!
This is prime real
estate, you know.
Location, location, location.
You'd me a perfect person
to write an article on it!
Yeah, it would bring some
hype to the mega mall!
[Grace chuckles anxiously]
Or is that beneath you?
You are little miss famous
now, aren't you? [Laughs]
I have both your novels
on my bedside table.
- You've read my books?
- Read them?
I inhaled them!
I was so relieved when
Savannah finally left lyndon
to go pursue her own career,
and she can finally start
dating men of a higher caliber
and tax bracket, if you
know what I mean. [Laughing]
- Yeah.
Well, my characters await, so...
I should get back to it.
- Of course.
But I wouldn't
recommend doing it here.
The contractor's
in and out all day.
- Right, for the much
needed shopping mall.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
[Soft instrumental music]
[Grace sighs]
Lyndon and Savannah's
stroll through the Rose garden
became a march down blame Lane.
"I can't believe you'd tear
down the walls of our love
without so much as
running the idea by me first,"
Savannah snaps.
[Quirky music]
- Grace.
- "It's just a building, Ramona.
I knew you'd say no,
so I made an executive
decision," lyndon replies.
"What gives you the right?"
- Grace!
- I'm sorry, I'm try-
Sean.
- Sorry, I just heard your
voice and underwent a...
Minor heart attack.
[Grace chuckles]
- Were you sitting
there the whole time?
At our tree?
- Is this...
Our tree?
[Sean chuckles nervously]
It is, I...
No, no, no, I was...
On a work break and I
decided to get some fresh air.
- Right.
Wait, you work here?
Yeah, I got my
master's in architecture,
and then, what would you know,
first job I land is
right back at home.
- Building the new
shopping complex!
I heard.
- No, no, no.
I'm here to make sure
that doesn't happen.
I'm trying to get the old
mansion deemed historic
and save it.
- Really? That's amazing!
Uh...
Sorry, I kind of
went a little crazy
when Heather told me
they were tearing it down.
- Heather told you?
- Can you believe it?
She actually sounded
excited about it too.
Same country Princess as always.
- She was a sucker
for outlet stores.
[Grace laughs]
- So does this mean you're
gonna the blue moon ball?
- I haven't missed one yet.
Are you going?
- I am now.
- I'm really glad
that I ran into you.
Or bothered you.
- At least some
things never changed.
[Both chuckle]
- You look really good.
- I am really good.
- I think you're
supposed to say that...
I look really good too.
[Grace laughs]
- Isn't that a given?
- Well, I've...
Got to get back to work.
I got to find grounds to
deem the mansion historic,
then write a 20-page proposal.
- Save the blue moon ball.
- Exactly!
So...
I'll see you around, I guess?
- Maybe.
Danny, hey.
- Hey.
Can you come to my office?
I want to talk about
the book signing.
I heard through the grapevine
that after selling one book,
you proceeded to pack up early.
Tell me the grapevine lies.
- I did.
You told me to go to the
place where I first fell in love,
so I flew home last night.
- Flew home?
I was talking about in
your mind, not on a plane.
- Oops.
- Well, you're there
now, I suppose.
Getting lots of writing done?
- Tons!
- Great.
Send me the pages by Friday.
- Prepare to be amazed.
- You know, in this profession,
I prepare for the worst
and I pray for slightly better.
Bye, grace.
[Hangs up phone]
- By-
- [contractor] Joe, come here!
[Curious music]
- [Heather] Sean!
- Hey, Heather.
How was your day?
- Oh, good as good can be.
Spent most of it
at the riding club,
practicing dressage with star.
I'm gonna need new gloves soon.
- My day was good too.
Thanks for asking.
- Somebody's grumpy.
- I heard you've been
talking up the shopping mall,
which seems a little strange,
given that it's my job to
make sure that doesn't happen.
- It's your first job,
baby boo. A practice run.
Besides, you know how
proud my daddy's gonna be
when you declare
that site a tear-down.
- Thanks for the
vote of confidence,
but this mansion is
really important to me.
It's a link to some of this
town's most important history.
It's not a tear-down.
- I love that you always
think with your heart,
it's the perfect balance
to overly logical me,
who has no choice
but to point out
that old house hasn't been
used in who knows how long.
It's a financial black hole.
That's why the cassidys
are finally dropping it.
- You know, I
heard they're living
in the suburbs
somewhere back east.
The suburbs! Poor things.
People will come
shopping here every day
from all over the
county and beyond.
It'll increase our
town's economy tenfold.
- You know, I didn't need
your dad to give me this job.
I can stand on my own two feet.
Of course you can, sweetie.
- You ever gonna
stay at your own place?
- Why would I do that, silly?
I make this place
just barely livable.
Dinner will be ready in fine
[emotional orchestral music]
- Well!
If it isn't my goddaughter!
- [Grace] Sheriff Carson.
- How are you doing,
sweetie? [Laughing]
- When I heard you
were back in town,
I decided to camp out
in your mom's kitchen.
That way you have no
choice but to say howdy.
- Camp out means eat the fridge.
[Sheriff Carson laughs]
- Best fridge in town.
- Well, I'd never come
home without visiting
the best storyteller in town.
- Um...
How did the writing go?
Did you manage
to stay incognito?
[Grace scoffs]
- As if.
I had to personally
introduce myself
as the great-great-granddaughter
of the man who helped
build that mansion
to every demolition
contractor in the county.
- So you know.
- [Grace] Why didn't you tell me
they were planning
to tear it down?
- It's a tragedy, grace, not
one we have any power over.
- And it's a reminder
that the blue moon ball
is not about fancy location.
It's about bringing the
community together.
- So you're gonna host
the party in your backyard?
- If it came to
that, in a heartbeat,
and anyone in town
would do the same thing.
- Yes, ma'am, all true.
- Sean's trying to have
the mansion deemed
as a historical site.
- Right. Sean.
I was wondering when
your two paths would cross.
- Do you think there's any
chance he'll manage to save it?
- Well, Sean's a smart man.
The town's lucky to have him.
That said, he's not
exactly the persuasive type.
[Grace snorts]
- That's definitely true.
He could never get
me to do anything.
- Yes, I know that.
You were always the ring
leader with the bright ideas.
You know, I remember
the time you and Sean
stole that fire hose
and flooded out old man
Jeremiah's taxidermy shop.
Woo hoo hoo hoo!
He was hopping mad!
- Don't encourage her.
- Like two peas in
a pod of mischief.
- I plead the fifth.
[Soft piano music]
- [Grace] Hey, phone?
[Phone beeps]
- [Phone] Yes?
- What does love mean?
[Phone beeps]
- [Phone] An intense
feeling of deep affection.
Example: His love of football.
[Phone beeps]
[Phone ringing]
- Grace montague speaking.
- [James] Hey,
grace, it's James.
- Hey!
- You'll never
guess where I'm at.
Back at the scene of the crime.
Look, I know it's a
little bit late for brunch,
but my work is taking me
out of the city tomorrow.
So, if you're free tonight,
maybe we could
squeeze in that date.
- I'm actually not
in la right now.
I'm on a bit of a
work trip myself.
- Oh, well, yeah, I
knew it was a long shot.
- Um...
Weird question for you.
But I was just wondering,
how do you know when to
stop diagnosing a patient?
Like, how do you know
when you're done testing them
and you can just treat
them for what you think it is?
- There's no hard and fast rule.
When I've exhausted all
the possibilities I can think of.
Then I just trust my gut.
- Does your next romance
novel need a doctor?
[Grace chuckles]
- No, but that actually helped.
Thanks, James.
Have a good night.
- You too.
Bye, grace.
- [Grace] Hey, phone?
[Phone beeps]
- [Phone] Yes?
- How to write a
persuasive study
on historical property value.
[Phone beeps]
- Approved historical property
applications: 1,021 entries.
[Phone beeps]
- Hey, phone, email links to me.
- [Phone] Emailing links.
[Phone beeps]
[Typing on keyboard]
[Owl hooting]
- Mom, are you awake?
Mom.
Are you awake?
- What happened?
What time is it?
- 5:00 A.M.!
[Mom sighs]
- I've been up all night
trying to figure out how to
help Sean win a zoning permit,
and I think I've done it.
- So you're an architect now?
- I know!
But like sheriff Carson said,
Sean doesn't need an
architect; He needs a writer.
And I'm a writer!
I'm persuasive!
- And loud.
- Yeah.
[Mom sighs]
- You know, grace,
this is a noble project,
but do you think
it's a good idea
to be working with Sean again?
I mean, I remember
when you two broke up.
It just really hurt you.
- It was years ago.
We were just kids.
We've grown past all that.
- Yeah, but what
about your work?
Don't you have a deadline
the night of the ball?
Shouldn't you stay focused?
- I can do both.
See?
Did you see?
Oh.
[Gentle instrumental music]
I didn't know they
taught the two-step
at architectural school.
- Whoever built this place
knew exactly what
they were doing.
This house is built
with a sprung floor
that absorbs shock.
So when I lift you up...
And then drop you back down...
- I don't break an ankle.
- Exactly.
I want to tell you something.
- Yeah?
- I was hired for this job
because the
contractor knew I'd fail.
It's my first job with the firm.
I'm a newbie.
- How would the contractor
possibly know that?
- The contractor
is Heather's dad.
- Ugh!
Classic small-town nepotism.
- I'm glad you came home.
Might be your last
chance to say goodbye
if I botch this job.
- My mom used to tell me stories
that my great-great-grandpa
helped build that red barn.
How could such a precious place
not have any
historical significance?
- That's so weird!
No, my family used to tell
me the exact same story.
- Maybe our ancestors
built it together.
And maybe that's why we
need to work together now.
We're not gonna let some
rich country bureaucrats
take over our town!
If you can prove what
makes the site historical,
I'll come up with
the arguing proposal.
What do you say?
[Bright orchestral music]
Team?
- Team.
- So what's first on the list?
Library archives or a town-wide
save-the-mansion petition?
- Actually, I noticed
a quarter wall panel
that looks a little too new.
- So it's been updated.
That's good, right?
- Yeah, but it only
takes up half the wall.
- So it's covering something up?
- Exactly.
- Fingers crossed
it's not black mold.
- Well, I'm gonna head
home and grab some tools.
I'm gonna get that paneling off.
- Great! I can
see your new digs.
- Actually, I've had
a bit of an infestation.
- Mice?
- Something like that.
I'll drop you off at home and...
We can meet up later.
- Yeah, yeah, that sounds great.
I have some writing
to do anyway, so...
No way!
You're still driving Jess?
- Of course!
- You put some work into her.
Ah, there's no more hole
in the passenger seat.
- You don't need that
old striped pillow anymore.
- Oh yeah! I totally
forgot about that thing.
- Got new mud tires on her too.
- Must be the season.
Heather was just telling me
that she got the same
thing for her truck.
- Her truck.
Great.
- Mom?
I have a problem.
[Mom chuckles]
As a kid, you would
always say that
when you didn't know
how to finish a story.
- Well, at least with a story,
I can always erase
it and try again.
Those look lovely, by the way.
- Thank you.
- With this, if I mess
up, there's no do-over,
no back button.
- And exactly what problem
is it we're discussing?
- Sean.
He's acting all weird and aloof.
- Well, you know, maybe his life
is a little more
complicated than you think.
- What do you mean?
- Well, I'm not one to pry
into other people's
affairs, but...
You know, your history
together is complex.
- Technically, I guess we
never called off our engagement,
but that was years ago.
- Mm-hm. And now?
- Now we're working together...
And it just feels
like all those years
of being best friends
never happened.
It I'll just makes
me feel more...
- Interested?
- Confused.
- Are you still
in love with him?
- No!
I'm in like,
emphasis on the like.
And I have no idea if
he feels the same way.
- Do you remember
when you started writing?
- No.
- It was after your father died.
You needed to just sort
through your feelings,
write them out.
So the stories and
the poems were fiction.
But your emotions were real.
- So you think I should journal?
- I think it would give
you the clarity you need.
- Thanks, mom.
You always have the best advice.
[Gentle orchestral music]
[Truck rumbling]
[Papers tumbling]
- Hey Sean!
You still want to
see a movie tonight?
- Yeah, yeah. Just one sec.
- What's with all the letters?
- I just...
Nothing. Just junk mail.
Makes good fire starter.
What movie are we
seeing again tonight?
- Okay.
What do I want to
say about Sean?
It depends on what
he has to say about me.
[Sean grunting]
[Upbeat funk music]
[Grace sighs]
[Wood panel clunking]
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
- Hey! Are you busy?
- If you consider staring at a
blank computer screen busy,
then yes.
- Sounds rough.
- Yeah. I need a break.
- Good. You're never
gonna believe this.
- What is it?
[Mysterious music]
What is all this?
- It looks like an old doorway
that someone filled in,
and some vandalism.
- I don't think it's vandalism.
An old tradition, maybe.
- Names and hearts. Past lovers?
- Okay, what were your
grandparents' names?
- Albert and Marjorie. Why?
- Do you think this was them?
- There's only
one way to find out.
- They're still alive?
- Grandpa Albert is.
Present's a little tricky,
but the past he knows
like the back of his hand.
- You up for a trip
down memory Lane?
- On one condition.
- Anything from
my partner in crime.
- I get to drive Jess.
[Energetic rock music]
- I really appreciate
you doing this, grace,
especially when you
have work of your own
you've got to get back to.
- I wouldn't exactly
consider this work.
- Lucky!
I barely slept with all the
thoughts racing through my mind.
- I mean, there's really only
two ways we can go, right?
- You're right.
We save her or we don't.
Hey, I'm really doing everything
I can to save the mansion.
I know I screwed up and
disappointed you in the past,
but I'll try not to let
that happen again.
- Disappointed me?
Sean, I sent you about
101 text messages,
countless embarrassing
late-night voicemails,
and you couldn't so
much as call me back?
- But...
You never came back!
- I was chasing my
dreams to be a writer!
You said you wanted that for me.
- And I did!
- So I don't get it.
You're not making sense.
- I really screwed up, didn't I?
[Truck turns off]
[Grace sighs]
- You did.
[Upbeat clapping]
Do you think it's
too late to fix it?
- Fix it?
- I still have the bolt, Sean.
- Get down!
- What?
- Your hair!
There's a bug in it!
Let me get it!
- [Grace] There's a-
ew!
Ew, ew, ew! Get
it out, get it out!
Did you get it?
Sean!
- Got it.
- Let me see it!
- I smashed it.
Wait here.
I'm gonna get grandpa.
- Yeah.
You go get grandpa.
[Grace shrieks]
- Hi, Mrs. Montague!
- Oh, well, Heather! Hello!
Did you jog all the way here?
- Exercise keeps me focused.
- I love the determination.
What brings you out to the area?
- Well, it's a town-wide survey,
I want to know exactly
what kind of stores
this town wants to
see in the new mall.
A new tech shop, a trendy
cafe, arts boutiques, you name it.
- I'm very sorry, Heather.
I just don't think it's
right I take the survey.
Grace and I are dead set
against the mansion demolition.
- Well, that's all
right. [Chuckles]
You have a great
day, Mrs. Montague.
- You too.
- Mrs. Montague?
- Yes, dear?
- Grace is really lucky to
have such a supportive mom.
- [Sean] How are you feeling?
How they treating you in there?
- Well, I can't
complain, you know.
I mean, I started
out with nothing,
and I still have
most of it left.
[Both laugh]
- [Sean] You're doing
great. I mean, look at you.
- Well, you know.
- Grandpa Albert,
this is the friend
I was telling you about, grace.
- [Grandpa] Who? Speak up.
- Grace!
- Eh?
- Oh!
Marjorie, my dear!
Let's go to the races!
- Grandpa Albert, that's
not Marjorie. She's-
- at the riding club.
- Oh, at the riding club?
- Well, of course
she is. [Laughs]
I'm sorry, dear.
My mistake.
- I guess the green
family loving me
must be a genetic trait.
[Grandpa chuckles]
- Taxi driver...
Take me to the mansion gardens!
I haven't seen a
blooming lilac in years.
- Yes, sir.
- [Grandpa] Oh, what
a time to be alive.
- Grandpa?
- Eh?
- I wanted to ask you
about the blue moon ball.
Do you remember it?
- Well, of course I remember it!
Dancing under the blue moon
is how every man in this town
found the love of his life,
glowing under Luna's soft kiss.
- That's beautiful.
Is that how you met Marjorie?
- Oh, no, no, we
grew up together.
We were in the same class
all the way from kindergarten
through graduation.
- Just like us.
- Albert, we were
wondering about the mansion.
We found some carved initials,
and we were just wondering
if they had any
sort of significance.
- Significance?
[Scoffs]
It's a tradition!
As old as the blue moon itself.
Legend had it that if a young
man would carve his name
next to the name of
the woman he loved,
they would be
brought together again
under the next blue moon,
and the moon would see to it,
no matter what
the circumstances,
that their paths would
cross and their love blossom.
- Does it work?
- Ask Marjorie.
We've been married since 1960.
Why are you asking
all these questions
about the blue moon ball anyway?
- Grandpa Albert...
There are some people who
want to tear the mansion down.
Me and grace,
we're trying to gather
as much information as we
can to stop that from happening.
- That's criminal!
[Grandpa groaning]
- Grandpa!
Where are you going?
- The study!
- There's a study?
- Not that I know of.
- [Sean] Grandpa,
where are you going?
- You'll see.
[Grandpa chuckles]
Prepare to be amazed.
- [Grace] Nice work, Sean.
- That's a boy.
Ah, here we go.
Whoa-ho, here it is.
- Is this an original
map of our town?
- [Grandpa] Uh-huh.
- It can't be.
The year's 1831.
We weren't found until 1845.
- That's right.
The original founder of
this land, Austin Hastings,
bought over 10,000 acres
and built this
mansion for his wife.
They knew they had
something special here,
so they started
giving land deeds
to some of the
struggling local farmers
to foster a community.
He envisioned a town,
and this is what it became.
- Enough to have to have
it declared a historic site?
- I mean, if we can
find the original deeds,
I don't see why not.
- Find 'em? [Chuckles]
My grandpa used to bring
me here to the mansion
when I was a child
for history lessons.
Now, Mr. Hastings kept
every document he ever had
right here in this desk.
There you go.
[Grace chuckles]
- Look, we're all here. The
montagues, the Greens.
- As a gesture of appreciation,
the local farmers built
Mr. Hastings the red barn.
- Grace, I...
I wanna ask you something.
- Yeah?
- It's kinda awkward.
I'm more just
asking for a friend.
Oh, well, yeah, let's hear it.
- He has this girlfriend...
And she was supposed
to be just a rebound
to help him get over the
biggest heartbreak of his life.
But that rebound
turned out to be
more permanent than he expected.
And he's been trying to break
up with her for months now,
but he doesn't want to
hurt anyone's feelings.
- Us girls are
tougher than we look.
You should just
be honest with her.
No one likes
getting strung along.
Do I know this couple?
- Yeah.
It's Heather actually.
- Ugh.
I pity the man who's ever
crossed paths with her.
- Me too.
Pot hole!
[Tires squealing]
[Police siren blaring]
- I don't know about you,
but I'd sooner take a
pothole over a ticket.
- It's Jess we're talking about.
- You've got me there.
Just let me do
the talking. It's fine.
[Upbeat funk music]
[Grace chuckles]
- Sorry, officer. I was
just avoiding a pothole.
- Mm-hm.
Well, grace, I know
these country roads
aren't as pristine as la.
That with some
pretty erratic driving,
even for the likes of this town,
not to mention
you're in the company
of one of the most notorious
party boys in these parts.
- Sean?
- Me?
- No, I'm talking about Albert.
Best square dance caller I know.
[All laughing]
So, to ensure that we
keep the streets safe,
I'm gonna need you to prove
that you haven't been drinking.
Hop on out of the
car, miss montague.
You, too, partner.
- What can I do
for you, sheriff?
Want me to walk the line?
- Not quite, grace.
I've found line dance is a
much better judge of sobriety.
[Turns on music]
- You're kidding!
I don't even remember
how to line dance!
- Maybe your good friend
Sean here can remind you.
Come on. Hop to it.
- It was the line
dance king in the day.
[Grace laughs]
[Upbeat country music]
- Cowboy up!
Come on!
- Oh! [Chuckles]
[All laughing]
I haven't done this
since the last ball.
I can't believe my feet
even know what to do.
- It's not your
feet. It's your heart.
[Grace and Sean laughing]
- Sweetie?
[Knocks on door]
Are you awake?
I know you've been up for
hours writing, but I made cookies.
[Mom shouts]
[Dishes clatter]
- Oatmeal raisin! My favorite!
- I thought you were in your
room. Did you sneak out?
- Sneak out?
I hate to burst your bubble,
mom, but I'm not 16 anymore.
- No, six is a better estimate.
- Come on.
I want to tell you about
my ideas for the mansion
that required your
wisdom and expertise.
- Oh.
[Bouncy instrumental music]
[Crickets chirping]
- Sean says the biggest
problem with the mansion
is keeping it heated
and maintained
while it's not being used.
- Which is 99% of the time.
And if we had a ball
there every night,
well, then we'd
lose the very rarity
that makes it so special.
- The town's been
helping the cassidys
with the costs for a long
time, but it's a big number.
Maybe it doesn't
have to be a ball.
What about a farmers market?
- Or a wedding venue.
It's so beautiful.
- Why not both?
- Well, people have been asking
for an indoor farmers
market for years.
We could use the barn.
- And the house and the
grounds are magazine worthy.
We'd just need a marketing
campaign to get the word out.
- Oh! They're perfect.
But who'd run it.
- I happen to know a
certain empty nester
who's been needing a new baby.
[Mom laughs]
- Am I so obvious?
[Grace laughs]
- Look, a shooting star!
- I wish that you and
Sean save the mansion.
- I wish the universe
would give me a sign.
If Sean's the one
I meant to be with,
have him call me right now.
[Phone ringing]
- You're not gonna get that?
- It's a telemarketer.
- Just because
you don't get a sign
doesn't mean it's
not gonna work out.
[Light piano music]
[Crickets chirping]
- Hey, hon.
I saw your track of the
old fogeys home today.
Visiting grandpa?
[Gentle orchestral music]
Sean?
[Mysterious instrumental music]
[Phone ringing]
- [Dad] Hello?
- Daddy, we have a problem.
- [Dead] Heather, what now?
- He's finding evidence.
Good evidence.
I think maybe
someone's helping him.
- [Dad] Heather, do
you want to be appointed
executive developer
of this mall or not?
- Wh-
yes!
I want him with
anything in this world.
- [Dad] Then start making
some executive decisions.
You know this man, you
know how to shake him up.
Change his mind!
Am I making myself clear?
- Crystal.
[Suspenseful instrumental music]
[Door clunking]
[Step clunking]
[Gentle piano music]
- [Mom] Morning!
- Good morning.
- Dressing up for someone?
Please tell me that
manicure is for your keyboard.
- There's point in
trying to figure out
the ending to my novel
without first finding out
how my love story ends.
- I think it's great
that you want to reflect
your life experiences
in your writing,
but don't forget that
relationships take work.
- Writing takes work.
Relationships only
take one thing: Love.
Fate brings people together,
and if it's meant to
be, it should be easy.
- I don't know if your father
would have agreed with that.
- Well, let's see if Sean does.
[Sean sighs]
[Bouncy music]
- Okay.
Time to rip off the band-aid.
- [Heather] Miss pick here
and let me just cut to the chase,
I can't won't call you back
if you don't leave your
name and number, so do it!
[Voicemail beeps]
- Hi, miss pick.
I mean Heather.
It's Sean.
My number is 555...
Listen, we need to talk.
Today.
I feel like things have
been a little off recently,
and if you could
just give me a shout
when you have a chance.
Bye.
♪ So if she runs away
♪ well then I better
chase after her ♪
♪ I'm never pushing anything
♪ she's trying to pull
me back for more ♪
♪ caught up in the moment
♪ I'm just keeping my cool
♪ I'm a sucker for love girl
♪ yeah you know I'm your fool
I heard the siren's call.
- Whatever do you mean?
- Please.
I'd recognize our
song three miles away.
- What took you so long?
- There was something I
needed to take care of first.
So I could give
you my full attention.
- And did you manage
to take care of it?
- Not quite.
But I'm resolute.
What's this?
- This is the finished proposal
and an idea for a farmers
market and a wedding venue
overseen by my sweet mother.
- You are my savior!
♪ Bad times
anything in between ♪
♪ the ups and downs and
baby you're still my queen ♪
- Sean...
There's something I've
been meaning to tell you.
- You can tell me anything.
♪ The plan was to
grow old together ♪
- I don't want to be friends.
♪ If she runs away well
then I better chase after her ♪
- What do you want to be?
- This.
- [Heather] Help me!
I've been maimed!
[Quirky music]
- What happened?
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not okay!
I'm seriously wounded!
I'm just lucky it was
my leg and not my neck!
- You fell?
- Yeah.
I got your voicemail, and I
was hurrying into the mansion
when this happened.
Step broke right through!
Just imagine the lawsuit
if it weren't someone
as spry as myself.
This whole place
is a death trap.
The whole structure's
just rotting away.
- I don't know about
the whole structure.
It was just one step.
- Give me your keys.
I'll get the truck, and we
can take her to the hospital
and make sure nothing's broken.
- Oh!
Oh, I can't put
any weight on it!
I can't put any weight on it.
If it's not broken, it's
definitely fractured.
[Heather grunting]
I'm so lucky to have you.
I'm probably gonna
be out of commission
for the rest of the summer.
I'm gonna need you.
Help me get dressed,
drive me to the stables...
Feed me.
- Are your arms broken too?
- I was just saying
how lucky it is
and fortunate that I have
someone who loves me,
someone who would choose
me over some old building.
So what was your
voicemail about?
- Nothing. Don't worry about it.
[Heather grunting]
Okay, do you want...
[Stammering]
- Do you need help?
We should get something
to stabilize her leg.
- Oh, don't worry
about it, grace.
My seanie will stabilize
it while you drive.
- My seanie?
- Maybe she hit her head
too. We'd better get going!
[Frantic music]
I'll be right back
with a wheelchair.
Don't talk to each other!
- [Grace and Heather] What?
[Both sigh]
- He really is sweet, isn't he?
- He really is.
This town's lucky to have him.
- Good cheekbones.
- Contagious laugh.
- You really did capture him
in your novels, you know?
All his happy-go-lucky
mannerisms.
- I'm so glad you could tell.
It was really hard to
capture his character, his...
Essence.
- I don't know how you do it.
- Do what?
- You know.
Recall those feelings every
time you sit down to write.
It sounds exhausting.
[Door opens] [Grace shrieks]
- Everyone doing okay in here?
- [Grace] Sean!
- I was in a rush, I'm sorry!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Watch your leg, watch
your leg, watch you leg.
Okay, sit, sit.
- Ow!
- Ooh!
I'm so sorry.
- Grace.
- James!
What are you doing here?
- I applied for the
locum position here.
They offered me the job.
I don't know if
I should take it.
After looking around,
this town just seems so...
Quiet.
[Grace chuckles]
You don't live here, do you?
- No, no, I...
I mean, I did.
I'm just visiting.
[Quirky music]
- Grace was born
and raised here.
She's ours.
- I mean, she knows how
to appreciate the quiet.
How do you guys know each other?
- I sense tension.
Is this an la boyfriend
you've been keeping from us?
- James bought one of my books.
- It's hard to resist
a given saleswoman.
- I know we could all stay here
gushing over
grace's books all day,
but I need to see
a doctor, Sean.
- Right.
Grace, you coming?
- I'll just wait in the truck.
[Wheelchair clacking]
- It's the locks.
[Locks clicking]
It'll be a bit of
a wait for them,
and I'm just getting off work.
If you don't mind, I'll drop
you anywhere you need to go.
- Okay.
Sure.
- [James] Wonderful.
I'll be back in five.
- Sounds good.
[Smack]
Hi, mom.
- Oh, not so fast young lady!
- I need to get
inside and write.
I know how my novel ends.
- So what does that mean?
Sean's the only one for me.
No one, no matter how
dreamy, can take his place.
We're soulmates.
- That's amazing, sweetie.
I'm glad you're
proving me wrong.
Not to mention he's
driving quite the car now.
- Oh, that was
actually a friend from la.
- Your two worlds colliding?
- More like a surprise meteor.
- Isn't that what wiped
out the dinosaurs?
[Both chuckle]
- Go finish your book while
you're glowing with inspiration.
[Upbeat piano music]
[Typing on keyboard]
- Thank you.
- I just swear it was the
other leg you were clutching.
It's weird that the
one that hurt less...
Was the one that was fractured.
- Yeah, well, you're an
architect, not a physician.
Let's just stay in your field.
- Can I get you anything?
Water? Tea?
- How about the permit to
that old house's demolition?
As long as it's still standing,
people are in danger.
- I know you were planning
on being a lead investor
and developer
in the outlet mall.
- This has nothing
to do with that.
- Are you sure?
- How'd you know?
- You leave your
sticky notes everywhere.
It wasn't that hard
to piece together.
- That house is gonna
come down, Sean.
It's just a matter of time.
And the land is better
off in the hands of a local
than some outside builder.
- Have you ever considered
there might be a better
use for your money,
something that makes
it more positive change?
- I am not paying for
you to go on another
six-month archeological dig.
- It was a six-day
architectural convention,
and I paid you back.
- Old buildings, old
bones, all the same to me.
Now I'll take that tea, please.
[Typing on keyboard]
[Grace sighs]
[Car trunk shuts]
[Car starts]
- That everything?
- For now.
Store everything
near the kitchen.
The decorating
crew will be in tonight.
- I can't believe
that ball's tomorrow.
This week flew by.
- Life does that.
And the older you
get, the faster it goes.
- Call you in a bit.
- No mansion means no dancin'!
No mansion means no dancin'!
- Grandpa Albert?
What are you
doing here so early?
You must be freezing.
[Grandpa grumbles]
- I'm hot with a raging fire!
Sweating for justice!
- Does the nursing
home know you're here?
[Grandpa grumbles]
- Do those people know anything?
The newspaper said
that a step came loose
and some local lady got injured.
They said the
mansion was a hazard.
- That doesn't necessarily mean
the building will be demolished.
We get the final
word this afternoon.
- Those bureau-rats
should know the facts!
- Sean, I need you to
get to the mansion now!
- What facts, grandpa
Albert, are we talking about?
- I proposed to
Marjorie on those steps.
They're as sturdy
as our marriage.
What we're dealing with
here is first degree sabotage.
- Joe, come here!
Hey, Joe!
- Wait here.
- Hey! What are you doing?
- Marking the placements.
For the explosives?
They need to be aligned
with the support beam
to ensure the entire building
comes down in one go.
- You can't implode the mansion!
No final decision's
been announced!
- We're just doing some
preliminary work, okay?
We won't do anything
actually until the results are in.
- So stop digging holes!
- If I don't dig holes,
the wrecking ball
guy may take my job.
We're all fighting for
something here, sweetie.
- [Grandpa Albert] No
mansion means no dancin'!
- You hit a gas line?
- No dancin' [Car horn blaring]
- Albert!
- No ma-
Marjorie!
Oh, I'm so glad you came back.
This is what happens when
problems get swept under the rug.
Couples fight.
- Grace?
- Sean!
- Grandpa Albert?
- Come again?
- This isn't what it looks like.
- I was professing my love.
- All right, it's exactly
what it looks like.
- Come on, grandpa.
We need to get you
back to the home.
This will be your 10th demerit.
[Light instrumental music]
- Can I have one last
look inside the mansion?
- Those contractors are
already planning her implosion.
That's how certain they
are that we already failed.
- We put up the
best fight we could
for the people of this
community, living and passed.
That's what the
blue moon's all about.
- Speaking of...
You haven't officially
asked me to the ball yet.
- I think I asked you last time.
Doesn't that make it your turn.
- Sean green...
Will you go to the ball with me?
- I'll see if I can
fit in my schedule.
[Grace scoffs]
- Great.
I'll come by yours
tomorrow and pick you up.
- Um...
Maybe I should pick you up.
- [Man] Sean?
Sean green?
- [Sean] Hi, Oscar.
- Hey, good luck.
My daughter, she's been
looking forward to this ball
for five years straight.
It'll be her first one.
- Let's hope.
[Taps stair]
- Steps seem fine. [Chuckles]
[Soft instrumental music]
- Well, what are you
waiting for? Open it.
- What if we didn't get it?
I'd be chased out of town!
- Sean, no one would blame you.
We did everything we could.
- You open it.
If we got the permit,
it's all because of
you're amazing proposal.
Well?
- I'm sorry, Sean.
Sorry that you ever
doubted yourself!
We got the permit,
and the town's gonna
buy out the cassidys.
We did it!
- Yes!
- I guess the blue
moon had our back.
- This wasn't the
blue moon, grace.
This was all you!
- We make a great team.
I'm gonna let grandpa know!
- Okay.
I'm gonna let the newspaper know
that the ball is
full steam ahead,
and I'll be at
your place at six.
- Six? Tonight?
[Indistinct] I like sweet
shiraz and chardonnay.
[Bouncy instrumental music]
- Heather...
I want to break up.
We don't love each other.
I don't even think you like me.
Is there another woman?
Well, if we're being honest...
Heather, put down
the dinner plates!
No, no. Can't we talk about
this like civilized adults?
Get out of my house!
This is my house!
[Eastern instrumental music]
Heather?
You home?
[Quirky music]
[Heather grunting]
- [Heather] I'm in here!
- We need to talk.
- Are those the permit
results for the mansion?
- The results have nothing to
do with what I'm about to say.
- Unless you're about
to say the results,
which I'd really like to know.
- Heather, I want to break up.
We don't love each other.
If anything-
- okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah, fine. Let's break up.
- Just like that?
- I'm gonna need some
alone time to grieve.
Mind leaving?
- Actually, this is my house.
- Both my leg and my
heart have been broken
in the past 24 hours,
and you have the gall-
- okay.
Sorry, you're right.
Take all the time you need.
Sorry.
[Quirky music]
I thought your leg was broken.
- Ow, ow, ow!
- It's the other one.
[Quirky music]
- I'd loved to have
seen Heather's face
when she heard the news.
- I don't know what you
have against that girl.
She spent her whole life
wanting to be just like you.
- Very funny.
I'm the last person that
Heather would ever want to be.
I'm proud of our family,
but compared to her,
I grew up with nothing.
- That may be true, but just to
imagine how she sees things.
You grew up earning
everything that she got for free.
And you're the one with
the career and passion.
She may have money, but her
dreams haven't come to fruition.
If she even knows
what her dreams are.
- I never thought
of it that way.
Do you think-[Phone ringing]
Hold that thought.
- Hello?
- Grace, finally!
Either you're in some
backwards hole in the wall
with no WiFi, or you
have developed a tendency
to hang up on me.
- I would never.
Did you get a chance
to read my novel?
What did you think?
- I think we should
discuss this in my office.
Can you come in
tomorrow morning?
- Tomorrow?
Is it urgent?
- It certainly shouldn't
be postponed.
Is that a problem.
- No, no. No problem at all.
I'll book a flight
back to la tonight.
- Great.
Okay, kiddo, I'll see you soon.
- See ya.
Sean.
[Gentle orchestral music]
- I've faked a lot of things
these past few months, but...
I never faked how
badly I wanted this.
It would have been a chance
to make something of myself.
- You're a pick.
You're the top of the town.
You never had to prove yourself.
- Maybe not to you, but
to myself and to my family?
[Heather sighs]
I can't just live off
daddy's charity forever.
Anyway, that's enough that
rich girl's sob story for today.
Thank you for not freaking out.
- How could I be mad?
- I've made my fair
share of mistakes
in this relationship too.
[Emotional orchestral music]
[Knocking on door]
- [Grace] It's open.
- What's going on?
- Oh, you know.
Just realizing i'm
living in a fantasy.
Truth is so much
crueler than fiction.
- I don't think that's
how the saying goes.
Are you leaving?
- My publisher told
me to come back to la
'cause my novel
was a total flop.
- He said that?
- He didn't have to.
- But the blue moon
ball is tomorrow night.
- Trust me, I know.
- I'm just scared
that you're going back
with more mixed
emotions about this place
than when you came here.
- I'm focused on my
career, not my emotions.
- You are gonna have the most
amazing writing career, grace!
I just worry you're
gonna have regrets
in other aspects of your life.
- Like my
non-existent love life?
I don't think so.
Here.
[Grace grunts]
I don't need any
more reminders of him!
[Grace grumbles]
Delete.
[Emotional guitar music]
♪ After the night was through
♪ I left and still
thinking 'bout you ♪
♪ I had a question or two
♪ I never asked you
♪ headlights on the interstate
♪ I drove slow
I rolled in late ♪
♪ blank stares [Hammering]
- Hey!
No demolition!
[Hammering]
- No demolition.
Just some much-needed repairs.
[Hammering]
- Have a safe flight,
and remember to call
and let me know what they say.
And remember, grace, you
always have a home here.
- I'll call you when I
get back to la, okay?
- I love you, grace. Stay safe.
- I love you too, mom.
[Car starts]
[Curious music]
- I saw a car!
Was she in it?
- You just missed her.
- She's leaving?
Because of me?
- You've gone ahead and
broken Gracie's heart again.
I'd be shocked if she ever
wants to come back home.
- I broke up with Heather.
- A few minutes
too late, it seems.
- Grace kept the pillow?
- She's always clung
onto a piece of your, Sean.
I'm sure she'd love to
have all of you for once.
- I can't believe I lost
my chance with her.
- Love has nothing to
do with chances, Sean.
Aw, Sean, you have a good night.
[Truck starts]
[Intriguing music]
- My cinderella.
[Knocking rapidly]
- Oh, Sean, I
feel badly for you,
but I don't think my
daughter would appreciate me
comforting you on the
night of her breakup.
- What if this doesn't have to
be the night of her breakup?
What if this could be the first
day of her cinderella story?
I have the best idea.
I know this will. Please,
I know this will work.
[Gentle instrumental music]
- Grace, it's my job
to be honest with you,
so that's what I'm gonna be.
A good romance novel,
heck, a good relationship
has lovers that beat the odds,
characters who confront
their biggest fears
and come out on the
other side stronger.
Lyndon and Savannah's
problems disappearing
under the blue moon is...
It's ex machina.
- Do you think it's possible
that maybe you're
interpreting it wrong?
What you're reading
as ex machina
is meant to be read as fate.
True love conquers all.
- What exactly did they conquer?
- The distance that
held them apart.
- Yes, right, so
they move closer
and they're no longer
physically distant.
What about the
emotional distance?
What about lyndon never
replying to her letters?
What about Savannah's
fear of commitment?
- I can add those pages in.
Consider it an epilogue.
- I'm gonna think
of it as a total bust.
- What's this?
- Your severance check.
Good luck, grace.
- But it's a trilogy. What
about the third book?
- Grace, you know,
sometimes an open ending
is more satisfactory
than the wrong ending.
- Um...
Right. Yeah.
- You know, one day you may
wake up to that happy ending,
but until then, maybe
you should stick
with user manuals
and technical writing.
- Um...
Fyi, Danny...
Happy endings don't exist.
[Emotional guitar music]
- I think my ex-wife would
agree with you on that one.
- I've only spent
one day in pediatrics,
but I am certain that's
where I'm supposed to be.
Now, there's something
about working with children
that makes me feel like
I'm making a
difference in the world.
- That sounds so amazing.
- I'm sorry.
I've been going on
and on about myself.
What's it like being a writer?
It's...
Challenging. [Chuckles]
Sometimes I wish I could just...
Disappear into my books.
Can you tell that
from my writing?
- I haven't actually had a
chance to read your book yet.
[Grace laughs]
- That's okay.
It's probably for the best.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, did I say something wrong?
- No, it's not that.
You're perfect, James.
You're the kind of
guy I write books about.
- But that's fiction.
- Exactly.
I'll see you around.
♪ Sometimes
♪ oh but I
♪ I need to be reminded of
♪ what's good what's true
[paper tearing]
♪ You are beautiful again
[Muffled scream]
[Grace sighs]
♪ I'd like to get it over with
[knocking on door]
- Go away!
[Knocking on door]
No one's home!
[Grace cries] [Knocking on door]
I said go away!
Mom?
Broken.
Just like me.
[Knocking on door]
♪ A place where all of
my worries are deceased ♪
♪ never to be mentioned again
- [Sean] Dear grace,
this is the 53rd letter
I won't be sending.
Every day I stay away
is a day you can make
your dreams come true.
You're going be the
most amazing writer.
You've already written the
best love story across my heart.
Love you always, Sean.
[Paper crumples]
- Sean green, I know
you can hear me!
Guess what?
You're too late!
53 letters too late!
[Light piano music]
- This dress will look
better on you than me?
[Knocking on door]
- My turn.
Grace, I know you're a girl
of fairytales and
cinderella stories,
but maybe our
romance isn't that simple.
Maybe our love has
to break convention
for it to be real
outside of your books.
- What are you doing here?
- Winning you back.
Here.
Ask me anything.
- Okay.
Why are you wearing a dress?
- To make you laugh
and maybe let me in. Next.
- Why didn't you tell me
that you were dating Heather?
- I tried, but...
Things are never that simple.
I was hoping you
wouldn't have to find out.
- So there could be
another secret between us?
Like all those letters
you never sent?
- I never sent the letters,
because I was scared
that if I admitted
that I loved you,
you'd come back
to our small town
and leave your dreams behind.
I was scared that I
would distract you
from becoming who
you were meant to be.
- You were never
a distraction, Sean.
You were my muse.
Don't you get that?
- I was scared I...
Wouldn't ever be good
enough for you, grace.
- Sean, you've always been
everything I ever wanted...
And exactly what I needed.
- I've loved you from
the moment I saw you.
And that's never changed.
Please forgive me, grace.
Is it too late?
- The truth is I could have
come home anytime to see you.
I was scared too.
I guess being disappointed
was easier than
taking a risk to get hurt.
And in my imagination,
love was always perfect.
But that's not real life.
- Can we fix it?
- It'll never be
too late for us.
Too bad it's too
late for the ball.
- Then I guess it's a good thing
I already booked
two flights back home.
- Wow!
You were really confident
you were gonna get me back.
- I took a chance and
believed for a change.
Come on!
Let's catch that plane.
[Grace laughing]
- Wait.
- What's wrong?
- Do you mind if
I wear the dress?
[Both laughing]
[Upbeat jazz music]
[Crowd chattering]
- I'll have to later about it.
- This place is amazing,
even more spectacular
than I remember.
- I have something to show you.
- I love it!
We're leaving our Mark.
In the words of grandpa Albert,
if lovers carve their names
on the walls of the mansion,
the blue moon will see
to it that they are reunited.
- I think I lost another bet.
But you kids were right.
Fate works in mysterious
and wonderful ways.
- It wasn't fate.
It was respect and
communication.
- Honesty and forgiveness.
Were finally both all in.
- And ready.
- Well, then I can
guarantee it's a relationship
that's gonna last,
one worth lasting.
- May I have this dance?
- I'd be delighted.
[Grace laughs]
- I think he was talking to me.
- If you think so.
- I heard there was
a young woman
in need of a dance partner.
Now, I've only got 15 minutes
before bed check at the home,
so hate to make this
a dance to remember!
- Okay!
[Upbeat jazz music]
- Sean, there's something
I need to tell you.
- Please don't say you
want me in that dress again.
- Despite how
cute you looked, no.
I...
I lost my publishing contract.
My agents hated my latest novel.
- Grace, I'm so sorry.
- Me too.
- Can you try again
at a new version
now that your muse is back?
- I could write the
best novel in the world
and I don't think he'd
give me a second chance.
- Well, I might know someone
with a large sum of money
who's looking to invest.
It's a bit of a long
shot, but who knows?
The timing might be just right.
- Really?
You think they've
read my novels?
- Read them?
They're your biggest fan.
And they're here tonight.
Do you want me to introduce you?
- Sean, that's amazing!
I love you.
- Say it again.
- I love you.
- Again.
- I love you too, grace.
I'll get you a real engagement
ring, but until then...
Will you marry me?
- You couldn't
stop me if you tried.
[Grace chuckles]
Now you have
lipstick all over you.
- Who's that scary investor?
- Grace, this is Heather.
Heather, grace.
[Curious music]
- Sean?
- Sure, you've gone
to school together.
Maybe you've even
been friends at one point.
But you've never
been business partners.
- What are you talking about?
- You've wanted to
make a name for yourself
ever since your dad got you
tour first set of business cards
in the sixth grade.
- You have money and
business sense but...
Not a stitch of creativity.
And grace, you're all
passion and creativity,
but completely lacking in
practical, commercial skills.
- Sean, what are
you babbling about?
- I think what he's
trying to say is...
I could really use your help.
I'm looking for
someone to invest
in the publication
of my third novel.
- You want that person to be me?
- I would love that.
He's right.
We'd make a good team.
[Heather giggling]
- A toast!
[Glasses clinking]
[Gentle orchestral music]
- There you are.
My beautiful fiancee.
Everything all right?
- Sean. I love you.
And I love this town.
But...
I don't think I can
live here anymore.
- What?
- My career and
my life are in la now.
- You just lost your contract.
- I know.
You're right.
We can make this work.
If you want to stay
here or come with me...
We can make it work this time.
- Grace, this is crazy deja vu.
I can't believe
you're saying this.
- I know, and I'm sorry.
But I've been out here
trying to figure it out and...
I know that if I stay
here, I won't be happy...
And that's gonna hurt us.
Maybe not
immediately, but in time.
Please just come with me.
- I have an old house
i'm renovating that I love.
And I have a job here.
This is where we're
supposed to be.
I can't believe
I'm hearing this.
- Sean-
- no, I need to think.
[Soft piano music]
[Crowd chattering]
- I am such a huge fan of yours!
I can't believe that
I'm finally meeting you!
- That is so sweet.
There you go.
Ester!
- I think it's about time I
get a signed copy of my own.
- Of course.
- If I had known, I would
have had one ready for you.
- Oh, that's all right.
I was hoping to
meet your new Beau.
- He's not here.
- I am so sorry!
- Excuse me, excuse me.
I'm sorry I'm late.
[Cheerful music]
- So this is the man
worth 90,000 words.
[Books tumbling]
I think I'd like
your signature too.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
[Cheerful instrumental music]
♪ Hey.
[Upbeat instrumental music]
♪ On a path to destruction
♪ couldn't care
if I live or die ♪
♪ I drown the pain
that I've created ♪
♪ make amends lord
knows that I've tried ♪
♪ 'cause I'm gone
♪ I'm so gone
♪ been wandering
around but I'm never lost ♪
♪ oh I'm gone
♪ I'm so gone
♪ I've stumbled on the
line that I shouldn't cross ♪
♪ hey
♪ oh oh oh oh
♪ I've been riding all alone
♪ just a victim who
lost everything ♪
♪ it's hard to carry on
♪ I black out to ease the pain
♪ with no one there
to comfort me ♪
♪ and tell me it's okay
♪ just tell me it's okay
♪ I heard you call
me a train wreck ♪
♪ informing me
like I didn't know ♪
♪ try to tell me
what I should do ♪
♪ and I can tell you
where you should go ♪
♪ 'cause I'm gone
♪ I'm so gone