Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
I wish you'd knock.
I did knock.
...is knocking.
Come on Grandpa, I need to clean in here
before taking Diego to school.
You can read your poetry
in the living room.
Come on.
Do you want to take the Rubik's Cube?
Yes.
Let's go, son.
Where is he?
Maybe he forgot.
Do I have to go with him?
Yes, son. He is your dad.
Here he is.
Your role model.
Hi!
What's up, Max?
Hello, Antonio.
How are you, little man?
Hi Dad!
Not a little man any more,
you have grown up a lot...
You're so grown up! Look!
It's cool, right?
It's super cool, Dad.
You're not too old to play
with small cars, right?
No!
It's very cool!
- It has a helmet and the full gear
for an adventure.
- Thanks, Dad.
Cool, little man.
Don't you think this might be too much?
I bought him something simple
for his birthday.
It's only a small car...
...it's really not a big deal.
Besides, it's not that expensive.
I have to leave now.
Remember, try not to give him candy...
...that he needs to brush his teeth,
and is in bed at 8.
What?
Oh María, it's just that...
A job came up.
No, come on! No...
It's a very important recording session
in San Miguel de Allende.
Also, it's important for my reputation!
You have one of those?
Gosh, Max.
How do you manage to be that rude to me
and still make me laugh?
So what do I do? What do I do?
I don't know.
I can't take Diego with me.
I don't know what to do.
But I can't quit either...
...please?
I promise this is the last time
I let you down.
Ok?
Son...
I have to leave.
I'll come get you after
and we'll have a great time...
...and I'll bring something back for you
from my trip.
Thank you.
I love you little man!
See you, Max.
Thank you.
I owe you one.
No, no, you owe me like three hundred!
Let's make it four hundred!
I'll make it up to you later, OK?
Thank you!
Well, I've still got this work trip!
So, what do we do?
Well, I can stay with my great grandpa.
Of course, I can take care of him.
No, no. The two of you alone
are more dangerous
than a monkey with a gun.
I am eighty years old.
Exactly.
Come on, go pack!
I made the card!
I made it!
It’s in Spanish, Mama.
What?
Oh yes, of course.
Why is she laughing?
This English man thought
I translated his book.
That's very funny because
you don't do anything!
I'm a hag!
Careful!
Hey!
Watch your step!
Do you have your eyes stuck
up your butt, dude?
What's up with that guy?
Come on Diego, let's get out.
Help your great grandpa.
Yes, help him, help him.
The car seat!
The seat!
The seat, please!
Yes, just next to it.
Please welcome the author of
El Corazón Sensible...
Henry Copper!
Welcome, Mr Copper.
First I'd like to thank you,
on behalf of everyone here,
for this gift...
...this delicious book.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
I would like to start, if I may,
by asking you...
...how did you get the idea
for this torrid romance?
Experience and imagination.
You must be very imaginative then...
and very experienced!
Of course, when I say this
I'm thinking of one
particular part of the book.
Do you mind if I read it out loud?
You know what? We would love to.
But Mr. Copper is a busy man.
He has many things to do...
novels to write...
OK. OK. I'll just read it quickly.
Just quickly.
Chapter nine, the morning after
Claire meets Martin.
We’ve all read it, what’s the point?
“Every fibre of Claire’s being
was transformed...
...Martin’s powerful desire
had overcome her fear of love.”
You describe the workings of desire,
of lust, so well.
It's incredible.
And best of all it’s like you understand
what it is to be a man and a woman,
sexually possessed.
May I read my favourite part?
Another one? Dear God.
I am going to read THE scene.
"That night he came to her again,
charged like a stallion."
"Claire, he said, we will always long
for each other's touch,
each other's taste,
but it will always be forbidden."
“But tonight let us forget the rules...
...tonight we are unashamed,
we are beasts...
...beasts in the desert heat."
"Claire, he said, tonight...
"Claire. Tonight...
That’s not what it says!
She’s making it up!
Oh so now we're all translators!
She’s a liar!
Yes! Translate it properly!
Yes! Translate it properly, you cow!
Hey, hey... a little respect, no?
I mean, I mean...
Perhaps you would like to
refresh your memory of the text.
But...
What the hell is with this woman?
It's her job...
No, no, I'll read it. I'll read it!
That's better!
What was that all about?
I think your mother is about
to get into trouble.
Pedro! So happy you're here now!
Hi María!
Where were you?
We were just talking, Grandpa.
I'll explain later. Get in! Get in!
Damn English.
Mama, shouldn't you say it's your book?
It seems really unfair.
Welcome to the entire
history of women, Diego.
Oh my God!
It’s you! Henry Copper!
I love your book!
You're so handsome!
My next guest is the author
of the literary sensation of the year,
The Sensible Heart.
I love this book!
It makes me tingle inside!
And his translator, María Rodeo.
Rodríguez.
Of course. The Usurper!
I just changed everything.
I'm sorry, what?
Yes, I mean...
...I changed everything
from English to Spanish...
...making sure to keep
the brilliant, amazing words
of Mr. Copper.
You must feel very lucky?
You have no idea.
Yes
Always ask for a hardback.
More money for the author... and me.
Your book has filled my heart with love
and my body with desire.
You!
Mr. Copper, I never understood men
before I read this book.
Now my bed is never empty!
My partner and I dress
as your characters for...
...our intimate moments.
Here, here. Look!
Thank you.
No, no. Stop, stop.
For Miguelito.
What the hell?
What's up, María?
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
What are YOU doing here?
You said you were in San Miguel.
Ah, yes. I did go.
We had the recording session,
and I did really well!
I'm sorry, I know I should have told you.
But that's how these things are...
...they invited me on a tour so here I am.
Where is Diego?
Where do you think? Sleeping.
Let's see. You left my son alone?
You really are unbelievable.
Here!
Do you want to know what love is?
Love is being lied to.
Love leaves you stranded...
...alone, and penniless ...
...with a grandfather and a child
who won't let you even breathe...
Diego, listen to me...
No, no I didn't mean it!
I don’t speak English.
Don't speak...
One moment.
I wish...
...to buy...
...some hens.
Your mother...
...is...
...ill.
Your mother...
...is...
...angry.
But...
...I love you.
She...
...loves you.
The woman...
...is crazy...
...but she loves you...
...because
...you are...
...her husband.
Her man.
She is angry...
...with me because...
...I am...
...a spoon.
Please...
...show me...
...your towels.
I have broken my bottom.
You understand?
Very good, Pedro, very good.
Mama, you didn't say he was funny!
Where were you?
Can you forgive me, son?
I'm sorry my love.
Can I have a hug?
Do you have the TV remote? Turn it up!
Who is this guy?
Thomas the chauffeur!
Who are you?
Goodnight.
On the count of three, say "Pedro!"
Let's go!
Come on son, get in the car.
Expecting someone?
For you and me.
But I'm working, Antonio.
María, the place is empty.
Come on, sit with me!
Ok, fine.
So where's your British friend?
Ah! So you're watching me?
I'm not watching you,
it's just social media!
Yes, you're watching me!
No! You open social media
and photos start to show up...
Anyway. This is why I came.
For Diego and for you.
From the gig.
Thank you.
I'll take it off what you owe me.
It's not that much!
You're wearing the shirt
you had on when I first met you.
And the truth is...
...you look just as beautiful and as sexy.
Thanks for reminding me
I have no new clothes.
María, how are you?
You know you can count on me, right?
You can trust me.
We're a family.
Have you ever...
Have you ever had a week where...
...where everything made sense?
As if...
...as if your life was just
as you dreamt it?
And then suddenly...
...you come back to reality and...
...it's over.
Nevermind, forget it.
Pretend I didn't say anything.
I understand.
I understand perfectly.
We've all been through moments like these.
Come on!
Why don't we go somewhere else?
This place is a little depressing,
isn't it?
We could go somewhere else and talk.
Talk?
Though not at my house because
my roommates are having another party...
...and you know how it gets.
Ok. Let's go to mine.
But just to talk.
Just to talk.
I'll come back for breakfast.
OK.
I'll call you.
Sure.
No, no, Pedro, no!
I've helped you already, I'm done!
But María, you'd only do half the work!
Yes, and he would be getting
all the credit.
Yes, but it's his name that will
sell the book.
Credit doesn’t pay your bills.
Just think about it, and then say yes.
You can use my house.
We both know that man
can't do it without you.
Good morning, María Fernanda Rodríguez.
It's good to see you again.
Good morning, Mr. Copper.
Goodbye!
How are you?
Hey! Here you go!
Thank you!
Happy Carnival!
How are you, Antonio?
How are you?
I get it now. I get it.
Everything you talked about in the bar...
...is because you met this
English man, right?
So what? You thought that your life was
going to suddenly become
marvelous and fantastic?
María, you really think this guy is going
to make you a writer?
No, I don't think so,
because I already am a writer, Antonio.
Yes, I am.
María, be realistic. He is
a writer. You work in a bar.
That's it. That's reality,
whether you like it or not.
I'm not saying it's fair...
...but life isn't fair
and you know that very well.
I don't understand what the hell you want!
You do know. Stop playing,
you're not a teenager anymore, María.
It's your turn to
take care of Diego on Saturday. Show up!
No, no. If you want I can
pick him up right now...
...so you can party!
Good morning.
See you later.
Hello!
That son of a bitch!
Mama! Come with me! Quickly!
What are you doing here, son?
No, you have to see this!
Hurry!
Wait!
Wait, Diego!
Hey! What?
That's your name.
Wow.
He put your name on it!
Yes.
You wrote it, right?
Then you should be there!
It's today!
Let's go!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Please welcome, Mr. Henry Copper!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your warm reception.
I don't deserve it...
...even though I am pretty sexy...
Yes, he is!
...for an Englishman.
I mean it...
...you should see some of us.
Generally, we are awful.
Yeah, sometimes they stink.
Thank you.
I knew it. I knew it!
It's her!
Hello.
What did he say?
He said he's an idiot.
Yes!
He's an idiot.
What are you doing here?
According to them,
it's a lovely story, but...
Sorry?
Who are you?
Sorry.
I'm her husband, she's my wife!
It's the husband!
Through common law.
It’s not the same thing!
This is better than a telenovela!
And him?
Who is he?
Have you asked yourselves?
That Englishman has come here
and stolen my woman.
Are we in the stone age or what?
María, what happened?
I thought I could have you back...
...and my son...
...and the love of my family.
And then, I open this shit
and I read page 125.
"They made...
...love like two dragons...
...exploding in the flames of a volcano."
Hey, spoilers!
No, no it's not a spoiler.
It's the trash that Henry Copper
wrote about my woman.
Yes, yes, very sexy.
Sexy? This nerd? No, no...
Believe me, Antonio...
...Henry knows a lot about sexy.
You think because you play the trumpet,
and lounge about all day...
...and never button up your shirt,
that you’re a man?
Is that what being a man is?
Staying out, never being home,
and never being there?
That's not true, María.
I've always been there for you.
A few days ago when you were sad,
where did you cry, huh?
Here! On my shoulder!
Stop him!
I'm going to kill you!
Let me go!
Yeah, get out!
Tie him up and throw him
straight into the trash!
I think my water just broke.
It's coming!
María, what a pleasure!
So, what a great book!
Very impressive!