EAST JAPAN RAILWAY COMPANY
MORIOKA SHINKANSEN ROLLING STOCK CENTER
AOMORI BRANCH OFFICE
This is a passenger car.
Please make your way to the back.
Welcome to the Aomori
Shinkansen Stock Center.
Wow!
Cool!
-This is where we temporarily park
-This way.
-The Tohoku-shinkansen train cars.
-Wow.
-So nice.
-When the Shinkansen opened between
-Tokyo and Osaka in nineteen sixty-four,
-This is crazy!
It was
the fastest train in the world
and was called the Dream Super Express.
This E-Five series Shinkansen travels
at a maximum speed of 320 kilometers per
-hour.
-Some parts are made of aluminum alloy,
and the axles are hollow in
order to help reduce weight.
It's the newest model that connects
Tokyo and Shin-Hakodate-Hokuto in four
-hours.
-It may not seem like it,
but this is a coupling mechanism.
Oooh! Whoa!
You'll be boarding a train car
just like this one later.
Okay everyone, please watch your step.
Alright.
Does anyone have any questions
for Mister Takaichi?
This way, please.
So, what made you,, uh…
wanna become a train conductor?
Why not a train driver?
-Good question.
-Yeah.
Many different types of people
ride the Shinkansen.
There are always
a lot of students in school trips,
like you.
And then those students might
come along a few years later and
board the Shinkansen to go
watch their best friend get married.
He's talking about me, y'know?
-Definitely!
-One passenger might be going
on a family trip, while another
is coming back from a business one.
Strangers to each other,
boarding the train for different purposes,
yet all of them heading
in the same direction.
Once they arrive,
they're back to being strangers.
There is something nice about the way
it feels to watch all that.
I don't really get it but
it sounds kinda deep.
Let's get a group photo in
front of the Shinkansen.
Here, here.
-Okay, gather up over here.
-Okay.
-"Cheese!"
-Ready? Say, "Cheese!"
SHIN-AOMORI STATION,
AOMORI CITY, AOMORI PREFECTURE
Mister Takaichi.
How's it going?
Hi.
-I'll be joining you today.
-Great.
Should be easy.
How was the student tour earlier?
Kids don't wanna hear what an
old man like me has to say.
I'm a young guy, why not have me do it?
"My mission is to deliver
each
and every one of my passengers
safely to their destination every day."
Right?
That's not something you
should make light of.
This is a serious job, you know.
I'm sorry.
But you know,
-I agree with you, actually.
-What?
I'll talk to the district
manager about you, Fujii.
-Thank you so much!
-But you know I don't call the shots,
right?
This train will stop at Ninohe,
Iwate-Numakunai,
Morioka, Kitakami,
Ichinoseki, Furukawa, Sendai, Omiya…
The train on Track Fourteen,
departing at three seventeen p.m.,
is the Hayabusa Number Sixty,
bound for Tokyo.
This train will stop at Hachinohe,
Morioka, Sendai,
Omiya
and Ueno,
before arriving at our destination, Tokyo.
Once the train arrives,
the red gate of the safety
barrier will open.
Please wait behind the safety barrier
until the train comes to a full stop.
Thank you for your patience.
The train arriving on Track Twelve is
the Hayabusa Number Eight for Tokyo,
departing at seven forty-one a.m. This
train will be in a ten-car formation.
-The doors are opening.
-Side light,
on.
-We're getting on, everybody!
-This train will stop at Morioka,
Sendai
and Omiya
before arriving at our destination,
Tokyo, thank you.
Thank you for taking
a JR East train today.
This is a Hayabusa train
on the Tohoku-shinkansen
Line, bound for Tokyo.
All seats on this train
require a reservation.
Non-reserved seating is not available.
The next stop is Hachinohe.
Smoking is not allowed anywhere on this
train, including the restrooms and end
sections of the cars.
Listen, what if we just deleted
this part about the energy policy?
-Thank you for your cooperation.
-No, come on.
Everyone's really tuned in on the
subject right now because of the crazy
energy prices. It's a great
chance to get support, alright?
When using your cellphones, please
go to the end sections near the doors
Okay,
so as not to disturb
other passengers. Thank you.
You're right.
Welcome on board the Tohoku-shinkansen.
This is the Hayabusa
Super Express bound for Tokyo
Sorry…
-with stops at Hachinohe,
-Tsk.
Morioka, Sendai,
Omiya,
-Ah.
-"Temo,"
-and Tokyo.
-You're Todoroki, right?
"The Unemployed Rich Man"?
-All seats on this train are reserved.
-Oh.
The tickets for standing is valid for
the train and car shown on the ticket.
Thank you.
Please do not smoke in this train.
-What do you think you're doing?
-Oh. Sorry, ma'am.
"Passenger items are permitted on
trains and its installations."
Oh! Hello there!
I know her!
Mommy! It's the Sugar Mama politician!
-You can't just say that, honey. Shh.
-"Oh no--"
You know,
that politician from that scandal.
JR EAST SHINKANSEN
GENERAL OPERATION CONTROL CENTER
Unload it at Shin-Aomori Station,
-copy that.
-There's an out-of-service train there…
Right.
So let's try to plot it.
Copy that.
Yes.
OK a sick passenger?
-Male.
-Medical emergency on
thirty twenty-five B!
He's conscious but has a severe headache.
Headache?
Let's get an ambulance there,
just in case.
How long to Morioka?
Twenty-five minutes.
Have them stop at Mizusawaesashi.
That's the closest station to it.
Copy that.
Sixty-one B's gonna have to
wait at Ichinoseki for a bit.
-I'll let the station know.
-Send an ambulance to Mizusawaesashi.
Sure.
-"I'll be right back, okay?"
-This is Transport Dispatcher.
This is Itsuki,
-Transport Dispatcher.
-There was a medical emergency on train
thirty twenty five B, so if you could send
an ambulance to Mizusawaesashi, please.
Please plan on making an unscheduled
stop at Mizusawaesashi, copy?
Repeater signal, "On."
-"I think this is it right here."
-Let's go man! We'll miss it!
"Oh, dang it, we're gonna miss
it, dude! Run! Let's go already."
-"Go, go, go, go!"
-Excuse me! We're getting on, man! Wait!
-We're coming, we're coming!
-Please stand clear of the closing doors.
We're coming, wait a sec!
Hurry up, man, come on!
Departing Shin-Aomori Station
at three seventeen p.m.
Time, check.
Boarding, check.
-Please stand clear of the closing doors.
-Closing doors.
Doors are closing.
Side lights, off.
Signal clear.
Time check,
done.
Doors
closed.
Brakes
released.
The safety barrier gates are closing.
Please stand clear of the closing gates.
-Bye bye!
-"Bye, train!"
"Bye bye train!"
-Bye bye!
Okay.
On time.
Fifty sixty B has departed on time.
Good morning.
And thank you for traveling
with JR East today.
This is the Hayabusa Number Sixty,
bound for Tokyo.
This train is scheduled to
make the following stops:
-Hachinohe,
-I'm a big fan, can I
-three forty-one p.m.
-have your autograph?
Oh.
-Morioka,
-Sure, yeah.
Four eleven p.m.
Sendai,
four fifty-six p.m.
Omiya,
six-oh-seven p.m.
-Ueno,
-"It gets on your fingers."
-"Yeah, I know, right?"
-six twenty-six p.m.
We will arrive at our destination,
Tokyo Station, at six
thirty-two p.m. Thank you.
-Bummed there were no bears.
-Yeah, man. No bears at all.
TOKYO
EAST JAPAN RAILWAY COMPANY
HEADQUARTERS BUILDING
Good morning, and thank you
for calling JR East Call Center.
If it's a matter of articulation, we can
definitely make sure to train them better
-so it doesn't happen next time, yes.
-My name is Noguchi how can I help you.
We apologize for the inconvenience,
and "thank you so much for calling."
Hello there and good morning.
Thank you for calling
the JR East Call Center.
"Thank you so much for bringing this to
our attention, ma'am. We really appreciate
-it."
-I'm Miyashita, how can I help you today?
There's a bomb
on the Hayabusa Number Sixty
going to Tokyo.
Sir, I'm sorry but…
would you mind repeating that from
the beginning, if that's okay?
The bomb will go off if the train's speed
drops below one hundred kilometers
per hour.
To show this is real,
the same type of bomb
was planted
on Freight train twenty seventy-four
of the Aoemori Railway Line.
What's wrong?
That one is set to go off if the speed
drops below five kilometers per hour.
A bomb?
-He hung up, sir.
-W-Wait.
He did?
I PLANTED A BOMB.
AOMORI-HIGASHI STATION,
AOEMORI RAILWAY LINE
Hi.
Aomori-Higashi Station.
Huh?
A bomb?
What?
Is it a prank?
Wait, huh…
The speed's not dropping below
five kilometers per hour so--
Do the cops and the feds know yet?
They do, sir.
A joint HQ
is being set up at the TMPD.
We're sending people there immediately.
JR EAST SHINKANSEN
GENERAL MANAGEMENT DEPARTMENT
Just like the bomber said.
As soon as the speed dropped below five,
it exploded.
Exactly like the one-oh-nine case.
Call the Control Center.
Yes, sir.
Under a certain speed, a
bomb goes off?
If this is true,
then the Hayabusa Number Sixty will
have no choice but to keep running.
Where is it now?
How fast is it going?
It's about to reach Shichinohe-Towada at
two hundred and fifty-seven kilometers
per hour.
Tell them to keep their
speed above one hundred.
I'm heading over there right now,
but you can handle any minor
decisions until I get there.
Yes, sir.
The was the General Manager,
you heard what he said, right?
Fifty sixty B is going
to turn the ATC off,
and go through Hachinohe at one hundred
and twenty kilometers per hour.
It shouldn't go too fast.
We have to buy time,
prepare ourselves for the worst.
All Hokkaido and Tohoku shinkansen
services are suspended.
Hokuriku and Joetsu lines
will turn back at Omiya.
Evacuate all trains now.
All trains, sir?
We need to clear the tracks
for Fifty sixty B.
Yoshimura told me to handle
minor decisions for now.
-That's not a, uh…
-"Minor"?
Nothing's more important than
the safety of our passengers.
Now go!
Yes, sir!
"Thirty ten B…"
SHICHINOHE TOWN, KAMIKITA COUNTY,
AOMORI PREFECTURE 633 KM TO TOKYO.
Fifty sixty B,
this is Transport Dispatcher, Nagano.
Yes. This is Matsumoto,
fifty sixty B's driver.
Stay calm and listen carefully.
A few minutes ago,
we got a call from an anonymous individual
who said they planted a bomb on
the Hayabusa sixty.
What?
Uhh- This is…
some kind of… drill, right?
This is not a drill.
Okay, copy that.
We'll inspect the train
once we stop at Hachinohe.
He said it'll go off
if the train's speed drops bellow
one hundred kilometers per hour.
So I can't stop the train?
They didn't find anything
during the inspection.
Are you sure it's not a prank?
I'll have to stop at
Tokyo Station no matter what--
This is Kasagi,
Commander of the Control Center.
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say.
Please disable the ATC,
maintain a speed of 120 kilometers
per hour and pass through Hachinohe.
We're doing everything we can to fix this.
Okay, sir. Copy that.
ATC
is off.
ATC DISABLED
It's off.
Check.
The ATC is off.
Since the freight train exploded,
they probably weren't lying about the
bomb on the Fifty sixty B either.
And so what should I tell the passengers?
Tell the passengers you're unable to stop
at Hachinohe due to technical issues.
So then…
nothing about the bomb?
Do not disclose that.
We need to make sure no one panics.
OIRASE TOWN, KAMIKITA COUNTY,
AOMORI PREFECTURE 612 KM TO TOKYO
Oh hi, how are ya?
You got ice cream?
Absolutely, sir.
-Ice cream, coming right up, ok?
-"That one's so good, right?"
Also…
Can I
-have your Instagram?
-He actually asked her!
Sir, I'm afraid this
is not compatible with Instagram.
-Rejected!
-Wasn't gonna happen, Takei!
Takei's just trying
to get Aoi's attention!
-"Please, stop it."
-Stop it, that's gross.
He is, right?
That's what I thought, too.
Right, Yuzuki?
Huh?
What were you saying?
Wait, you didn't know?
Takei told Aoi he liked her.
What! Really?
So he just got a rejection,
and he's trying to pretend
-like everything's fine.
I can hear you.
-And you know you're wrong.
-Come on, shut up and
get out of here, gosh!
-Sit down, Takei.
-She's so cruel!
Yeah, just give up already!
Come on, don't let it get to you, Aoi.
He really said that? That's crazy!
Can I have your attention, please.
-We are now approaching Hachinohe Station.
-"You think you hurt his feelings?"
However, due to technical
difficulties, this train will not be
-stopping at Hachinohe Station.
-"I hope I did, because he's a jerk."
We apologize to all passengers
who were affected by this change,
I will now repeat this announcement.
Due to
technical difficulties,
this train will not be stopping
at Hachinohe Station, thank you.
Uh--
Do you think something's wrong?
Well…
as long as it stops in Morioka,
it should be fine, right?
Here it is.
Okay, let's go one by one.
Okay.
Twenty thirty B is at
Kitakami, track one, going southbound.
Twenty thirty B,
passengers getting off at Kitakami.
Thirty twenty-five B is
already at Morioka's Stock Center.
Okay.
Next. Sixty-six B for
Sendai, track one, northbound.
Okay, tell Sixty-six B's driver
to stop at Mizusawaesashi Station.
-I'll take Omiya-dai.
-Okay.
Got it. Next, fifty-one fifty-two B,
Ichinoseki. Track one, southbound.
Fifty-one fifty-two B, the
passengers got off at Ichinoseki Station.
Ichinoseki. Got it.
Lastly, ninety-one sixty-six B,
Furukawa. Track one. Southbound.
All routes to Sendai have been cleared.
-Ninety-one sixty-six B, clear to arrive.
-Alright. Where's fifty sixty B?
Got it.
-The TMPD is here.
-It's--
Kawagoe, Special Investigation Team.
Yoshimura, General Manager, JR East.
Kasagi, Commander of the Control Center.
I heard about the case.
-Is the bomber calling here?
-Yes.
All of his calls will be forwarded
to our first line here.
Fifty sixty B is almost at Hachinohe.
Can you check their ATC again?
They won't be stopping.
-Okay.
-ATC?
Automatic Train Control system.
All Shinkansen trains are
equipped with a system that
slows them down automatically
if they exceed the speed limit.
The speed limit at most stations
is Seventy Five Kilometers per hour.
So the system's off?
Yes, of course.
Unless it doesn't work properly.
Fifty sixty B just left
the Takadate Tunnel.
It's three kilometers away
from Hachinohe Station.
The ATC is off.
Check.
HACHINOHE CITY,
AOMORI PREFECTURE 595 KM TO TOKYO
-Your attention, please.
-That way. Towards the
The Hayabusa Number Sixty train bound
for Tokyo will not be stopping at
ticket gates, please.
-Hachinohe Station today.
-"If you could please head
towards the ticket gates."
Passengers booked on this train should
return to the ticket gates.
Your attention, please.
The Hayabusa Number Sixty
train bound for Tokyo,
will not be stopping at
Hachinohe Station today.
Honey, they're not stopping.
-I wonder why they're not braking.
-Get out of the way!
Ha?
Are you okay?
Fifty sixty B just passed
through Hachinohe.
The ATC did not engage.
Incoming call.
Incoming call,
line one.
This is Yoshimura, JR East.
So if you're willing to
pay a deactivation fee,
I'll tell you how to defuse the
bomb on the Hayabusa sixty.
The fee is one hundred billion yen.
What?
One hundred billion?
There's no way we can
get that kinda money on such short notice.
I don't want JR to pay it,
I want the citizens of Japan to pay it.
-Come on, the citizens of--?
-Hello?
Divide that amount
among everyone in Japan,
-Yes.
-Already?
-It's a thousand yen a person.
-Can you have them wait?
You can figure out how
to collect the money.
Only rule is one hundred billion
yen from the people of Japan.
That's it.
This goes far beyond
what we can deal with.
At this scale,
the government should get involved.
We do not negotiate with terrorists!
My name is Sasaki,
Special Advisor to the Prime Minister.
-I'm JR East's…
-No need for introductions,
Shinnosuke Yoshimura, General Manager.
This case needs to be handled
within a very short time frame,
I'm sure you know that.
Lieutenant Kawagoe,
I saw you there.
Yoshimura. Let's get right to it.
I want you to warn the
passengers about the bomb on the train.
What?
But, if the passengers hear about what's
going on, things could get out of control.
Of course I know that,
Control Center Commander, Yuichi Kasagi.
At this speed, the train will reach Tokyo
in five and a half hours.
We need to let everyone
know so we increase
our chances of finding out who's doing it.
Oh and by the way,
this is a government decision, am I clear?
NINOHE CITY,
IWATE PREFECTURE 573 KM TO TOKYO
Okay, I undestand.
Thank you.
They want us
to tell them everything?
But everyone will panic.
There's no way.
Sure, easy for them to say when
they're not the ones in danger like w--
-Fujii,
-stop!
Look I'm scared too, okay?
But the worst thing that can happen
is for any of us to panic right now.
Can I have your attention, please.
According to the latest information,
there's a security threat
on the Hayabusa Sixty.
An explosive device has
been placed on the train.
According to the latest information,
there's a security threat on the Hayabusa
Sixty. An explosive device
has been placed on the train.
Everyone shut up!
-Oh no.
-This device is set to detonate
-An explosive device? What?
-if the train's speed ever drops
-below a certain threshold.
-Are you kidding?! this is crazy!
Since we were unable
to confirm our safety,
we passed through Hachinohe Station.
-What happened?
-The police are
It's okay, it's okay.
Currently investigating to
try and resolve the situation.
-We should do something.
-Go find out what's happening!
Is this train going to… explode?
-JR East is working closely with them.
-They're talking about explosions.
Panic in a crowded train car can
become extremely dangerous.
To ensure everyone's safety,
we ask that all passengers
stay calm and follow the instructions
of the crew.
I repeat.
-An explosive device has been planted
-It has to be a prank or something.
On this Hayabusa Number Sixty train.
Didn't you guys
check this train before
leaving the station?
-Or am I crazy?
-Yes-No--
We conduct safety inspections
before every departure.
However, if
it was planted after the inspection,
it would be hard to detect.
-Is that so?
-What? Why? That makes no sense at all!
I think you just didn't do your job well.
-We're sorry for the inconvenience.
-You're kidding, right?
It's like you don't care
about your passengers at all.
He's right! I've got places to be, man!
-Things to do!
-I think
this could be a good way to shift
the focus off the scandal.
Again, we're sorry for the inconvenience.
-Yes, we completely apologize.
-We're very sorry.
Listen up, everyone!
Listen up!
Let's all calm down a bit, shall we?
The real bad guy
is the criminal who did this, right?
There's no use in venting about
it to our conductor here, am I--
-Hey!
-Sir, please!
I'm not venting here at all.
I'm actually
doing them a favor right now.
I'm helping them do a better job.
Back the hell off, Sugar Mama!
That's right! Who do you think you are,
Sugar Mama? You tell her!
Yeah, you slut!
What, are you so stupid that
you can't see how panicking will just
-make everyone around you
-"Miss Kagami."
-Calm down,
-panic as well, you piece of shit?
Calm down.
-Don't you!
-"Piece of shit"?
-Please calm down!
-"That's right!"
-Get off me!
-"Oh, shit."
Whoa!
-What the hell are you doing!
-Fujii!
Calm down!
Calm down now!
-"S--"
-You don't have to
protect someone like her.
Every passenger
is equally important to me.
It's my job to ensure the safety
of every single passenger.
So please…
-if you could all return to your seats.
-What the hell, man!
Please!
I promise I'll let you
know if I hear anything.
Please!
Sir, please.
Excuse me. Please.
That way.
Back to your seats.
You handled that very well,
Mister Takaichi.
If you need anything, just let me know.
I'm in car number nine.
YUKO KAGAMI TOWARDS A THOUGHTFUL
AND KINDER SOCIETY I AM YOUR REFLECTION.
Thank you.
We're now interrupting our regular program
to bring you live coverage
of Chief Cabinet
Secretary Suwa's press briefing.
Uh…
At around three twenty-five p.m. today,
JR East received news that
the Hayabusa number sixty
was under serious threat after a,
bomb had been planted on the train.
In line with the
Japanese government's
fundamental policy
of not negotiating with terrorists,
we are focused on apprehending
the perpetrator,
all while making
passenger safety our top priority.
The Prime Minister,
who is in the U.S. on an official visit,
was immediately briefed on the matter.
He has ordered us
to keep the public informed
with timely and precise updates.
Incoming call, line one.
This is Yoshimura.
Why didn't you mention
the hundred billion yen?
You shouldn't waste your time,
you should let the people
know as soon as possible.
-The Hayabusa Number Sixty--
-This is the Special
Advisor to the Prime Minister.
I'm sure you're aware
that we have no precedent
for anything like this.
We have no framework in place to
collect funds from every citizen.
We have no legal basis for it either.
The Legislation Bureau's…
Oh.
Could you trace it?
The Prime Minister
-was immediately briefed on the matter.
-What? Uh…
-We are investigating
-"Framework", right.
Along with the local governments
and police departments
to quickly understand the
full scope of this case
and to provide--
The bomb on the Shinkansen Hayabusa Number
Sixty will detonate if its speed
drops below one hundred
kilometers per hour.
The deactivation fee is
a hundred billion yen.
The bomb will detonate if the
speed drops below one hundred.
The deactivation fee is
a hundred billion yen.
The bomb will detonate if the
speed drops below one hundred.
Whoa!
-What the hell?
-The deactivation fee is
one hundred billion yen.
-What?
-"What's going on?"
What?
The deactivation fee is
one hundred billion yen.
The bomb will detonate if the
speed drops below one hundred.
-Huh?
-The deactivation fee is
one hundred billion yen.
The bomb will detonate if the
speed drops below one hundred.
The deactivation fee is
one hundred billion yen.
The bomb will detonate if the
speed drops below one hundred.
The deactivation fee is
one hundred billion yen.
-That's Aomori's Stock Center.
-Yes. No mistaking it.
The deactivation fee is
one hundred billion yen.
-Check the servers,
-Find the account
-and analyze the video.
-The bomb will detonate if the
-speed drops below one hundred.
-Why is the file
for the one-oh-nine case in
the seventies taking so long?
The deactivation fee is
one hundred billion yen.
I'm on it!
The bomb will detonate if the
speed drops below one hundred.
The deactivation fee is
a hundred billion yen.
-"Oh my goodness."
-"The bomb is real?"
Oh!
-Yeah, that's what they're saying.
-What's going on?
-It's a bomb!
-Huh?
-I heard it's a bomb!
-A bomb?!
"Yeah, it's a--"
One hunded billion? That's impossible!
What the hell are you saying?
-"You really want us to die?"
-I'm saying it's impossible!
Shut up!
-No you shut up you, diva.
-Sit your ass down!
Please wait!
Wait!
No, give me that!
If we don't do something, we're dead!
We're all gonna die!
It's all going to shit!
-No, it's too dangerous, ma'am.
-I have to do something, Hayashi!
-Wait, hey, calm down, okay?
-I don't care! We're all gonna die!
I can't take this anymore.
-I wanna go home.
-The bomb will detonate if the
speed drops below one hundred.
The deactivation fee is
one hundred billion yen.
The bomb will detonate if the
speed drops below one hundred.
IWATE TOWN, IWATE COUNTY,
IWATE PREFECTURE 531 KM TO TOKYO
I sent the video to the Stock Center.
They think the bomb was planted
on car four, on the
front left of the chassis.
Transport dispatcher.
There could
-be more than one bomb, though, right?
-Right.
Commander.
What is it?
Train thirty thirty-two B is
stopped just past Morioka
at switch number fifty-one.
It's ahead of the Hayabusa and unable
to move due to a malfunction.
What's the cause?
Can we move it?
Apparently a bird collided with the
pantograph, so it short circuited.
It's going to take at least an
hour to get it running again.
Move the Hayabusa to
the northbound track.
Not possible.
Thirty twenty-seven B is currently
on the northbound track.
So they're going to collide!
3032B BOUND FOR TOKYO
STOPPED ON SOUTHBOUND TRACK
3027B BOUND FOR SHIN-HAKODATE-HOKUTO
AND AKITA ON THE NORTHBOUND TRACK
FIFTY SIXTY B BOUND FOR TOKYO
ON THE SOUTHBOUND MAIN LINE
Fifty sixty B is now eleven
kilometers from Morioka.
Five and a half minutes.
How long until Thirty twenty-seven
B passes Morioka?
Just under six minutes.
We have to do it.
We route it northbound
on the main line and have it
run in a reverse direction
just before Morioka at switch sixty-three.
Instruct Thirty twenty-seven
B to increase its speed.
Yes, sir!
-I'll notify Morioka Station!
-Yes, please.
Can you connect the short one to that?
Reverse direction?
Yes.
This is the train that's stopped,
the thirty thirty-two B.
This is the Fifty sixty B,
the Hayabusa Number Sixty.
And this is the Thirty twenty-seven B,
the Hayabusa Komachi twenty-seven,
which is heading towards it.
The fifty-sixty B will switch
to the northbound track here.
But it's almost immediately after
the other one
passes the switch.
…Switch it northbound.
That's what we'll do.
-What?
-Trust me.
Slow your speed to 105
kilometers per hour.
We need to buy as much time as possible,
every second counts.
But
entering a switch going that fast is
-far too dangerous!
-There's no other option here!
Reduce your speed to 105 kilometers
per hour immediately!
Okay, copy that.
120,
119,
118,
115,
112,
110, 109,
108,
105.
Apparently it's supposed to shake a lot.
We have to make sure the
passengers are seated.
Don't let the passengers
see you looking like that.
Got it?
O-- Okay.
We are approaching a switch
and the train will shake quite a bit.
So everyone remain seated for your safety.
And please keep your heads, down.
-Please put your seats back in place.
-Put the seats back, kids!
-We expect the train to shake quite a bit.
-Yuzuki,
-So, please remain seated!
-don't leave me, okay?
If you could please remain seated,
keep your heads down,
for your own safety.
Stay low.
-Keep your heads down.
-Sir--
Sir, uh-- why did you say that?
Is the bomb going off?
No. It's to prevent it from going off.
Don't worry.
Please just follow our instructions
for now, okay?
For your own safety, please remain seated.
Thirty twenty-seven B is
now approaching Morioka
at 320 kilometers per hour.
Good. Maintain that speed.
Fifty sixty B,
slow down to 102!
We need every last second.
103…
102…
MORIOKA CITY, IWATE PREFECTURE
The train thirty
twenty-seven B will soon be arriving.
Keep going, please.
Keep going forward.
-They'll help at the ticket gates.
-"Yes, that way, please."
-Sir, please stand back!
-The train thirty
-twenty-seven B will soon be arriving.
-Stand back!
The train's here!
DEPUTY HEAD, RAILWAY OPERATIONS,
MORIOKA BRANCH OFFICE
Thirty twenty-seven B
just passed Morioka Station.
Fifty sixty B is now approaching
the switch!
Thirty twenty-seven B
is passing the switch!
Reverse switch sixty-three.
Now!
It's dropping.
Faster!
This is the Thirty twenty-seven B driver.
We've just made an emergency stop.
The conductor's checking the situation.
This is the Fifty sixty B driver.
Our first car collided with them.
There was a big impact,
but so far the train seems
to be running fine.
Got it.
We've confirmed that as well.
Increase the speed to 120,
and move back to the southbound
line using switch number fifty-three.
Copy that.
You need it?
Takaichi,
what was that impact?
There was a slight collision
with an oncoming train, but
we made it safely through the switch
and the train's running without problems.
So don't worry.
Well done, Mister Takaichi.
Sure.
Just doing my job. Excuse me.
-Good thing she's on board.
-It's okay now.
-Thank god she's here.
-Having a member of the
Parliament on board's definitely a relief.
All she did was sit there, c'mon.
Was everything okay there?
I…
thought I was about to die.
Don't tempt fate, you know?
I'll go see what's going on.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I have a, uh-- favor to ask.
Oh!
Uhh- Hi folks!
Sorry to disturb you during
these hard times.
This is… To Do Rock It!
-My name is Mitsuru Todoroki.
-Fujii…
You know the author of the best-selling
book "Unemployed Rich Man"
does that ring a bell.
That's me. I'm the author.
The bomber's video.
You all saw it, yeah?
-I did.
-Yeah.
He mentioned a deactivation fee of one
hundred billion yen from the entire
-nation.
-He's even more handsome in person.
As far as I can tell, no one has made
any real moves to deal with this up to
-this point, right?
-His clothes look super expensive.
I wouldn't expect less from him.
You know, at a time like this,
we're all hoping the government's going
to take the lead and act fast to help us.
However, a huge ship requires a great
deal of time and effort
to make even a slight change of course.
For that reason,
I've created a website so that
we can start collecting money.
I've posted all the details
on social media,
so please check it out.
-You heard that, didn't you?
-Let's spread the word
-about it as much as we can.
-So cool.
-Look, right here.
-This guy, right?
You know, we're the ones stuck in this
train right now, so it's only fair we ask
-the country to chip in.
-I don't know how to do that!
Hey,
-what if we all make a video…
-Right.
Hey, guys.
Let's make a video too.
Post it on Insta
or whatever. Right?
-"Oh… yeah that's a good idea!"
-In this day and age, we have
everything we need to look after
ourselves.
Come on, where should we post that?
We can't just rely on the government
or local authorities.
-Let's turn despair into hope.
-Okay?
Let's do it!
Alright?
Let's make a miracle happen.
To Do Rock It!
Thank you for listening, y'all.
Excuse me.
Coming through. Sorry.
Sorry, coming through.
Why…?
We're students at Taiyo High School.
My name's Aoi.
We're currently on board
the Hayabusa Number Sixty.
-Don't give up on us, alright?
-We need your help.
"Please help us." "Donate as much as you
can." "Please don't give up on us."
Wait…
-Oh, it's right here.
-Where is it?
-Oh, right.
-Oh, this is it!
Noice--
We're on board the Hayabusa
Number Sixty right now.
-We heard someone's trying to blow it up.
-Yeah, yeah. Oh, can I have some water?
Sure.
-Thank you so much.
Here, this is it. Check this out.
#I_SENT_MONEY
I'm Fukuda from the Daily Nitto.
A civilian has already set
up a donation website,
but there's still no word on
the government's response.
What's your take on this?
We are aware of the existence
of this website.
We learned about it through
news reports earlier.
However,
this is not in line with our policy of
not negotiating with the
demands of terrorists.
We're considering the possibility of
closing this website.
So you're abandoning the
people in the train?
Do you have a clear strategy for
handling this situation yet, sir?
-Yeah, do you, sir?
-What're your thoughts?
How will the government
tackle this problem?
What else do you have in mind?
-What authorities have you consulted?
-Please let us know your thoughts!
At around twelve forty-five p.m.
on August thirtieth nineteen seventy-five,
there was a sudden explosion.
I was shocked by that huge
cloud of smoke in the sky.
An investigation was launched
immediately and a joint task force was
-created.
-You're not doing anything!
Based on everything we've seen so far
and the information we've
gathered up to this point,
one thing is clear—
the perpetrators used dynamite components.
The most important question:
Who planted the bombs and
what was their motive?
Acts of terrorism such as this
one should never be tolerated.
The type of bombs used,
the warning explosion
to support the threat,
the deactivation fee…
It's a carbon copy
of the "one-oh-nine case"
in nineteen seventy-five.
I'm sure there's a connection
between them.
There has to be.
The only difference is the
amount they're asking for.
Even factoring in inflation,
one hundred billion yen is roughly
seventy times higher.
Telling us to 'figure out' how to
gather that ridiculous sum is just
plain insulting.
Mister Todoroki,
can you hear me?
-Let's go with Camera three.
-Yes.
-Keep it on Camera three.
-Seems like the
government wasn't particularly
happy with your website.
Yeah, I mean, I'm making them look bad,
so of course they wouldn't like it.
It's like my website is worse
than terrorism, huh?
I don't get why they're criticizing it.
They should be thanking me
for taking definitive action.
There are
concerns about whether the money
is being handled transparently.
I've just added a meter,
so now everyone can see how much
money has been gathered so far.
Well,
that doesn't help if their issue is
with me specifically being behind this.
Look at that reaction.
-That's good, switch to camera four.
-Okay, camera four. Get that reaction.
As you can see, I'm a hostage,
so I can't just run off with the cash.
Just think of it as like a subscription to
an exciting show and throw in some money!
To Do Rock It!
Mitsuru Todoroki, out!
Todoroki-san…
I think a more levelheaded approach would
be in everyone's best interest, right?
Handing over a hundred
billion as they demand?
That's madness!
On a weighted average,
Hayabusa Sixty's passengers have about
forty-five years left to live. See?
If they all spend around three hundred
million in their lifetime,
then every passenger's death equates to
a loss of one hundred sixty million.
Let's multiply that by three
hundred and fifty passengers.
Fifty six billion yen.
-Ah.
-Factor in lost revenue, compensation,
damages and whatnot, and suddenly, one
hundred billion
doesn't seem so far-fetched.
The stance against negotiating
with terrorists
exists to prevent further acts of terror.
You don't get it, do you?
You're just being impulsive and selfish.
All that talk about principles--
can't you see we're about to die?
By the way, Kagami-san…
why don't you use your power as
a member of the Parliament to
give a little boost to
our collective funding.
We need to find some kind of synergy here.
Synergy? What're you, nuts?
Why don't you stop trying--
You're aware we don't have much time, huh?
The sooner you start helping us collect,
the better our chances are.
If we're being reasonable about it.
KITAKAMI CITY,
IWATE PREFECTURE 453 KM TO TOKYO
KINTEKI GOOD LUCK, SEARCHING TARGET
You're Goto, from "Go
To Chopper Tours", right?
Go-chan.
Did you know your picture's a trending
topic on social media right now?
-Check it out.
-Sure you knew.
Tons of folks are saying
that they won't pay the
deactivation fee because you're on board.
You guys know him?
-It's Goto.
-You know?
That Goto.
But if you apologize on
camera, maybe that could change.
That's right.
-Stop it.
-Yeah.
-Do it.
You could admit that it was your fault
that a poorly maintained tourist
helicopter crashed into a
school and killed eight people.
Just say you're sorry, dude.
Oh, he's being violent. This
is bad. Bad, bad, bad, bad.
You think I'm gonna say I'm sorry just
because you assholes are telling me to?
Wait, wait…
-Stop recording! Stop recording!
-More people are gonna die because of you!
Just say you're sorry, dude!
Get on your knees and apologize!
On your knees! There you go, buddy.
Subscribe to our channel.
-And don't forget to donate.
-Thank you.
Kinteki Good Luck.
Get off me!
Out of the way!
What's wrong with you,
dude? Just say you're sorry!
Aren't you the one in charge?
Shouldn't you be intervening here?
You're the one who's a big hero.
You intervene.
Drop kick!
Hey!
Sorry,
-excuse me.
-Please stop.
Sorry.
-Calm down.
-Get away, please.
-Calm down, please.
-Everyone calm down.
-Please.
Are you okay, sir?
Let me off.
I wanna get off this train!
Takaichi!
Are you okay, sir?
Oh, no. Don't… What're you--
Hey, don't run away!
Get off me!
I'm getting off this train!
Please!
Press it!
-Press the button!
-Don't press it!
Don't press it!
Please! Now!
Please!
Do it!
There's nothing to worry about.
That button only alerts the driver,
it doesn't stop the train.
Matsumoto,
this is Conductor Takaichi.
A passenger pressed the
button by mistake during a fight.
Oh man, I thought that was it for us.
Just keep the train running.
I'm sorry.
Coming through.
I'm sorry, excuse me.
May I have
your attention, please?
Is there a doctor on board?
If you are a doctor,
please come to Car number five.
Fifty sixty B
is passing the Four Forty Kilometer point!
He's okay, it's not life-threatening.
Just let him rest for a while.
Thank you very much.
What's the point
of saving a man like him?
What are you talking about?
We could die because of this guy.
You heard what they said about him, right?
And so saving him is pointless?
It doesn't make sense, though.
What if we can't raise enough
money for the ransom
and we die because of
him? That's absolutely crazy!
Delivering our passengers
safely to their destinations.
That's the whole point of us being here.
I'm going to the driver's cab.
When the SOS button was pressed,
I almost stopped the train, y'know?
Yeah, that's not funny.
Want some water?
Not really, but thanks.
I can't go to the bathroom,
so why risk it, right?
You're right.
Is there anything else you need?
A cheeseburger with fries
and an apple pie, thanks.
I'll get that once we're outta here.
I won't stop the train even if I die.
So don't you worry.
That's not funny, either.
Oh, Takaichi.
Uhh- here.
MORIOKA SHINKANSEN CREW DEPOT
FIRST-LINE MANAGER, TAKAICHI,
SPECIAL ASSISTANCE STAFF
Thank you.
Are you okay, by the way?
Uhh--
I'm sorry, sir.
You got in trouble with the driver because
I pressed that button.
Hey, don't be sorry.
Everyone was stunned when you pressed it,
which helped defuse the situation.
You saved us.
Thank you.
Uh-Why did you save a guy like him? Uhh…
What, made you do it?
A guy like him?
A person everybody hates.
And who's probably better off dead.
Funny-- Someone just asked me that.
And what was your answer?
That it wasn't a big deal.
Because it's your duty, right?
Ensuring his safety is my duty.
That doesn't mean it's always simple,
that much I can say.
But truth is,
I wanted to save him,
I'm not lying to you.
I'm sorry, that was, uh…
a weird thing to ask.
You want to uncouple the last
car of the Hayabusa Sixty?
While it's running?
Is that gonna even possible?
Shinkansen trains automatically apply the
brakes if cars become uncoupled while
in motion.
But it is technically possible
if we disable that system.
First,
we'll have another train run parallel
to the Hayabusa Sixty to provide them
with the tools they'll need for the job.
We'll open the crew cabin's
door and transfer
the tools from one train to the
other using ropes and pulleys.
Once they pull all the
tools into the train,
the tech guys at the stock center
will guide them over the phone
on how to disconnect both cars,
physically and electrically.
Once the last car is uncoupled,
a rescue train without a front car will
catch up to the Hayabusa sixty and
connect to it's second-to-last car.
Wait a minute…
So you're gonna move
the passengers from here
to here,
and then the rescue train will just leave?
That's right, yes.
And you have to do all that while going
120 kilometers per hour without using
the emergency brakes?
Are you absolutely sure this
is the best plan we've got?
I don't know if it's the best.
But the question is,
are we doing it or not?
We have a responsibility.
ICHINOSEKI CITY,
IWATE PREFECTURE 410 KM TO TOKYO
He's awake.
I gave him some water
and made sure he was okay.
Great,
thank you.
What's next?
What's the plan now?
We should rest in shifts--
Hello,
this is the Fifty sixty B's conductor.
This is Kasagi. Open your tablet.
Copy that.
We're carrying out the rescue plan now.
Check the document I've just shared.
Okay, got it.
I'll open it up now.
Next is the rescue plan.
ANNOUNCEMENT
May I have your attention, please?
We're about to start
the rescue operation.
Please remain seated
-until further instructions from the crew.
-Did you hear that?
Also,
If any qualified electricians or
similarly trained individuals are aboard
Everyone, be quiet!
Please make your way to the conductor's
cabin in Car Nine.
-What's going on here?
-I repeat.
Honey,
-it's finally time for you to help people.
-Attention, all passengers.
Huh?
-We're about to start
-Listen, they need an electrician.
The rescue operation.
They need an electrician.
The last car has to be
uncoupled before the
Fifty sixty B passes the Stock Center.
Transport dispatchers,
switch to the group call from now on.
Copy.
Situation?
Ninety twelve B is now approaching
Fifty sixty B.
Ninety twelve B will
move to the northbound
line at switch fifty-three.
Fifty sixty B is forty four kilometers
from the Stock Center. Travel time,
twenty-two minutes.
Can I have your attention?
We're going to start the rescue
operation, and this car will be uncoupled.
Finally.
-Now I'm going to need you follow me
-What?
-What's going on?
-To the car in front us,
-please. Right this way.
-What's wrong?
Hey!
Unfortunately you'll have
to leave your luggage behind.
Wait a sec- Who in the what now?
Here it comes!
Ninety twelve B is here.
Our speed
is fixed at 120.
This is Ninety twelve B.
Just keep your speed fixed
at one hundred twenty.
We'll adjust if needed.
A little slower.
Slower, slower.
Fix it.
Open the crew door.
-Go ahead, Ninomiya.
-Okay, I'm on it.
-Oh!
-Careful!
Launching the guide rope.
-Step back!
-Direction, check.
-Pressure, check.
-Launch!
Pick it up!
Yep!
-Yes, I got it!
-They're pulling it.
Tie the guide rope!
Okay, it's done!
Great.
-You can send it!
-Okay!
Okay!
Lift the cargo.
Okay,
-keep it at that height.
-Pull it!
Okay.
The first batch is being
transferred, cargo units one and two.
Yeah.
-Take this.
-Good, keep going.
Okay!
Eighteen minutes to the Stock Center.
That's it.
Keep pulling.
Almost done. Keep it up!
Easy, now!
Are you okay?
Yes!
The first shipment's here!
Second shipment. Pipes and cargo three.
Let's go!
-Okay!
-Come on!
Yeah!
Keep pulling!
-Pull it!
-Twenty-nine
kilometers to the stock center.
-I got it!
-Alright!
Now for the third and last shipment.
-That's it. Keep going.
-Watch out, the uncoupler's really heavy!
Fifty sixty B will soon
pass Furukawa Station.
Fourteen minutes to the Stock Center.
Here it comes.
Everything okay?
Everything's okay.
We have all the gear.
Thank you!
This is Ninety twelve B.
We're all set.
We're praying for Fifty sixty B's safety.
Copy that.
Let's connect them to the engineers.
We have twelve minutes to
complete the uncoupling.
SHINKANSEN ROLLING STOCK
MAINTENANCE CENTER
The uncoupling process for Hayabusa Sixty
is about to begin at assembly plant
spot six.
It's connected. Go ahead.
Let's begin.
-Okay.
Open the wall panel next to the
left-side door in car eight.
Okay.
Do you see a row of wires labeled BRK?
I see it.
-That's the line for the emergency brakes.
-Hand me a screwdriver.
That's how we're going to disable them.
Shinohara, come here, please.
Okay.
Here we go…
Preparations
for the transfer to the rescue
train are in motion.
To ensure a smooth
process and avoid accidents,
I gotta take this at least.
We kindly request that you
leave your baggage behind.
They don't make these anymore.
-We'll begin the transfer shortly.
-I was saving for so long to get it.
Seniors aged sixty-five and older, as
well as kids under the age of ten years
old, will be given
priority during the transfer.
-"I need it."
-"Please,
just let me take it. It's no big deal."
Please head to Car Number Eight in an
orderly manner as soon as you're ready.
Come on, you heard him leave-- no,
leave it here, leave it here, leave it
The transfer to the
rescue car will begin shortly.
Here.
Only important stuff…
You don't need that!
To ensure a smooth
process and avoid accidents,
Only the important stuff!
We kindly request that you
leave your baggage behind.
Connect that cable to terminal
B Zero on port seventeen.
Okay.
NO. 17 TERMINAL
Good!
It worked, the power's on.
The final step is:
disconnect cable number sixteen.
Careful now, Mister Shinohara.
If you do it wrong,
the emergency brakes will activate.
We don't want that to happen.
NO. 16 TERMINAL
Speed and car status, all clear.
The brakes
have been disabled.
-We did it!
-Great job!
We just killed the brakes,
no need to cheer.
It's only the beginning.
Let's get to the uncoupling process.
Shinohara,
you handle the cables and connections.
And Takaichi, you handle the shock
absorber in the conductor's cabin.
Let's go.
Yeah.
-Okay, I'll handle the shock absorber.
-I got it.
Here we go.
-There it is.
-Got it.
-I'm holding it.
-Okay, okay.
Okay.
That's it.
-I'm passing it.
-Great.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, Jesus.
-Ready, go!
It's off.
-Give it to me.
-Good.
Next, please.
-Here.
-Thanks.
-Be careful, honey!
-I'm going down.
-Take it easy.
-Okay.
Here,
gotcha!
Less than ten kilometers.
Five minutes to go.
Good, you got it out.
This one, too.
It's all disconnected.
Now, we're going to disconnect
the coupler.
-Help me with the decoupling device.
-Okay!
Roger that.
Done.
-Put the peaks facing downwards, go.
-Right here, get it in
-there, there you go.
-Nice!
Four minutes to the Stock Center.
-One, two…
You did it!
-Takaichi!
-Oh, watch out!
Takaichi!
Come here.
-Oh, no!
-Come here quickly! Ahh!
Car nine is slowing down.
That means
the cars are uncoupled.
-Jump, jump!
-Now!
-Takaichi!
-Hurry!
"Come on!"
-I gotcha!
-Are you okay?
How's the power?
Still working, sir.
So the bomb in car four wasn't
the only one after all.
Call the Stock Center.
Itsuki, the train!
Transport dispatcher to
ninety fourteen B,
you are clear to depart.
ATC disabled.
Check.
Reverser, check.
Rescue train ninety fourteen B, departing.
FIRST-LINE MANAGER,
THE STOCK CENTER
The rescue train is leaving
the stock center.
It's heading towards Tokyo.
Speed is increasing. Wind pressure's fine.
You're in the clear to keep going.
Roger.
To the rescue team,
stay sharp out there. No reckless moves.
Copy that.
This is Mukai, in charge of Omiya-dai.
I'll take it from here.
Roger that.
The rescue train
is about to enter the main line.
Fifty sixty B is running on the main line.
Fifty sixty B is in sight.
We're catching up.
Wait until you pass Sendai Station,
and then get close to the Fifty sixty B.
We're coming to you live from
a rooftop near Sendai Station.
At this moment, the
Tohoku Shinkansen lines…
Hey,
there it is.
Ah,
it's here!
The Hayabusa Sixty!
The Hayabusa Sixty, with bombs reportedly
planted on board, is now passing in front
of Sendai Station
It's the Hayabusa Sixty. It's still
running nonstop at over one hundred
kilometers per hour.
-And… Oh,
-Another Shinkansen train is running
right behind it, practically chasing the
Hayabusa Sixty.
Another Shinkansen train is
running on the same track.
It looks like it's going backwards,
and apparently faster
than the fifty sixty B.
It's almost catching up
to the Hayabusa Sixty!
Fifty sixty B has passed
through the Shiga Tunnel.
This is Fifty sixty B.
Right now,
I'm still fixed at one twenty.
I'm at one hundred thirty
kilometers per hour.
I'll slow down now.
Uhh-
The distance, about sixty meters.
Fifty.
Fourty.
Thirty.
Twenty-five.
This is the rescue train,
we slowed down to one twenty one.
Get ready to link up soon.
The pipes are ready!
The footplate is unlocked!
Get ready, everyone!
I'm gonna start measuring the distance.
Watch the winds!
Taking off the shield!
I'm going to the edge.
Hold it!
I got him!
Okay, got it!
Ten meters to go.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Lift the footplate!
-Four.
-Got it.
-There.
-Three.
Slowly let it go.
Slowly, slowly!
-Slower!
-Keep the tension!
Slower!
-Come on, hold it!
-Two.
Slower! Slower!
One.
-Yes, we got it!
-We're holding it!
Zero!
Great!
We did it!
-"We did it!"
-They're connected!
-Great!
-Get the ropes ready.
Let's get started.
Okay.
The distance between the ninety fourteen B
and the Hayabusa sixty is
zero.
We did it!
You're all doing a great job!
Yeah and we're just getting started.
Let's keep going.
Sure!
Give them the hooks first.
-Be careful, okay?
-Sure.
Here,
-take this hook.
-Hold it.
-Here, a hook.
-Here. Take it. Hold that.
Okay, I got it.
-I'm ready over here!
-Next one.
-Okay, go ahead.
-I got it.
Great.
-Okay, one more coming.
-Keep passing them!
Thank you.
And the ropes.
-Pass it!
-Tie it over there.
Pass it to me.
-The pipes!
-Okay!
-Insert them into there.
-I'll tie it up.
This one's all set, we got it!
Let's get them all through!
-Yeah!
-Excuse me,
coming through.
Sorry.
Let's go! Now!
Okay, time to go!
One at time, alright?
Okay,
take it easy, don't rush.
-Make sure you hold onto the ropes.
-Okay!
Watch your step.
-Hold on to the ropes!
-Slowly.
Okay, come over here,
sweetie. You're doing great. Come on.
There's room for everyone,
okay? No need to rush.
-Women and children first.
-Let them through!
-Make sure you hold onto the ropes!
-Okay, stay calm. Don't worry.
Hey, wait.
Wait! It's scary, I just need a
hand! Keep holding onto the rails!
-Come here.
-Hey, don't-- don't grab--
-don't grab me, what are you doing?
-Thank you.
Wait for me! Hey I said wait!
Stay calm!
-Don't rush, take it easy, go slow.
-Don't look down.
-I can't. I-- I-- I don't wanna die.
-You just have to walk.
-Make sure you hold onto the ropes!
-Right now? Seriously?
-Don't look down.
-Keep going, please.
-Move into the train!
-Okay, come on.
-Take your time!
-Okay,
walk slowly.
-Make sure you hold onto the ropes!
-Hold onto the ropes.
Here. Good!
Two hundred passengers
are already on the rescue train.
We just have to keep up that pace.
This is a special
Tohoku-shinkansen rescue train.
I guess this website
Once all the passengers have transfered
into this train, we will uncouple from the
Hayabusa Sixty and
return to Sendai Station.
-Is useless now, huh? Well…
-I guess it was more useful than
what the politicians did?
Since many passengers will be moving,
please fill every seat, starting from Car
Number Ten at the rear of the train.
Miss Kagami. I got a text from Chief
Secretary Suwa with some very kind words,
did you get it too?
-Let me see.
-To keep things moving smoothly,
I'm glad you're safe, Kagami. Your
presence on the Hayabusa Sixty helped tone
-avoid stopping in the gangways or aisles.
-Sure.
Down the public's
criticism of the government.
-Amazing, isn't it?
-You cunning old man.
Coming through! Please make
way, we're coming through!
What's wrong?
What happened?
That helicopter guy did this.
-I'm dying.
-We were trying to help him
cross, but he got a golf club
and hit him in the face with it.
-Come on, don't hit me dude.
-Oh, sorry.
Hey,
calm down!
Stop!
Calm down, sir.
I want to die!
This is my chance!
Just let me die!
-Miss Ichikawa.
-Huh?
-Yuzuki isn't here.
-Please remain seated until
-all passengers are aboard.
-She isn't?! Since when?
I don't know.
-I'll go find her, ok?
-Uh-huh.
-You wait here.
-Okay.
Stay seated!
Yuzuki.
-I hope she's not having an attack.
-Wa-Wait. Hey! Hang on!
The Sugar Mama politician went too.
To keep things moving smoothly,
avoid stopping in the gangways or aisles.
She's a hero.
Please remain seated until
all passengers are aboard.
Oh! You're going too, Todoroki?
Huh?
It won't be long before all
passengers from the Hayabusa Sixty are
-safely transferred.
-Huh? Huh? What?
Once all the passengers have transfered
into this train, we will uncouple from the
Hayabusa Sixty and
return to Sendai Station.
Good for you, Mister Todoroki.
You're very brave.
-Excuse me.
-Oh!
-I'm just--
-It's dangerous!
Don't go back!
-My student's there!
-We're about to disconnect the car.
It's dangerous, get back here!
No! Hey, I'm telling you it's dangerous!
-Hey!
-Let me die, please!
I beg you!
Get off me!
You should've heard what they all said.
-Hey, wait.
-The victim's families want me
-to die, I'm better off dead!
-Listen. Calm down!
I wanna die!
Stop this nonsense!
Stop this right now.
You just don't know when to give up,
do you?
Shut your mouth, you bitch!
You know what?
That accident was all your fault.
You politicians
and your regulations and laws
that screw us business owners!
Blaming politics for everything.
You're a coward!
I'm sick of you complaining
about this shit.
If you were a real man,
you'd know how to tough it out!
Anyway…
you can still start over.
I know how ruthless people can be.
I know that all too well.
If you give it enough time,
people will forget any scandal.
Even someone like me…
I'm sure people will vote for me again.
One seventeen…
One sixteen… The speed is…
decreasing!
Is the ATC on?
-It's not, it's still disabled!
-It's Ninety fourteen B!
The rescue train's emergency brakes are
working.
-Sorry,
-Are you okay?
Sorry. Excuse me.
Ma'am!
I have to find Yuzuki.
Fujii,
-take them to the rescue train.
-Got it.
Let's get you up, now.
What? Hey,
they need help.
-Thank you so much.
-No problem.
Watch out.
Follow me, this way!
Let's go, Miss Kagami.
Oh!
What are you doing here?
I don't know, actually.
-What?
-Hey. Let's-- Let's go, come on.
-This is bad.
-Okay.
Here.
I really don't.
The brakes.
Can you disable them?
I can't!
Please!
-Oh, no!
-We have to uncouple it right now!
Can you…
Can you remove it?
Oh, look out!
-Are you okay?
-Careful.
-Careful, Totsuka.
-I can't remove the
wires, they got entangled!
A little more.
We're almost there.
What is this?!
Why?
Why?!
Step back! It's too dangerous!
-Move back!
-Whoa!
You can't use this.
"It's too dangerous!"
It's dangerous, you could die!
Step back!
Totsuka, get outta there!
-It's too dangerous!
-If it keeps slowing down like this,
both trains will suffer from the
explosion!
We didn't evacuate passengers
to this train for nothing!
-It's going to crash! Get inside!
-Look out!
-Bring him in!
-Come on!
Come on!
-Hurry up!
Are you all right?
Yeah, thanks.
Was that an explosion just now?
No.
An explosion would've
derailed the train.
TSUTOMU ONODERA
Yuzuki!
What were you doing?
Everyone's in the rescue train.
-Let's just go to the back for now.
-Okay.
Oh…
-Here.
-Thanks.
Fujii…
No…
No way…
SHIROISHI 2
SHIGA
SHIROISHI-ZAO
Fifty sixty B's back to seventy five.
The rescue train's running
without problems, sir.
According to the report
from Ninety fourteen B,
we rescued three hundred and forty people.
One crew member
and three hundred and thirty
nine passengers, commander.
The remaining
nine people,
are three
crew members
-and six passengers.
-Yes!
We did it!
We just have to do the same thing again!
Unfortunately,
we can't bypass the circuit twice,
the train's not built for that.
So it's impossible to run
the same operation again.
-Can't you make it work come on?!
-Even if we could,
we don't have enough time to
repeat the same operation now.
I need an estimate of the damages
if it explodes in the urban area!
Assuming an explosion as big as the one
we saw were to happen on every train car,
they would derail,
and it's likely that many of the cars
would break through the barriers…
We know for sure the damage
will be massive.
Tokyo Station's in the
heart of the capital
the whole city would suffer immensely.
SHIROISHI-ZAO STATION
286 KM TO TOKYO
Hey.
What are we gonna do now?
Do they have another plan? Do you know?
No one called me yet.
And what about the bomber?
Apparently,
they haven't called in the past two hours.
It's
not going up at anymore.
It's not really my fault, you know?
I mean,
there are only nine of us left, right?
No one else is gonna bother
to donate anything now.
What if…
they end up running out of ideas?
Well, I'll tell you one thing,
for the government…
if there's no chance of
disarming the bombs,
then letting this train reach
Tokyo Station is not an option.
That's for sure.
What?
Can you imagine the damage if
it explodes at Tokyo Station?
They'll never let that happen.
W-- w- w- wait, d- d- do you mean that…
they might force this train to stop
before it reaches Tokyo Station?
Is that wh- what you're --?
I'm sure there's still
something that can be done.
We just need to find some kind of
synergy to make it work.
Right?
You know what? To hell with synergy.
Huh?
-Um…
-Take it easy.
Can they
really do that?
Forcing this
train to stop, is that--
Is that even…?
Takaichi.
Technically speaking…
they can.
But don't worry about it.
They're doing their best to--
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna go call my dad.
She's a kid,
look at her. We can't let her die.
If only we could keep running
through and not stop at Tokyo Station…
That's impossible. You
know that, don't you?
It's the end of the line,
the train has to stop.
I mean, it's a given.
Mhm.
TOKYO STATION
TO TOWNS AND TO PEOPLE.
WHOOSH, WE CONNECT!
But what if they're connected?
KUNIMI TOWN, DATE DISTRICT,
FUKUSHIMA PREFECTURE 269 KM TO TOKYO
We have two and a half hours.
Are you implying
that there's a chance you'll resort to
your alternative plan if we don't
think of anything else?
Alternative plan?
You mean…
you're thinking of stopping
the Fifty sixty B?
There are crew members…
passengers inside that train,
and they need us!
I get how you feel, I mean it.
But there are literally millions of people
who depend on the Shinkansen trains
to work.
This is politics, we act fast and
not stall until the worst happens. You
-understand?!
-How dare you treat human lives like that!
What is going on here.
You're all talk, but
you clearly don't care.
Don't do that!
-These are real lives!
-Calm down,
-calm down!
-You think it's easy for me?
Stop!
-Huh?
-Stop,
stop!
Transport Dispat--
General Commander.
It's the conductor on Fifty sixty B.
This is Kasagi.
Huh?
You wanna connect the train directly
to the Tokaido Shinkansen line?
Wait you're saying the tracks…
-aren't actually connected.
-The Tohoku-shinkansen and the Tokaido
Shinkansen lines are only about five
meters apart at Tokyo Station.
I we connect those railroads,
we can keep the fifty sixty B running
to Kagoshima-Chuo station.
We can still make it if
we start right away.
We need your permission.
Two and a half hours to go, huh?
Sasaki.
Please let us do it!
Make sure you finish it in time.
I'll figure out how to get a permit.
Thank you!
Let's see if we can provide an
E-seven-type train compatible with fifties
-and sixties.
-Let's get a track
-maintenance vehicle out!
-Copy that, sir!
Tokyo-dai,
connect with the Tokyo Stock Center.
Omiya-dai,
connect with the Omiya Tech Center.
Set up a joint task force!
Breaking news on the Hayabusa Sixty case.
Cars nine and ten have exploded near
Rifu Town in Miyagi District.
Fortunately, there were no passengers
nor crew members onboard.
No injuries have been reported
among passengers
or local residents so far.
I repeat.
Cars nine and ten have exploded,
but fortunately
there were no passengers
or crew members onboard.
No injuries have been reported
among passengers or local residents.
Yuzuki. Do you know how
many times I called you?
Oh my.
-This is still "so scary for all of us"--
-I'm very sorry,
Dad.
So, uh…
Are you on board
Number Sixty?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
I thought so…
Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
Mhm.
It's all good.
What?
What do you mean "all good"?
Yes.
Thank you, I'm okay.
Dad.
Yes.
Thank you, I'm okay.
Yuzuki.
I know what this is.
This is revenge.
Whoever was left from back then
must've found new allies
and they're out for revenge on me.
Those jerks.
To hell with them.
I'm gonna find every last one of them and
kill them all, I'm telling you!
Never gonna happen, dude.
What?
What did you say to me?
I said…
it's never gonna happen.
An old fart like you, killing the bomber?
No way in hell.
You
just
called me--
Did you forget that I'm your father?
-You show me some respect!
-You'll never kill the
bomber, and you know it.
'Cause you know what?
Truth is
I'm the bomber.
What?
I guess you don't wanna believe
thats true, do you?
I did it.
I planted the bombs.
I've been hearing you brag nonstop
for years about how "put a bullet in
that bomber's head", it just--
makes me wanna put a
bullet in my own head.
So I decided to plant my own bombs.
I know it, I'm sure you know it, too:
that bomber blew himself up.
You didn't kill him.
He just didn't wanna be thrown in jail,
so, he chose to die with honor.
I think he's way more honorable than you.
Are you out of your mind?
What the hell did you just say?
Koga is more honorable
than me? How dare you.
That's a load of shit.
You're way out of line!
I'll never forgive you for
for saying that.
How can a snotty kid like
you make bombs anyway?
Enough with your stupid jokes.
I'm not joking at all.
Why don't you just…
turn around and see for yourself?
What the hell is this?
Yuzuki.
Incoming call.
Incoming call, line one.
This is Yoshimura.
I'll tell you how to defuse the bombs.
I'm sorry, who…
is this?
Yuzuki Onodera.
I'm the one who planted bombs
on the Hayabusa train.
You gotta be kidding…
Yuzuki Onodera?
Are you on board the Hayabusa
Sixty right now?
Yes.
Did you
really do it?
Why would you plant bombs on
the very train you're on?
I just killed my father
with the same kinda bombs I used here.
This is not about the money, is it?
What the hell do you want?
I already got what I wanted.
My dad is gone,
and I got to see the sight
I was hoping for.
So, I'll tell you how to defuse the bombs.
Alright.
So tell me.
The bombs will deactivate on their own
if one of these passengers takes my life.
I have a chronic illness,
so I have a small heart monitor
implanted in my chest.
If I die and my heart monitor stops,
an app on my phone emits a signal
which deactivates the bombs.
That's how it works.
How do we know you're… telling the truth?
Hello?
Hello!
Damn it!
The Kanagawa Fire Department just reported
that a bombing occurred in Shibusawa,
Hadano City, about five minutes ago.
It matches Tsutomu Onodera's
current address.
Did you really do it?
Is it true that
they'll automatically deactivate
if-- you die?
There's only one way to find out,
don't you think, Todoroki?
We're working with crews
from various stations,
so let's stay organized and be
mindful of the adjacent tracks.
Okay, let's do a quick roll call.
Right side?
-Ready!
-Left side?
-Front side?
-Ready!
-Standby!
Yes, sir!
Hello?
This is the on-site team.
Yeah.
And you're sure
we'll get the permit, right?
Okay.
Okay, copy that.
I trust you.
Okay.
Let's get to work!
Yes, sir!
All right everyone, let's go!
-Take your places!
-Yes, sir!
Okay!
-Connect me to JR Tokai!
-How does it look?
It's gotta be two feet
closer to Shinagawa.
Got it,
Put these away for now.
That's not our priority.
-I'm on it!
-Fifty sixty B's ETA is nine-oh-four p.m.
Okay, they're moving the
truck. You guide it, okay?
Sounds good, let's set the course.
I need some more over here!
Keep it coming!
-Service cart, coming through!
-Here you go.
Watch out behind you!
Take that to the Shinagawa side, stat.
Watch your step.
Go ahead.
They need some help over there!
How does it look?
JR Tokai's crew is coming over as well.
Let us know if HQ needs anything from us.
One, two!
They told me
they started working on extending
the tracks minutes ago.
You think they
can finish it on such short notice?
No idea.
We just have to trust them
and hope for the best.
Uh-
Mm-
By the way,
if this plan fails…
w-
what's gonna happen to us?
What if
I do it?
I'm the least likely to
get in trouble over it.
You know…
Oh…
Th-- That's right.
You're right.
And yeah, if you do it,
you'll be saving eight people, you know?
That even balances out the
chopper crash.
-Yeah?
-Balances out?
What do you mean by that?
Because, you know,
the accident killed eight people,
didn't it?
It's a net zero.
Uh-huh.
You're fucking crazy.
Huh?
That's right.
You're fucking crazy.
What the hell is your problem anyway, huh?
Hey. J-
Just think about it, will you?
Actually, shouldn't it
generally be the politicians' job
to make ruthless
decisions in cases like this?
Uh--
You don't know shit about politics,
asshole!
-Hey!
-You don't know shit about it!
Please!
-Calm down!
-Let go!
-Hayashi!
-Let me go!
-Calm down, guys, please.
-You're tearing my clothes. Come on,
-Hayashi, cut it out!
-this is expensive.
-Stop it! Please, stop it!
-Hayashi!
-This is a high-end cardigan.
-You're a stuck-up piece of shit!
Calm down!
Stop it!
-Stop it! Come on!
-You have no right to
talk shit about politics!
-Come on! Please!
-Get off me, damn it!
Hayashi! Enough!
-Calm down!
-He started it! It's all his fault!
-Just try to calm down.
-Hayashi!
Stop it!
-You old fucker!
-Calm down!
-Please stop!
-I'm gonna sue your ass when
-we're outta here, you'll see!
-Please just calm down!
-I'm gonna take your ass to court!
-Hayashi! Cut it out!
-Hey!
-Go to hell!
-You're not getting away with this!
-Shut up!
Stuck-up piece of shit.
Stop!
Yuzuki Onodera's mother passed
away nine years ago.
We talked to the neighbors,
and they told us they started hearing a
lot of yelling from the house after that.
And it turns that Sutomu Onodera
is linked
to the "one-oh-nine case."
In fact,
he was one of the cops on the scene when
they tried to catch one of the bombers.
But then the bomber blew himself up.
I guess the higher-ups back then thought
that might make them look bad.
So they turned him into a hero
by spreading the story that he shot and
killed the bomber in self-defense.
And then,
Onodera actually started
boasting about it and taking
credit for it later.
"The Shinkansen is still
here today because
of me"…
And other things like that.
I reached out to Yuzuki Onodera's doctor.
She does have a heart monitor
and a chronic illness,
so she wasn't lying about that.
And I reached out
to the cyber crime guys,
and apparently you can
link a bomb detonator to
an app on your phone.
So that's probably true, too.
Manufacturing explosives,
planting them underneath the trains…
It's hard to
believe she did all this by herself.
I bet there's a collaborator somewhere.
Can I
have a word with you, Yuzuki?
What is it?
Is there…
anything I can do for you, Yuzuki?
You can kill me, I'd love that.
Other than that.
If… you're going through something and just
need to talk it out, if
that'd make you feel better, then…
Miss Ichikawa.
You knew about me, right?
About my family and all.
That's why you've always been suspicious
of me, keeping an eye on me all the time,
right?
Checking to see if I fit in
and making sure I'm not causing trouble.
And then when you realized everything
was okay, you felt relieved, right?
Are you saying this is my fault?
This isn't just one person's fault.
Everyone clings to this
illusion of normalcy
with their happy little lies,
it's just so stupid.
And I had to force myself
to keep up the act,
just so everyone else could feel better.
So they could have the life they wanted.
That's why…
I decided to shatter
that dumb illusion,
and see just how far I
could poison everyone.
People crying,
screaming that they don't wanna die,
lashing out,
turning on each other…
I just wanted to see everyone be
real for once and drop the act.
I'm happy now.
I got to see that look on you.
This account belongs to Yuzuki Onodera,
apparently.
"Symbols, symbols, symbols.
I don't get how people don't go crazy."
"The roaring sound of silence.
The abyss
staring back at me."
"Lies and asphalt.
I just want to tear it all away."
FOLLOW 31 POSTS 1 FOLLOWER 0 FOLLOWING
This
is her last post as of now.
"Destroying the illusion of normalcy"?
Look,
I found something else.
1 LIKE FEBRUARY 8
LIKE KEISODO75 KEISOUDO FOLLOW
They've been texting each other
a lot for a little while now.
They even had a conversation
about explosives as well.
KEISODO75:
"I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO, BUT I CAN."
YUZUKI: "I LONG FOR A STRONG POWER
LIKE BOMBS. BECAUSE I'M WEAK."
KEISODO75:
"I REALLY UNDERSTAND HOW YOU FEEL."
"An ugly world full of lies
and hypocrisy"…
So this guy got in touch with her first,
huh?
Do you know who he is?
Yeah, I do.
He's in his fifties,
lives in Saitama,
his address is listed right here.
Works as a blaster
for a company called Daiei Industry.
DAIEI INDUSTRY CO.
As it stands, the Hayabusa Number Sixty
is currently keeping its speed fixed at
120 kilometers per hour and is
quickly heading towards Tokyo Station.
Saitama Prefectural Police.
There was a similar
incident when we were kids, right?
Is Masatoshi Koga here, by any chance?
A similar incident?
Yes, where they planted, you
know, bombs on a Shinkansen train.
Right. Oh, that's right.
That train, uh… was actually heading to
Hakata back then, right?
-Yeah.
So technically speaking, it is pos--
NIHONMATSU CITY,
FUKUSHIMA PREFECTURE 231 KM TO TOKYO
Here you go.
This is
pretty bad, isnt it?
Fujii…
Fujii, listen.
Fujii, talk to me.
Fujii!
Wake up, Fujii!
If we don't take him to a hospital soon,
he might not make it out alive.
He's a really good guy.
A little naive, but…
he's really eager,
and passionate, and…
I beg you.
I want to…
save his life.
Then please just kill me, Takaichi.
Why's that the only option?
That's your duty, right?
You have to do what's best
for your passengers.
And what's best for this
crazy passenger who everyone wants dead
is for you to just kill me right now.
Everyone here, myself included,
are just waiting
for me to finally stop breathing.
I would never do that, do you understand?
Wait, hold on, don't--
That doesn't make any sense!
I gave them my word!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
My word!
Of course I know that!
-But every minute counts right now.
-Yoshimura.
You know that, right?
We didn't have the time to
do it completely by the book.
What? What do you mean?!
Please. Can't you treat this as an
extralegal measure and make an exception
-for us?
-You can't be serious, there
are lives at stake right now!
Exactly.
-It's the only solution we could find!
-Besides,
how can you just make
a decision without--
We're not doing anything, and
now we're impeding their work?
That will destroy our image!
General Manager?
The whole nation's watching the
fate of the Hayabusa Sixty!
Please reconsider your decision, that's
all I'm asking. I'm begging you, please!
We're discontinuing the
work at Tokyo Station.
For what reason?
What reason, huh?!
Hello?
Hello!
We're supposed to solve this
within our jurisdiction.
And the track extension plan is not.
FUKUSHIMA
One, two!
Okay!
-One more time!
-Yes, sir!
One, two!
One--
You can't imagine how
sorry I am
for being helpless.
I'll let you know right away
if there's any progress.
At this stage,
you're the only one we can count on.
Please keep an eye on our passengers.
Make sure they don't
do anything impulsive.
Maybe I will.
What?
The track extension plan
had to be canceled.
Takaichi…
Don't do it.
That's the expression I wanted to see.
Stop! You're creeping me out!
Stop it!
I said stop!
But no one…
no one cares if I live or die.
She's had
a miserable life.
Her father treated her
like garbage.
After her mother died,
the beatings got even worse.
What did he always to say her?
Right…
"If only you'd been born a boy."
It's like he wished she'd never been born.
And that's one of the
harshest realities anyone could ever face.
So you decided to make bombs and
give them to her, didn't you?
The bomber of the "one-oh-nine case," whom
Tsutomu Onodera claims to have shot dead,
Masaru Koga is…
your father, isn't that right?
Yeah.
I'm sure you think your father
wanted to face death with honor,
but Onodera denied him that.
Correct me if I'm wrong, go ahead.
I'm sure…
you all know what kind
of person Onodera is.
He used to say things like
"I shot that bomber dead in a second,"
"I'm the hero of the 'one-oh-nine case'."
A despicable man who took pride in lies.
That's exactly why Yuzuki wanted
to target a Shinkansen.
Shinkansen trains are a reminder
of the hatred she has for her father.
The government just
gave us an order to forcibly
stop the train.
Takaichi has made an honorable decision.
He is our pride.
-I'll send a stop signal.
-No.
I should do it.
It's my responsibility until the end.
Alright.
We found out where each of the bombs are.
Koga said there's three bombs left.
In car one,
car four,
and in car number six.
Three bombs exploding?
There'd be no stopping it.
Yoshimura. Where's the zero kilometer post?
Eleven kilometers from Omiya Station.
What is it, Kasagi?
WASHINOMIYA
The question really is,
can everyone on the train endure it?
And we need…
We need a show of goodwill
from the government.
Hey, can you connect them, please?
It's connected.
We're going to uncouple
the Hayabusa Sixty while it's
moving using two switches.
To keep damage to a minimum,
we'll carry out the operation
on the branch
line to Washinomiya Maintenance Center,
which is in a less populated area.
Cars one through six will be directed
onto the northbound track.
And then,
as soon as the front truck
of car seven passes,
we'll operate switch A.
This will send car seven
skidding diagonally
across both the southbound
and northbound tracks,
followed by car eight.
Once the train
reaches the branch line at
the Washinomiya junction,
we'll operate switch B.
By timing the switch activation with a
specific car, we can uncouple the train,
sending cars one through six ahead
to explode on the branch line,
while cars seven and eight
stop on the main line.
That's the strategy.
Each car is twenty five meters long.
If the train's going one hundred
kilometers per hour,
we'll have less than a second
to operate switch A.
Plus, switch B is used for maintenance,
so it can only be operated manually.
Jesus.
This sounds as easy as catching
smoke with your bare hands.
Even if we do pull off the uncoupling,
derailing a train at one hundred
kilometers per hour…
That will definitely deal a serious
blow to the Hayabusa sixty.
You told me the bombs can't be defused.
Are you absolutely sure?
Is everyone aboard the Hayabusa
Sixty on the same page?
Yes.
Let's try that.
Okay, then.
Tell me all the equipment we need.
Thank you very much!
-Great.
-Yes!
Let's get to it!
-Okay.
-Yes, sir.
UNCOUPLING POINT
NASUSHIOBARA CITY,
TOCHIGI PREFECTURE 160 KM TO TOKYO
I'm heading to the driver's cab now.
See if you can find as much soft,
cushioning material as you can, okay?
-Got it.
-Okay.
-Yep.
-Be right back, ma'am.
Soft stuff… There.
And this.
This'll work, too. Okay.
The Hayabusa Number Sixty
is nearly reaching Washinomiya.
It has been running continuously since
it departed Shin-Aomori Station.
Matsumoto, we have to go.
Okay.
Takaichi.
I have a favor to ask.
My hand…
Could you take it off
the master controller?
Of course.
120 kilometers per hour,
check!
Watch out, that's high voltage!
Start deploying the ladder!
-Turn the ladder.
-Make sure the
information-sharing system is ready to go,
ASAP.
Our priority here is to
rescue everyone on board.
Don't worry about vehicle damage.
The command center has been set
up at the heart of the field.
-Kabuki Construction, crash cushions!
-Go around!
-That way! That way!
"That way!"
The high voltages ones are three and up.
-Water!
-Releasing water!
Pressure's coming up!
Lift them up! Step back.
Hoist them up!
Okay. Step back!
Alright, keep it going.
A track maintenance vehicle is coming in.
Two,
one…
Okay, it's stopped.
We're setting up three separate
blocks of these on the main line.
Yeah!
Okay, that's good!
-Three, two, one…
-Here, take this.
-Okay.
-There you have it.
-Ah.
Hang in there.
Come on.
You'll be safer here.
Oh, you haven't met her, right?
This is the driver, Matsumoto.
I, uh…
I'm sorry.
I braked too suddenly.
And I know that because of that, it----
No need to apologize.
Just help us find stuff
to cushion the impact.
Sure.
Fujii!
Don't worry about it.
We're gonna save him, okay?
After the hijacking of
Japan's iconic Bullet Train…
Six hours have passed since the
Japanese bullet train was hijacked.
The government has initiated
a high-stakes rescue operation
The government has issued an
operation order to rescue the nine
remaining passengers and crew aboard.
Aimed at freeing the nine remaining
passengers and crew. Details of the
operation remain unclear,
it is expected to be highly dangerous, as
authorities attempt to stop the speeding
train. At the train's
anticipated location--
Yuzuki.
-A coordinated effort is underway,
-It's ready.
All right.
Let's go. You keep it going. See you. Bye.
Will the mission
succeed in saving the nine?
Will the nine be successfully rescued?
We're all waiting for the outcome with
-hope.
-We all await the outcome with hope.
KOGA CITY,
IBARAKI PREFECTURE 62 KM TO TOKYO
WASHINOMIYA ROLLING STOCK
MAINTENANCE CENTER, SWITCH NUMBER 51
No foreign objects detected!
Okay.
We're almost done over here.
-Great.
-Let's start testing the switch!
Okay, sounds good.
Okay, guys.
Six minutes left.
-Okay!
-Hurry up!
-Power's ready.
-You handle it, okay?
Yes, sir!
Power on!
And testing!
That looks good.
-Make sure that's tight.
-Yeah.
Oh.
-It's not too tight, is it?
-No.
Great.
Okay.
Good.
This should be fine. Oh,
let me make that tighter.
Great.
When did you get that?!
Give that to someone who can handle it.
I mean, I guess you're right,
but that's not all yours.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
Fujii.
Hang in there.
It's close!
It'll be at the uncoupling point soon.
Fifty sixty B is approaching
at one hundred and twenty-one
kilometers per hour.
It's here!
Fifty sixty B is approaching the switch.
Wait for car seven.
Ten…
Nine…
Eight…
Seven…
Six…
Five…
Four…
Three…
Switch fifty-two.
Throw it!
Switch fifty-one.
-Throw it!
-Yes, sir!
Matsumoto!
Fujii!
Fifty sixty B has stopped.
Car eight of Fifty sixty B has stopped.
Cars one through six have derailed
on the Washinomiya branch line.
Cars one, four and six are on fire.
ERT, on our way to the scene.
Copy.
This is the Heli Musashi.
We'll transmit the video footage
from near the junction.
ERT.
We're almost at the scene.
We're at the scene.
We're entering the car.
Ready?
-Two, one…
All right.
The path is clear.
We're in the car now.
We're searching for survivors.
Watch out for the cables.
-They're broken.
-We're a rescue team.
-Hey!
-Can anyone hear me?
Please respond if you can hear us.
Okay.
We're here to rescue you.
Can anyone hear me?
Can you hear me?
How is it over there?
Haven't found anyone yet.
-Let's go to the back.
-Okay.
Okay.
-Please respond if you can hear us!
-No! Damn it!
Can anyone hear me?
Hey, can you help me lift
this thing over here?
Yeah, coming.
Damn it!
If you hear me, please make some noise!
Over here, I got something! Over here,
they're here! Come on! I need help over
-here!
-Coming.
They're all here, we're
gonna check on them right now.
They're here!
Hm?
-What was that?
-We found them, sir!
-Say that again!
-We found them all, we were just checking
if they're okay, and all nine of them are
alive, sir.
I'm okay.
We've confirmed that everyone is alive!
Yes!
It worked, thank god!
Great job, everyone.
Thanks for everything!
Let's get back to business
and resume service.
Cancel all trains between
Omiya, Oyama, Sendai and Furukawa,
and resume service on
the other sections one by one. Clear?
Yes, sir!
-Train list check!
-Thank you so much!
-Thirty thirty-two B. Morioka, southbound.
-Great job!
-How's the pantograph thing?
-Really, really well done.
It's working now.
Thirty twenty-seven B., also
heading to Morioka, derailed.
-Alright, back to work?
-I'll contact headquarters.
All right. Please double-check the tracks
and the electricity.
-We gotta bring it down-
-We're here by switch fifty-one.
All three operators are safe.
Copy.
Good job, everyone.
The patient's ready.
We're good to go.
You'll be okay.
-We're taking you to the hospital, okay?
-Fujii!
Hurry up, he needs a transfusion.
-Okay.
Fujii.
He's gonna be fine.
We'll take care of him.
Let's go.
Okay.
-One, two, three…
-Three…
All right.
Door's closing.
We'll check the evacuation
status, starting with Honden-cho.
Yeah, okay.
The ambulance is turning left.
The TMPD will handle the suspect.
Saitama PD, continue assisting at the
-scene.
-Omiya Tech Center staff,
gather at the command center!
Saitama PD.
Copy that.
Paramedic captain speaking.
One victim was transported
in grave condition.
The other eight have minor injuries,
but nothing major.
-My name is Kawagoe.
-SPD, HQ. Copy that.
I'm in charge of your investigation.
Do you regret it?
Not at all.
Because I did it of my own free will.
Koga took advantage of your hatred
to get his revenge on Tsutomu Onodera
without getting his hands dirty.
Your free will
was very convenient for Koga,
don't you think so?
Does thinking like that
make you feel better?
I'm just a poor, miserable girl who was
used by an evil adult.
The illusion of normalcy again.
You strike me as someone who
hates everyone and everything.
But…
I wouldn't say
the world is completely hopeless.
-Take her away.
-There's a lot of reporters out here.
Copy that.
Can we get someone to
set up a barrier, please?
This is the fire headquarters. There
are no injuries around the branch line.
Copy that.
-We'll check with the local authorities.
-This is the command center. Copy that.
Sounds good. Copy that.
They're suppressing the fire
at cars one through six.
Copy.
-Thank you.
-We've expanded the barriers.
Kawagoe, TMPD.
The suspect is being taken
by the paramedics.
Copy that, sir.
I'm still burning from that drink.
Of course you would say that.
All twenty-one people from eight
households have been confirmed.
Okay.
-One day we'll all laugh about this…
-Moving on to Jonan.
-Eight people.
-Okay. Next, Aoba.
Eighteen people, five houses, confirmed.
Okay.
-Honmachi.
-The van is here!
Fifteen people, four houses, confirmed.
Okay.
I guess that completes
the evacuation report.
Great.
-JTSB is arriving. Make room.
-Let's make sure they all get
shelter information as soon as possible.
-I'll leave it to you.
-Copy that.
Let's do it.
The van is ready, it's right this way.
Here.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you. I appreciate it.
-Thank you. The van is this way.
-Take care of yourselves.
-Thank you for taking care of us.
-You're very welcome.
I received a message from the TMPD.
Good!
And salute!
-I brought you…
-Kawaguchi Fire Department!
Relief supplies.
Sir!
-Oh!
-Kawaguchi Fire Department!
-There's an apple pie in there, too.
-Sir!
Thanks, I'm starving.
Could they come here and check?
I'm sure JTSB will step in before that.
-The van is about to depart!
-Of course they'll handle the fire, but
JR needs JTSB's decision before doing
anything.
We made it!
-You did it.
-Takaichi!
Well done!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate that.
We were worried about you, Takaichi!
Thank you so much!
Thanks to all of you!
We did it!