Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
Emma...
You didn't even
close the door!
The carpool was late,
and I don't want to miss
the beginning
of Plumshire Manor.
It would be so cool
to have a life like that.
Work for royalty,
travel to exotic places,
eat gourmet food,
be in charge
of an entire estate.
Well, you can start
by cleaning your room.
Mom!
All right, all right,
after the show, hmm?
Being a Butler
here at Plumshire Manor
is the greatest honor
of my life.
All right, everybody,
your penne, ma'am,
and your penne,
and this one's gluten-free.
Is everything
looking good, guys?
You're good?
Okay, I'll be back
with those two drinks.
Okay, that's got to be
a new record.
What was that like 19 dishes?
I've been practicing non-stop.
Why?
You know it's okay
to take more than one trip.
Mm-mm.
At the butler academy,
they expect you to carry
multiple dishes at once
with no tray.
Of course they do.
Butling is a lot harder
than people think.
I'm sorry, what?
"Butling"?
That can't be a real word.
It must be called
something else.
Mm-mm. The official term
is "butling."
Huh.
Speaking of,
have you heard anything?
No.
I'm hoping for an acceptance
letter from the Academy
any day now.
Well, I'd cross
my fingers and toes for you,
but that would make me
a very dangerous waitress.
Emma, you home?
I got takeout!
Yeah, I'm in the kitchen!
Another rejection?
Yeah.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
You look tired.
You're working too hard.
What time did you get home
last night?
I learned about hard work
from you.
Yes, but I was a single parent
trying to raise you.
You're doing it--
Because the guy
from the Butler Academy
said I needed more
service industry experience.
Well, you put yourself
through college,
got a degree in communications,
took three different
language courses,
moved back home to save money.
I mean, you'd think
that would be enough
to get you in.
Does this go with Chinese?
Yeah, I don't know, it's red.
Mom, these schools are
hard to get into for a reason.
Graduates from these programs
end up working for some of
the most important dignitaries,
monarchs, and politicians
in the world.
They make, like, six,
or seven figure incomes.
I know,
I just wish you didn't
have to break your back
just to be considered.
You know, this one person
in that chat forum I'm in
made the point
that butler school
can be harder to get into
than law school.
Well then...
try law school?
Kidding.
Look, I'm just--
I'm just worried
you're putting all your eggs
in this butler basket,
and I know you'll get in,
and you'll go,
and you'll be great,
but I just don't want you
to miss out on life
while you're at it.
I'm not.
I'm not missing out on life,
I have a life.
Really?
Yeah.
Today, I hung out with Marie.
At work?
Doesn't count.
Chow mein?
Hello?
Am I speaking with
Ms. Emma Conroy?
You are.
Ah, good afternoon, Ms. Conroy.
This is Charles Wiloughby
from the American
Butler Academy.
Hi!
I am calling with regard
to your most recent application.
Yes,
I received your letter
of rejection yesterday.
Ah, well, there's been
a slight change of plans.
At the last minute,
we had a student drop out,
and if you're
still interested,
we'd like to offer you
the open spot.
Hello?
Ms. Conroy?
Are you still there?
Yes, I am here,
and yes,
I definitely want that spot.
Wonderful.
Thank you so much.
My pleasure.
We shall be in touch,
and, uh, good day to you.
Okay, thank you so much.
Okay, bye.
Yes!
- Oh! Sorry!
- I'm so sorry.
How gorgeous is this place?
I know, I just can't believe
I'm actually here.
Same.
Applied multiple times?
Yes, and to so many
different programs.
Me too!
I hear this one
is one of the best, though.
Oh, definitely.
Congrats.
You too.
Hey, I'm Lisa Bolster.
Emma Conroy. Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Do you know what type of butling
you're hoping to do
after you graduate?
Yeah, my dream
is to be a butler
at one of those grand estates
in Europe.
Amazing.
What about you?
Yachting.
I've been trying
to get into it for years.
The most successful
yacht butlers
all graduated from here.
So cool.
All students,
please gather
in the entrance hall.
Here we go!
Okay.
Did you do the tour online?
Of course.
Five times.
So, I've been working
in a restaurant.
I wouldn't say it's fine dining,
but it's sort of fancy...
Welcome. incoming students
of the American Butler Academy.
My name is Charles Wiloughby.
I have dedicated my life
to the craft of butling,
and opened up this school
to pass on my knowledge
to the next generation
of great butlers.
These next few weeks
will be hard and grueling.
You will be bombarded
with information and skills
that you will need to retain
immediately,
but I promise you
it will all pay off in the end.
- It better.
- I hope so.
Now, the hardest part
about being a butler
is balance,
both figuratively
and literally.
The cart behind you
symbolizes the skills
that you will have to master.
By the end of this course,
you should be able
to carry one full service
in one trip.
I assure you,
I am not kidding.
Is there anyone amongst you now
who cares to try it out?
See if there are
any early standouts among you?
Ah...
initiative and confidence,
two excellent attributes
in a future butler.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Okay...
One full service?
Four plates?
I believe that's what I said.
Okay.
I've got this.
Two...
three...
Whoo!
I was a server for a while--
Oh!
Yeah, I'll call you back.
I am so sorry,
I was-- I was on the phone,
and I-- Are you okay?
A prime example
of why butlers
need to be prepared
for anything and everything.
Proximity to doors
is always something to note,
Ms. Conroy...
Mm-hmm.
...and Mr. Walker...
...nice of you
to finally join us.
Hey, guys.
I am so sorry.
In your hands,
you have a crisp, white shirt,
Windsor-cut collar,
along with a black or gray tie,
which should be
in a Windsor knot,
always.
Also, a vest, or waistcoat,
with the bottom button undone,
as per tradition,
dating back to Edward VII.
Smooth top, no wrinkles.
Cufflinks are a must,
and the shirt sleeve
is the transition
from the jacket to the hands,
and should be visible
two centimeters
outside of the jacket,
and we measure...
Are you really taking notes?
Yeah, this is important...
When wearing a jacket,
again,
you should leave
the bottom button open.
Trousers should always be
as long as two centimeters
above the heel of the shoe.
Shoe shine is available
in all of your rooms,
and should be used daily.
You spelled "trousers" wrong.
Do you mind?
Sorry.
There will be uniform checks.
The first will be
tomorrow morning.
When you hear the bell,
you will have precisely
10 minutes
to come downstairs
fully dressed,
in pristine condition.
Yes.
What happens
if we miss a button
or we tie our tie wrong?
Hmm, well,
like everything we do here
at the Academy,
you'll be graded and tested.
The better you do,
the higher your class ranking.
The higher your rankings,
the more likely you are
to receive a letter
of recommendation.
Fully one-third
of the students at the Academy
fail,
so please act accordingly.
Now, join the lovely Ms. Martin
as she assigns you your rooms.
Please follow her.
Oh, Ms. Conroy,
would you mind
holding back a moment?
It was chance
that gave you your spot here.
I hope you keep that in mind.
Yes, I will,
and I want you to know
I'm so grateful to be here.
Mm-hmm.
Then please don't speak
when I am speaking.
In fact, chitchat
is a slippery slope,
and something
butlers should avoid.
100%.
I don't even know that guy.
He's just some rude person.
It won't happen again.
I'm sure it won't.
Off you go.
Yes.
Sorry.
- Hi!
So glad we got assigned
as roommates.
Same.
I feel like
you're one of the few
friendly faces I've seen
since I got here.
I think the instructors
are just really serious people.
You know that Mr. Wiloughby
worked for the Swedish
royal family
for, like, 30 years.
Really?
That's impressive.
I hope I get
on his good side.
You will.
Hardest part was getting in.
Now we're here, we got this.
You're right.
Thank you.
I'm not gonna let some latecomer
ruin the fact that I'm here,
and I'm ready to learn.
Exactly!
Here we go!
Lisa!
Five more minutes.
No, I don't think
it works like that.
The bell means
we have 10 minutes to get ready
and lined up
in uniform downstairs.
Is the sun even up?
Yes!
Shoot, I'm missing a cufflink.
What? Already?
Oh... it's so tiny.
I'll help you look for it,
but you have to help me
tie a Windsor knot.
Hands out of pockets.
Your trousers are creased.
Ah...
good knot.
Wrong button...
Ah, hardly a Windsor.
That is a Charlie knot,
Mr. Archer,
and you must shine
the spots off your shoes.
Spots?
I don't even see any spots.
Hmm!
Therein lies
your first problem.
Hmm, Ms. Bolster,
good knot.
Do up your jacket.
Uh, overall, too much space
between jacket and wrist.
Ms. Conroy,
where is your cufflink?
I couldn't find it
anywhere, sir.
I'm so sorry.
Butlers don't make excuses,
they find solutions.
Of course.
Retrieve your cufflink.
In any household,
a mishap like that
could cost you your position.
Ah, Mr. Walker,
you're late.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, my alarm did not go off.
It is early.
Despite his tardiness,
Mr. Walker is wearing
his uniform
close to perfection.
Please all take note,
this is how
you should all look
going forward,
but that is the second time
you've been late.
Don't let it happen again.
Yes, sir.
Please follow me for breakfast.
I shall be going over
class schedules.
So...
can anyone tell me
where the word "butler"
comes from?
Yes.
The word "butler"
comes from the old french word,
"bouteiller"
which means "cup bearer".
In Ancient Greece and Rome,
butlers were in charge
of the household's refreshments.
Yes,
and do you know why this was?
Yes, I do.
Alcoholic beverages
were stored
in earthenware containers,
which were considered
very valuable to the household,
so only the most trusted
of servants
were allowed to handle them.
Okay, yeah,
so they technically
were not butlers.
What do you mean?
They were just servants
who poured wine.
Mm, no,
it was more meaningful
than that.
Mm, no.
What we now know as butling
didn't exist until
the 17th and 18th Century.
No, butlers have existed
since the dawn of hospitality,
which can be traced
as far back as 15,000 B.C.E.
Oh, come on.
It's true.
The Lascaux caves in France
were the first documented
shelters in history
where people accommodated
others from a different tribe,
so, really, butling
is older than the wheel.
That's a bit of a stretch.
Actually,
the young lady is correct.
The role we presently play
in high society
dates back
to when civilization began.
Okay, right,
the history is important,
but the actual act
of being a butler
requires much more
than that, right?
Much, much more.
Which side is the water glass
supposed to be again?
Water glasses are the left.
Uh, no, the right.
I don't know why
I keep blanking on this.
I've studied this.
Salad fork
comes after the fish fork.
The menu you're setting
has it as an appetizer.
Yeah, the fish fork...
It's the smaller one
with the incurve.
Precisely.
I know that.
No, Mr. Archer.
Always make sure to measure.
The distance between
the water glass
and the top of the knives
needs to be exactly one inch.
The bread plate
goes to the left,
above the other plate.
Yeah, I know.
I worked at a restaurant.
All right,
I'm just trying to help.
No need, I've got this.
I just haven't had to set tables
under this pressure before.
You think this is pressure?
Just wait
till we have to do this
for actual royalty.
Wait, what?
Oh, yeah.
Our final dinner
we set and serve
is for real nobility.
Friends of Wiloughby's.
Excellent work, Mr. Walker,
though no surprise there.
Oh, thank you, Ms. Martin.
No, Ms. Conroy.
The knife blades
always need to face the plate.
Look to Mr. Walker's
as an example.
Mr. Wiloughby
will expect you all
to set a full table for eight
in under ten minutes
by this Friday.
A well-made floral bouquet
can transform any room
from the mundane to the elegant.
Do butlers have to create
flower arrangements often?
My old boss,
the Prince of Sweden,
he used to insist on waking up
every morning
to the fragrance
of the freshest flowers.
It is a necessity.
Fragrant flower.
He's not even
making a bouquet.
He's looking at tomatoes.
Maybe he's allergic
to flowers?
I don't get it.
He doesn't want to be here,
and he doesn't participate,
but he knows everything
about being a butler.
Right?
That Henry Walker guy?
Yeah, what's his deal?
He's a legacy butler.
A what?
A legacy butler.
He comes from
a long line of butlers.
I looked it up
last night before bed.
His family has been butling
for a duke's estate
for over 200 years.
Over 200 years?
Wow.
I think he's friends
with Henry's whole family.
That makes sense.
That's why he's getting away
with everything.
Nepotism at its finest.
Ugh, I hate that.
Well, that doesn't seem fair.
Although
you'll rarely have to do
the cooking yourself,
it is important for most butlers
to have a basic understanding
of the culinary arts,
and how to properly plate.
I think your bread is burning.
Oh, no.
You used way too much butter.
Thank you for the input.
Mm, that looks wonderful,
Mr. Walker.
Oh, thank you, sir.
- I'm using a peach glaze.
- Mm-hmm.
I can smell it caramelizing.
And Ms. Conroy,
what is it that you're making?
I'm making a grilled cheese.
With a Dijon vinaigrette
perhaps?
Or herb chèvre?
Uh, no, I was just going
for the basic sandwich.
I eat out a lot,
or I eat at work,
so I don't have
a lot of time to cook.
Mm-hmm.
Well, in order to excel
at butler duties
such as food preparation,
table management,
and stocking the household
for the chef,
knowing the bare bones
is a must.
Hey, add some apple and Gruyère
to the sandwich,
it will balance
the burnt flavor.
Is it true
that you're a legacy butler?
Glad to know
my reputation precedes me.
May I ask what, then,
are you doing here?
Same thing as you.
I'm getting my butler education.
Yeah, but it seems like
you know most of this stuff
already.
You do realize
this is one of the most
prestigious butler academies
in the world, right?
Do you even want to be here?
No, not really.
Um, you're doing this
all wrong.
If you slice it
a little thinner,
it's much better for a sandwich.
Did you apply?
Oh, and if you add
some mustard,
this will bring out
the flavor of the Gruyère.
You didn't answer my question.
Try this.
Not bad.
And yes,
to answer your question,
I did apply.
Ms. Conroy...
you're not supposed to eat
the dish yet.
Sorry.
Jared, that cotton
has a sheen.
You need to iron
the other side of the fabric,
and change to medium heat.
I never knew this job
required so much ironing.
It's important.
Is it?
If an estate has a butler,
surely, it has a maid.
Mm-mm, depends on the estate.
Usually, the butler is expected
to prepare the tablecloths,
but most butlers
help their clients
pick out and prepare
their wardrobe every day.
It's part of the glitz
and glamour of it all.
I'm sorry,
I think there is
something very glamour-ful
about taking care of some of
the most magnificent homes
in the world,
and managing those households
so that those who live there
can reach
their fullest potential.
Okay, I don't think
"glamour-ful" is a word.
and your tablecloth
is on fire.
Oh, no!
This needs to be
on a lower setting!
Perhaps concentrating
on your work,
instead of debating
other students
will help you
not burn down the manor.
Today,
I want you to understand
how to pair wine with meals,
and, most importantly,
how to properly serve that wine.
I swear
I've been to a million
wine-tasting bridal showers,
and I still
can't tell the difference
between most reds.
Tell me about it.
My go-to
is whatever's on sale,
and sometimes,
that's Franzia.
I'm sorry, you--
you drink wine from a--
from a box?
I mean, sometimes,
when the occasion calls for it.
What, uh,
what occasion could possibly
call for that?
You got home late from work,
you made some popcorn,
you poured yourself
a glass of wine.
Why? What's your go-to,
some rare bottle from 1912?
I mean, while the 1912
Rebello Valente Port
is really good,
I'm sure you'd agree,
Ms. Martin, right?
But, you know,
I usually don't have
three grand lying around.
Do you?
Now, Henry,
do you know the difference
between contrasting pairing
and congruent pairing?
Oh, sure, of course, yeah.
So, contrasting pair,
they create balance
by putting differing flavors
and tastes together,
and congruent pairing
creates balance
by, um, how do you say it...
amplifying shared flavor compounds.
I can see why Mr. Wiloughby
spoke so highly of you.
Now take up the bottle
in front of you.
Eventually, we will work up
to synchronized pouring,
but we will start
with mastering the basics.
We got this.
Getting wine into a cup
has never been
a problem for me.
A butler must pour
with confidence.
Hesitation will result in a mess.
Always have a napkin or cloth
to catch any drips.
Always have the label
facing the guest.
Always hold from
the bottom of the bottle.
Only pour to one third
of the glass
to allow the wine to aerate,
and end with one swift twist
to cut the pour,
and always return
to ready position
with one arm behind your back
when you finish.
I want to see
your perfect pours,
and remember,
always approach your guest
and their wine glass
from the right-hand side.
You just stained
a client's cuff.
Sorry.
Hold the bottle up higher,
Ms. Conroy.
Yeah.
It's like this.
No, I--
Oh!
Oh, my gosh, I'm so sorry.
I don't know what happened.
A butler moves quickly
to clean up any mess,
especially one they made.
Sorry, I just...
I'll use your--
Club soda, stat!
Right.
Take him to the kitchen.
I can't believe
I just did that.
It's okay,
it was just a mistake.
No, every little thing counts.
I've seen her making marks
on her grading sheet--
Just calm down.
It's just a couple marks,
it's not a big deal.
I've made so many
avoidable mistakes already,
I could easily fail,
and unlike you,
I actually want to graduate.
Okay, well,
I want to graduate, too.
No, you don't.
You've already told me
you don't want to be here.
Yeah, I don't want
to be a butler.
Every member of my family
has gone to an academy
like this,
so I...
I feel like I have to go,
follow tradition.
What would you rather do?
Cook.
Be a chef.
Open my own restaurant.
Cool.
Yeah.
You're starting to make
a little more sense.
What do you mean?
Well, my first
impression of you
was that you thought
you were too cool
for butler school.
Yeah, that part's true.
It's very true.
You're just like
the rest of us.
How?
You're trying to find
your path
without hurting anyone
or letting anyone down
in the process.
You missed a spot.
Actually, you missed,
like, 20 spots.
Yeah, I don't know
what to tell you.
Ms. Conroy,
you're one of a few students
I wanted to talk to
regarding your rankings
thus far.
If you continue
at this present level,
I simply can't pass you.
I don't know
why I'm not nailing it.
It's like I get nervous,
and I have stage fright
or something
when it comes to the tasks
I thought I had a handle on.
Hmm.
Well, you must devise
a way to overcome this,
and quickly.
A butler has to be alert, sharp,
and ready to focus
on the moment at hand.
I will do my best.
Good.
That's all, then.
You wanted to see me?
Yes, please, take a seat.
Yes, of course, I will.
Fine.
Okay.
I will.
Bye.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
I didn't realize
anyone else was down here.
I was just practicing
the table settings
for the quiz tomorrow.
Who were you talking to?
My dad.
He's just checking in on me,
making sure everything
is going smoothly...
Mm.
...and that I'm excelling.
Have you ever told your parents
that you don't actually
want to be a butler
and that you'd rather be a chef?
Oh, yes.
Many times.
It has not gone well.
It's much easier said than done.
My parents and my grandfather
simply won't hear of it,
at all.
They've been in this
line of work for generations.
My mom's American,
I went to school here,
but she has bought into
this whole thing as well.
It's some family business.
Yeah.
I don't know what I would do
if someone told me
I couldn't pursue
the career I wanted.
What, being a butler?
Yeah.
And this is all
because of that TV show
you were telling Lisa about?
Plum...
Plum hire M-mountain?
Plumshire Manor.
Right.
Yes.
I mean, the show
planted the seed,
but once I researched
everything a butler does,
and everything
a butler gets to experience,
I knew I wanted that life.
Hmm.
What?
I just, I've never
looked at being a butler
as something you can aspire to.
It's always felt
like an obligation to me.
Oh, yeah,
no, there are very few jobs
that let you be in a room
with some of
the most important people
on the planet,
and help make their day better.
Okay, so the way
that you feel about butling,
that's how I feel about cooking.
Though I'm a really good cook,
and your butling is...
it needs some work.
And just when I thought
we were finding common ground.
Goodnight.
When Mr. Wiloughby says,
you will have five minutes
to set one setting
in front of you
based on this menu,
you must also choose
which wine to pair
with the first course.
We will only be here
to observe and grade,
we cannot offer any help.
- We got this.
- Yeah.
Five minutes.
And...
commence.
Okay.
Whoa, okay, um,
we have the tablecloth.
You do plates,
I'll do linens.
On it.
Yup.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The salad plate
is the one on the right.
- This one?
- No. No, no, no,.
- The bigger one, the left one.
- I'll go with it.
And I'm gonna make sure
it's one inch.
Okay...
We have soup.
We need soup bowls,
You're right.
Those are dessert bowls.
Half the allotted time.
Shrimp is... before salad.
We need wine.
Two of these...
No.
25 seconds.
What order are these spoons?
I feel like
we're forgetting something.
What are we missing?
Time.
The centerpiece.
Yes.
Not only have you
forgotten the centerpiece,
but the choice of wine
would make the shrimp cocktail
taste metallic,
and you completely disregarded
the mousse selection on the menu
with regard to spoons.
I won't even address
the state of the tablecloth.
End of another week,
Ms. Conroy.
Mm-hmm.
Did you eventually find
the cufflink?
Yeah, it's, uh...
not looking so good.
Would it be possible
to get a new pair?
I shall add it
to your tuition.
Where is Jared?
I don't know.
The latest class rankings
have been posted.
Please use it as a, uh, guide,
and a motivational tool.
Oh, not bad.
The rankings are up.
Can I see?
Good morning, everyone,
just wanted to say goodbye,
I'm leaving today.
What?
You know, only like
60% of students make it
all the way to the end.
It's bound to happen
to some of us.
Hey, it's all right.
What happened?
Mr. Wiloughby made it clear
that I do not have what it takes
to be a butler.
I'm so sorry.
Maybe you could reapply,
or, I don't know,
try another school?
Yeah.
Nah, sometimes, you just
have to know when to quit.
Good luck.
You too.
Thanks.
Goodbye.
I'll miss you, Jared.
- Bye, Jared.
- Goodbye.
Let me guess,
another late night studying?
You saw
what happened to Jared.
You're like the hardest worker
here, though,
I don't get it.
I know, right?
In the classroom, I'm great.
Subjects like language,
and manners,
and house management,
I've got down.
When it comes to food, or wine,
or table settings,
I'm terrible.
I can't help you there.
I got a 4
on my wine-pairing quiz today.
I got a 2.
You know who does
seem to thrive in that arena?
Henry.
Yeah,
that's because he has
the advantage of being a chef,
and he was raised by butlers.
Maybe he's a good resource.
Have you thought about
asking him for help?
No. No thanks.
- Why not?
- Because he's Henry.
He's been driving me nuts
since day one.
All right,
if you say so.
Besides, he doesn't even
like this stuff,
he's just doing it
to make his parents happy.
Yes, but he's still doing it,
and doing it well.
I'm just saying
it's something to think about.
You could have your own tutor,
and I bet you
he wouldn't even ask for a fee.
Think of it as a dance.
One, two, three, four.
The best way to do it together
is to form
your own silent tempo.
Now place the dish.
And turn.
Your other left, Ms. Conroy.
Select your wine,
complete the circle...
...and pour
in unison.
Wrong wine, Ms. Conroy.
All right.
Once more.
Uh, Ms. Conroy.
a word, please?
I know the passion is there,
but you're making far too many
little mistakes.
I know.
I'm trying so hard.
I want to do better.
You're trying too hard,
that's the problem.
You're getting in your own way.
Perhaps you need a guide
of some sort.
Someone who sees these tasks
differently.
Like...?
Well, I'm thinking,
very possibly,
of Mr. Walker.
Oh.
Don't be too proud
to ask for help.
Thanks.
Is Henry really
the best person to help her?
Well, she has the drive
and adoration for this work,
he has the know-how,
and the sense
to connect to the moment.
I think
they rather need each other.
Hmm.
- Hi.
There you are.
Hey.
What are you doing in here?
I thought the chef could use
a few more herbs
in his cooking.
I was just checking it out
to see what they had in here.
That makes sense.
What are you doing?
Usually, you're in the library
during lunch.
Yeah, uh...
Well,
I just wanted to say that...
I know you're really good at
all things to do with
food and wine.
Thank you?
Yeah, uh...
the second part is...
I was wondering if maybe,
if you happen to have
some free time after class,
and you were willing,
if-- if you would consider...
...giving me some pointers.
You asking for my help?
Yeah.
You know, I don't know
if that's the best idea.
Why?
Well, uh...
you're really
into the whole butler thing,
you know,
and I'm not that into it,
so I don't know.
I don't know if
I'm the best teacher for you.
Fair enough...
but what if I could
show you something
that would inspire you
to see how I see?
We'll always be here
for you to rely on, Lady Jane.
Advising you
means the world to me.
This is unbelievable.
Yeah, it's so good.
No, it's not--
Oh, shh, shh, shh!
This is the good part.
You are more than
just a butler, Stevenson,
you are my greatest confidant,
...and my guiding light.
Thank you, M'lady.
Are you crying?
It's just so sweet,
the bond that they have.
He would-- he would get fired
for being
all up in her business
in reality.
We learned about this.
Client discretion?
- Yeah, but...
- It's important.
...he earned her trust.
Okay, you wanna know
the most unrealistic
part of it?
Not really.
Well, it's when Mr...
What's he called? Clump--
Crumpet.
Nobody's named that.
When he falls in love
with the town baker?
Oh...
That would not happen.
Butlers don't have time for that.
They don't...
They don't have a life.
I mean, your parents
must have found time,
they had you.
My mother was willing
to give up her entire career
to move to the Duke's grounds,
but I have plenty of uncles
and cousins
who never had time
for marriage or for kids.
It's easy to get swept up
in the job
when it's all about
other people.
I guess I never thought
about it that way.
Butlers make a great living.
It's a great trade, right?
Mm-hmm.
If you are willing
to devote yourself,
your life,
to the job, and to other people.
I'm not going to do that.
No way.
I don't want that.
I want a family,
and I want kids,
and I want the time to enjoy it.
I have to plug in the computer,
um, and the charger's
right there.
Oh.
Well, let me retrieve it
for you, Ms. Conroy.
Very good.
Let me plug it in for you...
Uncanny.
Here we go.
Let me find the outlet.
Hey, look.
My cufflink!
Oh, but I already
bought new ones.
Well, now you have a backup
for when you lose those.
Ow!
Jeez.
Well, it's past my bedtime.
I should get going.
Mm-hmm.
Wait,
before you go,
you didn't really
give me an answer
about helping me.
Okay,
meet me tomorrow after class?
Really?
Yeah, say, what,
6:00 in the kitchen?
Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Really?
- Really.
- Thank you!
Thank you, I'll be there.
Good evening, Ms. Conroy!
So when anyone is cooking,
the five basic elements
of flavor
are very important
for pairing and balance,
and they are sweet, sour,
salty, bitter,
and umami.
Okay.
No, do not take notes.
- No, no, no, it helps me--
- Put this down.
No, I don't care,
put this down.
It's not... I don't think
it helps you, actually,
because what it does,
it gets you in your head,
and you're not
enjoying the moment.
It becomes work,
it becomes a chore,
am I right?
I'm definitely right.
- Okay.
- It's no longer enjoyable.
You need to get out of your head
and in your body.
- Enjoy the moment.
- Okay.
- We're in the moment.
- I'm in the moment.
In the kitchen,
we're living life, okay?
Okay...
You good?
I'm good.
Okay, can you pour
the rest of those for me?
Yeah.
How did you get
so good at this stuff?
Oh, you know,
I, uh...
I just lived in the kitchen.
Always.
I loved the kitchen,
and the chef was...
the chef was
really important to me.
I cared more about
what the chef was doing
than what my parents were doing.
Oh, man, it just always
smelled so good.
It brought me
a lot of comfort and solace.
It was like
a stress relief, you know?
So your real life passion.
Yeah, I guess so.
Yeah.
What about you?
Passion?
Yeah, you have
anything like that?
Mm-hmm.
I would say my life passion
is setting goals.
You're a very determined person.
- I am.
- You're diligent, right?
Yup.
You have a really strong
work ethic.
That's, like,
not what I meant by passion.
Passion is...
It's-it's-it's this.
It's this.
It's something you do for fun.
It's something you do
outside of work.
It's something
you don't strive for,
you just love to do it.
I guess
I never really had time
for anything like that.
I think that's the thing,
I think people
don't make time for it,
but everybody needs to.
Everybody needs to make time
for balance.
Where-- Okay, so, like,
let me ask you this,
if you were gonna have
a weekend off,
and you were gonna have fun,
and were gonna go out
and do something,
whatever it is,
what would that be?
I...
Emma Conroy, having fun,
what is it?
I'm Emma Conroy,
I'm having fun, and I'm...
watching Plumshire Manor.
You've gotta be kidding me.
I don't know.
I'm--
Plumshire?
An old...
It's a sad life.
So, that's...
No, it's not, it's just...
If you wanna be good at this,
truly good,
and I know you want to, right?
You wanna be great.
You need balance.
It cannot be all work.
You, as Emma, need balance.
Food needs balance.
It makes everything better.
And you, do you
practice what you preach?
All the time.
But wouldn't you rather
have a job that you love
so that you can be
doing what you love
all the time?
Like being a chef?
Yeah, I...
I just, I just can't.
I can't.
It's complicated.
No, there must be a way
for you to show your family
that you're meant to be a chef
and not a butler.
Tell me how.
I don't know how.
I'm just...
gonna think on it.
Well, good luck.
Mm...
a delicious Cabernet.
Merlot.
Right.
Lisa told me
you wanted to see me.
What's all this?
Yeah, I had a, uh,
I had a fun idea
for a way to get you
out of your head.
So, flavor and pairing
takes practice, right?
Table settings,
I've seen you do it,
I know you can do it.
You do it well,
it's just when there's pressure,
that's when you mess up.
Yeah, you're not wrong there.
So I came up with a game.
A game?
Yeah. We're gonna race.
Randomly pick
a dining scenario.
The first
to correctly set it wins.
Well, what does
the person win?
N-- A point.
And what happens
if you get the most points?
You just have to wait and see.
Okay?
Ooh. Okay.
Let's go.
I'm nervous.
Don't be nervous.
Just read it off.
High tea.
- High tea!
- Yeah.
You ready?
- On your marks.
- Yeah.
Get set, go!
All right, here we go.
Make sure you don't forget this.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Uh...
Cream and sugar...
I've got it.
Don't touch mine
Oh, sorry, that was--
That's my side,
that's my side.
I'm in control of this.
No, I don't think so.
Out of my way.
- And... done!
- Done!
All right, all right, Conroy.
You want to check mine,
I'll check yours.
Okay.
Let me measure this.
Oh...
well done.
Mm-hmm.
Actually this is...
this is perfect.
Huh.
Shall we go again?
Okay.
Five-course dinner,
plus soup, cheese plate,
and dessert.
Okay, ready?
On your marks, get set, go!
Hey, that was cheating!
And for the winner
of today's table-setting race,
we have my famous
peanut-butter cookies.
Ooh...
Mm, yum.
Seriously, you did great.
Thanks.
Yeah.
That time,
there was something
about the competition
that made me more relaxed.
Is that weird?
No.
No, you were having fun.
So your brain couldn't trick you
into freaking out.
You just existed
in the moment,
instead of
worrying about the next one.
Yeah.
Now I just have to harness
that power in class,
on quizzes,
and in the real world.
You can do it.
I know you--
What?
What is it?
Mom, Dad, hey,
what are you doing here?
We thought we'd drop in
for a surprise visit.
See how you're getting on
this time around.
Okay.
Yeah, everything is going well.
Why aren't you in class?
We're on a break.
I see.
Mr. Wiloughby
has invited us for dinner.
Okay.
Great.
The Earl rang
to ask if anyone could
read him a bedtime story.
I assumed that he must have
brought his children, but--
When Phillip asked him
what kind of book he'd like,
he said--
"Something boring
to put me to sleep."
We're all hanging out
with your parents.
Why don't you join us?
Um, because
the sooner I finish,
the sooner
I have to go in there.
So I'm going to take my time.
Oh, come on,
they're not that bad.
Okay, which story
did he tell?
It was the Earl story,
wasn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
It was good.
I love them,
but they do not stop talking
about being a butler,
ever.
Nothin' wrong with that.
Come on.
"Something
boring to put me to sleep."
Hey.
Henry, come sit here.
All right.
I've missed you, darling.
I've missed you, too, Mom.
So, this is Emma Conroy.
Yeah, we met. Hi.
Hello.
She's, uh,
wanted to be a butler
since she was, what, 10?
Mm-hmm.
Well...
isn't that refreshing to hear.
So where are you looking
to butler after you graduate?
Resorts, hotel?
Private homes?
Honestly, I would love
to work in a household
similar to yours.
There's something
that really appeals to me
about working for nobility.
Hear, hear.
Did you hear that, Henry,
very appealing?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Henry has been helping me a lot
with all things culinary.
He's quite the chef.
That he is.
He's so good that, uh...
I almost think
he should pursue that full-time.
Uh, yeah, yeah,
I was thinking
maybe there's a world--
I was thinking, um...
maybe I could cook full-time,
you know, see where that goes.
Nonsense,
butling is in your blood.
We've been through this.
Your hobby can be food,
but your trade is a butler.
Right, yeah.
Phillip, I just had an idea.
You know,
the Count of Kensington
is looking to hire
a new underbutler.
Well, Emma?
If you like,
we could inquire about it.
I would love that.
Of course,
you would have to get
a letter of recommendation
from Mr. Wiloughby.
Which shouldn't be a problem.
He usually writes one
for all the top students.
Oh, good.
I'll get one of those.
So, Henry,
tell us everything
you've been up to.
Hey...
saved you a cookie.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That was so nice of them
to suggest a job for me.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're, um...
They're great people.
Have you ever
thought of just going off
and becoming a chef
without their blessing?
Every day.
What's stopping you?
Oh, I don't know,
ending six generations
of my family's legacy.
Don't let your parents
or the generations
before them stop you.
How am I supposed to do that?
You heard them.
I don't know.
Show them.
Just don't give up, okay?
Conroy, you know what,
if this whole butler thing
doesn't work out,
you could be
a motivational speaker.
A backup plan?
Yeah.
Henry!
Time for your mother and I
to be going!
Thanks for the advice.
Anytime.
Hey.
There you are.
Hi.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
I thought I would practice
my place settings.
I just made record time.
Wow, nice.
So, this is what you're doing
on your day off?
Yeah.
You're forgetting,
I'm on thin ice.
Yeah, but come on,
you're doing so much better.
I'm glad you guys
feel confident enough
to go to town
and take a break.
I can't afford that luxury.
Okay, what...
Let me ask you something.
What if I told you
that there was a place
that exists
where we could go
you could one,
have fun on your day off,
and two, learn some new skills,
further your education,
would you believe
such a place exists?
No.
All right, grab your jacket,
meet me in 20.
I'm gonna show you!
So this place
has five different cheeses,
all imported,
and all properly aged.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
And I see each one
pairs with a different wine.
Yeah, see?
You see? It's enjoyable,
it's also educational.
Imagine that.
The perfect combo.
Right.
Uh, how about a toast?
To pairing!
To the perfect pairing.
Ah-hah.
I can fondue to that.
Oof.
Bad, right?
- Bad joke.
- Mm, not great.
Little tip,
the wine should always
have more acidity
than the food.
So for example,
the more bitter the cheese,
the drier the wine.
Mm, good tip.
Mm-hmm.
You cannot beat
real-world experience.
That's it.
What?
That's how you should
convince your parents.
Have you ever cooked for them?
Here and there
over the years.
What about one big meal
that showcases your talents?
A real knockout punch.
Yeah, maybe.
Something to consider.
Amazing,
just this little store
in the middle of the country.
It's the best vanilla ice cream
I've ever had.
Mm...
Also, take note,
pairs well after any meal.
Bien sûr.
Oh!
Wow...
Beautiful accent.
Somebody studied French.
Yeah, it was
my fourth rejection letter
that inspired me
to take French classes.
Ah.
The fifth inspired
an art-history course
because the Finnish
school of butling
said I didn't have
enough culture on my resume.
It's so crazy
how hard some of these schools
are to get into.
Feels like
it's harder to get into
than Harvard sometimes.
You know,
I've dropped out of a few.
Really?
Yeah.
This is my...
fourth butler academy.
Wow.
You're so good at everything.
I thought I could
convince my parents
that I wasn't good at anything,
so they'd get off my back
about following
in their footsteps.
On purpose?
And it didn't work?
No, they saw right through it.
Hmm.
Henry, I just want
to thank you for today,
and for helping me in general.
It means a lot.
Yeah, of course.
I really enjoyed today.
I don't know, I, uh...
I like spending time with you.
We should probably get back.
We have a lot of work to do.
Yeah... yeah.
Right.
Sorry.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, that...
I can't have
any distractions.
With my ranking not being great,
- I have to...
- Right.
I have to focus, and...
Right.
Keep my eye on the prize,
you know?
I totally get it.
Don't worry about it.
We're good, right?
Yeah. Yeah, we're good,
we're good.
You wanna...
You wanna walk up?
- Yeah
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Ms. Conroy.
Come in.
I hope I'm not
interrupting anything.
Well, somewhat,
but nothing that can't be
put aside momentarily.
To what do I owe this visit?
I wanted to inquire
as to what I could do,
potentially,
to make you feel as though I...
Out with it.
What do I have to do
to get a letter
of recommendation from you?
The Walkers mentioned
a position opening up
at the Kensington estate,
and it sounds like my dream job.
A very esteemed position.
Yes, very.
Well, as of now,
I can't in good faith
give you a letter
of recommendation.
However,
if you continue
to apply yourself
and successfully
complete the final,
I can reconsider.
I would so appreciate that.
I think collaborating
with young Mr. Walker
is helping a great deal.
It is.
Yeah, his passion
for everything in the kitchen
is really inspiring.
Indeed.
You know,
as a young underbutler,
I, too, struggled a lot
with the showmanship aspects
of the job.
Got a bit of, as you say,
stage fright,
myself.
How did you get past it?
By remembering
there was a greater purpose
to everything
that I was tasked with.
A butler doesn't exist
to dazzle.
A butler exists
to be of service.
Hmm.
I promise you
I will show you
I have what it takes.
Good.
I look forward to it.
Thank you.
Good night.
We have come here today
so you can witness
the role of a butler
in a modern hotel.
Later tonight,
dignitaries from around the world
will gather at this table
for a five-course dinner.
Some have brought staff
from their own countries,
but for others,
the hotel butler
must supervise everything,
fulfilling any guest request.
Where does the ins--
Emma, come here.
This is Chef Shinkai.
He's the head chef here.
- Hi.
- Hello.
And I should get back to it.
Scallops don't sear themselves.
- My regards to Mr. Wiloughby.
- Yes.
Nice meeting you.
You too. Bye.
Come here. Come here.
I cannot believe
I just met him.
I've...
I've been following his work
for years.
You're totally fanboying!
No. No...
Maybe...
Yeah, I am.
I just...
You should see
what he does with a risotto.
It's unbelievable.
Did you ask
if there's any openings here?
I can't do that.
Why not?
First of all,
I'm sure he uses a head hunter.
Second of all,
I have a job already.
Yeah, one that you don't want.
What's the harm in asking?
I don't have the skills.
I've had your food,
and trust me,
you have the skills.
How will you know
if you don't ask?
Commence!
I need two wine glasses.
I'm on it.
Teacups...
- Teacup.
- Got it.
Wine. Wine.
Check this...
One inch...
And... time.
Perfect score.
Okay...
I'm third?
Congratulations!
I mean it,
you've been
working so hard.
I'm really impressed.
Thank you.
You're going to do great
on the final!
Hey, Conroy.
What's up?
We're all heading
into dinner.
Come here,
I want to show you something?
What are you doing?
Where are we going?
I cooked us a special dinner,
my favorite dish,
Beef Wellington.
Just for us?
Yeah.
A surprise celebration
for you rising in the ranks,
but you have to be the one
to pick the wine.
Okay, um...
What do we have here?
Well, it has to
stand up to the meat,
while still complementing
the puff pastry.
Uh-huh.
So I would go with
the medium-bodied pinot noir.
Spot on.
Perfect.
Well, I had a great teacher.
Really, though,
you didn't have to do all this.
I wanted to.
Friends like to cook
for friends.
I'm a very lucky friend.
It's too bad.
We'll probably end up
working on different continents.
Hey,
don't tempt fate.
We haven't graduated yet.
There's always time
to flunk out.
Yeah.
So here's to...
continuing success
and, uh...
and to not flunking out.
To not flunking out.
Commence.
What is it?
This is the wrong red.
One second.
[Lisa, whispering] Hurry.
And pour.
Thank you.
I am happy to say,
for all of you here
still standing,
you have passed
this evening's graduation exam
with flying colors.
You are all going to be
full-fledged butlers.
Ms. Conroy.
Yes, sir.
Tonight,
you impressed me.
You kept calm
and worked well under pressure.
As a result,
my letter of recommendation
will be off to Kensington
first thing in the morning.
Thank you so much!
Earned and deserved.
You're going to make
a splendid butler.
Thank you.
Oh, well done, Emma,
well done.
Thanks.
Sleep well.
Good night, everybody.
Well done, you all.
- Good night.
- We did it!
Good night.
There you are.
You sorta disappeared
after we all got the good news.
Yeah, I just needed a second
to take it all in.
I'm happy for you.
I am.
You did it.
Thank you.
I couldn't have done it
without you.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just grappling
with the idea that I, um...
that I'm gonna be a butler
for the rest of my life.
Ha ha.
It's okay, though, it's good.
It is.
You've shown me
so many good parts
about the job.
But not enough
to make you want to be
a butler?
What about trying
one last Hail Mary?
What do you mean?
Well, your parents are coming
to the graduation celebration,
right?
Yeah.
What if you ask Mr. Wiloughby
if you could cater it?
You do not give up, do you?
Never.
You should always go after
what you want.
Let me think about it.
And so
I'm personally thrilled
to be graduating
this fine group
of dedicated young men and women
who will soon be
joining the ranks
of one of the most
honorable professions
in existence,
being of great service
to others
and representing
the very pinnacle of decorum.
Ms. Martin and I
offer our heartiest
congratulations to them,
and wish them
the greatest of good luck
with their careers.
So, how about
a big round of applause?
I'm so proud of you, honey.
Years in the making,
and here you are,
getting everything you wanted.
Yup, years and years.
Yeah.
Thank you, Mom.
Who's that?
Oh, Henry.
I don't think I've ever seen
your eyes light up like that.
Shh! Mom,
this is Henry Walker,
and his parents,
Dana and Phillip.
Nice to meet you.
You as well.
I'm glad your mom
is here for this.
We were able to secure
a position for you
as underbutler
to the Count of Kensington.
What?
You... You were?
Seriously?
Thank you so much.
I don't know what to say.
Thanks.
We're happy to help.
Henry speaks so highly of you,
and we can see why.
Aw...
You're going to love Scotland.
It's beautiful.
Oh, I know I will.
I can't even imagine.
Scotland?
Oh, wow, that's far.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah.
Mom, I've been working
towards this my whole life.
Yeah.
Mm, you're right.
Ever since
you were a little girl.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Have you tried the food?
Aye.
The sausage rolls
were to die for.
And the sauce
on the shrimp?
Amazing.
Right? You should try
the crab cakes.
Here I go.
Mm, it's delicious.
- Oh, indeed!
- Mm-hmm.
Did the school chef
cater this, then?
Actually, no.
No, I did.
What, as your final, then?
No.
No, Dad, I, uh,
I volunteered
to cook the food for this.
So well done.
Really? Thanks, Mom.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
I'm, uh...
I'm very, very glad
to hear you say that.
Of course.
And the reason is...
I was actually hoping
you would enjoy the food so much
that you would see
why I think I'm suited
for a career as a chef
and not a butler.
Your skill was never in doubt.
That's why as a butler
you can go further
than anyone could.
It's because
of your many skills
that you can truly
control a house.
Hey.
Can I help you carry those?
No, no, no, I got it.
You sure?
Mm-hmm.
All right.
So this is it, huh?
Goodbye?
I guess so.
Yeah.
I'm going to miss
seeing you around.
Ah, I don't know.
I don't know about that.
I will.
Um... do you remember
when you fell
and smashed all the dishes
on this carpet?
When I fell.
Nice.
Yeah, that's
how it happened, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean,
maybe I nudged you.
Mm-hmm.
- Bye.
- See you.
I wouldn't have
made it through without you.
Yeah, you would have.
You would've found a way.
Mm... I'm not so sure.
I hope you know
that you're a fantastic chef,
you really are,
and no matter
where you're working,
or what uniform you're wearing,
you'll be great.
You gotta promise me something.
Okay.
Take a day off,
like, once in a while.
Enjoy your life.
Okay.
Outside of work.
Promise?
I'll do my best.
Okay.
All right.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
See ya.
The grounds extend
all the way down to the stream,
up past the foothills
on the north side.
In the house,
you'll be responsible
for every room,
including the master's study
and personal billiards room.
On your days off,
feel free to go explore town,
but I must warn you,
as a new butler
it's doubtful
you'll get any time off.
My first year,
I believe I only had
a single day to myself.
Now, come inside,
and I'll show you
the kitchens.
The last one, he said,
"It's haggis.
You eat it!"
Oh, my...
I just don't know
if I like Nice in the summer.
Too many tourists.
That's what you said
about the Amalfi Coast,
and you loved that.
But that was different.
We had our own villa.
I remember that.
Absolutely fabulous views.
Oh, Positano?
Beautiful.
It was our anniversary.
We had a lovely time,
didn't we, dear?
I bought her that pendant.
Aye.
That smells delicious.
Beef Wellington.
It's the Count's favorite.
- Aye.
- Mine as well.
- Oh.
- Really?
I'd like to propose a toast.
Hey, honey.
It must be late there.
It is.
Well, everything okay?
Yeah.
How did that big dinner go
with the guys
from the House of Lords?
It went well.
It was, um...
yeah, exactly what I pictured.
Okay, so why do you sound
so down in the dumps?
What if I was wrong?
About what?
What I thought I wanted.
Well, then you'd...
you'd be human.
I love being a butler,
I really do,
but I...
I don't know,
I want to experience
all of life.
Look, whatever you decide,
I love you,
and I support you.
I love you, too.
Bye.
I love America,
but it's good
to be home in England.
Henry!
- Yeah?
- Come here.
I want to make a toast.
All right.
Tomorrow is your first day
carrying on the tradition
of the Walker family,
and I could not be more proud.
Smells wonderful, honey.
Oh, thanks, Mom.
See?
Cooking will always be
a great hobby for you.
I ironed your uniform.
I know it's something
you should do,
but I couldn't help it.
And...
I think you should wear
my lucky cufflinks.
You must give Chef the recipe.
No.
Come again?
I said no.
This is my recipe, all right?
I created this.
I perfected it over the years,
and I'm gonna keep it,
and I'm gonna serve it
in my restaurant one day.
Henry.
The night before
your first day,
you really want to go through
all this again?
Yeah, I do.
I do, Dad,
and I want you
to listen to me right now.
I want to be a chef.
No, I'm going to be a chef,
and I'd rather deal with your--
your disappointment
and heartbreak
than live
the rest of my life unhappy.
I love you, all right?
I love you, I really do,
but whether you give me
your blessing or not,
I'm doing this.
Henry...
You are going to make
a marvelous chef,
and I want you to be happy.
Thanks, Mom.
Hi.
Thank you.
Wait!
Stop the car!
Stop the car,
stop the car.
Wait.
Henry?
Emma, hey!
What are you doing here?
I, um...
came up from my parents' place
last night,
and, uh...
I did it.
I did it, I told them
I don't want to be a butler.
- Wait, what?
- Mm-hmm.
And, you know, it was, um...
it was because of you.
You're amazing, Emma Conroy,
you know that?
You are.
You go after life,
you set your goals,
you achieve them,
no matter what anybody says,
and...
you made me believe
that I could do that, too.
I'm so proud of you.
What is this?
Where are you going?
Um...
I decided to quit.
What?
Wh-Why?
This is your dream job!
Dreams change.
I want to work somewhere
I can build a home
and enjoy a family.
I don't want to give that up.
I realize it wouldn't be
a dream come true
if I only got half of it.
Hmm.
A family.
You know, it's funny,
I mean, I was literally
going to look for jobs
around here
so I could...
maybe take you on a date
on your day off.
Well, I wouldn't have gotten
any days off anyway, so...
Right.
Another good reason to quit.
I don't have a job,
you don't have a job.
No.
What are we gonna do?
Don't worry,
I have an idea.
Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Huh.
But first...
I believe the kitchen
is your jurisdiction, sir.
I know,
but suite 504 just canceled
their chocolate-dipped
strawberries
and I really don't want them
to go to waste.
You know what pairs well
with chocolate-dipped
strawberries?
What's that?
Chardonnay, of course.
Ah, very good.
Very good.
Speaking of good pairings...