Sir, one minute warning.
Congratulations again.
Heard anything from Betty,
from my daughter?
No, sir.
We tried her several times.
Okay.
Thank you.
All right, New Hampshire,
we are moments away.
Are you ready?
Ready for Ross!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the next President of
the United States of America,
Thaddeus Ross!
Thank you.
Tonight, America has spoken
in one of the most important
elections of our lifetimes.
We've recognized the urgency
of this moment.
From the disappearance
of half of mankind
to the emergence
of a celestial mass
in the Indian Ocean,
the threats we face show
no signs of slowing down.
But the only way we can
overcome them is together!
Tonight, President Ross
embraced
the theme of togetherness
in his acceptance speech,
but his past
tells a different story,
especially when it comes to
working with heroes
like Captain America.
As two of our nation's
most important leaders,
some question
if they can overcome
their at-times
tumultuous history
to face the challenges ahead.
Here you go, Cap.
During his time as a...
Put your money away.
It's on the house.
Thanks, Charlie.
...leading to Ross
being branded with the moniker
of "the Hulk Hunter."
Following Hulk
and the Abomination's
destruction of Harlem,
Ross was criticized
for what some called
"an unwarranted outburst"
during a press conference.
In fact, many blamed Ross
for the collateral damage,
believing it was his
relentless pursuit
of Banner's Hulk
that led to the rampage.
It also resulted in
the President-elect's
estrangement from
his daughter,
Doctor Betty Ross,
Bruce Banner's ex-girlfriend.
But in a surprising turn
of events,
he managed to
shift the narrative,
and silence
his harshest critics
by apprehending
the man responsible
for the Abomination.
How we lookin' down there?
Well, SERPENT mercenaries
entered with a package
about an hour ago.
They're handing it
to the buyer any minute.
We know what they're carrying?
That is classified
per the White House.
Of course it is.
Where's Eagle-One?
We have strike authorization.
Eagle-One is entering
the target airspace now.
Upload the compound's
covert entry points.
Covert? Really?
You must be new.
Wait for it.
Sam, SEAL team
is six minutes out.
Copy that.
How the hell
did he just do that?
Cap's gear was a gift
from the Wakandans
for helping them out.
I heard even the wrapping
paper was made of vibranium.
No, man. I'm kidding. Come on.
Joaquin, Redwing's pickin' up
hostages inside.
-I'm goin' in.
-Negative.
The package is the priority.
Have
the SEALs track the package.
I'm on the hostages.
Redwing, send them a scan
of the building.
What is it?
That's Sidewinder.
He's the head of SERPENT.
He's not supposed to be here.
Ah.
You're praying, Padre.
Padre.
Padre. Padre, Padre, Padre.
Kill them.
- No. No!
- Kill them one at a time.
Silencio!
Captain America is here.
Do you copy?
Move, move, move!
Vámonos, vámonos.
Get the package outta here.
SERPENT's on the move
with the canister, Sam.
I'm kinda busy right now!
Redwing, on my mark.
Stop.
Stay back!
Or we'll shoot them.
SERPENT's gettin' farther away
with the canister, Sam,
and Sidewinder's
headed to the chapel.
I already know
what you're trying to do.
You can't be at two places
at once.
All right, this time.
But don't get yourself killed.
No dying. Copy that.
Buyer didn't show.
Looks like you need
better clients.
You don't need to worry.
I'll find whoever
wasted my time.
You have bigger concerns.
The Captain America
I dreamt of killing
was bigger than you.
I'm happy to disappoint.
I bet you break easy.
Not that easy.
Not that hard.
I heard your rib go.
You need a minute?
Nope. Nope,
let's get this over with.
I got shit to do today.
Whoo-hoo!
Damn.
Nobody saw that.
Sam, package is secured.
I'll add your star
to my collection.
Need a minute?
That's what I thought.
Save some for us, Cap.
He has a fractured arm,
so be gentle.
"Keep your face
always to the sunshine,
and the shadows
will fall behind you."
The quote was Betty's idea.
She's still not speaking
with you?
No.
She doesn't believe
I've changed.
Really changed.
I don't think I'm gonna get
another shot.
Comin' up on the end of
my first hundred days, Leila.
They're gonna define me.
This treaty's gotta work.
Hello.
Mr. President,
the mission was a success.
All right, fill me in.
Cap and the
SEAL team saved the hostages.
The package is secure
and en route to the US.
How's your brother?
Oh, wow, you remember.
-He's in the Air Force.
-Yeah.
Probably 'cause of you.
I try not to hold that
against him.
It's a weird place
-for a handoff, right?
-Mm-hmm.
Wide open, soft perimeter.
You think the buyer
ever intended on showin' up?
You think SERPENT got played?
What are they sayin'?
Same thing.
Contract was anonymous.
Fifty mil to steal the
canister en route to Japan.
Then show up here
and meet the buyer.
Hmm.
Let us know if you get a trace
on Sidewinder.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
You'll notice, I did not die,
and people are saying
I did not die in style.
Who is saying that?
-People.
-What people?
Everybody.
Everybody is saying that.
Look, tell me I don't make
your old gear look brand-new.
You've got on the greaves
upside down.
I'm joking.
You look good, man.
All right. Fair enough.
That means that
you're finally gonna
introduce me to Ant-Man?
Nope.
Well, at least
you gotta teach me
your aerial kick, man.
Look, if I'm gonna be Falcon,
I gotta know everything.
In no way
are you ready for that.
But I got a guy who'll
teach you the fundamentals
from the ground up
Absolutely.
Now, he's not a people person.
So you gotta learn
how to keep your mouth shut.
Can you do that?
He's gonna love me, bro!
Are you kidding me?
-That's not the right answer.
-He's gonna love me.
What's up, OG?
Who's the pretty boy?
"Pretty boy"? You didn't
tell gramps about me?
I'm the new Falcon.
-No, you're not.
-Yes, I am.
This is Joaquin Torres.
Been workin' with him
for three years.
I haven't figured out
how to shut him up yet.
So what are we doing here?
Orthopedics? Uh...
How to relearn how to walk
after you break a hip?
Oh, sh--
Oh, shit.
That's Isaiah Bradley.
The-- The Isaiah Bradley?
You brought me to
the forgotten Cap?
Why didn't you say something?
It is a pleasure to meet you.
Your missions in Korea
are legendary.
And what, and after that,
no action?
I mean, a lot's changed
in the world.
We could've used
another super soldier.
The United States government
threw me in prison
for 30 years.
They experimented on me
for decades.
Yikes, that's-- that sucks.
Can we start?
Let's do it.
No vibranium wings,
no shield,
no super soldier serum.
I wanna see
if he's got three in him.
Get those flags, Sam!
Cap v Cap!
That's one.
Let's go!
Orthopedic.
That's two.
I'm sorry.
What were you sayin'?
See? Not a people person.
-In a fight, the last hit...
-Is the only hit that matters.
I know. Shut up, but thanks.
All right, that's it.
Tag me in. I'm ready.
Captain America doesn't
get to take five. Let's go.
I need to take this.
I'm not takin' five.
-You still got the plastic on.
-No! I don't...
Maybe I wanted it on there.
Oh, you want me
to make the text bigger?
So you can read it?
Yeah, I'll hold
for the President.
Where you going?
You wanna talk about it?
It just doesn't
sit right with me.
Captain America,
answering to the President.
The President of the country
who stole your life?
It's not just that.
We're talkin' about
Thaddeus "Thunderbolt" Ross.
Son of a bitch
earned that nickname, too.
Look, I know, Isaiah,
firsthand.
Remember,
Ross threw me in the Raft.
Hounded me, Steve and Natasha
for years.
So why are you
workin' for him?
As long as you do,
Captain America
stands for people like him.
You've got no business
workin' for the government.
You see what's going on
out there?
The country is lost.
Standing next to
the President,
even if it's Ross...
it gives people hope.
Now, come on,
give me some credit.
I have a friend who works
in the White House.
She'll let me know if Ross
starts acting out of turn.
None of this means
I forgot about you.
I see what you're doin'.
What?
Pullin' that counseling
bullshit on me.
Look, trust me.
My eyes are wide open on
this, okay?
I know Ross will never change,
but he is the President.
So you gonna tell me
what he wanted
or are you plannin' on
makin' me guess?
He invited Joaquin and I
to the White House,
and I said
under one condition.
If he extended an invitation
to you as well.
I know you're gonna say no,
but it would mean a lot to me
if you were there.
We just...
gotta get you a suit.
I have a damn suit.
For real?
Then why are you
always wearin'
that ratty-ass sweatsuit?
Come on,
you gonna come or what?
See, Isaiah? This is
what I'm talking about.
Now you're going to
the White House. Look at that.
- You look good, OG.
- Wow, man. Damn.
I told you I was gonna get you
out of those sweats.
Look at you now, man.
Yeah, I didn't know
Men's Warehouse
made that size.
Hey, Faith and I
got married in this.
Okay, all right, all right.
I'm sure she would be proud.
I hope so.
Feels strange to walk right
into the belly of the beast.
Hey, I'm sure
it can't be easy.
It ain't.
Which is why
we gotta celebrate.
I don't care
if it is Ross in charge.
We are guests of honor
at the White House, man!
- When does that ever happen?
- Right.
And they sent us a limo, man.
What?
And we look good.
- Yeah.
- What?
Old school,
you got your smell-good on.
What?
And you got
the houndstooth on.
And we got the good stuff.
It's party time.
Captain America!
Captain, Captain, over here.
- Cap, over here!
- Mr. Bradley.
Over here!
-Hey, Isaiah. Check it out.
-Oh.
Whoa, man, look at this!
Oh, we gotta get a pic.
Let's do it.
Tres amigos on three.
Uno, dos, tres. Ah!
Yeah, that's my
new wallpaper. Look at that.
- Pretty good.
- It's good?
Can you send it to me?
Yeah, I'll AirDrop it to you
right now.
You do know
what AirDrop is, right?
Of course,
I know what AirDrop is.
What's AirDrop?
You see, you should have it.
Just hit "Accept"
and it pops up.
- I did that.
- Excuse me, gentlemen.
The President
needs Mr. Wilson.
I'll see you guys inside.
-Hey.
Sam, just keep an open mind.
Why? What am I walking into?
Thi-- This is not
the picture you took.
Oh, I sent you
the wrong picture.
Oh, my Lord.
Well, that's
a very good point.
I'll consider it.
Wilson.
Folks, can you give us
the room?
Uh...
Thanks.
Doctor's orders.
Not quite a cigar,
but better than that damn gum.
Hmm.
Thanks for comin' in.
Welcome to the White House.
Well, thank you
for the invite, sir.
I have to admit, I'm still
gettin' used to the new look.
Yeah, well,
they said lose the mustache
or lose the election.
Thanks for your help
down in Mexico.
Retrieving that canister might
just have saved this treaty.
I was just doing my job, sir.
You and I
haven't always agreed
on how much latitude
enhanced individuals deserve.
But what you've accomplished
has given me reason
to reconsider.
Which is why I want you,
Captain America,
to help me
rebuild the Avengers.
-The Avengers?
-Yes, sir.
Well, with
all due respect, sir,
when you passed
the Sokovia Accords,
you tore the Avengers apart.
Why the change of heart?
I represent all Americans now.
Hell, half of 'em
wouldn't even
be here without the Avengers.
The country needs this.
And when we disagree on
how to manage a situation...
what happens then?
We figure it out together.
Look, you don't have to
give me an answer now.
Just think about it.
Prime Minister Ozaki.
-Great to see you, sir.
-And you.
Thank you for being here.
Here we are.
Sam Wilson,
Prime Minister Ozaki.
Not bad.
Would you like a picture?
Sure.
Sam, please.
Now,
stand a little bit closer.
-Thank you, gentlemen.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Work with me, Sam.
We'll show the world
a better way forward.
That was unexpected.
Maybe it's an opportunity.
So?
How was it?
He asked me
to restart the Avengers.
Wait, what now?
-That's huge, man.
-I don't know.
We'd have to work for him.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the President of the
United States, Thaddeus Ross.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
It's my great privilege
to host you
at the White House
on this historic evening.
When the celestial mass
emerged in the Indian Ocean,
we did what we often do.
We squabbled over it.
Countries rushed in
to claim it as their own,
setting up research facilities
to exploit its resources.
What was found
inside that island
is nothing short of
the discovery
of the millennium.
Its potential applications
in tech, in medicine,
in defense are immeasurable.
It's even more indestructible
than vibranium.
And it's not controlled
by an isolationist nation.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I present to you...
adamantium.
The first and only
refined sample
was stolen from
a Japanese mining site.
But happily,
it's been recovered
and is in a secure location.
And we have two incredibly
brave men to thank for that.
Joaquin Torres and our own
Captain America, Sam Wilson.
What we do next
with this discovery
will determine
how history judges us.
If we ratify this treaty,
together we can produce
enough adamantium
to fairly and equitably
distribute it
around the world.
Sir, you need to sit down.
Isaiah! What are you doing?
Sam!
-Sir, are you hit?
-No.
Go, go, go!
Mr. President, come with me.
Shit.
Isaiah!
-Get on the ground now!
-Do not move.
What's happening?
I don't know.
But you gotta stop.
- Stop!
- Don't!
I can't go back inside, Sam.
Run, and it'll be
worse than that.
Please, Isaiah.
Hey, take it easy!
Watch my suit.
Please, watch my suit.
Cap, I can't let you in.
Hey!
Sam!
Sir, you can't-- you can't--
Sir!
- Sorry, Mr. President.
- Hey, hey, hey.
He stays.
Everybody else, out.
Agent Taylor, you too.
Are you okay?
I should be asking
you that, sir.
Not my first time
being shot at.
Look, I know how
this must look, but...
Can we have a minute?
She stays.
Meet Ruth Bat-Seraph,
my security advisor.
Sir, there's no way
Isaiah could have done this.
-Except he did.
-Maybe somebody got to him.
You're really defending a man
who just tried to kill
the President in front...
-We don't know what happened.
-Enough.
What do we know?
There were five shooters.
Isaiah was one of them.
As was Secret Service
and active military.
This was a coordinated
terrorist attack, sir.
What else do you have?
The song
that preceded the shooting,
we think it was a cue
for the attack.
Sir, Isaiah looked like
he wasn't in control.
He had no idea where he was.
So you're suggesting what?
Let me investigate.
Don't you think you're
a little too close to this?
Sir, your inner circle
has been compromised.
There's possibility
of another attack now.
And what exactly
do you have to offer
that our entire intelligence
and defense apparatus can't?
Well, I won't sit around
and let Isaiah...
Look, I know how important
Bradley is to you.
But consider the optics.
Captain America conducts
a personal investigation
of a friend who tried
to assassinate the President.
Isaiah sacrificed everything
for this country.
He's a soldier. A patriot.
He had no reason to do this.
He had every reason.
Bradley was in prison
for rescuing his own men,
experimented on for 30 years.
The things done to him are
enough to make anyone snap.
Sir, you invited me here
to work together.
-So let's work together.
-I'm afraid that offer expired
when your friend tried
to kill me.
Sam, you shouldn't even be
in these situations.
You're not Steve Rogers.
Ruth,
you have my full authority
to put this thing to bed.
Before this treaty
gets compromised any further.
So that's it?
I'm done?
You're done.
This is bullshit,
and you know it.
This is politics.
So you better wise up, son.
"Son." Who you calling "son"?
Sam. What the hell
are you doing?
I'm going to clear Isaiah.
Storming in there
ain't gonna help him.
-You need Ross on your side.
-Ross?
Open your eyes.
I offer to help,
and he sends me packin'.
Ross is on his own side.
He always has been.
Either you can't see that,
or you don't want to.
Hey.
Don't be that guy.
And what guy is that?
The one who has to do it
the hard way.
Looks like I am that guy.
The nation remains
on high alert.
The Justice Department has
signaled a death penalty case
will be pursued
against Isaiah Bradley.
Just five minutes, Cap.
I could be court-martialed
for this.
I appreciate it, Payumo.
Yes, sir.
How you holdin' up?
Not so good, brother Sam.
Isaiah.
Look me in the eye.
Tell me you didn't
conspire to kill Ross.
Of course I didn't.
What in the world happened
to make you shoot
at the President?
I don't know.
You gotta give me more
than "I don't know."
Is there anything
you remember?
I got a haircut,
picked my suit up at
the cleaners and came to you.
We rode in the limo,
took our photo.
But my phone was on the fritz.
And then, we went over
to the East Room.
One moment I'm sittin' there,
the next I'm standin'
in that park.
I should have stayed
in my damn house,
minded my business.
No, this isn't on you.
Someone's behind all this.
Sam, the last thing I want
is for this to touch you.
Besides...
Look, there ain't no escapin'
for me this time.
I'm gonna die in here.
No, you're not.
I'm gonna get you out.
- You wanna help me?
- Of course.
Don't come back.
Guard.
Sergeant Payumo, get me
a copy of that conversation.
I wanna take another look.
Yes, ma'am.
And good work with Wilson.
Let me know
if he pays another visit.
Roger that.
You get in?
I think I committed
treason and espionage,
but I made it into
the White House's CCTV system.
What am I lookin' for?
When Isaiah went off
in the White House,
it made me think
of a friend of mine.
He was being controlled
by trigger words.
Do you see any strangers
talkin' to Isaiah?
No, well,
we got there, took a picture,
I AirDropped it to him,
but nothin' crazy.
Yeah, but he said his phone
was on the fritz.
Ah. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sam, I think I got something.
What is it?
His phone is like
flashing at him.
Oh, shit, I got
the same thing happening
to one of the other shooters.
What the hell?
Warden Cooper, Ross here.
The prisoner, he's secure?
I can confirm the prisoner
is in his cell.
Do we have eyes
on the bastard?
Personally.
I'm looking at him
right now, sir.
Thank you, Cooper.
Thank you, Mr. President.
I keep goin' back to Mexico.
We were at the White House
because the buyer
never showed.
Why hire SERPENT if you have
no intention on collecting?
Maybe they were expecting
Captain America to come.
What if the buyer wanted
Captain America to come?
And what if they wanted us
at the White House?
But how would
the buyer predict
that we'd get the invite, or
that you would invite Isaiah?
The buyer must be
watching us somehow.
Another thing.
Ruth Bat-Seraph,
Ross's security advisor,
find out what you can
about her.
Copy that.
I'll call you back later.
Target eliminated.
Stand by for proof of death.
Hmm.
No way you came
all the way from Mexico
just to blow up my car.
So you must have made up
with the buyer.
Get him on the phone.
Let me see
if I can resolve this.
"Resolve this"?
The buyer told me everything.
He mentioned that if you
survived the grenade,
there was a 77% chance
you'd try to talk me down.
Hmm.
Look at that.
The buyer told me
a lot actually.
After he didn't show
in Mexico,
he agreed to pay me double
to take you out.
What he doesn't know is that
I would kill you for free.
How often do you get a chance
to kill Captain America?
You're desperate
without your gear.
Nope.
Just a little meaner.
Hello.
Well done, Captain.
But you're not going to like
what's coming next.
Who is this?
How can we trust you to lead
when you can't even keep
your own house in order?
We have the shooters
in custody.
All I'm asking for
is patience.
Patience?
From the Hulk Hunter?
That was a long time ago.
Well, Mr. President,
I was almost killed
in your home yesterday.
And today, you are still
locked in your bunker.
You are not in a position
to be asking for anything.
I agree.
We should continue this
conversation another time.
Gentlemen, wait.
Please.
This treaty is too important
to let it fall apart now.
We made a promise
to our people.
to the world.
We must prevail.
We'll need Japan to proceed.
And
Prime Minister Ozaki's absence
speaks volumes.
I'll get Japan back
to the table.
Ozaki and I go back
a long way.
He's running for re-election.
He needs to assert leadership
on this treaty.
All right, Mr. President,
we'll remain patient
while you try
to get Japan on board.
But if you don't,
we'll have to take
measures into our own hands.
I've gotta get out of here.
Sit down.
Sir, the sweep's not complete.
The longer I stay here,
the weaker I look.
The hell happened to you?
Sidewinder tracked me down.
Well, it looks like
he did a lot more than that.
He's in police custody now.
-Shit, you good?
-I will be.
Last call, trace it.
All right.
Yo, get this.
Ross' advisor,
Ruth Bat-Seraph,
she was born in Israel
and trained in the Red Room.
She's ex-Widow.
That basically means
stay the hell out of her way.
Trust me.
Yep.
Now, this is weird.
Isaiah had Ross
in his crosshairs.
Couldn't miss.
I don't get it.
Why go through all that
trouble just to not kill Ross?
I don't know.
Oh, shit.
I think I located
Sidewinder's last caller.
It's in the middle of nowhere,
West Virginia.
It's just, like,
near some forest.
Database only shows one name.
Camp Echo One.
No satellite imagery.
Away from air traffic.
No infrastructure in the area.
-Do you think it's military?
-Yep.
It's a place they send you
and you never leave.
Ross told me stay out of this.
Eh, he's just the President
of the United States.
You don't have to come
with me.
Duh, I know.
That's what makes it so noble.
Pack as much gear
as you can carry.
I don't know
when we'll be back.
What, you mean like,
"right now" right now?
Yeah.
Oh, shit. Okay.
Well, it's a long-ass drive
to West Virginia,
so we're gonna need
some snacks.
Why did I invite you?
What? Wait, wait, wait.
Wait up!
Ruth Bat-Seraph.
Isaiah Bradley's
in holding cell 14.
-The other shooters are in 15.
-Okay.
Do you need an escort?
Think I'll be just fine.
-Thanks.
-Yes, ma'am.
I'd like to speak to them
one at a time.
Can you... Excuse me?
Payumo.
I'm talking to you. Hey.
Stop! Drop your weapon!
Payumo, what are you doing?
Drop it.
Increase that cadence
and resistance.
Or do whatever the hell
you need to do to get there,
all right?
Just stay in your lane.
Stay in your lane. Here we go.
Out to third!
Eye on the prize.
Eye on the target, baby.
- That's enough.
- Don't think about speed now.
Think about direction.
Think about intention.
If Doctor Eccles asks,
you tell her
I did the whole five miles.
That look.
We touch down in Tokyo
at 0600.
You still think
this is a bad idea?
Sir, whoever orchestrated
the attack
on the White House is still
in the wild.
International travel
brings security risks
we can't anticipate.
We barely got Congress
together on this thing.
If we lose
our international partners,
this treaty's toast.
I have to make this work.
Three miles and change.
I'll let Dr. Eccles know.
Five.
-Five.
Do we have eyes on Wilson?
He left the base a few hours
ago with Joaquin Torres.
They ditched
their smartphones.
They're off-grid.
Well, I don't want a variable
out there
that I can't control.
Get a team,
pick him up, bring him in.
-Yes, sir.
-Yeah.
Breaking
news out of Washington,
President Ross is
on his way to Japan
just a day after surviving
an assassination attempt...
Bet you used to play this
old-ass game all the time.
Damn it.
This is hard.
Right.
The high-stakes
diplomatic visit...
How far are we
from Camp Echo One?
...over control
of Celestial Island.
We're about, like,
an hour away.
Sam, shit. They just
shot up Isaiah's prison.
Is he okay?
Yeah, Isaiah's good,
but the others...
they're dead.
Shit.
Should we go back?
No.
We keep going.
The buyer is pretty smart,
but we're not taking the bait.
Only way to help Isaiah is to
figure out who's behind this.
And whoever is behind it,
they do not want
us getting closer.
Cooper.
What's happening?
Mr. President,
as a precautionary measure,
I have moved the prisoner to--
President Ross,
I miss our little visits.
Tell me something.
Do you ever stop
to ask yourself
who's playing the music?
It's you.
The White House,
the assassination attempt.
That's a way of putting it.
I helped you more
than anyone else.
Only to get what you want.
What do you want?
I wanted my life back, but
it's too late for that now.
You've gotta--
You gotta understand
my position.
-I...
-Oh, I do.
You let me rot in this prison.
And it was my curse
to watch your betrayal
written in probabilities.
I'm making my own choices now.
So many surprises left.
When I'm done,
everyone will know
just who you are,
and Betty will despise you
even more.
Goodbye, Mr. President.
The hell is going on?
I'm putting you in solitary.
Yeah.
Nobody's gonna put me
in solitary ever again.
It's for your protection.
I'll tell you this one more
time for your protection,
I ain't goin'
in a box ever again.
I won't be able to
guarantee your safety.
Safety ain't all
it's cracked up to be.
You still think
I had somethin'
to do with all of this?
I don't know.
Mr. President.
I need you
to drop whatever you're doin'.
Camp Echo One's
been compromised.
Yes, Mr. President.
This is it.
Camp Echo One.
Telescopes must be a facade.
We gotta see
what's underneath.
We've got cameras and guards.
Redwing, cut the fence
and go loop the feed.
Yeah, we got a 28-second
window to get past the guards.
We gotta do the door manually.
Three, two, one,
go.
15 seconds.
I'm trying, man!
Shit!
There's no prisoners in here.
Why is there a lab
in this prison?
What the hell is this place?
What the hell?
Ozaki-san,
I want to assure you
America remains committed
to sharing our adamantium
with the rest of the world.
I trust Japan shares
that commitment.
The world needs this treaty.
Diplomacy must be hard
for you
A man in a country
so used to taking
whatever he wants by force.
Excuse me?
How else to explain your theft
of our adamantium,
only to return it to us
in Washington.
What you're accusing us of
is baseless
and insulting.
So, the information
my intelligence team received
and verified
is incorrect?
Wh--
I'm a fool.
I'm a fool to negotiate
with someone so naive
they don't realize
they're being played.
Naive?
If I'd stolen the sample,
why would I order Captain
America to retrieve it?
I suppose
we'll never know the truth.
Whatever game you're playing,
Japan wants no part in it.
Don't test us, Mr. President.
He's got optogenetic data
on a lot of people.
Don't make me look up words,
Joaquin.
I think he's figured out a way
to plant commands
into people's subconscious
using flashes of light.
This "Mr. Blue" song seems
to be some kind of trigger.
Mind control.
Yeah.
That explains Isaiah.
And that's more important.
Take risks.
Use those incredible brains
of yours.
Wasn't
half bad-looking, was I?
Samuel Sterns.
You know, it takes
an awful lot to surprise me.
There was an 89% chance
you'd turn around
if I put Isaiah Bradley
at risk,
yet here you stand.
You're the buyer.
Indeed.
Hiring SERPENT was
a necessary step
to create a chain
of statistical certainties.
Maybe you're not as smart
as you think you are.
I am, actually.
My mind sees it all,
every probable outcome.
So you hire SERPENT
to steal the adamantium,
shoot up Ross' summit
announcing it
and now you're just
sitting here, waiting.
Why do you wanna kill Ross?
Why does everyone think that
I wanna kill Ross?
Is it because he imprisoned me
here without a trial
after an infusion of gamma
warped the structure
of my brain?
Damn.
Once Ross discovered
how useful I could be,
he kept me here for 16 years,
turning my mind
to solving his problems.
My solutions brought him the
highest office in the country.
If I wanted Ross dead,
he'd be dead.
Well, whatever you're doing,
you're hurting a lot of
people, including my friend.
So this is the last chance
I'm gonna give you to stop it.
Why are you protecting him?
Ross knows I'm responsible
for the White House,
yet he's still letting Isaiah
sit in prison for it.
You know he'll never change.
Let me finish my work.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Please don't be boring!
You think they'll stop us?
For long enough.
You're a fascinating problem.
But soon
you'll be off the board,
so you don't
surprise me again.
This is messed up, man.
It's not even their choice.
I know.
Just try and neutralize.
Punk-ass.
Stand down!
I'm taking them in.
I'll deal with these two.
Okay.
What the hell
are you guys doing here?
Well, that's what
I should be asking you.
Where's Sterns?
If Sterns is in the wind,
we need to set a perimeter,
roadblocks, air support.
He can't have gone far.
Why are you helping us?
'Cause you were right.
I thought that was obvious.
- Freeze!
- Oh. It's okay.
We have orders to take
Captain America into custody.
You already have one
Captain America in custody.
You want another?
You're under arrest
for trespassing
on restricted
government property.
Being right
always go like this?
Most of the time.
I have the clearances.
It's been a long day.
She's ex-Widow.
Just zap the guy.
These orders come
from the President himself.
Get them out of here.
Then we'll just call him.
Ruth, uncuff us now!
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Not again.
- Run!
- Go, go, go. Come on.
Go!
Mr. President,
Japan's claim
seems to be true.
We're trying to determine
the point of the breach.
Sir, we have to tell
Ozaki's team something.
We've got to stop
the bleeding.
I need some time alone.
We don't have much time, sir.
Ozaki just decided to advance
his navy on Celestial Island.
He intends to secure
the adamantium for himself.
Jesus.
France and India are drawing
up occupation strategies...
Mr. President, I suggest that
we return to DC immediately.
-No, I disagree.
-Immediately.
We are going to lose
our opportunity with Ozaki.
We need to regroup and figure
out a different solution.
We can't do that.
No, absolutely not!
We need to ask
for another meeting, sir.
If we call on Ozaki now,
and try to reach out to him,
we can...
We're not gonna miss
the opportunity.
We have to have
another meeting!
I want Carrier Strike Group
Five deployed immediately.
Tell 'em
I'm on my way there now.
Sir, are we seriously
talking about taking control
of Japan's adamantium?
I'm not going home
empty-handed.
If only one country is going
to control adamantium,
it's going to be us.
Make the call!
Taylor!
The President has informed me
that we need to move
Strike Group Five
to Celestial Island
immediately.
I want to be en route to the
Indian Ocean within the hour.
Mr. President,
this is extremely dangerous.
If a war breaks out...
I was a wartime general.
Now I'm a wartime president.
Yes, sir, Mr. President.
What are we doing here?
You say Ross' orders was
to take us into custody
so I called in a favor.
Thanks for doing this.
No problem, Cap. Brass never
makes it down here.
Terminal's set up,
ready to go.
You sure you can knock out
Sterns' mind control?
I should be able
to run a program
that blocks the light signals
that Sterns has been
sending out to control people.
What if
he's already gotten someone?
That's a good point.
Are you crazy?
We're clear here, at least.
You have anybody
that you trust
that can take a look at these
and tell me what's in 'em?
Sure, I got someone.
I'll get on it.
-Thanks. Our guy here?
-Through there.
Listen in.
I'm amazed
you're still standing. Hmm.
Most men don't survive
an axe to the gut.
Kevlar weave, I presume?
Perks of the job.
You said you were gonna find
the man who wasted your time.
I wanna know what you learned.
Samuel Sterns.
Gruesome fella,
don't you think?
I've seen worse.
Not without your Avengers.
Full immunity and I'll talk.
You're crazy.
Who you kiddin'?
You're here because
you're all out of options.
You heard
what he did to those shooters.
A guy like Sterns doesn't like
loose ends alive.
Reduced sentence,
Allenwood, my own cell.
Lemme hear what you got first.
You know, it was my old unit
that found Sterns
in the wreckage of Harlem.
They said he'd been infected
with Bruce Banner's blood,
but it didn't
give him strength.
What did it give him?
A mind capable
of impossible calculations.
Ross being Ross,
he saw an opportunity.
Instead of removing the gamma
from Sterns' blood,
he upped the dose.
Made Sterns his own
personal think tank,
creating technology
and weapons for the state.
Holy shit.
Why did Sterns
go along with it?
Camp Echo One was the stick.
I imagine
a pardon was the carrot.
Ross told Sterns he'd let him
go once he became president.
And yet, here we are.
So Sterns hired you
to steal Japan's adamantium
knowing it would divide
the two countries.
He paid us
through a CIA black fund.
That could kill the treaty
and start a war.
And Ross would be blamed
for the chaos.
How do you think a man
with Ross' temperament
will deal with being caught
in a trap?
If you break out of Allenwood,
I'll find you.
When I break out, Captain,
you won't walk away alive.
-Did you know?
-Of course not.
But Ross is not
that man anymore.
None of us have to be
defined by our past.
Cap, my guy needs 24 hours
on the pills.
Okay. We need to get to DC
and tell Ross
what Sterns is planning.
President Ross isn't in DC.
He's on the USS Milius.
They just moved
into the Indian Ocean.
Japan's warships are also
in proximity.
Shit. Suit up.
We need to move.
May I help you?
Hello, Admiral.
May I use your phone?
Hey, honey.
Who's at the door?
Holy shit.
You ever see
anything like this?
No, I haven't.
Let me do the talking
or he'll never listen.
I haven't seen Ross like this
since the army.
He better snap out of it.
Because whatever Sterns is
planning, it's happening soon.
I want a fleet of F-18s
ready to catapult.
If they turn that ship around,
I want...
What's he doing here?
I told you not
to get involved, Wilson.
I brought him, sir.
I want him outta here!
Sir, you asked me
to run this investigation,
-and the situation is--
-Don't bother with excuses.
You had a simple job
and you failed.
Mr. President,
we've uncovered intel
at Camp Echo One
that could put millions
of lives at risk.
Now, you and I both know
Isaiah's innocent.
I'm happy to have
this conversation in public,
if you like.
This is crazy.
Japan's supposed to be our--
Jackal?
Jackal, do you copy?
Make it quick, Wilson.
I've got Japan's fleet
on my ass
trying to make it to
that island before we do.
That's exactly what he wants.
Sterns has been pulling
the strings on everything.
SERPENT's theft
of the adamantium,
the attack on the White House.
The CIA leak to Japan.
He's pitting you and Japan
against each other
to ensure that
this moment happens.
How the hell did he do
all that from prison?
Mind control.
He created a technology
that allowed him
to control the minds
of anyone he targeted.
Including maybe you, sir.
Have you been feelin'
like yourself lately?
Of course I have.
But he has
your data, sir. Why?
I don't know.
If he can control minds,
surely he can hack files.
The logs show that you visited
Camp Echo One numerous times.
To ensure a high-value
prisoner was secure.
Yeah, but the scans, the EKG,
the blood work
was all taken there, sir.
This is ridiculous.
Mr. President,
answer the question.
I don't have to answer you!
Why visit a Black Site,
-in the middle of nowhere...
-Wilson, stop!
I order you to stop!
-...to conduct these tests?
-I order you to stop!
-Why?
-Because I was dying,
goddamn it!
Because my heart was failing!
No one could figure it out
until he did.
These things
have kept me alive.
And in return, I gave him hope
that he might get
his life back.
He got a lab to do the work.
I even tried
to get him moved but--
But you couldn't risk
losing the pills.
After your friend the Hulk
and the Abomination
destroyed Harlem,
someone had to take the fall.
Sterns was just...
collateral damage.
I have dedicated
my entire life
to serving this country.
The one person that matters...
doesn't seem to understand.
Betty never forgave me for
sending the army after Banner.
I had to survive...
...so that my daughter knew
that there was more
to her father.
That I'm the same man
that used to take her
to see the cherry blossoms.
She still can, sir.
I know what it's like...
to feel you have
somethin' to prove.
Everyone only seeing
one thing.
But when showing
there's more to you,
it's not about
when times are easy.
It's about moments like this.
Now, we're here
because Sterns wants revenge
and doesn't care
if he incites a war.
We're playing right
into his hand.
Mr. President,
two of our F-18s
just fired
on the Japanese fleet.
Keep hailing those pilots.
Damage
to Japanese fleet minimal.
Ready air defense systems.
What the hell
are those pilots doing?
Call them back in.
We tried, sir.
Jackal and Whiskey
won't respond.
We gotta get our birds
in the air.
You have two ready
to fly now, sir.
Go.
Sterns got to our pilots
before I shut down the system.
We need to get the Japanese
out of the air.
Stay close
and don't get yourself killed.
No dying, copy that.
Return to your fleet.
Jackal's headed towards
the Japanese fleet.
Shit! He just fired on them.
Mr. President,
do not send more fighters up.
We need Japan to see
we're trying to deescalate.
Sir,
six Japanese missiles inbound.
Launch intercept missiles.
Damn, two got through.
Take the one on the right.
Redwing, a little help.
Sir, you need to convince
Japan to ground their planes.
This is what we expected
from a Ross presidency.
Mr. Prime Minister, two
of our pilots have gone rogue.
Call off your planes.
We're being manipulated.
Certainly.
By you.
Hiding your assassins
behind Captain America.
He's trying
to bring them down now, sir.
If those pilots are not
taking orders from you,
then who gives them
their commands?
That's what I thought.
Mr. President?
Ah,
now we're getting somewhere.
That fire in the belly.
The rage.
Why don't you just let it out?
Are you all right, sir?
I just need a moment.
Joaquin,
Whiskey's coming at you.
Copy that.
Sam, once we're done,
you gotta teach me your moves!
Altitude. Altitude.
Altitude.
Whiskey's away.
Send rescue.
Roger, sending rescue.
You have two Japanese fighters
coming up on your tail.
Why the hell
are they still chasing us?
We're trying to help them.
Because Ross won't tell
them who's really behind this.
All that hatred
you try to hide,
all the ugliness,
it's still there, Ross,
smoldering behind the eyes.
Joaquin,
I'm goin' after Jackal.
Roger that.
I'll keep these guys busy.
What have you done to me,
you bastard?
What we agreed on.
Maybe a hair more.
You poisoned me!
Stop taking the pills then.
But we both know you won't.
Give me what I want.
Stop fighting it.
No!
Sam, Jackal
just fired his last missiles!
I got one.
Going after the another.
- Back off! I'll get it!
- No, no! I got it.
-Back off!
-I got it.
Joaquin!
Joaquin's down!
I'm goin' after him.
We'll send search and rescue.
You have to stop Jackal.
Damn it!
I'm putting an end
to this now.
Give in to your rage.
I'm taking your legacy
as we speak.
Come on, Ross.
You're almost there.
You can rip their fleet apart
with your bare hands,
and kill Captain America.
Oh, shit.
Let the monster
inside you out.
Altitude, altitude, altitude.
Unleash your anger.
Unleash your hatred.
Redwing, stabilize!
Nothing can stop you, Ross.
You can crush them all.
Mr. President?
Sir. Are you okay?
Captain America neutralized
the rogue pilots.
Japan's recalling
their planes.
Get Ozaki back on the line.
We can fix this.
Where's Joaquin?
Med-evac just got to him.
Thank God.
A crisis was narrowly avoided
when a brief dogfight
broke out
between Japanese
and US military forces
over Celestial Island.
US Air Force Lieutenant
Joaquin Torres
was shot down
during the skirmish,
and is now in surgery at
Walter Reed National Military
Medical Center.
His condition is critical.
Here, give me that clamp.
Gonna need to pack this!
The pressure's stable.
Suction!
I can't see anything.
More suction.
Retractors.
It's a private room.
Go away.
I missed you, too.
I hate to admit it,
I'm glad you're here.
You looked good out there
on that six o'clock.
But then I saw this.
The doctors had to
restart his heart.
They don't know if...
This isn't your fault.
It makes me think of Steve.
How many alien invasions
did he stop again?
Two.
Wow.
What made me think
I could follow that?
I should've took the serum.
Like Steve, like you.
Why?
Because this is all startin'
to seem much bigger than me.
Ross, he asked me
to restart the Avengers, Buck.
But Joaquin's in here,
Isaiah's in prison,
and Sterns...
I had him. I had Sterns
right in my hands.
And he got away.
He damn near pushed us
to the brink of war,
because I wasn't...
Say what you need to say.
Steve made a mistake.
No, he didn't.
He gave you that shield
not because
you're the strongest,
but because you're you.
You think
if you had that serum
you'd be able to protect
all the people you care about.
Steve had it, and he couldn't.
You're a human being,
and you're doing your best.
Steve gave people
something to believe in.
But you...
you give 'em
something to aspire to.
Did your speechwriters
help you with that?
They did, yeah.
The ending, a little bit.
Well, did you like it?
No, no, it was good.
Solid B-plus.
-Emotional.
-Yeah, very. I felt it.
But just enough.
Yeah.
Listen, I gotta catch a plane.
I have a campaign fundraiser.
It's so stupid.
It's gonna be all right, man.
Thanks, Buck.
I love you, buddy.
-Was that...
-Yep.
Future Congressman
James Buchanan Barnes.
He's taller in real life,
nice smile too,
good amount of teeth,
great posture.
He's 110 years old.
I can work with that.
While the investigation
into the White House
assassination attempt
and the shocking shooting at
Joint Base Anacostia-Bolling
is still under way,
Isaiah Bradley is set to go
before a military judge
tomorrow.
I need some air.
It's a stunning
fall from grace for a man
brought out from the shadows
by Captain America.
Just two years after
being exonerated
for unjust charges,
Bradley now finds himself
held in solitary confinement
and facing a possible
death sentence.
Okay, reset.
Let's go again.
Talk to me.
Dunphy,
you check out my report?
All right,
what am I looking at?
Those pills you gave me,
they're loaded
with gamma radiation,
engineered to be
absorbed into the blood.
Where the hell
did you get these?
Shit. I gotta make a call.
This sound is currently
affecting your equilibrium.
When I turn this dial,
it will disrupt
your heartbeat.
I take no pleasure
in your death,
but I can't have you
calling the Captain.
Who are you?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm the hero.
Sir.
Agent Taylor.
Just wanted to let you know
that every guest
has been screened,
and we also did three sweeps
of the Rose Garden.
Thank you.
-See you out there.
-Yes, sir.
Hello?
Hello. Hi.
I... how are you?
I'm sorry,
I should have called
after the attack
at the White House.
Are you okay?
Oh...
I'm fine.
It's really good
to hear your voice.
I didn't think you'd answer.
Betty, I... I know I've made
a lot of mistakes.
But I'm trying to change,
to be a better person.
Um...
Maybe we could take a...
a walk sometime?
See the cherry blossoms,
like the old days.
Yeah. That could be nice.
Okay. I love you.
Bye, Dad.
Please.
Good afternoon, everyone.
When I took office,
I promised we would create
a true, lasting peace.
Today, we begin
to realize that promise.
Captain America...
would you do me the kindness
of counseling a bitter man
at the end of his rope?
That's what you do, isn't it?
Guess we have five minutes
until the MPs drag your ass
outta here.
You ruined my grand finale
on the Indian Ocean.
So now I'm forced
to turn myself in
to get what I want.
Well, if you're waitin'
for an apology,
we'll be here awhile.
I'm waiting for you to realize
that we both want
the same thing,
for the world to see Ross
as he truly is.
I'm proud to say our treaty
will finally be signed.
I'll take a couple questions.
Sir, what do you say
to reports
that relations with Japan
broke down
over your handling
of the White House
assassination attempt?
Despite fabrications
that some have used
to turn us against each other,
our bonds have proved strong.
You kept Ross alive for years.
Didn't kill him when you had
the chance at the White House.
The way I see it,
the Indian Ocean
wasn't about starting a war.
You wanted to
destroy his legacy.
Yes.
But you haven't
figured out how.
The pills.
I got somebody on that, too.
Not anymore, you don't.
Is it true hostilities
in the Indian Ocean
occurred because
the Japanese discovered
it was, in fact,
your government
who paid for the SERPENT
mercenary group
to steal their adamantium?
We did not pay them.
Ross turned me into a monster.
It's only right that I do
the same thing to him.
Why aren't you smiling?
-On the ground!
-Hold it!
You ever use
that big brain of yours
to consider that maybe
you're wrong about Ross?
Wanna bet?
Yeah.
-Where are you going?
-To stop this.
Get on the ground, now.
You have the right
to remain silent...
Captain America!
If I'm right about Ross,
you're going to die.
You're going to die!
Mr. President,
Dr. Samuel Sterns
just turned himself in.
He claims you
promised him a pardon
if he worked on secret
government projects for you.
That is a lie.
President Ross,
I miss our little visits.
What do you want?
I wanted my life back,
but it's too late
for that now.
Sir...
I helped you
more than anyone.
Well, let me explain.
They have to know.
You gotta
understand my position.
Oh, I do.
You let me rot in this prison.
Leave me alone!
- Leave me! Let me go!
- Sir! Sir!
I cannot let you.
-You can't let me? Let me?
-I cannot...
Everyone will know
just who you are.
And Betty will despise you
even more.
Sir, please.
Sir.
Oh, my God.
Since when were they red?
President Ross?
Agent Taylor, do we fire?
This is what Sterns wanted.
Jesus.
Sam, I gotta get these people
outta here.
Set a perimeter
around the White House.
No.
Fall back. Fall back!
Get down!
Sam, drones incoming.
Ruth, I need you to
clear Hains Point.
I'll lure Ross there.
Sam, are you crazy?
He'll kill you.
Do it!
You can still fight this,
Ross.
Do you see where you are?
You remember this place?
You used to come here
with Betty.
That didn't work.
Okay.
You want me?
Come and get me!
Sam?
Sam, can you hear me?
Sam, are you okay?
Please tell me I knocked
that son of a bitch out.
Shit.
Backup's five minutes away.
No, tell them wait.
What?
Should've taken that serum.
Bucky is full of shit.
I'm gonna lose that bet.
Ross.
We both know you can
take me out with one punch,
but I don't think
you wanna do that.
I know you've done
some terrible things.
Now, I might be crazy...
but I think you're
trying to change.
Now's the time to prove it
to the world.
Prove it to Betty.
The army is transferring
Sterns to a secure facility.
We should get you
to the hospital.
There's somewhere
we gotta go first.
That's three, old man.
I told you I'd get you out.
Took you so long?
Thank you, Sam.
I got you.
I have a few broken bones,
so...
Come on, Mr. Bradley.
We got a little paperwork
to fill out,
and then you're free to go.
Worldwide talks continue
in the arms race
for the new element
as we enter the
brave new world of adamantium.
Back in our nation's capital,
ground was broken
on the restoration
of the White House,
marking a significant step
towards normalcy
for the country.
Right this way.
Mr. President.
How're your digs?
Intentionally uncomfortable.
I heard the food
hasn't got any better either.
You heard right.
Bradley got out?
Yes, sir.
That's good.
Mr. President,
about your blood work.
It seems Sterns raised
the level of gamma
in those pills over time.
It built up in your body
over the years.
That led to your...
Led to my little tantrum.
Which is why I have to be
in here.
Good solid walls, these.
Yeah.
But I have to say,
it wasn't nothin' to see you
take full responsibility
for your actions.
Give up your office.
Accept your sentence.
I had to let the country
move on.
Japan decided to uphold
the treaty, by the way.
Us too.
The Ozaki-Ross Accords.
You did it.
Sam, why are you here?
Sir?
We were on different sides
of this thing
every step of the way.
Look, if we can't see
the good in each other,
we've already lost the fight.
Besides, I wanted to make sure
an old soldier was okay.
I'd love to stay, but looks
like you have another visitor.
Hi, Dad.
I guess I have to give you
a raincheck on that walk.
It's all right.
We could just sit and talk
for a little while.
I'd like that.
Me too.
How's the kid doin' today?
He's still a little out of it
but doin' better.
I'm gonna let you two
catch up.
Hey, where you headed?
Back to Baltimore?
No.
I got Ruth and me tickets
for tonight's game, courtside.
It's the least I could do
for gettin' me out.
You know,
I'm happy you found a friend
as grumpy as you are
to go to games with.
Say it again.
I'm playing.
Got you.
The Falcon awakens.
Couldn't let you
have all the fun.
I'm sorry I screwed up.
Screwed up? Get out of here.
I did.
You never messed up
like I have.
You never got
shot out of the sky
and nosedived into
the Indian Ocean.
You're always on point.
Yeah.
Because if I'm not on point...
I feel like I let down
everyone else who was fightin'
for a seat at that table.
That's pressure, man.
It weighs on you.
Makes you wonder
if you'll ever just be...
enough.
Where I grew up,
I only ever got
to see heroes online.
Or on TV.
It always felt so far away.
And I kept thinkin' maybe
if I get out of Miami,
you know,
maybe one day I could be...
Don't say Ant-Man.
No, man.
I wanted to be you.
Well...
Sam Wilson.
Because that guy?
That guy won't ever give up.
That pressure,
that responsibility
you talk about?
I want that too, man.
You know it's all
about timin', right?
Control your spin, then hit
your thruster before you kick.
- No.
- Yeah.
No. That's...
That's it.
I should get shot out
of the sky more often.
Yeah, you will.
Okay.
You know, you're gonna
come back from this.
I know.
And when that time comes,
make sure the suit's ready,
'cause Ross was right
about one thing.
The world needs the Avengers.
-For real?
-Yeah.
Hell, yeah.
I wasn't thinking
about it before,
but now that
you bring it up...
Oh, boy.
...since the wings
are damaged,
I was thinking, I'm like,
what could make--
No.
You didn't hear
-what I was gonna ask you.
-No. Whatever you ask, nope.
I'm just saying,
maybe you have, like,
the Wakandans on speed dial
and could get me some...
A hookup on an upgrade
on the wings.
You're gonna ask the Wakandans
for a hookup?
Yeah.
That is the most Miami thing
in the world.
Are you kidding? They gonna
hook me up, man. Yo.
Told you you were gonna
lose that bet.
You wanna know what's funny?
I'm not in the mood
for your jokes.
You killed a lot of good men
trying to get your revenge.
Trust me, we don't share
the same sense of humor.
We share the same world,
don't we?
This world you would
die to save?
It's coming.
I've seen it
in the probabilities,
seen it plain as day.
All you heroes
protecting this world...
do you think
you're the only ones?
Do you think
this is the only world?
We'll see what happens
when you have to protect
this place from the others.