Downloaded from
YTS.MX
♪♪
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
♪♪
-And now, how 'bout
something lovely?
Our next guests
are two legendary
Grammy award-winning
singer/songwriters
and member of
the Rock & Roll Hall of Fame,
and tickets for their
Troubadour Reunion Tour
go on sale on Saturday --
please welcome to the program
Carole King and James Taylor.
[ Applause ]
♪♪
-♪ Lookin' out
on the morning rain ♪
-James Taylor is
a major force in music,
one of the most popular
and prolific songwriters
of our time.
-I think she's
the best there is,
Miss Carole King,
ladies and gentlemen.
-Carole King began her music
career when she was just a teen,
and by the early '70s she had
reached the top of the charts
around the world.
-James Taylor, one of my
all-time favorites.
One of the most influential
singer/songwriters of all time.
-And now, Carole King
and James Taylor
are getting ready
to tour together
for the first time
in 40 years.
-It's a bit of history,
tell us about
the original
Troubadour Reunion.
-In November of 2007 James
called me and said,
"Let's get together and play
with some of our old friends,"
and we had such a great time.
-Like Carole said,
it felt so good,
we decided to take it
on the road.
[ Cheering and applause ]
[ Tuning guitar ]
♪♪
♪ There's something in
the way she moves ♪
♪ Looks my way,
or calls my name ♪
♪ That seems to leave this
troubled world behind ♪
♪♪
♪ And if I'm feeling
down and blue ♪
♪ Or troubled by
some foolish game ♪
♪ She always seems to
make me change my mind ♪
♪ I feel fine anytime
she's around me now ♪
♪ She's around me now ♪
♪ Almost all the time ♪
♪ If I'm well you can tell
that she's been with me now ♪
♪ She's been with me now ♪
♪ Quite a long, long time ♪
♪ And I feel fine ♪
♪♪
♪ Every now and then
the things I lean on ♪
♪ Lose their meaning ♪
♪ And I find myself careening ♪
♪ In the places where I should
never let me go ♪
♪ She has the power to go where
no one else can find me ♪
♪ And silently remind me ♪
♪ Of the happiness,
good times that I know ♪
♪ Well, I guess
I just got to know them ♪
♪ Isn't what she's got to say ♪
♪ Or how she thinks
or where she's been ♪
♪ To me, the words are nice ♪
♪ The way they sound ♪
♪ I like to hear them best
that way ♪
♪ It doesn't much matter
what they mean, oh ♪
♪ She says them mostly
just to calm me down ♪
♪ I feel fine anytime
she's around me now ♪
♪ She's around me now ♪
♪ I guess just about
all the time ♪
♪ And if I'm well you can tell
that she's been with me now ♪
♪ She's been with me now ♪
♪ Quite a long,
quite a long, long time ♪
♪ Yes, and I feel fine ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
-Carole's an interesting case,
because she worked as a
songwriter for 10 years, really,
before I met her, and she had
this entire career
as a major songwriter.
Mostly with Gerry Goffin,
but with a couple of other
people too.
-In -- in all cases the music
came through me,
and when it was somebody else's
lyric it integrated;
when it was my own music
and lyrics together
sometimes it would just,
all together, pop out of me.
-I asked her to be
a part of my band --
I -- I wanted her to play piano
in my band.
But of course, she was also this
major musical source,
that she'd written all of these
amazing tunes,
that some of which
were my favorite songs,
so I felt this thing that Carole
really should be,
you know, singing her own songs.
-And you -- I remember you
pushed me out on stage,
and I was your side man, and
that's all I ever wanted to be,
and then you said to me, "I want
you to go on stage tonight
and sings your song."
"Wha-wha-wha-wait! What? What?
No! No! I can't do it!"
"No, you're going to do it, no,
don't worry,"
and you gave me
the loveliest introduction,
and you said that, "Okay,
everybody, I'm gonna turn
the stage over to Carole King,
you all know her
as a songwriter, she wrote
blah-blah-blah-blah,"
and he listed the whole thing,
and what he did was
he made me pre-loved,
because everybody
knew all those songs.
[ Applause ]
I know that many of you are
admirers of James Taylor.
I am myself.
I don't know, uh,
if you know he's also really
a fine guitarist
as well as a fine songwriter
and singer,
and I'd like to try to get him
out here to help me --
he was kind enough to volunteer,
so, come on, James.
[ Applause ]
We're gonna do a song for you
called "So Far Away."
[ Applause ]
♪♪
♪ So far away ♪
♪ Doesn't anybody stay
in one place anymore? ♪
♪ It would be so fine to see
your face at my door ♪
♪ Doesn't help to know ♪
♪ You're just time away ♪
♪ Long ago, I reached for you ♪
♪ And there you stood ♪
♪ Holding you again
could only do me good ♪
♪ How I wish I could ♪
♪ But you're so far away ♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪ One more song about movin'
along the highway ♪
♪ Can't say much of anything
that's new ♪
♪ If I could only work
this life out my way ♪
♪ I'd rather spend it
bein' close to you ♪
♪ But, you're so far away ♪
♪ Doesn't anybody stay
in one place anymore? ♪
♪ It would be so fine
to see your face at my door ♪
♪ Doesn't help to know ♪
♪ You're so far away ♪
♪ Yeah, you're so far away ♪
♪♪
♪ Traveling around sure gets me
down and lonely ♪
♪ Nothing left to do
but close my mind ♪
♪ I sure hope the road
don't come to own me ♪
♪ There's so many dreams
I've yet to find ♪
♪ I've yet to find ♪
♪ Oh, but you're so far away ♪
♪ Doesn't anybody stay
in one place anymore? ♪
♪ It would be so fine
to see your face at my door ♪
♪ Doesn't help to know ♪
♪ You're so far away ♪
♪ Yeah, you're so far away ♪
♪ Hey-ey ♪
♪ You're so far away ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
-I guess the first time I played
the Troubadour was the --
was '69 -- was a big deal,
because it was the main gig
in L.A.
It had a proper stage
and a backstage,
and if you did well there,
people -- people noticed it
and, uh, the word got out.
-The Troubadour was a community
of people
who wanted to hear
that kind of music
and the bands
that chose to play there,
and they were often
interchangeable.
But this little unit
that we are right now
is an essential core of
the people that were there.
-We've been trying to --
to, uh...
recast our minds back and try to
remember what --
what songs were in the, uh,
in the set
that we played together when
Carole and I did the --
the Troubadour in --
back in 1903 or whenever.
[ Laughter ]
We can't, it's gone.
But probably, uh, we played
pretty much everything we had
back in those days, and, uh,
so this song
was probably in the set
somewhere.
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪ In my mind
I'm gone to Carolina ♪
♪♪
♪ Can't you see the sunshine? ♪
♪ Can't you just feel
the moonshine? ♪
♪ And, ain't it just like
a friend of mine ♪
♪ To hit me from behind? ♪
♪ Oh, I'm gone to Carolina
in my mind ♪
♪♪
♪ Karin, she's a silver sun ♪
♪ You best walk her way
and watch it shinin' ♪
♪ Watch her
watch the morning come ♪
♪♪
♪ A silver tear appearing now ♪
♪ Well, I'm cryin', ain't I? ♪
♪ I'm gone to Carolina in
my mind ♪
♪ There ain't no doubt
in no one's mind ♪
♪ That love's the finest thing
around ♪
♪ Whisper something soft
and kind ♪
♪♪
♪ And hey, baby,
the sky's on fire ♪
♪ I'm dying, ain't I? ♪
♪ I'm gone to Carolina
in my mind ♪
♪♪
♪ In my mind,
I'm gone to Carolina ♪
♪♪
♪ Can't you see the sunshine ♪
♪ I say, can't you just feel
the moonshine? ♪
♪ Ain't it just like
a friend of mine ♪
♪ To hit me from behind? ♪
♪ Till I'm gone to Carolina
in my mind ♪
♪♪
♪ Dark and silent,
late last night ♪
♪ I think I might have heard
the highway callin' ♪
♪ Geese in flight
and dogs that bite ♪
♪♪
♪ Oh, and signs that might
be omens ♪
♪ Say, "I'm goin', I'm goin'" ♪
♪ I'm gone to Carolina
in my mind ♪
♪♪
♪ It's with a holy host of
others standin' around me ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Still, I'm on
the dark side of the moon ♪
♪ And it looks like it goes on
like this forever ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ You must forgive me ♪
♪♪
♪ If I'm up and gone to Carolina
in my mind ♪
Carolina.
♪ In my mind
I'm goin' to Carolina ♪
♪♪
♪ Can't you see the sunshine? ♪
♪ I say, can't you just feel
the moonshine? ♪
♪ And ain't it just like
a friend of mine ♪
♪ To hit me from behind? ♪
♪ Yes, I'm gone to Carolina
in my mind ♪
♪ Oh, walk on home ♪
♪ Yes, I'm gone to Carolina
in my mind ♪
♪ Said I'm already gone ♪
♪ I'm gone ♪
♪ Say nice things about me,
'cause I'm gone ♪
♪ You got to carry on
without me ♪
♪ I'm gone ♪
♪ I'm gone, oh, I'm gone to
Carolina in my mind ♪
♪ I'm gone ♪
♪ Yes, I am gone to Carolina ♪
♪ In ♪
♪ My ♪
♪ My mind ♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
I'd like to invite a very good
friend of mine to be on TV
with me, Mr. Danny "Kootch."
In those times
in the early '60s,
when I was trying to learn
the guitar,
I met Danny on --
on Martha's Vineyard
and, you know, right away,
I started picking things up
from him.
-You have to remember
at that point in time,
there was a huge confluence of
all kinds of music
that were coming together,
and for anyone that was even
slightly interested in music,
it was a brilliant time
to be around.
-I brought a small band together
to make this first album,
and we already had
Danny Kortchmar,
James's best friend, and also
the person who had
introduced me to James
in the first place;
I found a drummer called
Russ Kunkel,
whom I first heard play at
a John Steward rehearsal.
-And the way
James accompanied himself
on the guitar and sang,
it was brand-new to me,
I never heard anything like it.
-And by this time we'd found
the bass player of our dreams,
Lee Sklar.
-His songs were really amazing,
his voice was amazing,
and his demeanor was --
was unlike most cats I knew at
that time.
-And finally, I had met
one of my idols,
one of the greatest songwriters
of all time, Carole King --
that was, by the way, Kootch who
introduced me to Carole as well.
I said to Carole, "About to make
this record with James Taylor,
and I wondered if you'd consider
playing piano on it.
Would you come over to my house
and meet him?"
So Carole said yes.
-Next thing I know, I'm down at
his house down in Hancock Park
and hooking up and we're all
talking about
doing this show.
-Which consequently
changed my life,
you know, for all intents
and purposes.
-I guess I didn't realize how
exciting it was at the time,
it is in retrospect that one
looks back and says,
"Wow, that was really exciting."
We were just out here, doing
what we did, being young,
and, you know, making music.
-It's kind of one of these
things I wished I had
been aware that my life was
changing at that moment,
because I might have absorbed it
in a different way.
It was one of those kind of
moments where
everything just goes "boom,"
and matches up,
and we all, you know, just took
off with them.
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪ Take to the highway won't you
lend me your name ♪
♪ Your way and my way
seem to be one and the same ♪
♪ Mama don't understand it ♪
♪ She wants to know
where I've been ♪
♪ I'd have to be some kind of
natural born fool ♪
♪ To walk on the road again ♪
♪ But you know
I could feel it ♪
♪♪
♪ Walkin' on country road ♪
♪ Sail on home to Jesus ♪
♪ Won't you good girls
and boys ♪
♪ I'm all in pieces ♪
♪ You can have my choice ♪
♪ 'Cause I can see a heavenly
band full of angels ♪
♪ Comin' just to set me free ♪
♪ No, I don't know nothing
'bout why or when ♪
♪ But I can tell that
it's bound to be ♪
♪ Just because I could feel it ♪
♪♪
♪ Walkin' on country road ♪
♪ Reckon my feet know
where they want me to go ♪
♪ Walking on a country road ♪
♪♪
♪ So, take to the highway
won't you lend me your name ♪
♪ Your way and my way, they seem
to be one and the same ♪
♪ Baby, no ♪
♪ Mama don't understand it ♪
♪ She wants to know
where the boy's been ♪
♪ I'd have to be some kind of
natural born fool ♪
♪ To walk on the road again ♪
♪ But you know I could feel it,
feel it, feel it ♪
♪ Feel it, feel it ♪
♪ Walkin' on country road,
walk on down ♪
♪♪
♪ Walk on down, walk on down,
walk on down, walk on down ♪
♪ Walk on down, and walk on
down, and walk on down ♪
♪ Walk on down, walk on down,
and walk on down ♪
♪ The country road,
walk on ♪
[ Humming ]
♪ Walk on down with me ♪
♪ So, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Said every time I walk on
the country road ♪
♪ Get the same feeling from
a get down [indistinct] ♪
♪ I don't know where it comes ♪
♪ Don't know where
this thing goes ♪
♪ Let's jump back
and feel some more yeah ♪
♪ Everything's fine
and I'm walkin' ♪
♪ I don't know how it happened
to me today ♪
♪ But every time I walk
on the country road ♪
♪ Just about the same thing
goes down, oh ♪
♪ Oh, I'm alright
without it ♪
♪ Every time
I fight on out ♪
♪ There's, oh, no doubt
about it ♪
♪ No, that's why
I'm all about it ♪
♪ I'm walkin' on country road ♪
♪ Said I'm walkin' hand-in-hand
with the one I love ♪
♪ Won't ever, won't ever,
won't now ♪
♪♪
♪ Well, you can feel it,
put your hands on up ♪
♪ Can feel it,
put your hand on up ♪
♪ If you can feel it,
put your hand in my hand ♪
♪ I said, walkin' on
country road ♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪♪
-♪ Now, Smackwater Jack ♪
♪ He bought a shotgun ♪
♪ 'Cause he was in the mood ♪
♪ For a little confrontation ♪
♪ He just let it all
hang loose ♪
♪ He didn't think about
the noose ♪
♪ He couldn't take
no more abuse ♪
♪ So he shot down
the congregation ♪
♪ You can't talk to a man ♪
♪ With a shotgun in his hand ♪
-♪ Shotgun ♪
♪♪
-♪ Now, Big Jim the chief ♪
♪ Stood for law and order ♪
♪ Yes, he did, y'all ♪
♪ He called for the guard
to come ♪
♪ And surround the border ♪
♪ Now, from his bulldog mouth ♪
♪ As he led the posse south ♪
♪ Came the cry,
We got to ride ♪
♪ To clean up the streets ♪
♪ For our wives
and our daughters ♪
♪ Oh, no, no ♪
♪ You can't talk to a man ♪
♪ When he don't
wanna understand ♪
Go get 'em, Danny.
♪♪
♪ The account of the capture ♪
♪ Wasn't in the papers ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ But you know they hanged
ol' Smack
♪ Right then ♪
♪ Instead of later ♪
♪ You know, the people were
quite pleased ♪
♪ Because the outlaw
had been seized ♪
♪ And on the whole,
it was a very good year, yeah ♪
♪ For the undertaker ♪
♪ You know, you know, you know,
you can't talk to a man ♪
♪ With a shotgun in his hand ♪
♪ I said,
a shotgun in his hand ♪
♪ Smackwater Jack,
he bought a shotgun ♪
♪ Oh, Smackwater Jack, he bought
a shotgun ♪
♪ Oh, yes, he did, he bought a,
he bought a shotgun ♪
♪ Talkin' 'bout Smack,
talkin' 'bout Jack ♪
♪ Talkin' 'bout Smack
and his shotgun ♪
♪ Talkin' 'bout Smack,
talkin' 'bout Jack ♪
♪ Talkin' 'bout Smack
and his shotgun ♪
♪ Talkin' 'bout Smack,
talkin' 'bout Jack ♪
♪ Talkin' 'bout Smack
and his shotgun ♪
♪ Talkin' 'bout Smack,
talkin' 'bout Jack ♪
♪ Smackwater Jack, yeah ♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
So, James, we got a problem.
-We have a problem here,
which is that we have
an embarrassment of riches --
she -- she wrote
too many good songs.
-As did he.
So, we've got these cards here,
and there are
way too many cards,
representing too many songs,
for the time we're gonna be
allowed to play for y'all.
So, this, this is Carole's
brilliant, uh uh uh uh,
solution to it, and it is a
request slot in the set.
[ Laughter ]
So what we did is we -- we chose
this position in -- in the set
as our request position, and we
took a sort of pool of songs
that we really couldn't do
but wanted to,
and we -- we polled you --
I hope you didn't notice --
we -- we polled you very gently,
and -- and with our websites,
and, uh, and, uh, Carole and I
alternate back and forth,
it's her turn tonight,
and, uh, this --
this is the song that --
that Uncasville seemed to want
to hear.
[ Laughter ]
[ Clacking drumsticks ]
-One, two, three, four.
♪♪
-♪ Hey, hey, hey
-♪ Hey, hey,
hey ♪
-♪ Yeah, yeah
-♪ Yeah,
yeah ♪
-♪ Hey, hey, hey
-♪ Hey, hey,
hey ♪
-♪ Yeah, yeah
-♪ Yeah,
yeah ♪
-♪ Hey, hey, hey
-♪ Hey, baby
-♪ Yeah, yeah
-♪ Yeah, yeah-ay
-♪ Hey, hey, hey
-♪ A-hey, hey, hey
-♪ Yeah, yeah
-♪ Yeah,
yeah ♪
♪ Loving you the way I do ♪
♪ I know
we're gonna make it through ♪
♪ And I would go
to the ends of the earth ♪
♪ 'Cause, darling, to me,
that's what you're worth ♪
♪ Where you lead,
I will follow ♪
♪ Anywhere that you tell me to ♪
♪ If you need,
you need me to be with you ♪
♪ I will follow
where you lead ♪
♪ If you're out on the road ♪
♪ Feeling lonely and so cold ♪
♪ All you have to do
is call my name ♪
♪ And I'll be there
on the next train ♪
♪ Where you lead,
I will follow ♪
♪ Anywhere that you tell me to ♪
♪ If you need,
you need me to be with you ♪
♪ I will follow
where you lead ♪
♪ I always wanted
a real home ♪
♪ With flowers
on the window sill ♪
♪ And if you wanna live in
Mystic, Connecticut ♪
♪ Honey, you know I will ♪
-♪ Yes, I will,
yes, I will ♪
-♪ You never know how it's
all gonna turn out ♪
♪ But that's okay ♪
♪ Just as long
as we're together ♪
♪ We can find a way ♪
♪ Where you lead,
I will follow ♪
♪ Any-anywhere
that you tell me to ♪
♪ If you need,
you need me to be with you ♪
♪ I will follow, oh ♪
♪ Where you lead,
I will follow ♪
♪ Anywhere that you tell me to ♪
♪ If you need,
you need me to be with you ♪
♪ I will follow where you lead ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Follow me now!
♪ I'm gonna follow
where you lead ♪
-♪ I'm gonna follow
-♪ I'm gonna follow, follow,
follow, follow, follow ♪
♪ Follow, follow, follow ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
-People are dying to hear this
stuff again.
They're hungry for it,
because it's uplifting,
'cause it's meaningful to them.
-When it wants me -- the muse
wants me, she comes and gets me.
So -- and as for this
Troubadour Reunion Tour,
as for working with James again,
and the band, and it's...
sheer joy, sheer pleasure, just,
"Oh, you called me for this?
Thank you!"
-The thing that I think makes
this -- this tour really unique
is the fact that
40 years have passed
since the first time we played,
but everybody is still at
the top of their game.
If this was the last thing I did
in my entire career,
I'm good with that.
-And the fact that they
play and sing together
and like each other and are
genuinely great friends
and musical collaborators,
is unique.
It's an event that
you don't want to miss.
-And even if we're not gonna be
in the Troubadour,
this is the most important thing
we cannot lose,
is that closeness that we feel
on stage.
We do it for each other,
but what they're seeing
is us having a great time
together.
-Our challenge was to figure out
how to do an intimate show
in a -- in a really large,
uh, arena.
-We wish everybody could be
close in.
Well, one way to do that is to
perform in the round.
-What we came up with
was the idea that we --
we would basically have a club
in an arena.
We're also rotating slowly --
the stage rotates.
Well, we've designed the show to
be as -- as close
and intimate as possible,
and to play to
everybody in the room.
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪♪
♪ Whenever I see
your smiling face ♪
♪ I have to smile myself ♪
♪ Because I love you ♪
♪ And when you give me
that pretty little pout ♪
♪ It turns me inside out ♪
♪ There's something
about you, baby ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ Isn't it amazing
a man like me ♪
♪ Can feel this way ♪
♪ Tell me how much longer ♪
♪ It could grow stronger
every day ♪
♪ Oh, how much longer? ♪
♪ I thought I was in love
a couple of times ♪
♪ Before with
the girl next door ♪
♪ But that was long before
I met you ♪
♪ Now I'm sure that
I won't forget you ♪
♪ And I thank my lucky stars ♪
♪ That you are who you are ♪
♪ And not just
another lovely lady ♪
♪ Set out to break my heart ♪
♪ Isn't it amazing
a man like me ♪
♪ Can feel this way, yeah ♪
♪ Tell me how much longer ♪
♪ It could grow stronger
every day ♪
♪♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Nobody can tell me that
I'm doing wrong today ♪
♪ Whenever I see your smile,
yeah ♪
♪ No one can tell me that,
tell me that ♪
♪ I'm doing wrong today ♪
♪ Whenever I see your shine that
lovely thing my way ♪
♪ Nobody, nobody, nobody,
no, nobody ♪
♪ You know, oh, no ♪
♪♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no ♪
♪ Whenever you know ♪
♪ Nobody gonna turn me around,
nobody gonna put me down ♪
♪ Nobody gonna push me around,
baby ♪
♪ Whenever I see your smilin' ♪
♪ No one can tell me that,
whoo ♪
♪ I'm doin' wrong today ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
You and I probably just had
the same musical DNA.
-Absolutely true, because you do
things with your guitar
that resonate -- like, I can
pick up on
something you're doing and it
comes out of my fingers
as you're doing it, almost,
it's --
it's the most remarkable thing,
how that happens,
and that was the thing
that happened
that first connection
at Peter Asher's house.
And it happened throughout
the Troubadour Reunion Tour.
[ Cheering and applause ]
Actually, I -- I've been a fan
of James Taylor's songs
since I met him in 1970.
[ Cheering and applause ]
In -- in fact, to the point
where, prior to hearing
James's songs, I was writing
with other people,
mostly Gerry Goffin
and Toni Stern.
And James inspired me to try
writing my own music and lyrics,
I hope that worked out okay.
[ Cheering and applause ]
We're gonna play for you
right now, and --
and, uh, see what you think.
[ Drumsticks clacking ]
♪ You got to get up
every morning ♪
♪ With a smile on your face ♪
♪ And show the world ♪
♪ All the love in your heart ♪
♪ Then people gonna
treat you better ♪
♪ You're gonna find,
yes, you will ♪
♪ That you're beautiful
as you feel ♪
♪♪
♪ Waiting at the station ♪
♪ With a workday wind
a-blowin' ♪
♪ I've got nothing to do ♪
♪ But watch the passers-by ♪
♪ Mirrored in their faces ♪
♪ I see frustration growing ♪
♪ And they
don't see it showing ♪
♪ Why do I? ♪
♪ You've got to get up
every morning ♪
♪ With a smile on your face ♪
♪ And show the world ♪
♪ All the love
in your heart ♪
♪ Then people gonna
treat you better ♪
♪ You're gonna find,
yes, you will ♪
♪ That you're beautiful
as you feel ♪
♪♪
♪ I have often asked myself
reason for the sadness ♪
♪ In a world where tears
are just a lullaby ♪
♪ If there's any answer,
maybe love can end the madness ♪
♪ Maybe not, oh,
but we can only try ♪
♪♪
♪ You've got to get up
every morning ♪
♪ With a smile on your face ♪
♪ And show the world
all the love in your heart ♪
♪ Then people gonna
treat you better ♪
♪ You're gonna find,
yes, you will ♪
♪ That you're beautiful ♪
♪ You're beautiful ♪
♪ Oh, you're beautiful
as you feel ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
-♪ You can play the game,
you can act out the part ♪
♪ Though you know ♪
♪ It wasn't written for you ♪
♪ Tell me
how do you stand there ♪
♪ With your broken heart ♪
♪ Ashamed of playin' a fool? ♪
♪ One thing can lead
to another ♪
♪ It doesn't take
any sacrifice ♪
♪ Oh, Father and Mother ♪
♪ And sister and brother ♪
♪ If it feels nice ♪
♪ Don't think twice ♪
♪ Just shower the people
you love with love ♪
♪ You must show them the way
that you feel ♪
♪ Things are gonna
turn out fine ♪
♪ If we only will ♪
♪ Only will, only just ♪
♪ Shower the people you love
with love ♪
♪ Show them the way that
you feel ♪
♪ Things are gonna be
much better ♪
♪ If we only will ♪
♪♪
♪ You can run
but you cannot hide ♪
♪ This is widely known ♪
♪ Oh, and what you plan to do
with your foolish pride ♪
♪ When you're all by yourself ♪
♪ Alone ♪
♪ Once you tell somebody ♪
♪ The way you're feelin' ♪
♪ You can feel it
beginning to ease ♪
♪ I think it's true
what they say ♪
♪ 'Bout the squeaky wheel ♪
♪ How he's
always getting the grease ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ Shower the people you love
with love ♪
♪ Show them the way that
you feel ♪
♪ I know things are gonna
turn out fine ♪
♪ If we only will ♪
♪ Only will, only ♪
♪ Shower the people you love
with love ♪
♪ Show them the way that
you feel ♪
♪ Yeah, now, things are gonna be
much better ♪
♪ If we only will ♪
♪♪
♪ Shower the people you love
with love ♪
♪ Show them the way that
you feel ♪
♪ Shower the people you love
with love ♪
♪ Show them the way
that you feel ♪
-♪ They say in every life ♪
♪ Sometimes a rain will fall ♪
♪ But like a pouring rain
pouring out ♪
♪ Make it rain ♪
♪ Make it rain, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
-♪ Shower the people you love
with love ♪
♪ Show them the way
that you feel ♪
-♪ Yeah, said everybody ♪
♪ Everybody ♪
-♪ Show them the way that
you feel ♪
-♪ Oh, everybody ♪
♪ You got to... ♪
-♪ Shower the people you love
with love ♪
♪ Show them the way
that you feel ♪
♪ I know that things are gonna
be much better ♪
♪ If we only will ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
-♪ Way over yonder ♪
♪♪
♪ Is a place that I know ♪
♪ Where I can find shelter ♪
♪♪
♪ From a hunger and cold ♪
♪ And the sweet-tastin'
good life ♪
♪♪
♪ Is so easily found ♪
♪ A way over yonder ♪
♪♪
♪ That's where I'm bound ♪
♪ I know when I get there ♪
♪♪
♪ The first thing I'll see ♪
♪ Is the sun shining golden ♪
-♪ Sun shining golden ♪
-♪ Shining right down on me ♪
♪♪
♪ Then trouble's gonna lose me ♪
♪ Worry leave me behind ♪
♪♪
♪ And I'll stand up proudly ♪
♪ In true peace of mind ♪
♪ Talkin' about it,
I'm talkin' about it ♪
♪ Way over yonder ♪
♪♪
♪ Is a place I have seen ♪
♪ In a garden of wisdom ♪
♪♪
♪ From some long ago dream ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow ♪
♪♪
♪ I'll find find my way ♪
♪ To the land
where the honey runs ♪
♪♪
♪ In rivers each day ♪
♪ Yay-yay-yay ♪
♪ And the sweet-tastin'
good life ♪
♪♪
♪ Is so easily found ♪
♪ Way over yonder ♪
♪♪
♪ That's where I'm bound ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Way over yonder ♪
♪♪
♪ That's where I'm bound ♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
-We're gonna move from that to
a, uh, a cowboy lullaby
for you now, I got to play a...
[ Cheering and applause ]
Partners.
Buckaroos.
[ Laughter ]
A song I wrote
for my nephew.
I had, uh...been overseas,
and when I came home,
my brother Alex and his wife
had... had had a kid,
and in a moment of, um,
relaxed judgment,
they had, uh, named the kid
after me, little --
little baby James.
[ Cheering and applause ]
I --
I wanted to write him a song,
I was trying to figure out, uh,
I drove down to North Carolina
thinking about it,
what kind of song would be good
for a little varmint like James,
you know...
Had to be a cowboy lullaby,
you know, Gene Autry, or...
Roy Rogers, and the sons of
the pioneers kind of a...
"Lights out in the bunkhouse"
kind of thing.
Go to sleep,
you little buckaroo.
[ Chuckles ]
Yee-haw.
[ Laughter ]
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪ There is a young cowboy ♪
♪ Lives on the range ♪
♪ His horse and his cattle,
they're his only companions ♪
♪ He works in the saddle
and he sleeps in the canyons ♪
♪ Just waiting for summer,
his pastures to change ♪
♪♪
♪ Yes, and as the moon rises,
he sits by his fire ♪
♪ Just thinkin' about women
and glasses of beer ♪
♪ Closin' his eyes
as the doggies retire ♪
♪ He sings out a song
which is soft, but it's clear ♪
♪ Just a if maybe someone
could hear ♪
♪♪
♪ He says goodnight,
you moonlight ladies ♪
♪ Rockabye, sweet baby James ♪
♪ Deep greens and blues
are the colors I choose ♪
♪ Won't you let me go down
in my dreams? ♪
♪ Yes, and rockabye,
my sweet baby James ♪
♪ Now, the first of December,
it was covered with snow ♪
♪ Yes, and so was the turnpike
from Stockbridge to Boston ♪
♪ Oh, the Berkshires,
they seemed dreamlike ♪
♪ On account of that frostin' ♪
♪ Ten miles behind me ♪
♪ And ten thousand more to go ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ There's a song
that they sing ♪
♪ When they take to
the highway ♪
♪ A song that they sing ♪
♪ When they take to the sea ♪
♪ A song that they sing of their
home in the sky ♪
♪ Maybe you can believe it,
it might help you to sleep ♪
♪ And singing seems to work fine
for me ♪
♪♪
♪ So goodnight,
you moonlight ladies ♪
♪ Rockabye,
old sweet baby James ♪
♪ Deep greens and blues
for the colors I choose ♪
♪ Won't you let me go down
in my dreams? ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ It's time to rockabye,
my sweet baby James ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
-♪ When this old world starts
getting me down ♪
♪ And people are just too much ♪
♪ For me to face ♪
♪♪
♪ I'll climb way up
to the top of the stairs ♪
♪ And all my cares just drift ♪
♪ Right into space ♪
♪♪
♪ On the roof,
it's peaceful as can be ♪
♪♪
♪ 'Cause there the world below
can't bother me ♪
♪♪
-♪ So when I come home
feeling tired and beat ♪
♪ I go up where the air
is fresh and sweet ♪
♪♪
♪ I get far away from
the hustling crowd ♪
♪ And all that rat race noise
out in the street ♪
♪♪
♪ Oh, on the roof, that's
the only place I know ♪
♪ Look at the city, baby ♪
♪ Where you just have to wish
to make it so ♪
♪ Let's go up on my roof ♪
♪♪
♪ At night the stars
put on a show for free ♪
♪♪
♪ And darling,
you can share it all with me ♪
♪♪
♪ Oh ♪
-♪ I keep on telling you ♪
♪ The right smack dab
in the middle of this town ♪
♪ I've found a paradise ♪
♪ And it's about
trouble proof ♪
♪♪
♪ And if this old world starts
a-gettin' you down ♪
♪ There's room enough
for two ♪
♪ Yeah, up on my roof ♪
-♪ Up on the roof ♪
-♪ Up on the roof,
no,no ♪
♪ Up on my roof ♪
[ King humming ]
♪ You gotta come on up ♪
♪ Bring it on up,
get it on up ♪
♪ Come along up
on the roof ♪
[Both] ♪ Drop what you're
doing tonight
♪ And climb up the stairs
with me and see ♪
♪ Baby, baby ♪
♪ We got the stars up above us
and the city lights below ♪
♪ Oh, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ No, no, up on the roof ♪
♪♪
♪ Up on my roof ♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪♪
♪ Stayed in bed all morning
just to pass the time ♪
♪ There's somethin' wrong here,
there can be no denyin' ♪
♪ One of us is changin' ♪
♪ Or maybe we've just
stopped tryin' ♪
♪♪
♪ And it's too late, baby, now ♪
♪ It's too late ♪
♪ Though we really did
try to make it ♪
♪ Somethin' inside has died ♪
♪ And I can't hide
and I just can't fake it ♪
♪ Oh, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪♪
♪ It used to be so easy,
livin' here with you ♪
♪ You were light and breezy,
and I knew just what to do ♪
♪ Now you look so unhappy
and I feel just like a fool ♪
♪♪
♪ And it's too late, baby, now ♪
♪ It's too late ♪
♪ Though we really did try
to make it ♪
-♪ We can't make it ♪
-♪ Somethin' inside has died ♪
♪ And I can't hide
and I just can't fake it ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
[ Vocalizing ]
♪♪
♪ There'll be good times again
for me and you ♪
♪ But we just can't
stay together ♪
♪ Don't you feel it too? ♪
♪ Still I'm glad
for what we had ♪
♪ And how I once loved you ♪
♪♪
♪ But it's too late, baby, now ♪
♪ It's too late ♪
♪ Though we really did
try to make it ♪
-♪ We can't make it ♪
-♪ Somethin' inside has died ♪
♪ And I can't hide
and I just can't fake it ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
[ Vocalizing ]
♪♪
♪ It's too late, baby ♪
♪ It's too late, oh,
now, darling ♪
♪ It's too late ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
-♪ Just yesterday mornin',
they let me know you were gone ♪
♪ Suzanne, the plans they made
put an end to you ♪
♪♪
♪ I walked out this morning ♪
♪ And I wrote down this song ♪
♪ I just can't remember
who to send it to ♪
♪♪
♪ I've seen fire
and I've seen rain ♪
♪♪
♪ I've seen sunny days,
I thought they'd never end ♪
♪♪
♪ I've seen lonely times when
I could not find a friend ♪
♪ But I always thought
I'd see you again ♪
♪♪
♪ Won't you look down
on me, Jesus? ♪
♪ You've got to help me
to make a stand ♪
♪ You've just got to see me
through another day ♪
♪♪
♪ My body's aching ♪
♪ And my time is at hand ♪
♪ And I won't make it ♪
♪ Any other way ♪
♪ Oh, I have seen fire
and I've seen rain ♪
♪♪
♪ I've seen sunny days,
I thought they'd never end ♪
♪♪
♪ I've seen lonely times
and I could not find a friend ♪
♪♪
♪ But I always thought
I'd see you again ♪
♪♪
♪ So I'm walking my mind to
an easy time ♪
♪ My back turned towards
the sun ♪
♪ Lord knows,
the cold wind blows ♪
♪ That can
turn your head around ♪
♪ There's hours of time
on the telephone line ♪
♪ Just talkin' 'bout
things to come ♪
♪ Sweet dreams
and flying machines ♪
♪ In pieces on the ground ♪
♪ Oh, I've seen fire
and I've seen rain ♪
♪♪
♪ I've seen sunny days,
I thought they'd never end ♪
♪♪
♪ I've seen lonely times when I
could not find a friend ♪
♪♪
♪ But I always thought that I'd
see you, somehow ♪
♪ One more time again, yeah ♪
♪ Thought I'd see you
one more time again ♪
♪♪
♪ There's just a few things
coming my way ♪
♪ This time around, now ♪
♪ I thought I'd see you,
thought I'd see you ♪
♪ Fire and rain ♪
♪ Thought I'd see you
just one more time ♪
♪ See you, yeah ♪
♪♪
[ Vocalizing ]
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪♪
♪ I feel the earth move
under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumblin' down ♪
♪ I feel my heart start
to tremblin' ♪
♪ Whenever you're around ♪
♪ Oh, baby,
when I see your face ♪
♪ Mellow as the month of May ♪
♪ Oh, darlin',
I can't stand it ♪
♪ When you look at me
that way, yeah ♪
♪ I feel the earth move
under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumblin' down ♪
♪ I feel my heart start
to tremblin' ♪
♪ Whenever you're around ♪
Yeah!
♪♪
♪ Oh, darlin',
when you're near me ♪
♪ And you tenderly
call my name ♪
-♪ Call my name ♪
-♪ I know that my emotions ♪
♪ Are somethin'
I just can't tame ♪
♪ I just got to have ya, baby ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I feel the earth move
under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumblin' down,
tumblin' down ♪
♪ I feel the earth move
under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumblin' down,
tumblin' down ♪
♪ I just a-lose control ♪
♪ Down to my very soul ♪
♪ I get hot and cold ♪
♪ All over, all over,
all over, yeah ♪
♪ I feel the earth move
under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumblin' down ♪
Let me hear you!
-♪ Tumblin' down ♪
-♪ I feel the earth move
under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumblin' down,
tumblin' down ♪
Pittsburgh!
--♪ I feel the earth move
under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumblin' down,
tumblin' down ♪
-Come on, let me hear you!
-♪ I feel the earth move
under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumblin' down,
tumblin' down ♪
-♪ I feel the earth move
under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumblin' down,
tumblin' down ♪
♪ I feel the earth move
under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumblin' down ♪
♪ A-tumblin' down ♪
♪ Tumblin' down ♪
♪ Tumblin'
down ♪
♪ Tumblin' down ♪
♪ Tumblin'
down ♪
♪ Oh, oh, yeah
[ Cheering and applause ]
Thank you so much.
-It was such a mutual thing,
you know,
it defies description.
When we first sat down together
and basically
went back and forth and we're
hearing these things --
-We were thinking so alike
at the time.
And when I wrote
"You've Got a Friend,"
i-it came through me, that song
purely, purely came through me.
I didn't have you specifically
in mind, though it
certainly applies -- has -- has
applied since I know you.
I didn't have anyone
specifically in mind.
I just sat down at a piano
and that song just came out,
just as you heard it,
just as you do it,
just came right now.
-On the opening night
at the Troubadour,
it was that afternoon that
Carole was doing her
sound check,
preparing for her first-ever
solo show that night,
just her and the piano
on the stage,
and she decided to run through
a song
she had just finished writing.
And James and I were sitting in
the balcony of the Troubadour,
upstairs, and that's when we
heard this brand-new song
called "You've Got a Friend."
-I'm not sure I was sold on --
on "You've Got a Friend,"
I-I mean, people say,
"Did you know?"
I didn't, I just thought it was
a very nice song.
I had no idea of the reach
it would have.
-As soon as I heard it, I said,
man, that's just --
that's just it, that's a great,
great song.
-And James went crazy, he fell
in love with the song,
told Carole it was one of the
best pop songs ever written
and asked if she'd mind if he
learned it.
And he did, he learned the song
from Carole,
worked out his own version,
and eventually
we did ask Carole whether she
would consider
letting James record
his version --
which I knew was against all
the rules of show business,
because she was about to make
her own first record
and it was clearly an amazingly
good song.
But Carole, with exceptional
generosity and grace,
said that would be fine,
I'd be honored
to have you record it as well.
-When we play it together,
the way your guitar
blends with my piano part is
just, it's like that first time
we played together, it's that.
-That's a good thing.
-We did that, buddy!
-A good thing.
-We did that!
♪♪
-♪ When you're down
and troubled ♪
♪ And you need
some lovin' care ♪
♪ And nothin',
oh, nothin' is goin' right ♪
♪♪
♪ Just close your eyes
and think of me ♪
♪ Yes, and soon
I will be there ♪
♪ To brighten up,
oh, even your darkest night ♪
♪♪
♪ You just call out my name ♪
♪ And you know wherever I am ♪
♪ I'll come runnin' ♪
♪ To see you again ♪
♪♪
♪ Winter, spring,
summer or fall ♪
♪ All you got to do is call
on me ♪
♪ And I'll be there ♪
♪ Yeah, I'll be there ♪
♪ You've got a friend ♪
♪♪
♪ If the sky up above you ♪
♪ Should turn dark
and full of clouds ♪
♪ And that old north wind ♪
♪ Should begin to blow ♪
♪♪
♪ Keep your head together ♪
♪ And call my name out loud ♪
♪ Soon you'll hear me knockin'
on your door ♪
♪♪
♪ You just call out my name ♪
♪ And you know wherever I am ♪
♪ I'll come runnin' ♪
♪ To see you again ♪
♪♪
♪ Winter, spring,
summer or fall ♪
-♪ All you got to do is call me,
call, oh ♪
♪ And I'll be there,
yes, I'll be there ♪
-♪ Now, ain't it good to know
that you've got a friend ♪
♪ When people can be so cold? ♪
-♪ They'll hurt you,
yes, and desert you ♪
♪ They'll take your soul
if you let them ♪
♪ Oh, but don't you let them ♪
♪♪
♪ You just call out my name ♪
♪ And you know wherever I am ♪
♪ I'll come runnin' ♪
-♪ As fast as I can ♪
♪ To see you again ♪
♪ Oh, yes, don't you
know 'bout ♪
♪ Winter, spring,
summer or fall ♪
♪ Darling, all you got to do
is call, and, oh, no ♪
♪ And I will be there,
yes, I'll be there ♪
♪ 'Cause you've got a friend ♪
♪♪
-♪ You've got a friend ♪
-♪ You've got a friend
in me, yeah ♪
-♪ You've got a friend in me ♪
-♪ Walkin' and talkin' friend ♪
-♪ Ain't it good to know,
ain't it good to know ♪
♪ Ain't it good to know,
yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ You've got a friend ♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
-At the heart of it, we have
a conversation with each other
and with the audience, you know,
like, we just feel like
we're there with
one collective friend.
-The connection with
the audience is a --
is a very interesting thing.
When people come to a concert
and dedicate
two or three hours to listening
to a program of music,
it still is a mystery why it
works the way it does,
but I -- I really love it
and live for it, really.
-What I -- I'm sensing people
responding to is
the simple presentation,
the authentic friendship
that we have.
People are not really coming to
see us as much as
they're coming to see and hear
that which we represent
to the audience.
I like knowing that,
because that keeps our feet
on the ground and it -- it isn't
about us.
We're the deliverer of that
which they came to see.
♪♪
♪ How sweet it is
to be loved by you ♪
-♪ It's all right to get on up
and shake that thing ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ How sweet it is
to be loved by you ♪
♪♪
♪ I needed the shelter of
someone's arms ♪
♪ Darlin', there you were ♪
♪ I needed someone to understand
my ups and downs ♪
♪ Baby, there you were ♪
♪ With sweet love and devotion ♪
♪ Now, yeah ♪
♪ Deeply touching my emotion ♪
♪ I just want to stop --
stop and thank you, baby ♪
♪ I wanna stop
to thank you baby, ♪
♪ All right, how sweet it is
to be loved by you ♪
♪♪
♪ How sweet it is
to be loved by you ♪
♪♪
♪ Close my eyes at night ♪
♪ Wondering where would I be
without you in my life ♪
♪ Everything I was into,
it was just an old bore ♪
♪ And everywhere I went it seems
I've been here before ♪
♪ But you brighten up for me
all of my days ♪
♪ With a love so sweet
in so many ways ♪
♪ I wanna stop --
stop and thank you, baby ♪
♪ I wanna stop
and thank you, baby ♪
♪ Thank you, yeah ♪
♪ How sweet it is
to be loved by you ♪
♪♪
♪ How sweet it is
to be loved by you ♪
Robbie Kondor.
♪♪
♪ You were better to me
than I was to myself ♪
♪ For me, there's you, baby,
I got no one else ♪
♪ I wanted to stop,
stop and thank you, baby ♪
♪ I just wanna stop
just to thank you, baby ♪
♪ How sweet it is
to be loved by you ♪
-♪ To be loved by you ♪
-♪ How sweet it is
to be loved by you ♪
♪♪
♪ I said now, how sweet it is ♪
-♪ To be loved by you ♪
-♪ Make the old place ring
one more time ♪
♪ One last time ♪
♪ How sweet it is ♪
-♪ To be loved by you ♪
-♪ Oh, strong and long,
come on, y'all ♪
♪ Yeah, now, now ♪
♪ How sweet it is ♪
-♪ To be loved by you ♪
-♪ Only thing to give,
long and strong ♪
♪ Like you mean it ♪
♪ How sweet it is ♪
-♪ To be loved by you ♪
♪♪
♪ How sweet it is
to be loved by you ♪
-♪ To be loved by you ♪
-♪ How sweet it is ♪
♪ Sweet it is ♪
♪♪
♪ And it feels all right, yeah ♪
♪ Here in the Mellon,
one last night, yeah ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Just! Just to be loved
by you, baby ♪
♪ To be loved by you ♪
♪♪
Oh!
[ Cheering and applause ]
-I loved every minute of it,
I truly, truly did,
and I don't love touring,
I love-love-love that we did
the Troubadour Reunion Tour
in particular,
I love every experience
that we have had together,
and we've been friends
for so long.
-You have one picture of it when
you approach the thing,
and as you're having
a concept of it,
but then, you know,
when it happens,
the reality, it's hard for it
to -- to measure up to
what you had anticipated.
And in this case, it absolutely
did everything
that it was capable of.
That it had all of its juice,
all of its power, you know.
Looking back on it,
it really worked.
You know? It really worked
as a -- as a thing.
-It did.
-You couldn't ask for more.
-Absolutely.
-You couldn't ask.
-It was an experience that we
had that we shared with
every band member,
every singer,
every crew member, and everybody
has the same treasure.
[ Cheering and applause ]
James and I really want to thank
you for all your support
all these years, and I know this
is a -- a --
a bittersweet night,
happy and also a little, um,
sad, but, uh,
we thank you so much for -- for
being there for us
all these years,
and appreciate it.
[ Cheering and applause ]
-I don't know if, um...
I don't know if it's possible --
-We love you!
-Don't know if it's possible for
a building to have a soul,
but, um, if it does, you're it.
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪♪
♪ Oh, the sun is surely
sinking down ♪
♪ But the moon
is slowly rising ♪
♪♪
♪ So this old world
must still be spinning round ♪
♪ And I still love you ♪
♪♪
♪ So close your eyes ♪
♪ You can close your eyes,
it's alright ♪
♪♪
♪ I don't know no love songs ♪
♪ I can't
sing the blues anymore ♪
♪♪
♪ Oh, but I can sing this song ♪
♪ And you can sing this song
when I'm gone ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪ It won't be long
before another day ♪
♪ We gonna have a good time ♪
♪♪
♪ And no one's gonna take
that time away ♪
♪♪
♪ You can stay
as long as you like ♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
♪ Only close your eyes ♪
♪ You can close your eyes,
it's alright ♪
♪♪
♪ I don't know no love songs ♪
♪ And I can't
sing the blues anymore ♪
♪ Yeah, but I can sing
this song ♪
♪ And you can sing this song ♪
♪ When I'm gone ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]
You guys are the best.
-Thank you.
[ Cheering and applause ]
Good night, safe home.
[ Crowd noise fades,
music fades up ]
♪♪
♪ Way down here
you need a reason to move ♪
♪ Feel like a fool
running your stateside games ♪
♪ Lose your load, leave your
mind behind, Baby Jane ♪
♪ Oh, Mexico ♪
♪ It sounds so simple,
I just got to go ♪
♪ The sun's so hot
I forgot to go home ♪
♪ I guess I'll have to go now ♪
♪ Americano got the sleepy eye ♪
♪ Body's still shaking
like a live wire ♪
♪ Sleepy señorita
with the eyes on fire ♪
♪ Oh, Mexico ♪
♪ Sounds so sweet
with the sun sinkin' low ♪
♪ The moon's so bright
like to light up the night ♪
♪ Like to make everything
all right ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh ♪
♪ My Mexico ♪
♪ Oh, my Mexico ♪
♪♪
Baby's hungry
and the money's all gone ♪
♪ Folks back home don't want to
talk on the phone ♪
♪ She gets a long letter,
sends back a postcard ♪
♪ Times are hard ♪
♪ Oh, down in Mexico ♪
♪ I've never really been
so I don't really know ♪
♪ Oh, my Mexico ♪
♪ I guess I'll have to see ♪
♪ Oh, Mexico ♪
♪ I've never really been
but I'd sure like to go ♪
♪ Oh, Mexico ♪
♪ I guess I'll have to go now ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm a-talking 'bout
my Mexico, Mexico ♪
♪ Oh, way down in Mexico ♪
♪ Oh, oh, Mexico ♪
♪ Mexico, down in Mexico ♪
♪ Come on, oh, oh,
down in Mexico ♪
♪ Guess I'll go, guess I'll go
down to Mexico ♪
♪ Watch there, oh, Mexico ♪
♪ Because oh, my Mexi--
let's go! ♪
♪♪
[ Cheering and applause ]