Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Don't tell me.
Over my brother's business?
So?
Sorry oh!
That's a lie.
For real.
Lie! You're lying.
She's legally married to my brother.
That's right.
I knew it would come to this.
He is my brother!
I knew it.
Hey! Hey!
Yes!
Oluwafemi,
I've told you several times.
English language
that twists the tongue.
As I was saying...
Ah! Taboo!
Sign it!
What about us?
-He's a man. You are ladies.
-So?
Don't be offended.
So frustrating!
You don't have the guts.
-No guts.
-Not your fault.
Who's this mad woman?
You either pack up or improve.
It's better you go sell smoked fish.
Are you foolish?
-Who's going to sell smoked fish?
-Sis, it's okay!
She said we should sell fish!
Get out of my sight.
Take your rubbish away!
With your wedding gown!
Take it easy.
I'm confused. Take a look.
Want to break me?
-You forgot how expensive it is.
-Small chops fried in oil!
Thank you for coming!
Thanks for coming.
You know me, though.
I don't care.
Where are these guys?
Shut it off.
Shut it off, please.
He has no money.
My money.
What a pity.
Won't I just begin--
Ah, I'm in trouble.
-Oh, please.
-Auntie A.
You're confusing me.
Honestly.
Calm down!
You've annoyed him terribly.
Is that how to show support?
Wait. Are you a child? Huh?
Don't you have any sense?
That's your cup of tea.
Please!
Who are you telling to chill?
Keep quiet!
Who is this skinny one?
She should know her place.
Come and sit.
There's money to be made!
Did you hear that?
It will shine everywhere!
-What's her name?
-Rihanna.
Sorry, it is not allowed
to make noise around here.
I am a Nigerian, I recognized
you guys, as soon as I saw you.
I'm happy
when I see my people.
I have a fine car.
Don't think that I'm joking.
Where are you guys going?
My car is here. Where are you going?
Nobody has this type
of car in Dubai.
I am a very popular guy in this city.
Everyone knows me in Dubai.
Come on, Sis.
End the call, let us discuss business.
We were supposed to send the proposal.
Are you jealous?
At least I got a man.
Meaning?
Come on, what's the matter?
You should be dancing!
Why are you always negative?
-You love being sad for fun.
-I was wondering as well.
-What?
-Money is money.
-Right?
-Right.
Hurry, hurry.
Let's think this through.
Tinu, the boss!
The tenacious Teni.
Tenacious.
-Hey! Look! Hey!
-Get out my way.
It was too good to be true.
Oh my God.
Come here.
When everything was rosy,
you didn't know we existed.
You're not serious.
Hmm? You and who?
-It's your family that'll die.
-It's your own cursed family.
Stop insulting each other.
Please, don't disturb us
with all these documents.
-What did you buy?
-We're finished.
Let us go.
I'm talking too much.
You wanna go?
Let's go.
You're the man.
I said it!
I know Dammy Baggio!
Dammy who plays for Royal Manchester!
Dammy! Talented guy, I tell you.
-I'm a Nigerian guy.
Fool! Look at his big head!