Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
♪
I promised I'd say
something witty right now.
If I wasn't so stunned.
You kind of just did.
[Tasha laughs]
♪
Will you do me the
honor of being my wife?
Yes!
♪
I don't want to do this.
It's the right thing to do.
You don't think it's too much?
It's the most highly
effective option.
Yes, I know the
statistics, Alexander.
I am a doctor after all.
This just feels unnecessary.
[Jan]
Now...
Inhale slowly
through your nose.
Pause.
[Jan] And exhale slowly
through your mouth.
Follow me.
[everyone in room - big inhale]
[everyone in room - big exhale]
Very good, everyone!
[King Edward on tablet]
Oh for heaven's sake Blevins!
Hold the camera steady!
Yes, sir. Very good, sir.
Sorry.
[King Edward]
You're making me seasick.
[Tasha struggles]
[King Edward }
Very nice form, Tasha!
It just feels a little
silly, Your Majesty.
But of course it's not silly.
This is for the future King
of San Savarre, after all.
King or Queen.
Yes. We could have a
boy or girl, Father.
You know we'd like to
keep it a surprise.
Oh I can tell you most
assuredly it will be a King.
The Cavalieri line has only
ever produced male heirs.
But seriously, what
if we have a girl?
You won't.
You realize there's a 50 percent
chance we'll have a girl.
And you must realize that
I am 100 percent certain
it will be a boy.
Yes Your Royal Highness?
Can I borrow this for a second?
Of course.
Thank you.
[slams shut]
Did you just hang
up on the King?
No. She hung up on
her Father-in-law.
[Jan]
Well done, Your Royal Highness.
Indeed.
[Bella] Extra security
will be provided
once we land in New York
and will escort us
directly to our hotel.
I should hope so, Bella.
They'll be at our disposal for
the entire North American tour.
I've streamlined the
itinerary to no more than
10 ribbon-cuttings per city,
and one overnight
in each location.
It's a full schedule.
At least we get to see my
brother Jeff and all the kids
at the hospital
on the last stop.
I can't wait to see him!
I can't wait to see Jeff
either, Your Royal Highness.
There will be the ribbon-cutting
at the new wing of
your old hospital.
I just wish we
could stay longer.
But you're not going anywhere
Your Royal Highness.
What?
Unfortunately
Blevins is correct.
There's no "we" on this trip.
I can safely travel
up to seven months.
Longer, actually.
We'll be back in San
Savarre in no time.
I think it's best if
you stay here and rest.
These trips are very hectic,
rushing from event to event,
not to mention how
sore one's cheeks get
from all those photos.
I haven't been able to
work at the hospital much
since my pregnancy,
and at least this way
I can still be of
service to this country.
It's my duty.
-Blevins.
-Uh huh.
Isn't it tradition
for the Princess
to travel with the Prince
on international tours?
Ah, as an outsider, or relative
newcomer to San Savarre,
I'm not certain you're
the ideal ambassador just yet.
But, um, you are correct.
It is tradition.
And maintaining this country's
tradition is essential, right?
Then it's decided!
Just, once moment...
It's decided.
Very well, then.
All right!
That settles it.
I think it will be a lot
more fun with you there.
It is a lot of work,
Your Royal Highness.
How complicated could it be?
♪
[phone ringing]
[Jeff]
Hey! What's up?
You don't usually call
when I'm on shift.
Everything all right?
How's my little niece
or nephew to be?
The baby's fine
and I'm ecstatic.
Well I'm glad to hear that!
So what's up, Your
Royal Highness?
Why doesn't it sound
respectful when you say it?
Because I didn't mean it to.
We're coming for the
opening of the new wing.
What?
Ah ah, say that again!
The Prince and Princess of San
Savarre will be present for
the opening of the
new pediatric wing!
[Kids cheer]
Needless to say, we're
all pretty excited,
ah, Your Royal Highness.
That's half-sister-doctor-royal-
highness to you.
Ah, that will take
too long to say.
Hey, so, um, how is such
an important royal person
as yourself needs to travel
with a lot of royal security.
Ah, yeah.
Can you think of
anyone in particular
who'd be suited for the job?
Come on, Tash.
Is she coming or isn't she?
Who, Bella?
Huh, let me check
the itinerary.
You really are wicked,
you know that.
Like, wicked awesome, right?
Jeff, of course she's coming!
She is?
Yay!
Wow! That's hurtful.
You're more excited to see
Bella than you are to see me.
Yes! Well, no.
Well, for different reasons.
[whispers] I'm thinking
of proposing!
What? You are?
Yeah, I already have
Grandma's ring.
I have so much planning to do!
I know. Me too.
Turns out I have a
lot of learning to do
before I can become an
ambassador for San Savarre.
You'll be great.
So will you.
[squealing with delight]
[clears throat]
[serious voice] All right.
We'll talk later.
Now...
Which one, Your
Royal Highness?
Ah ah!
Incorrect! Again.
Why are there three spoons?
Dessert, tea and soup, darling.
So I've been eating soup with
a teaspoon this entire time
and no one's
corrected me?
[crashing sound]
-Oh dear!
-What?
You may grab a dinner
roll with your bare hands
in North America,
but in San Savarre, we tend
to use the tongs provided.
Okay.
Oh!
What?
Oh right.
And posture!
Oh! Those look good.
Okay! I'm hungry.
I'm craving
everything right now.
And thank goodness you are.
You're eating for
two now darling.
See.
-Oh!
-What?
I'm not supposed to
pour my own water.
And that's not a water glass.
Perhaps we should move
on to something else?
Now, the press will throw you
curve balls and try to tempt you
with leading questions
leading into answering
in an inappropriate manner.
But you must always remain
one step ahead of them,
at all times.
[giggles]
The best course of action is
to turn the tables on them,
and ask them a
question in return.
I'm sorry Your Royal Highness.
Am I boring you at all?
[stifles a giggle]
[Alexander and Tasha laugh]
Your interview technique
is absolutely awful.
Now, at least we can
make you look the part.
For a two weeks trip, a
Princess traditionally requires
a minimum of 38
unique ensembles.
[Tasha]
Seriously?
Where the style of the
Royal Family is concerned,
I'm always serious.
Sporting attire, formal
attire, interview ensembles,
lunch-ready looks, gowns, ball
gowns, red carpet eye-catchers,
respectable cocktail hour
style, wardrobe for teas,
conservative business looks
for diplomatic photos,
active wear for planned
candid outdoor walk photos,
and that's just for
the first three days.
Ideally all with an
additional dozen as backup,
just in case of emergency.
[Tasha]
Emergency?
Besides a spill,
what could happen?
With you, Ma'am, I believe
anything is possible.
Aw...
[Tasha] Well, I'm sure I can
figure something out
with the clothes
I already have.
What do you think?
Hmmm.
How do you feel?
Um, well...
Like I might need some help.
That's what I'm here for,
Your Royal Highness.
Let's get to work!
Oh!
How do you feel now?
I feel ready.
What do you say, Blevins?
We've done all we can.
Time to go!
For my beautiful wife
on her first royal tour.
Oh Alec!
It's beautiful.
You're such a fabulous husband.
Only because I have
a fabulous wife.
[Alexander]
Darling,
[Tasha laughs]
That's easy for you to say!
You just need a few
suits and a tuxedo.
You're forgetting about
my military jacket
with all the medals
and ribbons.
It's very heavy.
[Tasha laughs]
I'm so glad that you're here.
How are you feeling?
I'm excited!
A little tired.
But mainly I'm craving a big
old American cheeseburger.
Now the first stop is
the ribbon-cutting
of the new San Savarre wing at
the Natural Historical Society.
No, the first stop
is Burger Cave.
Ummm...
One of the many
reasons I love you.
On behalf of the
country of San Savarre,
I'm sorry you had to
witness that spectacle.
It's so good. So good!
Uh huh.
Will we be getting a sneak
peek at the baby bump,
Your Royal Highness?
♪ [fast sexy music] Work it work
it - wa - wa - wa work it! ♪
♪ Work it work it
wa - wa - wa work it! ♪
♪ Whole lotta money don't get
the honey 'less you be alright ♪
A Princess for the people!
♪ Take that frown turn it upside
down and make it feel alright ♪
♪ If you lost your thing
it don't mean a thing ♪
♪ It's going to be alright
♪ No one else is gonna lift
yourself ‘less you be alright ♪
♪ Just be alright
[it's gonna be alright] ♪
[Tasha]
Can I try your hat on?
♪ It's gonna be alright
♪ Be alright
[be alright] ♪
♪ It's gonna be alright
♪ Work it work it
wa - wa - wa work it! ♪
♪ Do what you feel,
but just keep it real ♪
♪ It's going to be alright
♪ Cause a whole lotta paper
ain't gonna save ya ♪
♪ 'Less you be alright
♪ Gotta do it for yourself
and nobody else ♪
♪ And go be alright
[music ends]
The Princess is tired.
I think we all are.
This tour has been a whirlwind.
I think our next stop will
give us a much-needed boost.
[tablet rings]
It's the King!
Up and at 'em everybody!
Greetings and
salutations, Your Majesty.
Blevins!
Put the Prince and Princess
on the phone, if you will.
Ah yes, Sir.
Very good, Sir.
[King Edward]
It's been brilliant!
Oh, I must congratulate
both of you
on your extraordinary
diplomatic skills.
You have far exceeded my
hopes and expectations.
You have endeared yourselves
and, by extension,
all of San Savarre to
North Americans everywhere.
It's been our pleasure, Father.
[King Edward] The reviews and
reports have been exceptional.
Oh and Tasha, your
personal touch, well,
may be a little non-traditional,
has worked like a charm!
Well done!
You're very welcome,
Father-in-law.
So, just one last stop,
and then we have to get you on
that plane back to San Savarre!
I was actually hoping we could
spend a little extra time
in my hometown.
I'm just, I'm so excited
to see my brother Jeff.
Yeah, I know it's
important to Bella too.
She has some personal time
booked while we're there.
Oh. Is that so?
Um...
I think.
Do you think it's wise
to delay your departure?
Tasha is carrying a
very important part
of San Savarre with her.
I'm sure she's eager
to get our heir home
as soon and as
safely as possible.
Well I...
I can assure you, Sir,
that I will escort the Prince
and Princess onto the plane
in accordance with our
original time line.
And before any potential flight
restrictions for the Princess.
Time is of the essence!
You don't want to let the
country down, do you Tasha?
You absolutely must
get home on time.
[Dr. Gonzales]
I thought you hated tea.
[Jeff]
Oh, I do.
It tastes like dirty dishwater.
But Bella loves it.
And, I put a ring inside.
Because today's the
day that I'm gonna...
No, don't care.
We've got enough going on with
this whole Royal production.
All this planning and protocols
are taking me away from my...
and making me lose
my patience.
Ha! I see what you did
there, Dr. G. Good one!
Doctor Gonzales.
But surely you're excited about
the new wing they're opening?
Of course I am.
I just think it would
be so much easier
if they didn't have to
come here to open it.
[Mel] They're here!
They're here!
[Blevins]
Make way!
Pardon me. Coming through!
Coming through.
Royals coming through!
What are you doing?
Get over here!
It's so good to finally see
the little boy or girl!
-Good to see you, brother!
-Hey, brother!
Or should I say, Dad-to-be?
Hello.
What can I do for you?
Excuse me Prince Alexander.
May we please show you something
we made in the craft room?
I would love that.
Lead the way.
'Craft room' is not
on the itinerary!
Okay, come on now.
Come on then.
Here we go.
[slurping]
Hey.
Hi.
It is so great to see you.
It's nice to see you too.
Come here!
-Ahem.
-Oh right.
Hmmm.
Well, it seems like you're
holding down the fort over here.
Yeah, yeah.
Dr. Gonzales still isn't a big
fan of my hilarious jokes,
but she's seems to be coming
around on my nursing skills.
Well, that's because you're
great at what you do.
Minus the jokes, of course.
Very nice.
Ah, how about you?
How are you doing? Really?
I'm good. Yeah.
I'm, I'm really good!
Okay. Now, I know that face.
What's going on?
It's just...
I slowed down my work schedule
when we found out
I was pregnant.
King's orders.
And, I miss practicing.
I really miss the kids.
There are so many of
them that need help.
Can you believe that there isn't
a dedicated children's hospital
in San Savarre?
I just wish I could
be more helpful.
It's just for now.
It's not forever.
You know that?
I don't know about that.
I don't know if I can
handle having a family and
Royal duties, while maintaining
a career that I love.
You can handle anything
you put your mind to, Tash.
That's always been true.
You really think so?
I know so.
And I might be able to help.
Ah, there's this
special case that only
your outstanding doctoring
abilities can help with.
Would you be willing
to take a look?
Yes. Absolutely.
Right this way.
-Scalpel.
-Forceps.
-Felt.
-Felt?
Yes, felt. It's the
only thing that will do.
Felt.
Buttons.
You really do things
differently in San Savarre.
Just pass me the buttons, Nurse,
and I'll have the patient
recovering in no time.
Buttons.
You're the boss.
Is Peanut all better?
Yes ma'am. All better.
Thank you Dr. Tasha.
Hey, Verity. What about me?
What about you, Jeff?
She's the boss.
-That's true.
-No respect.
No respect, I tell ya.
She's actually having
a really tough time.
That's the closest to a smile
I've seen since she got here.
Really? What seems
to be the problem?
She just isn't responding
to treatment how we'd like.
I mean, the treatments
themselves are working fine,
but she's just so down.
Hmm.
Mind if I look at her chart?
Yeah. Go ahead.
It's right there.
The treatment seems right.
She's in room 104?
Yeah, why?
That room doesn't get
very much natural light.
Try supplementing a
sun lamp in there.
I bet she perks up a little.
Anyone ever tell you
you're pretty clever?
We sure miss having
you around here.
I miss practicing here.
I miss practicing there.
I miss making a difference
on a daily basis, actually.
You're still working
part-time in San Savarre,
and that's just for now.
How do you know?
Cuz you're the best.
The world needs more
doctors like you.
You always know
exactly what to say.
Hey, speaking of...
When are you
going to propose?
Oh! I have to read
the tea leaves first!
You know, I think a sticker
might look quite good here.
Yes! Wow!
What do we think?
We like this, right?
You know I think a sticker
might also look good...
Here.
[Kids laugh]
I think I might also need one...
Right here.
Perfect.
-What about this giant one?
-Yeah.
Like an earring.
Where'd he go?
Now, how about more on the card.
I think we need to decorate
this guy a little bit more.
-Okay.
-Yeah?
I'm sure the Queen is
going to love chocolate.
She's going to love it.
Here we go.
Oh wow.
Ah. Ring a ding ding.
Jeff?
[ring clatters down drain]
We have to go.
Oh okay?
Where are we going?
No, the "Royal we".
I mean that literally.
What? Already?
Right after the ribbon-cutting.
I'm doing security
for three now,
so the King is motivated to have
everyone home safe and sound.
But you can't, uh, you
can't leave just, just yet!
I don't want to.
We'll spend more time
together soon, okay.
Look, I know this whole long
distance thing is hard.
But I promise you,
it will be worth it.
It already is.
[alarm beeping]
Oh!
Ah, yes. I just need to
let everything sink in.
Okay.
It's truly an honor
to be present
for the opening
of the new wing.
At the place where
I first interned,
the place where I became an
attending pediatrician,
and the place where I
reunited with the charming man
who is now my husband.
The staff here are
like family to me.
Well, I should hope so!
I'm her brother.
All this to say, is I'm very
proud of where I come from.
It's made me who I am.
And I hope that this new
wing will help the children
who need it the most.
Thank you.
All right Your Royal Highnesses,
if you'd like to say your good
byes and we'll get on the road.
It'll be all right.
Yeah.
I'll have to meet my
little niece or nephew.
That's true.
And there's a little
unfinished business
that I still need
to attend to.
Right.
All right brother.
Good luck.
Hi.
Will you give this to
the Princess, please?
It would be my honor.
Thank you.
Next time.
I'll see you soon.
See you soon.
[Blevins]
Time is not on our side!
We must get going at once!
Come along Bella.
Come along! Chop chop! Come on.
[Dr. Gonzales] Let's go
everybody! Party's over.
Sorry!
It's all right.
I'll see them again
before too long.
No, sorry, can you move please?
Oh, sorry.
[Mel] Someone's got
to clean this up!
I'm getting back
to work, Doctor G.
Yeah, you better be.
[clears her throat]
So. Did you pop the question?
Because I didn't see
a ring on her finger.
No, unfortunately the plans
kind of went down the drain.
Speaking of which,
I need to call maintenance
and request a plumber.
[Blevins] Looks like we'll
make it to the airport
just in time.
[Tasha moans]
It's not that bad, is it?
I thought it was rather cute.
No, it's just...
I have a cramp.
A cheeseburger cramp, perhaps?
It's just a little ache.
I'm not due for
another two months.
[moans painfully]
Turn the motorcade around.
We have to go back to the
hospital immediately.
[Blevins]
But we don't have time!
If that baby is coming, we
need to get you on the plane!
He must be born on
San Savarran soil!
What? San Savarran soil?
Since when?
Yeah, since when?
Since always.
That's always been the law!
Don't you think you
should have shared
this important
information earlier?
I thought everyone understood!
Look, if your father...
It's okay. It's okay.
Just breathe, just breathe.
You're okay.
Everything's going to be fine.
The Royals are back!
The Royals are back?
[Mel]
The Royals are back!
Did you miss me?
What's going on?
What's happening?
She's having pains.
[Dr. Gonzales] Nurse Jeff, get
the patient a wheelchair.
We'll admit her.
And do a thorough
examination immediately.
Get the Prince in the
private waiting room.
Okay.
Thanks for bringing her back.
Hey, hey.
Look at me.
She's going to be just fine.
Okay?
Just fine.
It's perfectly normal to
experience these kinds of pains
at this stage in your pregnancy.
It's just a little scare.
Thank goodness!
Everything is fine Tasha.
I'm just going to need you
to stay on bed rest now.
Well, that simply
isn't possible.
Sure it is.
Certainly we can find
some kind of private jet
with a bed for her.
No. She's in no
condition to travel.
Well you just said she was fine!
She is fine.
As long as she's
placed on bed rest.
[Blevins] Let's say we
agree to this.
How long will it be
until she can travel?
Well, there's no way of knowing
if we're talking
about days or weeks.
Which is why we're going to
be monitoring her closely.
And for the record,
I don't need your permission
to do right by my patient.
Look, we need to return to
San Savarre immediately
in order for the Royal line of
succession to remain intact.
No! You look, little man.
I don't care about your
Royal "traditions".
I do care, however, about
the health and safety
of my patient
and her baby.
Which is why Tasha will
remain on bed rest.
That is the final word.
Well, I'm going to...
I'm going to tell
the King about you!
So there!
Do that!
I have words for him myself.
I'm letting the
entire country down.
You are doing no such thing.
In fact, by taking better care
of yourself, you are taking
responsibility for the
future of San Savarre.
What am I going to
tell your father?
Don't worry about that.
I will talk to him.
[Plumber]
Ah! There you are.
You slippery sucker.
Connie!
Did you find it?
Oh!
[British accent] Why Connie, I
don't know if I can accept.
Father would never approve!
You don't deserve me.
I do not want to do this.
What?
You don't?
Who told you?
Blevins.
How did he know?
I presume the King told him.
Well how did he know?
What are you talking about?
The King is calling momentarily
and it is not going
to be pleasant.
Ohhhh!
[chuckles]
He is not going to be pleased.
Bella, you can handle it.
You can handle anything.
You're such an
incredible person.
I've never known anyone as
strong, or as singular as you.
You care for people not
because it's your job,
but because it's
part of who you are.
You're a protector.
And I...
[Bella's phone rings]
Your Majesty!
Yes, that is...
[whispers to Jeff]
What are you doing?
Yes, no, I'm here.
Well the problem...
He hung up!
This is a disaster.
Yeah. Yeah it is.
[stretching]
Oh. That's nice though.
Listen to me!
You have to get Tasha
back here at once!
I will not risk the health
of my wife or my child.
Then this child will not
be a San Savarran citizen,
much less an heir
to the throne!
Tradition dictates
he will no longer be
in the line of succession.
Why do you keep saying "he"?
She could be a girl,
for all we know.
The Cavalieri family
always has boys.
There's never been a
female heir to the throne.
Not that it would matter
either way if the child
is not born here!
My wife's life is at stake.
My child's.
I will deal with this
and I will have their
best interests in mind.
You will find a way to have
that child born in San Savarre!
Now that is an ord...
Did you just hang
up on the King?
No. I hung up on your
Father-in-law.
[Tasha]
Blevins. Come on.
It's o...
Are you okay?
♪ [fun music starts]
♪
♪ You're so colorful ♪
♪ And I've got my kaleidoscope ♪
♪ So together we are magical ♪
♪ Your tide is high ♪
I've got it!
We take the whole hospital and
we put it on a hover boat?
♪
No.
♪ [music continues]
We are we are magic ♪
♪ We are we are magic ♪
♪ Abracadabra we're magical ♪
♪
♪ Caterpillar and cocoon ♪
♪ It's butterflies
when I'm with you ♪
♪ Together we are magical ♪
♪
♪ There's no harm in my melody ♪
♪ But you came round
to sing with me ♪
♪ And together we are magical ♪
♪
♪ We are we are magic ♪
♪ Abracadabra we're magical ♪
♪
I have a highly trained
task-force who could discreetly
extricate the Princess
under the cover of night.
It's unlikely anyone would
need to be seriously injured.
♪
No.
Everything looks really good,
but I'm still not comfortable
with you traveling.
♪
I'm just not used to
being the patient.
You know. It's so frustrating.
I hear you Tasha.
I really do.
♪
But I don't care.
♪ You shine up like
a lightening bolt ♪
♪ And I'm the calm
inside the storm ♪
♪ Together we are magical ♪
♪
How is "butterscotch pudding"
even still a thing?
♪
I love butterscotch.
♪ We are we are magic ♪
♪ Abracadabra we're magical ♪
[gags]
No.
♪ We are we are magic ♪
♪ And together we are magical ♪
♪
And then to cover your escape,
I take her place in the bed!
♪
No! It's a terrible idea!
Yeah. I just meant as a look.
♪
A triumph.
♪ Abracadabra we're magical ♪
[music ends]
This is impossible.
There just isn't a way
to make this plan work.
The King is going to banish me.
I just wish we could
take the hospital
and put it in San Savarre.
That's it!
Is the hover boat back in play?
No!
We may not be able to take
the hospital to San Savarre,
but we can bring San
Savarre to the hospital!
Are you feeling all right,
Your Royal Highness?
I think he's lost it.
No no. Don't you understand?
We can have the
hospital declared
sovereign San
Savarran territory.
There have been
a few precedents.
Other royal families
have been granted
the same opportunity
in the past.
Of course!
And then the royal baby
would technically be born
on San Savarran soil,
and the traditional line of
succession would be intact!
But, is this even possible?
Leave that to us.
I will call the ambassador.
I guess I'll clean up.
Look Mel, I'm really sorry for
how I spoke to you earlier.
It was uncalled for.
I'm just not used to being
on this side of things.
It's all right.
I know you're under
a lot of stress and
we just don't want
you to feel stress.
Thanks for understanding.
Of course...
Your Royal Highness.
Okay. There's no need for
that, Mel, it's just me.
Dr. Tasha, if I were a princess,
I would make everybody
around me bow and curtsy.
Your life must be the best!
Well, I don't get to work
as much as I'd like to.
I just get dragged to
all these fancy dinners,
and galas, and gown fittings.
Boring stuff like that.
Yeah, that sounds awful.
Now, I would love it if you
could please drink some water.
That pitcher is almost
completely full still!
No!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Wow. You're a good doctor
but a really bad patient.
I know. I need to work on that.
How are you feeling?
Much better.
Thank you Dr. Tasha.
More importantly,
how is Peanut doing?
All better!
He's a much better
patient than me, huh?
[giggles]
Yeah.
You know, I wanna be just
like you when I grow up.
A Princess?
I wanna be a Princess
and a doctor!
Being a doctor is cool because
you get to help people.
But being a Princess
is also cool because
you get to help people in other
ways, like charities and stuff.
And you get to
play dress-up too.
You know, you're
pretty clever, Verity.
When I grow up, I want
to be just like you.
Come here.
According to our ambassador, all
we have to do is convince our
American diplomat colleague to
temporarily declare Tasha's room
"sovereign San Savarran soil",
and all of our
problems are solved.
Hold on.
There are other powers that
be that need convincing first.
Like who?
[sniffs]
Oh right. No, yes.
Of course.
We would absolute need
your approval first.
I'm not so sure you're
going to get it.
Dr. Gonzales, why ever not?
Well because our ward
has it's own set of
protocols and standards
that need to be upheld.
Not to mention there would be a
whole river of red tape to make
something like this happen.
And I am but only one chief.
Would monetary remuneration
be an incentive?
What are we talking about here?
Well, if the hospital is
willing to cooperate,
Tasha's room will qualify for
the very generous funding
of the San Savarran
health system budget.
Money can't solve all
problems, Your Highness.
But it can provide a worthy
hospital with much needed
and brand new
medical equipment.
Doctor, I'm not
trying to bribe you.
But you'll need increased
staff to help move patients,
extra security to help
deal with the media,
that sort of thing.
We would more than
compensate the hospital
for the inconvenience.
Would this about cover it?
Welcome home, Prince Alexander!
What percentage of the hospital
does San Savarre
intend to assume?
The Princess' room is
four hundred and thirty-two
square feet.
We would require no
more and no less.
Is the attached restroom
included in that square footage?
Indeed, Ambassador McDavid.
And is that
absolutely necessary?
I should say so,
Ambassador McDavid.
Huh! Very well.
Next order of business.
How will the San Savarran health
system budget contribute to the
betterment of the
hospital room in question?
Well we have here is a
detailed and itemized list
including all the
innovations and improvements.
For not just the Princess's room
but to all the maternity suites.
The total's at the bottom there.
This is in San Savarran
dollars, I presume?
US dollars.
Well, I'm surprised to admit it,
but your requests are
completely reasonable,
and your contributions
are more than generous.
I believe we can
come to an agreement.
Very good.
On behalf of San Savarre,
to mark this momentous,
historic occasion,
I should like to bestow an
annual gift upon your country.
A small thank you, if you will,
for the generous hospitality
which you are showing
the Prince and Princess.
Completely unnecessary, Blevins.
I must insist.
5,000 San Savarre fir trees
will be shipped every year
on this precise date and planted
near your nation's capital.
Hmmm.
Playing hardball I see.
Very well.
In that case, 5,000 waffles,
baked in accordance with the
secret San Savarran recipe, will
be delivered to you every year
for Waffle Day.
Waffle Day?
You don't celebrate Waffle
Day in North America?
It's not a major holiday.
I fear they would spoil
before we were able to
distribute them, anyhow.
You're firm but fair, Ambassador
McDavid. Firm but fair.
Very well.
My final offer then is inspired
by the Princess's passion
project in our homeland.
We shall deliver to you 5,000
baby boxes on this occasion.
Starter kits with
everything a newborn needs.
Diapers, clothing, sleeping
bundles, outdoor wear, etc. etc.
The one where the shipping box
turns into the baby's first bed?
Of course.
In fact there is a small
mattress inside every box.
Just the thing to
give little ones
the right start in life.
We could help a
lot of new parents.
Is that a 'yes'?
Throw in some toys
and it will be.
Toys are included,
in the 'etc. etc.'
We will also require
a gift certificate.
Hmmm...
Your countrymen are rather fond
of Burger Cave, are they not?
Not that kind of certificate.
Should we require
your assistance,
we can call upon
you at any time.
A perfectly elegant solution.
You were right from
the beginning.
I shouldn't have never
come on this trip.
Everything has gone wrong!
I just, I wanted to
make San Savarre proud.
I wanted to make you proud.
I have never been more proud
to be your husband, Tasha.
I know things haven't
gone quite as planned,
but we're making it work.
Are we?
Our child won't be heir to the
throne, and it's all my fault.
Papers, please.
What's going on, Alexander?
We may not be able to take
you to San Savarre...
But we can bring
San Savarre to you.
Welcome home.
I don't understand.
The government of
the United States,
along with the hospital board
of this revered institution,
represented here by Dr.
Gonzales, has reached
a diplomatic arrangement with
the Principality of San Savarre.
I'm hereby delighted to announce
that as long as you are in this
room, you are on
San Savarran soil.
So, our baby...
Will be heir to the throne.
Oh!
Pretty clever, huh?
No.
My water just broke!
It's happening.
It's really happening!
[Dr. Gonzales]
Prince Alexander?
Alec!
There you go.
No no no!
Don't try to get up.
Have a sip of this first.
There we go. How's that?
Thank you. I apologize.
I think I got a bit overwhelmed.
That's normal. Come on.
Let's get you up.
[baby cries]
It's a girl!
Uncle Jeff has a niece!
Ho ho ho. Not so fast.
Not so fast.
We're not done yet.
[baby cries]
And a boy?
Tw -- Twins!
Twins!
[babies crying]
Well done.
[babies cooing]
Ah! You're awake, Your
Royal Highnesses.
It is indeed a day to celebrate.
Your first born child was a boy.
And the natural
heir to the throne.
The King will be pleased!
Back that up, Blevins.
Tasha's first born was a girl.
I was there. Don't test me.
Oh, never mind that. He's the
next male heir to the throne.
And the heir has
always been a male.
That doesn't really seem fair.
Our daughter was born first.
Oh, it's not about fairness,
Your Royal Highness,
it's about tradition.
The King would like to
speak to both of you
as soon as it
is convenient.
We'll schedule something
later with him today.
He's available now.
Ah, congratulations, my boy!
Well, you're not a
boy anymore, are you?
You have a boy of your own.
And an heir to the throne!
Our son wasn't the
first born, Father.
No, our daughter was.
Shouldn't she be the
heir to the throne?
We can quibble about
the details later.
The important thing
is that you get that
little girl and little boy back
here as soon as you can!
I suppose we can't
keep calling them
"little boy" and "little
girl" much longer.
No, I guess you're right.
We had it figured out when
we thought it was just one,
but I guess we'll
have to rethink.
Well, they'll be named
according to family tradition!
After my great grandparents:
Englebert and Gertrude!
Well, we can quibble
about the details later!
[slams tablet shut]
Did you just hang
up on the King?
Again?
No, I hung up on our
children's grandfather.
[tablet ringing]
Your Majesty?
I don't know what
happened there.
Must be going through a tunnel
or a black spot, or something.
Did Mommy just
hand up on Grandpa?
Ah! She did!
[baby cooing]
[light music, chattering]
It's a "Mom-Mo-Sa".
Pretty good, huh?
Jeff has been waiting his
entire life to be an uncle.
Well, he's a natural at it.
Jeff! You didn't have
to get us a gift!
Oh! Well that's a relief,
because I didn't.
This is way better!
It's a suggestion box
filled with baby names
from everyone at
the hospital!
Oh!
"The men's bathroom
needs nicer hand soap"?
Oh? Oh! I used the suggestion
box from the staff room.
That was my idea.
I think it's been
really helpful, too.
Right Mel?
There's a suggestion
box in the staff room?
Yeah, I suggest
you check it out!
Sorry, I should have
probably emptied it out.
Here, why don't you
keep digging, Tash.
Okay.
"Cutey Cute Sweetums".
Yeah. The kids were allowed
to put some in too.
Ah, yeah.
"Peanut".
I bet I know who
that one's from.
You got me!
That one is mine!
"Spaghetti".
And...
"Donna".
What do you think,
Spaghetti, Donna?
I think it's time for your nap.
Jeff. Thank you.
This is everything I
could have hoped for.
Yeah. I'm terrific.
[chattering]
-Congratulations!
-Thank you. Thanks for coming.
Hey. You're the best.
Well done.
[babies cooing]
You know, I've always
loved the name Grace.
[baby gurgles happily]
[Alexander] What do you
think about that, my love?
Do you think you're a "Grace"?
Well all right
then, Grace it is.
You know...
I've always thought the name
"Albert" was rather regal.
What are your thoughts
on that, young Prince?
[baby gurgles happily]
Well, then it's decided!
Grace and Albert.
Albert and Grace.
Built-in best friends for life.
[Alexander sniffs]
All right, which
one of you did it?
Oh no!
-Both of them?
-Uh hm.
Yeah. They're ganging
up on us already, huh!
Aren't you ready yet?
We haven't prepped for your
interview with Gabriella Kahn.
It's your first
engagement of the day.
I'm so sorry, Blevins.
I completely forgot.
I'm a little exhausted.
We'll prepare first,
then we'll tuck you in.
Now tomorrow morning,
first thing,
we do the exclusive with
Gabriella Khan about the twins,
and then...
We travel home.
San Savarre can't wait to
meet it's two newest Royals.
Duty calls!
Yeah, well... Ugh...
Doody also calls.
So, I'll go get ready.
And you take Albert?
Thanks Blevins!
Albert?
So. You have a name, do you?
Come over here, Blevins.
Grace and I will show
you how it's done.
It's very dandy Warhol,
isn't it?
[show opening music]
[audience applause]
Here you are,
at the end of your unexpectedly
extended North American tour.
I would say it's been
a raging success.
[audience applause]
How do you feel about
it, Prince Alexander?
San Savarre couldn't have
asked for a better ambassador
than my beautiful wife.
We're both very grateful
for the warm welcome.
Princess Tasha...
Oh, you can call me Tasha.
Tasha.
You have been photographed on
red carpets eating cheeseburgers
and hugging grumpy politicians.
For anyone else, this would
have been spun into bad press.
What is your secret?
I don't actually know.
Honesty, I suppose.
Alexander and I don't do
anything as a PR stunt.
We are who we are,
and we just hope that the
people we meet feel that.
Well they certainly seem to.
Now, you've had a few 'baby
bumps' along the way,
but you don't seem any
worse for the wear.
How are you two managing?
Are you exhausted?
[both together]
Yes!
Gabriella, I have
never been more tired.
I've also never been happier.
I'm in awe of my wife.
I have a healthy
baby boy and girl.
I'm living in a dream.
And your father, King
Edward, has just announced
the date of the christening,
where your son is going to be
named heir to the throne.
Oh, that hasn't
been decided yet.
Well, it certainly seems as
if His Majesty thinks it has.
Did you know about that?
No. No I didn't
We'll sort it out.
Well, I just don't
want "His Majesty"
to sort it out without us.
I'll fix it.
Well, you heard it here first.
Good night and tune
in again tomorrow.
[audience applause]
[babies cooing and gurgling]
I can't believe
you did this to us!
He's just a bit of
a traditionalist.
It comes with being a monarch.
Do you think he's right?
Shhh!
[Alexander] I think there's
value in some traditions.
But I want both of our children
to be loved, honored
and respected!
I want that for them too!
Then you need to
stand up for us!
[Jeff]
Shhh!
[quietly] Then you need
to stand up for us!
I would. But you're always
standing up to him first!
He doesn't listen to me!
I don't think he listens
to me either, Tasha.
So what do we do?
We talk to him together.
Come on.
[Tasha]
I wish we could stay longer.
But, looks like we've
passed our medical checks.
I get it.
It's time to go home.
Listen Jeff.
Thank you. For everything.
I couldn't have done any
of this without your help.
Well, yeah.
What else is new?
Oww!
You got that mom strength.
It was hard enough saying
goodbye last time.
Now it's not only my sister and
my best friend and my girlfriend
and the snooty guy, but also my
favorite two little bunnies!
I'm gonna miss you all so much.
I know.
We're going to miss you too.
You better.
-Take care.
-You too.
Sorry we didn't get to
spend much time together.
Me too.
When I'm back, we can plan a
real trip, start that countdown.
And we can be on the phone
every night until then.
Every night.
-Bye.
-Making a break for it!
Look at you. Hi!
[cooing]
-He's so tired.
-I know.
Your Royal Highnesses,
King Edward heard about
your little outburst on
the Gabriella Kahn show.
He's requesting a video
call with you both.
Well, you can tell the King
that we'll talk to him
when we're good and ready!
Oh! Hello, Your Majesty.
What was that you
were saying, Tasha?
Um. Well I, ah...
We...
We're concerned that
you're making plans
ahead of time for the
twins without including us.
And we don't like that
you've arbitrarily decided
that our son
will be the heir.
Of course he's the heir.
He's the first born
child of the Prince!
Technically, our daughter
was the first born.
[King Edward]
The heir is always male.
Why does it have to be our son?
Why not our daughter?
[King Edward] I understand
that some of our ways
may seem antiquated to
you, a "modern woman",
but traditions are
there for a reason.
The San Savarran crown
has passed down through
the male line
for centuries.
Okay, but don't you think
that San Savarre should,
I don't know, move
along with the times?
It's just tradition!
It's not the law.
Yes, well as far as I'm
concerned, tradition is the law,
and that's all I want
to hear about it!
Did the King just
hang up on you?
Yes.
Yes he did.
[babies fussing]
Hey, you're awake.
[Alexander]
Mean old king.
Are you happy to be going
home to San Savarre?
When's your next royal tour?
I think I can safely say that
there's no place like home.
Princess Tasha, what's it
like being mother to twins?
I think it means double
the diaper changes
and double the love.
Can you comment on your
Royal disagreement
between you and His Majesty?
We're not at liberty at this
time to talk about that.
And yet, we will.
Yes.
The simple fact of the matter is
that there was a disagreement.
We're a family.
Differences of opinion happen.
It's not juicy
gossip, we're just
overdue for a
heartfelt discussion.
And I'm very much
looking forward to it.
Right! Thank you.
Um, moving on.
Home at last!
[Tasha]
Finally.
A little time to ourselves.
We haven't had much of that
since Gracie and Albert came
into our lives, have we?
I don't think I've
ever had that.
Good point.
Heavy weighs the
crown and all that.
[baby fussing]
Oh, I think she's fussing
because she wants the crown.
Do you want the crown, Gracie?
Hmm?
Oh I'm not done
with that fight yet.
I would expect
nothing less, my love.
Oh, please, come in!
Well, no sleeping on the job!
There's much to be done.
There's documents to sign
and a baptism to plan.
Chop chop!
There's no place like home, huh?
Yeah, welcome back.
[Blevins] These are
formal thank you's
that require both
of your signatures.
[baby gurgling]
Albert wants to help.
Yes, well, if you could
tell Albert not to help,
that would
be very helpful.
It's just a lot harder without
an extra pair of hands.
Jeff made it so much easier.
Well, yes.
But you do have an entire staff
at your disposal, Your Highness,
ready and willing to assist.
Thank you, Blevins.
It's just not the
same as family.
Oh here.
Hey Blevins.
Since Albert is going to be
presented to the country as
heir, I was wondering if
you'd be willing to share
how succession in the
Royal Line actually works.
It's good of you to take an
interest in matters of state.
Yes. You're blossoming into
your role here very well.
Ah, well. It's my
duty, isn't it?
It is indeed!
San Savarre has always
followed the principles of
"primogeniture".
This means that the monarch's
eldest, and his descendants,
take precedence in
matters of succession.
The first born becomes the heir
apparent, and so on so on so on,
down the line.
-That's fascinating!
-Yes indeed!
So fascinating that Grace and
Albert have fallen asleep.
Yes, I would of thought it was
be of the utmost interest to you
Your Royal Highness, as
father to the rightful heir.
Of course it is,
isn't it sweetie?
Ah, yes. It is fascinating,
in its own way.
Where can I learn more?
The library holds many
historical documents about
the little history of our
little hereditary monarchy.
Heirs apparent, patrilineal
continuity, and, well of course,
that one time King Leon
the Third passed away
without having
named his successor.
That caused quite a
headache, I can tell you!
Well I'm sure!
Well, I must say I had
no idea this would
hold such interest
for you, Ma'am.
His Majesty will
be very pleased!
Now, when you finish
signing all this,
there are hundreds more
in the antechamber.
And I'll go and get them.
And perhaps...
A cheeseburger?
Oh!
What's gotten into you?
Well, a cheeseburger,
soon enough.
You're scheming.
You've that scheming
look on your face.
It's just an idea.
Hmm.
[Tasha reading]
Heir male or heir general...
There you are.
Ahem!
His Royal Highness requests
your immediate presence for, ah,
baby bath time.
Is it bath time already?
Yes.
Alexander?
[Alexander]
We got started without you
and it got very wet
very quickly in here.
I recommend you stay
outside and save yourself.
[Tasha]
Are you sure?
[Alexander chuckles]
Positive.
Clever girl.
I found something
in the library.
It's important.
[Alexander]
Oh?
So, technically,
Meaning that it has a hereditary
line of succession in which
the heirs male or heirs
general are stipulated.
[Alexander]
Heirs male or heirs general?
Meaning the oldest child
succeeds the throne.
Regardless of gender!
So Gracie could be the heir!
Exactly.
Although...
I'm pretty sure someone's
going to need some convincing.
I'm sure these two
could convince him.
Going to bring out
the big guns, huh?
He's already fast asleep.
[Bella] The Archbishop will be
presiding over the event
with only immediate
family in attendance.
No media will be allowed.
Save for the Royal
photographer.
We'll release the photos
the day after the baptism
at a scheduled media event,
so we can circulate the
images of Grace and Albert
in their gowns while keeping the
actual event a private affair.
Uh, yeah, it sounds like you
have everything under control!
I just really miss you, Jeffy.
I wish that you were here.
Surprise!
Hi!
You didn't think I'd miss
the big day, did you?
You're here!
Now that's more like it.
-I missed you.
-I missed you too.
[Bella's phone buzzes]
Duty calls.
Okay. Take me to your leader!
The King?
Oh, right. No, ah, I meant:
Take me to my sister!
Of course.
-Come one!
-Okay.
[babies fussing]
I can't believe you're here.
Well, I thought you'd need this,
and it was the fastest
way to get it to you.
Okay, what hilarious thing are
you going to prank me with?
No joke.
Here.
They were yours and mine.
I found them in the attic.
Oh Jeff. Thank you.
I'm so glad you're here.
It's been a little hard
looking after these two
without your help.
Aw, you're a natural, Tash.
I see the same
spark in you now
as when you're
treating patients.
Do you think it's bad to
admit that I'm kind of sad
to have left that part
of my life behind?
But, do you really have to?
I mean, what about opening
a children's hospital
here in San Savarre?
Well, you know how it is.
the schedule of a working
doctor a little difficult.
Maybe you can take a
more passive approach
until you're ready.
Like what?
Well you open the hospital,
and then until you're
ready to run it yourself,
you just fill it with
people you trust and love.
Yeah, like you?
Oh!
Yeah! Yeah, like me.
Wait, really?
Are you saying you'd be willing
to stay here in San Savarre?
Move your entire life here?
Well, I mean, with Bella and
you and Alec and the babies,
I mean, my entire life
is kinda here already.
The promise of a job, it'd
be hard to keep me away!
It could be fun.
Could be!
The Jeff Memorial Hospital.
Okay, no no no no.
Oh! Gorgeous, isn't it?
It's traditional
and it's appropriate.
Oh!
Change of plans.
I absolutely adore them!
Perfection.
It's a new tradition!
But the King will
have to approve.
[babies fussing]
[tablet ringing]
The King!
Ah, the King is calling.
[tablet ringing]
Father, we wanted to talk
to you before the baptism.
[King Edward]
Oh!
I haven't been this excited
since, oh I don't know,
since your wedding,
I suppose!
So, where are they?
Show me those little
bundles of bliss!
[Tasha]
Jeff brought the outfits.
They were ours when
we were christened.
What do you think?
[King Edward]
Absolutely charming!
It's a wonderful new
tradition, Tasha.
Many thanks to your brother
for his inspired contribution.
Thank you, Father.
[King Edward } Ah yes, Tasha,
I thought as much.
So I've been doing
my research...
Oh I am well aware.
Blevins has informed me of your
little digging expedition.
And he has shared with me
some of the relevant
history, actually.
Tasha...
You weren't exactly the
'traditional' choice of bride
for my son, and no one
could consider your
'cheeseburger diplomacy'
exactly traditional.
But every step of the way you
have taught me that, well,
that traditions are
what we make of them.
It takes bravery to step
away from the old path
and forge a new one,
and thanks to you, well,
I'm beginning to understand
the value in both
the old and the new.
Thank you.
[King Edward]
However.
There are certain traditions
that must be honored
no matter how 'old-fashioned'
they might appear.
Which brings me to the
future of San Savarre,
and the naming of
its eventual heir.
But, Father...
Don't you "but Father," me,
my boy.
[King Edward }
The fact is...
Tasha was correct.
The "Hereditary Line of
Succession" book does not
strictly stipulate that the heir
to the throne has to be male.
Blevins here was good enough
to point that out to me.
[King Edward] And if the
founders of our great land
decided it was unnecessary
to so stipulate, then...
Who am I to do so?
So, you're saying that...
Today we will
christen and present
the very first female heir and
eventual successor to the throne
the future Queen
Grace of San Savarre.
Thank you, Father.
Thank you.
Um, I'd actually
like to ask your permission
for one more thing.
Well, you've got me in a
very good mood right now,
so you might as well
proceed while you're ahead.
Well...
I'd like to open up a children's
hospital here in San Savarre.
And I recognize that my plate is
very full with Albert and Grace,
along with my Royal duties.
Yeah, I think...
And I know I can't do it on my
own, and I don't plan to.
But the fact of the matter is
looking after all children,
not just my own, is
more than a job to me.
It's, it's my entire life.
Yes, Tasha I think that...
A very young, wise patient,
Verity, once reminded me
the benefits of being both
a Princess and a doctor.
And I'd like to be like Verity.
I'd like to be both,
but on my own terms.
And that's it.
Now you can tell me why
that's such a terrible idea.
Tasha, if you'll just let
me get a word in edgewise,
I was going to
say that I think
it's an absolutely
wonderful idea.
Thank you.
Wait. What?
Well, it's not
going to be easy,
but then wonderful
things seldom are.
But it's a terrific
goal to work towards.
[King Edward]
And you have my full support.
Thank you so much!
No. Thank you, Tasha.
Now, I have to finish getting
ready for the ceremony.
[King Edward]
I'll see you both before long.
Goodbye for now!
-Goodbye!
[Alexander]
Imagine that.
A perfectly civilized end
to a phone call for once.
Darling, I am so proud of you!
Look at what you've
accomplished.
No. What we've accomplished.
Yes, yes, you're both terrific.
Now let's get a move on!
We've got a Royal
baptism to attend!
Who is this McDavid, again?
We met her on the tour.
She worked with her government
to allow the babies
to be born in San Savarre.
Oh right.
I like her.
She put a little piece of your
hometown in the middle of mine.
She's thanking you for
sending 10,000 baby boxes?
You sent 10,000 baby boxes?
It seemed right.
I'll always be grateful that
your country helped our babies.
The least we can do is
help some of theirs.
I love you.
I love you, too.
[babies gurgle happily]
[bells ringing]
-[Bella] All good?
-[Alexander] Uh huh.
Well?
Oh yeah. Bella loves baptisms.
She says there's less
people to wrangle.
You know that's
not what I meant.
I'm gonna do it today.
After the babies are baptized.
I can't wait any longer.
I'm just so nervous!
No. Don't be.
You can do it.
You can do anything.
Thanks for being here, brother.
Half brother.
I'll be back.
It's time! Ready?
Come on. Come on.
This is the best Christmas gift
I could have ever hoped for.
[babies cooing]
The babies' first Christmas.
♪
[Jeff]
You guys made history today.
One day, a Queen, your daughter,
will rule San Savarre.
See Tash, I told you
you could do anything.
Well, you can too, you know.
[Tasha]
Go on.
[Alexander]
Go for it!
Well. Here goes nothing.
Hey! Hi.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Hi.
Ah, do you have a minute?
Yes.
Um. Okay.
This is something I've
been wanting to...
[both say together]
What are you doing?
Proposing to you!
I've been wanting to do
this since the Royal tour,
and now you're
going to scoop me?
Well, I guess we're starting
a new tradition today.
Are you seriously...
Jeff, I love you so much.
Your corny jokes make me laugh,
your sweet empathy makes me feel
like I could cry if I need to,
and I want to spend
the rest of my life
laughing and
crying with you.
Jeffy, will you marry me?
Yes! Yes! Of course I will!
Welcome to the family!
You know, I've always
wanted a sister,
and I couldn't think
of a better one.
We've actually never
hugged before, have we?
No we have not,
Your Royal Highness.
But seems like we have
forever to figure that out.
Congratulations.
[Jeff]
Let's go show Blevins.
I think they're going to live
happily ever after, don't you?
Uh huh.
♪