Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Dear Alberto, guess what?
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
We got to use the big telescope
at school today!
It can see really far
but not Portorosso far.
Tell me how everything's going.
Miss you. Ciao, Luca.
Dear Luca,
life in Portorosso is awesome.
-Everything's perfect.
Oh.
Whoa.
Sono libero!
Woo-hoo!
Especially my new job.
I'm kinda the greatest fisherman
in the entire world.
Besides Massimo, of course.
Me and him, we're like pasta and pesto.
Massimo tells me everything.
Well, he would...
if he talked, which he doesn't. Ever.
Unless I'm breaking a rule.
-And even then, it's not much.
But I think he'll come around.
I'm gonna be the perfect employee,
and I'll make Massimo proud.
-- Ciao.
-- Alberto!
I know, I know,
I shouldn't use the boat on my own.
Am I fired?
-You're late.
-No problem. I got this! Be right back!
-Oh! I...
-Delivery!
Yes!
Dude, I don't mean to brag,
but Giulia's got some serious competition.
Am I fired?
-Lunch is on me!
-Huh?
Scusi, big guy.
Uh...
Hey, come on. I got this.
Okay, step one, sauce.
-Step two, fire.
Mangia?
Buongiorno, Massimo.
Just wait.
-Uh...
-Machiavelli, how did you get here?
He won't mind. Once he sees
the big catch we bring in, right?
I'll make him proud.
"Meow" yourself.
The fire's leaking.
The fire's leaking!
-Massimo, I didn't mean to--
-Massimo.
What are you doing?
I quit.
I can't do it. I'm not good at this.
I'm not good at being your... employee.
No.
Why do you even care?
You don't even like me.
You don't even talk to me.
Alberto!
-Ma, Alberto--
-Just let me go, Dad!
I once made my father so angry,
he punched a hole in a brick wall.
Really?
And then what happened?
Well, we fixed it.
I feel like we're gonna need
a lot more paint.
Ah! She's seen worse, you know.
-Worse than fire?
-Oh, sure!
Storms. Waves taller than the pescheria.
Whoa.
Um, try that.
-Oh!
Wait! Back to the waves thing,
what's the craziest storm
you've ever sailed through?
Oh-ho. Once I was caught
in a hurricane with two eyes.
No! Tell me everything.