Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
♪ Love is a game
since ever the same, ♪
♪ We win and lose
♪ I wonder who
might be to blame ♪
♪ Yes we wonder ♪
Russel: I believe in her,
and I believe in us.
Brenna, this next year is going
to be a new beginning
for our marriage.
We've been through
so much together.
Oh, god, that sounds terrible.
[clears throat]
Ok. Here we go.
I know that I've let you down
in so many different ways
and I'm sorry if I hurt you.
I really am.
But I was lonely and...
well the- that mistake-
and that mistake,
it made it clear-
it made it clear to me.
That mistake made
it clear to me
that you're the one for me,
Brenna.
You've always been the one
for me.
Yeah, that's good.
That's gonna work.
♪
♪ For trees must bloom ♪
♪ When spring is here again ♪
♪ So we are bound to play ♪
♪ Each time the same
old game ♪
♪ All leaves fall down ♪
♪ When Autumn comes again ♪
♪ So we are bound to play ♪
♪ each time the same
old game ♪
Hey. Merry Christmas.
♪
♪ Love is a game...
[gun shot]
[camera snapping]
Nine millimetre.
No weapon.
Sectioned off the perimeter.
Set up a team to do
some sweeps.
Maybe we'll get lucky.
Thank you.
Russel Douglas.
I recognize that name.
Peggy: People always
underestimate a former
beauty queen.
Glamour requires cunning.
Expertise.
Practise.
But hidden under it all,
innocence...
Peggy Sue Thomas.
I'm from the Washington
Celebrity News.
Why'd you do it?
They have it all wrong.
My only crime was falling
in love with the wrong man.
Here's where my story begins.
With an ending.
Sam Pasternak has left us
far too soon.
Tonight we're here to celebrate
his life.
A life well-lived.
Is he looking at me?
Sam, man, he really knew
how to live a life.
Whether it was bowling
or fly fishing...
He's looking at his shoes.
You're kidding.
Mmm-mmm.
So, you know, I appreciate
the time I had with Sammy.
'Cause it was far too short.
[begins to cry]
Oh... oh...
...When you lose someone early,
there's just that void.
[sniffles]
Well, now he's looking
at you.
Yeah, well that definitely
caught his attention.
I knew you'd think
of something.
Yeah, I usually do.
...his gusto, attitude.
-Let's raise a glass for Sam.
-To Sam!
I'm gonna miss you, Sam.
-To Sam.
Guest: Miss ya buddy!
[scoffs] I can't believe you are
still crushing on him.
All those years on the island he
never gave you the time of day.
Yeah, but we were young and
I was fat and things change.
Yeah, some things never do.
Meaning?
Nothing.
Just spit it out.
You're trying to get laid.
Janice, you say that like
it's a bad thing, big sister.
We're at a funeral,
little sister.
So what do you wanna talk about?
Death?
Well, our friend did die.
Oh.
And this was
his favourite song.
Are you sure?
No.
[laughs]
But I think we should
dance anyway.
[rock music]
♪
[laughter]
-Ok, um...
-Oh, my god.
Ok, I am... I'm gonna um,
get a drink.
No, you're leaving me?
-No.
-Yes.
I'll get you one.
Ok.
Alright. White Russian.
Double.
[rock music]
♪
He was a good man.
Those are hard to come by
these days.
Depends where you look.
I suppose.
To Sam.
Why is it good folks die young?
All evil bastards never seem
to get what's coming to them.
We're alive
so I guess that makes us
evil bastards then, huh?
I'm Jim Huden.
I know exactly who you are.
♪
You are something else.
You don't know the half of it.
Oh yeah?
Mmmhmm.
Why don't you
show me then.
What kind of girl do
you think I am?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought that-
[laughs]
I'm just busting you.
Why don't we go to
my place instead, hmm?
Jim: I say we focus on
developing a comprehensive
project management system,
not an update.
An entirely new
software package.
I'm telling you,
it'll be huge.
This is the software that'll
buy you that 100-foot yacht.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Let me stop you right there,
Jean.
Those subcontractors screwed
the pooch last time
and I don't think we should
rely on...
Listen, uh, let me
call you back.
Work stuff?
Just spitballing.
My business partner and I
own a company in Florida.
Mmm.
Microsoft shelled out large
for our last program
and this next one
is gonna be massive.
Oh, that's very exciting.
Don't let me interrupt
important business.
This morning is far too
beautiful to waste on work.
Then how should we waste it?
[giggles]
Oh...
You would not believe the things
that man can do with his hands.
And he has the most
gifted tongue.
Oh, it's curious, even.
I think we had sex for,
like, nine hours straight.
Maybe ten.
Well, Russel and I have lots
of sex, too.
Oh, I should hope so.
Yeah. Marathon sex.
Tons of it.
Right.
Yeah. He's into things
you wouldn't believe.
Ooh, things?
Yeah, like he got these
fuzzy pink handcuffs
off the internet.
[laughs]
Russel's into bondage?
Well, I think he'd like to be
into that kind of thing.
Do you want to be
into that sort of thing?
I mean, I'm not judging you
if you do,
but if you don't,
he's pressuring you.
Uh, it's not that.
It's- we fight a lot but I try
to focus on his good qualities.
Such as?
He's good with money.
If he wasn't managing
this place
we would have gone under
a long time ago.
Speaking of money, this is why
I hate being a landlord,
but I need to ask you for
this month's rent cheque.
You should just
buy my house already
so we don't have to keep
doing this.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I forgot.
Russel wrote the cheque
and I left it at home.
I'll get it to you.
Ok, thanks.
See? That's what
you really need.
You need an accountant.
You don't need Russel.
He's good with our daughter.
Ok, so you need an accountant
and a nanny then.
Seriously, you could do
so much better than Russel.
You think?
Yeah. I mean, maybe not at first
but once you drop a few pounds.
Excuse me?
Listen, I was a chubby
chunker, too,
but we all have the potential
to reinvent ourselves.
I mean, do you remember
when I got into shape
and I won the Miss Washington
pageant?
Yeah.
Hey there, gorgeous.
Hello, sexy.
[giggles]
Peggy: That is nice.
♪
Welcome to Taboo for You.
Do you long to indulge in
your naughtiest fantasies?
[giggles]
Sorry. Go on.
It's ok.
Where was I again?
Yeah, ok.
...indulge in your naughtiest
fantasies, hmm?
Then why not let Taboo for You
tickle your fancy?
[laughs]
Sorry. Sorry.
Just that thing looks like
a cat toy.
It's ok to laugh.
I mean, we wanna create
a fun environment so-
so clients feel comfortable
purchasing things like...
Mama's Secret.
Oh my god.
I know, right?
Bren, I'm telling you, the
mark-up on these things is huge!
We're gonna make a killing.
And where do you suggest
we sell this pervy stuff?
Well, there's a swinger's club
just out by the old gas station.
We could start there.
Nope, not happening.
Ok, we- we could throw parties
here at the house,
invite all our friends.
You don't have any friends.
Fine.
We'll invite your friends, then.
What about Peggy and whoever
she's dating these days?
Jim. She's dating
a guy named Jim
and I don't think they need
any help with their sex life.
You never know.
Plus, he's going back to Florida
in a few days.
Great! Is she throwing him
a going away party for him?
Not a party, just a couple of us
going out for drinks.
Perfect!
No way in hell am I showing up
at a pub
waving an armload of dildos.
Are you out of your mind?
I don't know, am I?
Wha? Look at...
[laughing]
I... I've got the tab.
I'm treating all
my ladies tonight.
-Thank you.
You two are like...
Romeo and fricken' Juliet
or something.
Just... you're so perfect.
Brenna: I think
it's really tragic
you're going back to Florida,
Jim.
It's so sad.
Um...
[teary] Peggy's...
she's gonna be... devastated-
[laughing]
Stop.
I should probably go because I
don't wanna be a Debbie Downer.
Ok. Ok.
Hold on here. I got you.
I got you.
Ok?
-You always do.
-Yeah.
You always, always get me.
That's why you're
my best friend.
Yeah, I know. I know.
Come on.
Get in there.
I know, I got ya.
Hey, Janice, do you think
you could-
-give her a ride?
Sure, no problem.
Travel safe, Jim.
Yeah, thanks.
You're not coming back?
Nah, it's late.
Let's go.
Come on.
-Goodnight.
-Thanks.
[chuckles]
Janice: You okay?
Wow.
Well.
Yeah.
I sure as hell don't want you
to be devastated.
Yeah, well Brenna can be a bit
over-the-top sometimes.
I sure am gonna miss you,
but uh, I'm a survivor.
You deserve more
than just survival.
I'd like to think so.
Are you satisfied
with your life?
I mean, who's ever
really satisfied?
Sometimes I think about leaving
Whidbey Island
and going somewhere warm.
I always thought, you know,
Vegas would be fun.
What about you?
Are you satisfied?
What's your dream?
Uh...
You wanna know the truth?
Nothing but.
I've always wanted
to kill someone.
[laughing]
Who doesn't wanna
kill someone?
Who's on your list?
Oh, bosses, ex-wives...
Wives?
[laughs]
But that's not really what
I'm dreaming about right now.
Yeah, well you're gonna have
to get used to dreaming
because this is your farewell
celebration, remember?
What kind of fool would
celebrate leaving you?
Damn right.
If I didn't have my whole life
back in Florida...
my business, you know.
It's just-
You know what I think?
I think what we have
is special,
and so normal rules,
they don't apply, ok?
Mmm.
[laughs softly]
You wanna get out of here?
-Mmmhmm.
-Me too.
[giggles]
Come on, let's go.
[giggling]
Good.
Thank you.
I like that better.
That's the trouble
with a whirlwind romance.
Suddenly, boom.
It's over.
[chuckles] I'm sorry
Jim had to leave you
but you had your fun, right?
I mean, you finally bagged
the one that got away.
And then he got away again.
Well, it's not like he wanted
to leave.
He's got that big software
company in Florida
and plus he plays in a band
down there, right?
Right. He's rich, talented,
and 3,000 miles away.
Well, maybe you could
visit him.
Oh, I don't chase men, Janice.
They chase me.
Suit yourself.
I'm putting all this
in the laundry.
Oh.
You treat me like a queen.
I know.
Damn.
So that's Jean.
Someone's got a wife.
[phone rings]
You miss me yet?
Peggy, I've missed you
since the minute I left.
This is torture.
And what're we gonna do
about it?
I have a proposition.
♪
Viva Las Vegas.
Oh, you know moving there
has always been my fantasy.
Now it's a reality.
Sounds dreamy compared
to my situation.
Russ asked me to make
marinated shrimp skewers.
So random.
I had to get them fresh
from the market.
What do you think, I should get
a house or a condo?
Condo.
And then he didn't even
try the shrimp.
He fell asleep eating
microwave popcorn.
Are you even listening to me?
Sorry, yes. Vegas.
I'm glad things are working out
for you.
Isn't life an amazing adventure?
[sighs]
One day you're a lonely,
divorced beauty queen
sweeping up hair
in a salon
and the next you're flying
to Vegas
to be with the man
of your dreams.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you.
That means the world
to me.
Oh, and I can finally get off
this crappy island!
I'm sorry.
I'm- I'm... sorry.
Whidbey is, like,
perfectly nice,
it's just, you know, it's a
little quiet for a girl like me.
I guess.
[sighs]
God, I do love that man.
And now we're never gonna have
to say goodbye
to each other ever again.
What?
Nothing.
I thought you were happy
for me.
I am. It's just...
Russ has been all up
in my face again.
Just thinking about
another thing that he did.
He was doing our taxes
and he's all like
"Brenna, where are
the bank statements?
"Where are the receipts?
"How do you manage to spend
$604 at Costco?
"Blah, blah, blah.
Dammit Brenna."
Oh, my god!
I'm so sick of listening
to you whine
about Russel this
and Russel that.
You can't even be happy
for me for two minutes
because you're so
busy complaining.
If you're so miserable why don't
you just grow a spine
and do something about it,
huh?
Well, it's not that simple to
just up and leave your husband.
Yeah, it is.
I did it.
Twice.
But we have a kid together.
I'm sorry.
I'm- I'm sorry.
Sally's great.
I... look, I'm just trying
to give you a little bit
of tough love.
Sometimes, the truth,
it's hard to take,
but when you- when you finally
face it it sets you free.
Hey, I know this is a bad time
but do you have my rent cheque?
Thank you.
Oh, there's my ride.
Listen, I know that
you've got this
because you are a smart woman
no matter what Russel says.
He never said I wasn't smart.
Did he say that?
You know what?
Why don't you come to Vegas
and party with me and Jim?
Maybe I will.
Bye!
♪...Yes, we wonder ♪
♪
♪ Love is a game... ♪
Brenna: He bought Egyptian
cotton sheets?
Mmmhmm.
Don't you have to
hand wash those?
Ugh, who needs
the extra work?
[laughs]
That reminds me,
the sink in the laundry
room clogged.
I have a bill from the-
from the plumber for you.
I tried to plunge it myself
but you should have seen
what was in there.
[laughing]
A big, slimy clot of hair.
It was super gross.
Anyways, I don't have
much to say,
Russel's out with Sally.
[laughing]
I'm bored out of my mind.
[laughs]
By the way, um, I'm gonna be
a teensy bit late
with rent this month,
just wanted to mention that.
So how are things going
down over there?
[laughing]
How's Jim doing?
Um, he's doing magnificently.
[snarling]
Did you guys get a dog?
[laughing]
Anyway, things are the same old,
same old here.
Except for the salon.
I mean, the salon is not
the same without you.
You know what, Brenna?
I gotta go.
Someone's coming.
[laughing]
Hey, babe.
You're late.
Yeah, sorry.
Just Sally was having so much
fun at the carnival.
The carnival?
Yeah.
Well, why didn't you invite me?
Well, it was uh, kind of a spur
of the moment thing, you know?
Why didn't you answer
my calls?
Well, it's a carnival,
you know.
It's loud and I guess I um,
I didn't hear my phone.
Mama, Fran won a bunny for me!
Fran?
Yes, mama.
Fran is super nice
and good at darts.
Plus, she got me a milkshake.
I guess Fran doesn't know
our daughter can't have sugar
before supper.
Yeah, sorry. She really wanted
a milkshake and-
Who the hell is Fran?
She's a friend.
She's the old lady you've been
sleeping with, isn't she?
Fran's not old,
she's like 42.
So you admit you were
with her?
[scoffs]
Brenna, you don't even
like carnivals.
Remember last time we went?
You puked all over
the Tilt-a-Whirl?
You took our daughter on a date
with your girlfriend?
She's not my...
What am I supposed to do,
hmm?
You never wanna go anywhere
with me.
Sometimes I feel like
you don't even like me.
Maybe I don't.
What?
I want you outta here.
Come on, you're not serious.
Get out!
Where am I supposed to go?
I don't care.
Just go.
Oh, you don't care.
Not anymore.
Bye.
Brenna?
I did it.
Yay.
What did you do?
I kicked Russel out.
No. Seriously?
[Peggy laughs]
Peggy?
Hmm?
Sorry, thought I locked it.
Ok, so Russel's gone.
Tell me what happened?
He pushed me too far,
flaunting his affair in my face.
So I screamed at him.
He was terrified.
It was awesome.
That's my girl.
Nice work.
I'm telling you, Brenna,
from now on everything is gonna
start getting easier.
And you know what?
When you get a big, fat divorce
settlement you can buy my house!
Yeah. Yeah, I guess I could.
Hey, listen. Um, it's
really late.
You mind if uh, I talk
to you tomorrow?
Ok. Goodnight.
Ok.
Brenna's gonna buy my house.
Cha-ching.
[distant sound]
Did you hear that?
Wait here.
Janice?!
I found a key under the mat.
I'm so sorry to show up
unannounced.
Oh.
I promise I'll call ahead
next time.
Jim, you're gonna scare
the poor woman to death.
Honey.
Honey, what's going on?
Everything.
He just kept yelling at me.
We were screaming
at each other.
I had to get outta there.
So I got in my car and I just
drove straight to the airport.
You're too good
for that man.
If I'm so great
why is he leaving me?
Oh...
I am so angry.
I could kill him.
If you want, I could take him
out for you.
Oh, that's so sweet.
He's not very social.
I don't think it would help,
anyway.
No, I meant take him out.
Permanently.
What?
I could end him.
No. No!
He is not perfect but he's
the father of my child.
I would never want him harmed.
Peggy?
He's kidding.
So, my half-sister took off
in the middle of the night.
I guess I scared her.
Do you want to explain yourself,
Jim?
I'm not a psychopath.
Well, that's reassuring.
And I'm not a sadist.
It's not- it's not like I enjoy
hurting people.
Jim, you offered to kill
her husband.
I know. I know.
Have you ever wanted
revenge so bad
that it poisons every bit of joy
that life hands you?
Revenge against who?
My step-dad.
He used to beat my mom
and I'd hear her screaming
and crying,
and if I tried to stop it,
he'd lay a beating on me, too.
I despised that man.
I am so sorry.
I get it. I get it.
I have my own demons.
I get it.
I'm the sorry one.
All these years and I'm still
filled with rage.
I should have protected her.
I didn't have the guts
to stand up to him.
Where is he now?
Oh, he's dead and buried.
Long ago.
So there's comfort in that,
right?
Not at all.
That bastard died peacefully
in his sleep.
He never got what he deserved.
I should have killed him
when I had the chance.
Jim, you can't keep living
with this.
There's gotta be some way
you can let it go.
Jim, I am here living my dream
in Vegas because of you.
You.
So I'll do anything to help.
Anything.
[music blaring]
♪
[phone ringing]
Hey, how's it going?
Jean: Hey, babe. I'm so excited.
I finally got a hold of you.
You answered the phone.
I can't hear you.
Can you hang on a second?
Work today was nuts.
I am so relieved
to finally...
So how is the vibe over there?
The band's hot,
did you hear them?
There's a ton of gigs
in Vegas.
I'll land something soon.
That's great, hon.
Yeah. Thanks.
Are you auditioning tonight?
Yeah. I'm at the uh,
rehearsal space.
They're just warming up.
Good luck. I guess.
Uh-huh.
I really miss you.
I can't manage this
business alone.
We're running out of money.
Hey, maybe I should come
stay out there with you
until we figure this out.
Oh, hey, the band's
calling me.
I gotta go, babe.
Jean: Bye.
Jim: Bye.
[hangs up]
You call your business partner
"babe"?
Crap.
How is good old Jean doing?
She must miss you terribly.
I do my research.
I've known about Mrs. Jim Huden
for quite a while now.
I'm so sorry, Peggy.
I shouldn't have hid it
from you.
Don't worry about me.
I'm a big girl.
I know what I'm getting
myself into.
It's gotta be a whole lot
tougher for poor Jean,
losing you to me.
Bang!
[groans]
You got me! Ahhhh!
[laughs]
You little rascal!
Hello, Russel.
Hey, Brenna.
We had a great weekend.
Sally got caught up with her
homework and we went to a movie-
Where did she get
those new toys?
I'm sorry?
We said no new toys
'til Christmas.
You're spoiling her
with these weekend visits.
I didn't buy 'em.
Then who did, Russel?
Oh, geez.
You took Sally to see her again,
didn't you?
Look, I'll take my daughter
wherever I damn well please, ok?
-Oh, really?
-Yeah.
Well, then you can take her
to work with you this week.
What?
Sally? How'd you like to spend
the week with Daddy
while Mommy goes to visit
Aunt Peggy in Vegas?
Sally: Yay!
Brenna. You know
I can't do that.
Figure it out, Russel.
[rock music plays]
♪
♪ You sure will remember
days like this, ♪
♪ I'll show you that
I like the taste, ♪
♪ I know what you're
thinkin' about... ♪
[laughter]
He's got slot machines
in the bar.
You wanna try your luck?
Luck? Me? I don't
think so.
Oh, there's our
favourite bartender,
and I'm his
favourite customer.
Although he forgets
our drink orders a lot
because he's eyeing me,
right, Jim?
I think Peggy's cleavage
has its own bar tab.
[laughter]
Drinks on me.
Seems like you two are doing
well out here.
Oh, honey, we are thriving.
Well, I am not.
Not so much.
Oh, what's going on?
It got declined again?
Can we uh, talk
about this later?
Of course, darling.
Is something wrong?
A glitch in the credit
card reader.
Well, maybe you can help him
fix it, Mr. Software Genius.
That's how Jim made
his fortune.
Oh.
Yeah.
Back in a sec.
I'm glad you guys are
so well off
because I don't have
good news.
I can't buy your house, Peggy.
What do you mean?
That's been our plan all along.
Well, with Russel gone
and the salon going under
I've got no money
and it turns out Russel's
got nothing in the bank.
Besides, even if
we do get divorced
it's not like I'm looking at
some huge settlement.
So you- you're broke?
Shit.
I had to empty
my bank account
to buy my plane ticket here,
so...
Why would you do that?
I don't know.
'Cause you're the one with
all the bright ideas, Peggy.
What're you talking about?
You don't even remember?
You told me to grow a spine
and do something
so I threw Russel out.
Now I got no money,
no husband
and no frickin' clue
what to do next,
so why don't you advise me,
all great and powerful
Peggy Sue Thomas?
Hi.
[clears throat]
Isn't she the best?
She's the best.
I just love this woman.
Brenna, you know I always
have your back
so we're gonna figure
this out.
Ok?
But first you need a drink.
Yeah.
Mmmhmm.
Oh, my gosh!
That's so strong.
You drink these all the time?
All the time.
[sighs]
Oh... I'm attracted
to his darkness.
I know that probably sounds
weird to you,
being married to Russel.
What are you attracted to,
his blandness?
[laughing]
What do you mean,
"his darkness"?
Oh, he had an awful childhood.
He and his mom were abused
by his step-father.
He's still haunted by it.
He's a complicated guy but I
love the way his mind works.
Hmm.
[chuckle]
Mama! I missed you!
Oh, I missed you.
Did you gamble away
all our money?
What did you say?
Sally?
What are you telling her?
Well, hello to you, too,
Brenna.
How was Vegas?
It was great.
Peggy and Jim sure know
how to have fun.
Not like some people.
Look at you, galavanting
all over the continent
with your drunk buddies while
I scramble to find child care.
Maybe I should do
a little travelling.
Take Sally to Alaska
to visit my dad.
You wouldn't dare.
You know what, maybe I'll
take her there permanently.
Sally!
It's time to go.
This is too far, Russ.
[mocking]
Say goodbye to your father!
Bye, Daddy!
Bye, sweetheart,
I'll see you soon.
[sighs]
This feels sudden, so I want
to talk it over with you.
If the judge signs
your restraining order
Russel won't be able
to contact you
or come within 100 yards
of you.
Are you certain you want
to proceed?
Absolutely.
Alright.
I'll need you to describe
the incidents
that have prompted you
to file.
He said he was gonna take Sally
to Alaska and not come back.
Plus, he yells at me.
-Verbal abuse?
-Big time.
And he yells at our daughter.
He neglects her, too.
He's a very neglectful father.
Has there been physical abuse?
Not so much.
But he says he's gonna get me
when I'm not looking.
Get you?
He said he's gonna punch me
in the face
and hold me under the tub water
'til my feet stop kicking.
I sleep with a knife
under my pillow.
I don't trust him.
[sighs]
I cannot believe that bartender
from the other night.
I mean, the nerve of that guy.
We spend so much money
in that place
you think they'd be begging us
to show up.
I do think we class up that dump
a little bit, don't you?
We need money, Peggy.
I thought you were a
self-made millionaire.
And I thought you were gonna
sell your house to Brenna.
Brenna's broke,
you know that.
So what's this really about,
Jim?
The Microsoft sale
was years ago.
That money's pretty much gone.
And what about that fancy new
software you're working on?
I haven't been developing
the software,
I've been partying with you!
Is that really so awful?!
No.
It's been great.
But I gotta go home.
You mean Florida.
I've gotta work.
We've been spending money
like crazy.
My credit cards are maxed out
and my savings account
is nearly empty.
You do realize that you could-
you could work here, right?
So why do you really wanna
go back to Florida?
She is my wife, Peggy.
Oh, finally.
Finally, the truth!
Plus, all my business
connections are in Florida.
And my software company.
My bank accounts.
And your precious wife, Jean.
Am I not enough for you, Jim?
You are more than enough for me.
But neither of us can afford
this lifestyle!
[exhales]
If you go back...
I will come down there
and I will bang and bang on
your door, wife or no wife.
[phone rings]
[sighs]
What is it, Brenna?
Guess what?
I took a restraining order
out on Russel.
And here I was thinking you were
calling to apologize
for the late rent, again.
Oh yeah.
Sorry about that.
Anyways, you wanna know
what pushed me over the edge?
When I came back from Vegas
he threatened me and Sally.
He was so abusive.
Now he can't come anywhere
near us.
And I say good riddance.
He's such an idiot.
Wasting money on skateboards
he can't ride,
guitars he can't play.
Life insurance he can't cash in.
Life insurance?
Yeah, he's got like
three policies now.
Anyway, babe, I gotta go.
Sally will be home soon.
I'll call you later.
And these are the lights.
[character voice]
I like the lights.
And that's my mommy.
Just eat your cauliflower
and then you can go play.
But it's gross.
It's good for you.
[character voice]
It smells like a diaper.
Just eat your food or
I'm telling your father.
You're gonna call Daddy?
Can I talk to him, too?
No.
But... I miss him.
I miss him, too, honey.
Then why won't you let me
see him?
Because it's- it just- it-
it's grown up stuff.
Just go to your room.
But...
Just go on!
Go to your room!
I hate you!
What have I done?
[phone ringing]
Detective Williams.
This is Brenna Douglas.
Mrs. Douglas.
How can I help you?
I wanna cancel the restraining
order.
Daddy!
Hey, honey.
I made a superhero cape
for my bunny.
Oh, that's awesome.
Can I see?
You did this all by yourself?
Wow, cool.
Hey, sweetie, um, Mom and I
need to talk.
So I should go play?
You got it.
Got it.
See ya, kiddo.
So, the restraining order.
So sorry about that.
What made you change your mind?
I was overreacting.
You didn't do anything
to justify that.
Well, I'm sorry
for the things I said.
I'd never take Sally
away from you.
You're a good mom, Brenna.
You're a good father.
We're just not a good couple.
We used to be, remember?
I remember being crazy
about you.
Same here.
Hey, can we try again?
Please?
Sally, it's time for me to go.
Bye, Mama!
I guess that's a "no".
Give me time.
These late fees,
they're- they're obscene.
I mean, how do you expect anyone
to off their bill
when you keep charging-
Collector: They're the
conditions you agreed to.
Unfortunately, there are
consequences for defaulting-
No, I understand
the consequences
of not paying on time,
I mean, I'm not an-
But your inability to make
the minimum monthly payment
we have to cancel your card.
No, no. You can't cancel
my card!
What am I gonna live on?
Have a nice day.
Dammit.
Hey, rockstar.
How was the audition?
They're a shit band, anyway.
Fran- Fran.
Russel, explain this to me, why?
It's over, ok?
Can you just tell me why?
I love Brenna.
And I'm gonna do whatever
it takes to win her back.
No. Please don't do this.
Goodbye.
Russel! Russ-
Do you believe me now?
Yeah.
Yeah?
[laughs]
Can I come home?
Please?
Patience.
We have a lot to work on.
Ok. Ok.
Patience. Ok.
This isn't very patient.
God.
Yeah, well, I'm sorry but
I've got bills to pay, too, Jim.
It's just until I get paid.
Paid?
I thought you couldn't find
any gigs.
I'm sure I'll get
something soon.
I hope so.
I can't send you any more money
'cause I don't have any.
Can you borrow some?
I'll try.
You know, I do miss you, Jim.
I gotta go. Bye.
I can't believe I haven't gotten
any offers on the house.
I really hope Brenna can buy it.
Brenna's broke.
Yeah, because Russel spends
all his money
on sex toys and life insurance.
You know, maybe we should
take a trip home for Christmas.
Hmm.
[phone rings]
Hey, Brenna, is
something wrong?
No, not at all.
I was just thinking...
maybe you could spend Christmas
with us.
That- that'd be great.
[phone rings]
Hello?
Russel.
Peggy. Hi.
I have a gift for Brenna.
Alright, great.
You have a present for Brenna?
That's what I said.
And Russel, listen,
we weren't supposed to get
each other presents
so it's a surprise.
You can't tell her, ok?
My lips are sealed,
I promise.
Alright, thank you.
I'm gonna hand you to Jim.
Ok.
Oh, look, there's Brenna.
I'm gonna go say hi.
Brenna!
Hey.
[laughing]
Hey!
I'm back!
Oh, I missed your hugs.
You're like a short,
little Grizzly bear.
So, what's new?
Tell me everything.
Oh, you know, the usual.
Sally's getting excited
for Christmas.
Of course.
She's thrilled that her father's
joining us for the holidays.
What?
I cancelled the restraining
order.
Uh-huh.
So I... I invited him over.
Oh, that's nice.
For Russel, at least.
Anyhow, we'll talk
about this later, alright?
Good morning.
Come on over.
Daddy!
There's my little elf!
[laughs]
How are ya?
Do you wanna help me?
Careful.
There's something special
in there.
-Hey.
How are ya?
Nice to see you.
-The place looks great.
-Thank you.
Look at this.
Is she finally in bed?
Yep.
Dreaming of sugar plums.
What's this?
Well, I know we said we weren't
gonna exchange gifts this year
but I just wanted to get
you something
letting you know how I feel.
Damn you, Russel Douglas.
Go ahead.
Open it.
It's a swing.
Like... from a jungle gym?
Not exactly.
Jesus Christ, Russel.
What, you don't like it?
We said we were gonna
take things slow.
You call this slow?
Well, I mean...
What're you doing?
Oh look, Bad Boys II is on.
Great.
[gunshots in TV]
[gun shot]
You must really hate them.
Huh?
Pigeons.
Oh yeah.
Well, it's flying rats, right?
They crap all over our patio.
I bought the gun so I could
get rid of them.
Well, it'll do the trick,
for sure.
You gotta any other questions
on how to use it?
What's up?
I was mean last night.
I'm sorry.
But today's a new day.
And you know how
I love blueberries.
Yeah.
What're you rushing around for?
I got an errand to run.
I can't find my shoes.
These'll have to do.
Socks with flip flops.
Sexy.
Yeah.
What kind of errand?
Well, it's a surprise,
but you're gonna like it.
From a friend.
I'll be back soon.
Ok.
♪
♪ Love is a game,
since ever the same ♪
♪ We win and lose... ♪
Russel: And I'm sorry if
I hurt you, I really am.
But you're the one for me,
Brenna.
You've always been
the one for me.
Yeah, that's good.
That's gonna work.
♪
♪ Love is a game... ♪
Hey. Merry Christmas.
Russel Douglas?
In the flesh.
[gun shot]
[knocking]
Detective Williams.
Mrs. Douglas, this is my
partner, Detective Steadman.
Hello, ma'am.
I wondered if we could ask you
a few questions
about your husband.
Is this about the restraining
order?
Things have been bad between us
for years
but we've been trying
to make our marriage work.
I hope we can.
How long have the two of you
been separated?
A couple of months.
And the reason
for your separation?
Well, she knows.
Um, we fought constantly
and he was cheating on me.
With whom?
Multiple women.
And men.
One man.
At least, I suspect.
And a variety of women.
Or- or one. One woman
for sure.
An older woman.
He liked to brag about having
sex and partying with her.
He was into some kinky stuff.
I- I just can't accept
his deviant lifestyle.
And by "deviant lifestyle"
you mean...
He wants me to swing with him
and he gets mad when I say no.
I think he wants
to join a key club.
I hear they meet Saturdays at a-
at a restaurant on the island.
Brenna, we um-
And he dresses like a freak.
He wore a kilt to work.
And he thinks everything he sees
on the internet is normal.
And he's very controlling.
And very abusive.
Physically abusive?
Well, not- not so much.
Just mentally.
Brenna, do you know why
we're here?
Not really.
Your husband, Russel, was found
dead in his car this afternoon.
Oh.
He was shot in the head.
[phone rings]
I should get that.
She didn't seem too surprised.
Didn't seem too broken up
about it, either.
Suspect?
Definitely.
So I'm gonna um,
head to the airport,
get on a stand-by to Miami.
You're not staying.
No.
Just, I... I thought maybe
I'd lay low for a bit.
Check in on the business,
you know?
But you're coming back, right?
Sure.
Remember what you told me?
What we have is special.
God, who would do such a thing?
Is it true that Brenna
and Russel
were trying to get
back together?
[scoffs]
It never would have worked out.
Those two were doomed.
Well, at least they were trying.
I wish my ex and I had tried
harder to save our marriage.
Poor Brenna.
She must be a mess.
You know the Whidbey gossips
are all over this.
People are saying
she's a suspect.
Hmm.
Spoken with the vic's family,
co-workers, landlord,
ex-girlfriend.
As far as I can tell,
Russel Douglas had no enemies.
He was well-liked by everyone.
Well, not everyone.
There is one person who doesn't
seem very fond of him.
You mean his wife?
Brenna's hard to read.
One minute she hates
his guts...
The next she's cancelling
the restraining order.
Your husband died December 26.
You filed an insurance claim
January 3rd.
Why the rush?
I'm real bad with money.
Russel handled all
the financial stuff.
I got jack squat in the bank.
My salon's going down the tubes.
I don't even own this house.
I just- I want enough
to support myself.
And my daughter,
of course.
Wheeler Pacific Insurance
empathizes, Mrs. Douglas.
Here's the problem.
The police informed us
you are a person of interest
in your husband's murder.
Why would I wanna kill
my own husband?
Well, some may say the insurance
money could be a motive.
Would you agree to take
a polygraph test?
Nope.
Nope?
My lawyer advised against it.
I'll be frank.
The company is reluctant
to issue the money to you.
We'd be willing, however,
to set up a trust fund
for your daughter.
My lawyer said you might
pull something like this
so we prepared a statement.
[clears throat]
I, Brenna Douglas,
categorically state
that I was not involved
in the death of my husband
in any way.
The insurance proceeds
are rightfully mine
and it is inappropriate
to withhold the money
or award it to my child based
on unsupported allegations.
There you go.
That's your copy.
Come on, Jim.
Where are you?
[glass shatters]
[phone ringing]
Whidbey Police,
Detective Steadman speaking.
How can I help you?
Tipster: Do you have
a recent unsolved murder
on Whidbey Island?
Yes, we have an open
homicide investigation
from December 26th.
Sir?
Are you still there?
I have information but
I'm scared to talk about it.
Ok, what kind of information?
The shooter is a friend
of mine.
Ok. What's his name?
He has this girlfriend.
All they do is party.
They've been hard up for cash.
Living off credit cards.
What's her name?
[hangs up]
Sir? Hello?
[dial tone]
Thank you, Mrs. Martino.
I'll be in touch if there's
anything else.
Peggy: Hey babe! Finally!
Is this Peggy Sue Thomas?
Uh, who's asking, please?
I'm Detective Williams,
Whidbey Island PD.
Peggy Sue Thomas?
Yes, this is Peggy.
Miss Thomas, I'm calling
because your name came up
in our investigation into
the murder of Russel Douglas.
Oh, really?
We gather you knew
Mr. Douglas?
Yeah, uh, a bit.
I worked at the salon
with his wife.
What a tragedy.
It's uh, I'm kind of an
unwilling landlord for Brenna.
She's planning on buying
my house, but...
Were you in touch with Russel
during the holidays?
Yeah, we played a little bit
of phone tag
trying to arrange
a gift exchange.
A gift exchange?
I got a surprise for Brenna.
Thank you, Miss Thomas.
I'll be in touch if I have
any more questions.
You'll be in touch if you have
any more questions?
Oh, I don't think so,
Detective Williams.
You called all the numbers
from Russel Douglas's
phone records, yeah?
I just got off with
Peggy Sue Thomas.
She called Russel a couple days
before Christmas.
Doesn't seem to be
anything there.
Alright.
Ok.
[ringing]
This is Jim,
leave a message.
[beep]
[teary] Stop being a wuss
and call me back.
We need to talk.
[ringing]
Peggy. I've been calling
and calling.
Why haven't you called me back?
I know, I'm sorry,
it's just uh...
ever since I heard about Russel
I uh, I've just been so upset.
Well, I've been upset too.
I- I needed you, Peggy.
I just didn't know
what to say.
It's just so awful.
And poor Sally,
growing up without a father?
Now all she has is me
and you know I'm a mess.
Yeah, well...
You know, Brenna,
you're gonna be stronger and
you're gonna get through this.
I just know it.
Ok.
Yeah. Thanks.
Hey, um, the police
just called me.
Did they- did they ask you
about me or something?
No, they probably got
your number
from Russel's phone records.
Of course. That makes
so much sense.
Yeah. Um, I have some news.
I had to fight tooth and nail
for it
but I finally got
the insurance money.
One policy, at least.
Oh my god,
that's great!
You can buy my house.
Yeah, um... actually,
I'm- I'm really sorry Peggy,
but I couldn't stay there.
There are too many memories.
I saw a house for sale and I
fell in love and I bought it.
This place, just-
it feels better.
It's a new start for us.
I- I hope you understand.
Peggy, are you there?
Yeah, I'm here.
Congratulations, I guess.
I hope you're not upset.
Brenna, I- I gotta run.
Can we talk about this
some other time?
I'm uh- I gotta go, ok?
God!!!
Hey.
Wanna go on a trip?
When you were gone I couldn't
catch a buzz
no matter how hard I tried.
Now I feel high
all the time.
I just wish you felt
the same.
You know me, Jean.
I've always had
my ups and downs.
Yeah, but not this bad.
Not like this.
You know you can
tell me anything.
[knocking]
Don't move.
Hello.
I'm sorry if my arrival
is uncomfortable for you.
But this?
This is bullshit.
Jim just came back so he could
sponge off of you.
He's not sponging off of me.
He left you.
He loves me.
And you need to face that.
Oh honey, you just don't get it,
do you?
His body, it may be here,
but his heart?
It belongs with me.
Tell her that's not true.
She's my wife.
I love her.
I'm not leaving her.
I'm sorry, Peggy.
You're a fool, Jim Huden.
You know, the cops called me.
What?
You better watch yourself, Jim.
[door opens, closes]
What was she talking about?
You remember what I told you
about my step-father?
Yeah.
Something happened
on Whidbey Island.
What? What do you mean?
Well, I did it, Jean.
I did it.
I was hoping you'd call again.
I didn't know if I was gonna,
but...
I keep seeing that poor guy
getting shot in the face.
Well, I'm glad
you did call back.
Yeah, well, whatever.
I heard something
kinda urgent.
Go on.
The shooter's planning
on flying to Vegas
to visit his girlfriend.
Uh, by girlfriend you're
referring to uh...
Peggy Sue Thomas?
[sighs]
Yeah, Peggy.
She was just here and they had
a big fight.
He's afraid that
she's mad at him.
Plus, he wants to make sure
that they have
their stories straight.
So he's going to Vegas soon.
You should probably
get to him first.
Well, it's tough for us
to catch this guy
if we don't know his name.
Sir, are you still there?
Jim Huden.
His name is Jim Huden
and he lives in Punta Gorda.
And who am I speaking to?
My name is Neil Dodson.
I'm his best friend.
[hangs up]
Uh, hello? Sir?
Uh, we need to get some-
Search warrants.
I'm on it.
Well, it's been a couple
days now.
Are you gonna...
say something or what?
That was a lot to take in, Jim.
But honestly, I've...
I've never felt closer to you.
And I understand
why you did it.
You had demons to slay.
Thanks.
I do have to take a quick trip
to Vegas.
What?
Why?
[knocking]
Jim Huden?
Yeah.
Detective Steadman.
Whidbey Island Police.
Mind if I ask you
a couple questions?
Peggy Sue Thomas?
Yes.
Detective Williams,
Whidbey Island PD.
We spoke on the phone.
Come on in.
Someone ambushed
Russel Douglas.
Now, I've been told
that you were the man
that pulled the trigger.
I don't know why someone
would say that.
I- I've never even owned a gun.
Ok.
Who told you that?
I'm not about to disclose
my source, Mr. Huden.
Damn, I knew she was pissed off
at me, but...
is Peggy angry enough
that she'd try to frame me
for Russel's murder?
We believe you were involved
in Russel Douglas's murder.
What brings you to that
ridiculous conclusion?
Jim Huden mentioned you
in connection to the crime.
I really doubt that,
but nice try.
We also have a sworn statement
from a good friend
of Jim Huden's.
I don't believe you.
Maybe you know him.
Neil Dodson.
So that's all you have
is hearsay.
Do you have any real evidence?
I'll ask the questions, Peggy.
What about a murder weapon?
Have you ever owned a gun,
Miss Thomas?
No.
So, you have no murder weapon,
what about a motive?
I mean, what possible reason
could I have for wanting
Russel Douglas dead?
We have our theories.
No, you don't have anything,
Detective Williams.
Sugar?
She's so smug you just wanna
slap that smirk off her face.
Mmmhmm.
Well, Jim Huden
is no prize, either.
Oh, about that time.
You really think this is
gonna help?
Somebody out there
knows something.
It's worth a try.
We now turn your attention
to the Whidbey Island
Police Department.
This is Detective Todd Steadman of the Whidbey Police Department
with a special announcement.
We are asking for
the public's help
in a homicide investigation.
Former Whidbey Island residence
James Huden and Peggy Thomas
have been identified
as persons of interest
in the Russel Douglas murder.
[knocking]
You're back.
How nice.
Isn't it, though?
The last time we spoke
you seemed disappointed
that we hadn't found
the murder weapon.
Do you recognize this gun?
No.
One of Jim Huden's friends
was holding onto it for him.
So?
We found your fingerprints
on the gun manual.
And?
And now we're gonna search
your house.
Gentlemen?
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Put him on the phone.
It's Peggy.
[slam]
Yes, Peggy?
You didn't get rid of the gun?
The gun?
I... I didn't keep it.
No!
You gave it to a friend
to hang onto!
And then you confessed
the entire thing
to your bass player!
How did you know?
Because the cops
were just here!
They're the ones
that told me!
Peggy.
Jim, I am absolutely
not going to prison
because of your
poor judgement.
Do you understand me?
Ok? They've searched my house,
they impounded my car.
Ok, we'll figure this out,
I just...
I didn't- I didn't think-
Oh, no, Jim.
No, Jim, you didn't think.
You didn't think at all, ok?
If I go to prison
it's all on you!
All on you!!!
So you tell me
you killed someone
and now you're just
gonna disappear
with the last of our cash?
And enough of my Oxy
to kill an elephant?!
Yeah, I saw what you packed.
It's not worth killing
yourself over.
I love you, Jean.
I love you.
So we still don't have anything
on Peggy.
And Jim?
All these months and we're
no closer to finding him.
I keep thinking if I look
hard enough
I'll find something new.
Well, I doubt Jim Huden is
hiding in these photographs.
Well, then where the hell
is he?
When Jim vanished those
were really dark times for me.
A lesser woman might have been
destroyed by what I went through
but if there's one thing
you can say about me
it's that I'm resilient.
You never fail to amaze me,
Peggy.
They say rebound romances
don't work and yet here you are.
Mmm.
Here I am.
It's beautiful.
It is, isn't it?
You know, Mark has
so much real estate
the whole family
could move down here.
Has he agreed to that?
He will. He just doesn't
know it yet.
[laughs]
Ooh, bubbly.
[pop]
[gasp]
Peggy: The end of my marriage
to Mark
was also the end of
my financial troubles.
My heartbreak over losing
him was soothed
by a brand new houseboat,
a ranch, and several cars.
If there's one thing you can
say about me
it's that I am resilient.
That is so unfair.
The other insurance
company paid me.
Agent: Ma'am, the policy on
pre-existing conditions
does not include...
That money is long gone.
Watch your fingers.
I'm a grieving widow.
How can you deny my claim?
Why should I be punished
because Russel didn't tell you
about his heart murmur?
This is a policy that has...
I've been keeping tabs
on the key players.
Brenna bought a house
then lost it to foreclosure.
Peggy got married
and divorced.
Williams: And what about
Jean Huden?
Jim's long-suffering wife.
Well, her suffering
is about to get worse.
What's that mean?
I just spoke to the Punta Gorda
Chief of Police.
Good news.
I'm heading back to Florida.
Mmmhmm.
[knocking]
Police!
Shit.
[knocking]
Police! Open up!
Oh, god.
Mrs. Huden.
You've been charged
on 18 separate counts
ranging from possession to fraud
to grand larceny.
Those are very serious charges.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
Obviously you're struggling.
Your husband cheated on you
and he left you dealing with
the aftermath of his crime.
I loved that man so much.
And look where
it's gotten you.
I have been so stupid.
Jean, you could go to jail
for a long, long time.
Or you could tell us
where Jim-
He's in Mexico.
He's teaching guitar.
They call him "Maestro Jim".
[strumming]
Steadman: Jim Huden.
Hello, Peggy.
Oh, you again.
I have something for you.
What is it?
You're under arrest for
the murder of Russel Douglas.
Special delivery
from Whidbey Island.
What is it?
It's a warrant for your arrest.
I need you to turn around and
put your hands behind your back.
No, you are not putting
those on me.
Actually, I am.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
-Peggy Sue Thomas.
-You can't do this!
You can't arrest me!
-You have been charged.
-I didn't do anything.
-with first degree murder.
-I didn't do anything wrong!
-You have the right
to remain silent.
-You can't make me...
-Everything you say can
and will be used against you...
-I don't even have shoes on!
Will you please let me go back-
Russel Douglas's death
was not just a murder.
It was an assassination.
Jim Huden walked up
to Russel's car,
looked him in the eye,
and shot him point blank.
I met Jim Huden but, uh,
I didn't really know him.
Did you tell Peggy Sue Thomas
that your husband, Russel,
had been abusive?
Yeah.
Jim told me his step-father
used to beat him.
He said "I always hated that man
with a passion.
"I wanted to find someone
who was just like him
"and get revenge."
And did he find someone?
He thought he had.
Peggy Sue Thomas convinced
him that Russel Douglas
was an abusive husband.
[courtroom chatter]
Will the defendant please rise?
The jury finds the defendant,
Jim Huden,
guilty of first degree
aggravated murder.
[slam]
[courtroom chatter]
Peggy: It took the jury eight
days to sentence Jim
to 80 years in prison.
80 years.
That's twice the normal
sentence.
I'm so lucky to be out
on bail.
Thoughts?
It's very Peggy.
And?
Maybe for a murder trial you
might wanna tone it down a bit.
See, that's why I love you.
You're very sensible.
Not that it matters
what I wear.
If there's any justice at all
I'll be exonerated.
D.A.: Mr. Huden, you've been sentenced to 80 years in prison.
Now if Ms. Thomas has played
any role in this murder,
volunteering that information
could result in a significant
reduction in your sentence.
Again, I plead the fifth.
Of course, Jim refused
to testify against me.
They don't have a single witness
that links me to this crime.
I thought his wife
claimed to-
Jean Huden, the druggie
with an axe to grind?
Uh, unreliable.
What about Jim's buddy,
the bass player?
What, Neil Dodson?
Oh, he's not testifying.
He's in the hospital
in critical condition
because he had
a heart attack.
[chuckles]
Karma's a bitch,
right?
I suppose.
You know, I have heard rumours
about a third witness
but I have no idea
who it could be.
I can't eat.
I can't sleep.
My hair is falling out.
I know this is hard.
But I really appreciate you
coming forward like this.
I can't stop thinking about
Russel sitting in his car alone,
and then...
Ma'am?
[sniffles]
How can people be so cruel?
I often wonder that myself.
Let's go through this
one more time.
We were discussing
my ex-husband
and Jim said "I can take him
out for you".
And what did you interpret
that to mean?
It was clear what he meant.
And Peggy?
She just sat there, listening.
Look, I know it's hard
to talk about this.
It takes a lot of courage.
Just try to get some rest.
Yeah.
I'm so tired.
I need sleep.
Thank you.
Given my client's
unique circumstances,
we're requesting a trial delay
so that she can tie up
loose ends.
Loose ends?
Mmmhmm.
Well, I may not be familiar
with the nuances, as you put it.
But I do know that your request
is highly unusual.
My client would like to speak.
Go on.
Your honour, I'd just like
to explain.
I need to attend a memorial
service for my sister
who recently took
her own life.
Your honour, may I remind you
that Ms. Thomas
is referring to her late
half-sister, Janice Nevins,
who gave a sworn statement
against her
before she committed suicide.
In addition, your honour,
I need to raise money
to pay to fight these
ridiculous charges.
I need to liquidate assets.
I must maintain my home
and my garden in keeping
with the standards of the
Homeowner's Association
of my gated community.
I need to go to the dentist
in Nevada,
I need to winterize
my houseboat,
and I need to retrieve documents
that'll be useful in my defence.
I also need to get
winter clothing.
And I need to transport
my vehicle to Whidbey
so that I can use it
during the trial.
Your honour, we do have dentists
here in Washington State.
And clothing stores
and rental cars.
And surely Ms. Thomas can find
someone to cut her grass
and winterize her boat.
Valid points, counsellor.
Most importantly, your honour,
the prosecution views
Peggy Thomas as a flight risk.
[laughs]
Your honour, do I really look
like some desperado outlaw
on the run?
My whole world has been thrown
into chaos.
My lover is gone to prison,
my sister has gone to her grave.
Ow, that stings.
Thanks, that's- that's better.
Anyway, my arraignment's
coming up pretty fast,
so I wanted to look my best.
I mean, there's bound
to be tons of people.
Paparazzi, even.
Plus, they don't let you wear
make-up in prison
so I thought I'd cover
all my bases.
I mean, you gotta admit
that it's pretty crazy
that judge just
let me outta there.
But in the last two weeks
I have had an epiphany.
I mean, why would I subject
myself to the public scrutiny
that an unfair trial
would bring?
So I decided I don't really want
a trial.
Peggy Sue Thomas,
you have pled guilty
to rendering criminal assistance
in the first degree.
Yes, your honour.
I- I just wanna be clear,
your honour.
One thing that we know
for sure now
based on the court's colloquy
with Ms. Thomas
is that she did in fact
knowingly, intelligently,
and voluntarily
admit to her involvement
in assisting Jim Huden
in connection with the murder
of Russel Douglas.
I'm sentencing you
to the maximum penalty
that can be imposed
for this plea.
Four years in the Washington
State penitentiary.
[slams gavel]
Some crowd.
Disappointed?
All that make-up
for nothing?
Peggy.
I'm from the Washington
Celebrity News.
Why'd you do it?
What makes you so sure
I did?
Why would I want
Russel Douglas dead?
I didn't profit from his death
in any way.
By pleading guilty
to a lesser charge
I'm avoiding an unfair trial
along with the insane 45-year
sentence I could have faced.
As for Brenna Douglas,
the cops never could connect
her to the murder.
She was never charged.
Whereas I've been sentenced
to four years in prison.
Four years for what?
For falling in love
with the wrong man?
And Brenna, all she got
was rid of Russel.
Plus, a big chunk
of insurance money
and the chance to start all over
again somewhere new.
She changed her name,
and left Whidbey Island.
And Sally?
There's still hope for Sally.
Lucky them.
Meanwhile, my life has become
a tabloid story
with headlines about
"The Beauty Queen Killer".
Like my looks have anything
to do with this.
I'm just another victim.
I'm losing four years of my life
just to appease my accusers.
But I think we can agree
I did nothing wrong.
Right?
♪
♪ Love is a game,
since ever the same ♪
♪ We win and lose ♪
♪ I wonder who
might be to blame ♪
♪ Yes we wonder ♪
♪ For trees must bloom ♪
♪ When spring is here again ♪
♪ So we are bound to play ♪
♪ Each time the same
old game ♪
♪ All leaves fall down
when Autumn comes again ♪
♪ So we are bound to play ♪
♪ Each time the same
old game ♪
♪ Love is a game
since ever the same ♪
♪ We win and lose and wonder
who might be to blame ♪
♪ Yes we wonder ♪
♪