Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[uplifting music]
[crowd cheers]
♪ Sometimes I just can't take it ♪
♪ Sometimes I just can't take
it and it isn't all right ♪
♪ I'm not going to make it ♪
♪ And I think my shoe's untied oh oh ♪
♪ I'm like a broken record ♪
♪ I'm like a broken record
and I'm not playing right ♪
♪ Drocer nekorb a ekil mi ♪
♪ 'Til you tell me on
a heavenly phone to ♪
♪ Hold tight hold tight ♪
♪ Come on come on ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Yeah don't let go ♪
♪ Hold tight hold tight ♪
♪ Hold tight hold tight yeah ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ It's all right it's all right she said ♪
♪ I got my hands up shaking
just to let you know ♪
♪ That you've got a higher power ♪
♪ Got me singing every
second dancing every hour ♪
♪ Oh yeah you've got a higher power ♪
♪ And you're really someone
I wanna know oh oh ♪
♪ This boy is electric ♪
♪ This boy is electric and
you're sparkling light ♪
♪ The universe connected ♪
♪ And I'm buzzing night after
night after night oh oh ♪
♪ This joy is electric ♪
♪ This joy is electric and
you're circuiting through ♪
♪ I'm so happy that I'm alive ♪
♪ Happy I'm alive at
the same time as you ♪
♪ 'Cause you've got a higher power ♪
♪ Got me singing every
second dancing every hour ♪
♪ Oh yeah you've got a higher power ♪
♪ And you're really someone I wanna know ♪
♪ I wanna know oh oh ♪
♪ You've got yeah you've got a higher ♪
♪ You've got ♪
♪ ♪ You've got yeah you've got a higher ♪
♪ My hands up shaking
just to let you know now ♪
♪ You've got a higher power ♪
♪ You've got me singing every
second dancing any hour ♪
♪ Oh yeah you've got a higher power ♪
♪ You're once in any lifetime ♪
♪ I'm going a million miles an hour ♪
♪ When for so long I'd
been down on my knees ♪
♪ Then your love song
saved me over and over ♪
♪ For so long I'd been down on my knees ♪
♪ 'Til your love song
floats me on ee on oh oh ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ The lights go out and I can't be saved ♪
♪ Tides that I tried to swim against ♪
♪ Have brought me down upon my knees ♪
♪ Oh I beg I beg and plead ♪
♪ Singing come out of things unsaid ♪
♪ Shoot an apple off my head ♪
♪ And a trouble that can't be named ♪
♪ A tiger's waiting to be tamed singing ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ Confusion that never stops ♪
♪ The closing walls and
the ticking clocks ♪
♪ Are gonna come back and take you home ♪
♪ But I couldn't stop that you now know ♪
♪ So I come out upon my seas ♪
♪ Cursed missed opportunities ♪
♪ Am I a part of the cure ♪
♪ Or am I part of the disease singing ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ And nothing else compares ♪
♪ Oh no nothing else compares ♪
♪ And nothing else compares oh ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ Sing home home where I wanted to go ♪
♪ Home home where I wanted to go ♪
[crowd cheers]
- Thank you so much, everybody.
Thank you so much for being here.
[crowd cheers]
Welcome.
Let's go, Will.
We're so happy to see you all.
[crowd cheers]
All right, whether you're
up at the top or behind us,
or all the way over there or down here,
we're both together, or
watching this at home.
We send you our love,
we're so happy to be here.
♪ When you try your best
but you don't succeed ♪
♪ When you get what you
want but not what you need ♪
♪ When you feel so tired
but you can't sleep ♪
♪ Stuck in reverse ♪
♪ When the tears come
streaming down your face ♪
♪ 'Cause you lose something
you can't replace ♪
♪ When you love someone
but it goes to waste ♪
♪ What could be worse ♪
♪ Lights will guide you home ♪
♪ And ignite your bones ♪
♪ And I will try to fix you ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ And high up above or down below ♪
♪ When you're too in love to let it show ♪
♪ Oh but if you never
try you'll never know ♪
♪ Just what you're worth ♪
- Let's go together now.
♪ Lights will guide you home ♪
♪ And ignite your bones ♪
♪ And I will try to fix you ♪
- Let's go, come on, you're the man.
All right.
♪ The tears stream down your face ♪
♪ When you lose something
you cannot replace ♪
♪ The tears stream down your face and I ♪
♪ Tears stream down your face ♪
♪ I promise you I will
learn from my mistakes ♪
♪ When the tears stream
down your face and I ♪
♪ Lights will guide you home ♪
♪ And ignite your bones ♪
♪ And I will try to fix you ♪
[crowd cheers]
- Now, I forgot how good you sounded.
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ I used to rule the world ♪
♪ Seas would rise when I gave the word ♪
♪ Now in the morning I sleep alone ♪
♪ Sweep the streets I used to own ♪
♪ I used to roll the dice ♪
♪ Feel the fear in my enemy's eyes ♪
♪ Listen as the crowd would sing ♪
♪ Now the old king is
dead long live the king ♪
♪ One minute I held the key ♪
♪ Next the walls were closed on me ♪
♪ And I discovered that my castles stand ♪
♪ Upon pillars of salt
and pillars of sand ♪
♪ I hear Jerusalem bells are ringing ♪
♪ Roman Cavalry choirs are singing ♪
♪ Be my mirror my sword and shield ♪
♪ Missionaries in a foreign field ♪
♪ For some reason I can't explain ♪
♪ Once you go there was
never never an honest word ♪
♪ And that was when I ruled the world ♪
♪ It was a wicked and wild wind ♪
♪ Blew down the doors to let me in ♪
♪ Shattered windows and
the sound of drums ♪
♪ And people couldn't
believe what I'd become ♪
♪ Revolutionaries wait ♪
♪ For my head on a silver plate ♪
♪ Just a puppet on a lonely string ♪
♪ Oh who would ever want to be king ♪
♪ Now I hear Jerusalem bells are ringing ♪
♪ Roman Calvary choirs are singing ♪
♪ Be my mirror my sword and shield ♪
♪ Missionaries in a foreign field ♪
♪ For some reason I can't explain ♪
♪ I know Saint Peter won't call my name ♪
♪ Never an honest word ♪
♪ But that was when I ruled the world ♪
- Lights over here, please.
[crowd cheers]
One, two.
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh now I hear Jerusalem
bells are ringing ♪
♪ Roman Calvary choirs are singing ♪
♪ Be my mirror my sword and shield ♪
♪ Missionaries in a foreign field ♪
♪ For some reason I can't explain ♪
♪ I know Saint Peter won't call my name ♪
♪ Never an honest word ♪
♪ That was when I ruled the world ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ World world world world world ♪
♪ When I ruled the world ♪
♪ World world world world world world ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ Turn your magic on umi she'd say ♪
♪ Everything you want's a dream away ♪
♪ We are legends every day ♪
♪ That's what she told me ♪
♪ Hey turn your magic on to me she'd say ♪
♪ Everything you want's a dream away ♪
♪ Under this pressure under this weight ♪
♪ Oh we are diamonds ♪
♪ I feel my heart beating ♪
♪ I feel my heart underneath my skin ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me feel ♪
♪ Like I'm alive again ♪
♪ Woo hoo ♪
♪ Alive again ♪
♪ Oh you make me feel ♪
♪ Like I'm alive again ♪
♪ I said I can't go on not in this way ♪
♪ I'm a dream that died by light of day ♪
♪ Gonna hold up half the sky and say ♪
♪ Only I own me ♪
♪ Now I feel my heart beating ♪
♪ I feel my heart underneath my skin ♪
♪ I feel my heart beating ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me feel ♪
♪ Like I'm alive again ♪
♪ Woo hoo ♪
♪ Alive again ♪
♪ You make me feel hey ♪
♪ Like I'm alive again ♪
- Okay, we haven't done
this for four years.
Let's try.
Everybody, everybody get low.
Everybody go low, let's go low.
Let's go low, just go real low.
Just real low.
Stay real low, trust me, stay real low.
Everybody real low.
Go real low.
One, two, one, two, three.
[crowd cheers]
♪ Woo hoo hoo ♪
♪ If we've only got this life ♪
♪ This adventure oh then I ♪
♪ You'll get me through yeah ♪
♪ If we've only got this life ♪
♪ This adventure oh then I ♪
♪ Wanna share it with you ♪
♪ With you with you ♪
♪ Yes I do ♪
♪ Now sing it ♪
♪ Woo hoo woo hoo ♪
[crowd cheers]
- Thank you so much, everybody.
Thank you so much,
but it still, it feels so
good to have our job back.
Thank you for that, thank you for that.
[crowd cheers]
There are,
there are a few things more
frustrating for family members
than a frontman who's stuck
in a cupboard for two years,
it's best to let us out
into the wild again.
Thank you for letting us come to
the first carbon neutral
building in the world, I think.
And playing the first concert here at
the Climate Pledge Arena.
We're so grateful to be
here and it's a real honor.
And we came to Seattle in the year 2000
for our first show here at the Showbox.
And I think most of you were there.
[crowd cheers]
And it's just basically,
we're starting our whole tour here again.
So thank you for letting
us be a launch pad.
[crowd cheers]
This is our mission control, okay.
This is an old, old, old
song where we come from,
and this is called The Scientist.
[crowd cheers]
Thank you.
♪ Come up to meet you tell you I'm sorry ♪
♪ You don't know how lovely you are ♪
♪ I had to find you to
tell you I need you ♪
♪ To tell you I set you apart ♪
♪ Tell me your secrets and
ask me your questions ♪
♪ Oh let's go back to the start ♪
♪ Running in circles coming up tails ♪
♪ Heads on a science apart ♪
♪ Nobody said it was easy ♪
♪ Oh it's such a shame for us to part ♪
♪ No one ever said it would be so hard ♪
♪ I'm going back to the start ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ Now I was just guessing
at numbers and figures ♪
♪ I was pulling the puzzles apart ♪
♪ Questions of science
of science and progress ♪
♪ Do not speak as loud as my heart ♪
♪ So tell me you love me
or come back and haunt me ♪
♪ Oh and I rush to the start ♪
♪ Running in circles
or chasing our tails ♪
♪ Coming back as we are ♪
♪ Nobody said it was easy ♪
♪ It's such a shame for us to part ♪
♪ No one ever said it would be so hard ♪
♪ Oh let's go back to the start ♪
- Let's sing along, all right?
♪ Oh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ah ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
[crowd cheers and applauds]
- Now please, please can we
sing one chorus together?
Yeah.
Just one chorus together.
Two, three.
♪ Nobody said it was easy ♪
♪ Oh it's such a shame for us to part ♪
♪ No one ever said it would be so hard ♪
♪ I'm going back to the start ♪
- Thank you, Seattle, for
letting us be the start.
[crowd cheers]
Thank you, everybody.
Go, Will.
[crowd cheers]
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ooh ooh ooh ooh ah ah oh ♪
♪ When she was just a girl
she expected the world ♪
♪ It flew away from her reach ♪
♪ She ran away in her sleep ♪
♪ Dreamed of para para paradise ♪
♪ Para para paradise para para paradise ♪
♪ Every time she closed her eyes ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ooh ooh ooh ooh ah ah oh ♪
♪ When she was just a girl
she expected the world ♪
♪ But it flew away from her reach ♪
♪ And the bullets catch in her teeth ♪
♪ Life goes on it gets so heavy ♪
♪ The wheel breaks the butterfly ♪
♪ Every tear a waterfall ♪
♪ In the night the stormy
night she'll close her eyes ♪
night away she'd fly ♪
♪ Dream of para para paradise ♪
♪ Para para paradise ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Sing la la la la la la la la la ♪
♪ La la la la la la la ♪
♪ And so lying underneath
those stormy skies ♪
♪ She'd say oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ I know the sun must set to rise ♪
♪ This could be para para paradise ♪
♪ Para para paradise ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo do do do ♪
♪ Para para paradise ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
- I don't wanna stop I don't wanna stop.
[crowd cheers]
Thank you, everybody.
Now please welcome from Los Angeles,
Paris and Amber Strother,
also known as We Are King.
This is a new song.
♪ Boys boys don't cry ♪
♪ Boys keep it all inside ♪
♪ I tried to hide it underneath ♪
♪ But still my heart starts to beat ♪
♪ My human heart only got a human heart ♪
♪ I wish it didn't run away ♪
♪ I wish it didn't fall apart ♪
♪ Oh my human heart ♪
♪ Night and day light and dark ♪
♪ Any day it could be torn in half ooh ♪
♪ Only got a human heart ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ Girls can make-believe ♪
♪ Girls wear it on their sleeve ♪
♪ Thought I could
pretend for trying sake ♪
♪ Still my heart had to break ♪
♪ My human heart ♪
♪ Only got a human heart ♪
♪ I wish it didn't run away ♪
♪ I wish it didn't fall apart ♪
♪ Oh my human heart ♪
♪ Night and day light and dark ♪
♪ Any day it could be torn in half ooh ♪
♪ Only got a human heart ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
- Thank you, guys.
[crowd cheers]
♪ People on the left ♪
♪ People on the right ♪
♪ Got a lion inside ♪
♪ People of the pride ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ There's a man who swears he's God ♪
♪ Unbelievers will be shot ♪
♪ There's a man who walks around ♪
♪ Like he owns the fucking lot ♪
♪ There's a man who takes his time ♪
♪ From his homemade cuckoo clock ♪
♪ And he makes us march around it ♪
♪ Tick tock tick tock tick tock ♪
♪ There's a crocodile cross-eyed ♪
♪ There's a turning of the tide ♪
♪ We're no longer going to fight for ♪
♪ Some old crook and all his crimes ♪
♪ There's a sewing up of rags ♪
♪ Into revolution flags ♪
♪ Got to stand up to be counted ♪
♪ Be an anthem for your time ♪
♪ It's just work ♪
♪ It's not easy and we
could all be blown apart ♪
♪ But heaven is the fire escape ♪
♪ You try to cling to in the dark ♪
♪ It's just work believe me ♪
♪ Still my beating heart ♪
♪ And we'll all be free to fall in love ♪
♪ With who we want and sing ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ Yeah yeah oh oh ♪
♪ And people of the pride ♪
♪ Go ♪
[crowd cheers and applauds]
[crowd cheers]
- We've really liked playing that song.
But it's our only real rock song, so.
So we get all pumped up.
Now we have to go back
to early Coldplay, okay.
[crowd cheers]
I'd like to thank those of
you who are new to our band,
and maybe this is your first
show, your first concert
of seeing our band.
[crowd cheers]
I'd like to thank those of you
who have been coming to see
us for 10 years or 15 years.
[crowd cheers]
Maybe in some cases you've
been coming for 20 years,
and that's just amazing.
We're so lucky, I mean,
we were lucky anyway in the first place,
but now with everything
going on in the world,
the fact that we get
to gather here together
with so many beautiful,
beautiful West Coast Americans,
it's just a privilege and a joy.
[crowd cheers]
I mean, thank you first
of all for the visas,
because getting into America is not easy,
even if you're soft rock superstars.
So we're just happy to be here.
And thank you for the effort you've made
to come to this concert tonight with
the pandemic and the travel
and the weather and the tickets
and all of the rigamarole.
[crowd cheers]
If you're sitting way, way,
way up in the top there,
miles away from us,
don't think we don't care about you.
And we really do.
As far as we're concerned,
we're all basically one big
family anyway, so thank you.
[crowd cheers]
This is a song we played in our first show
here in the Showbox
and we're going to pay it again now.
This is a song called
Everything's Not Lost by Coldplay.
♪ When I counted up my demons ♪
♪ Saw there was one for every day ♪
♪ With the good ones on my shoulders ♪
♪ I sent the other ones away ♪
♪ So if you ever feel neglected ♪
♪ And if you think that all is lost ♪
♪ Well I'll be counting
up my demons yeah ♪
♪ Hoping everything's not lost ♪
♪ Everyone was out to get you ♪
♪ You could feel it all around ♪
♪ Well ♪
- Let's do that one again.
Listen to this musicianship, okay.
We're not the best band in
the world at playing music,
but there's a thing Will,
Will will do this thing on the high hat,
which just shows he's a
truly professional drummer.
Ready?
You'll see it, you'll hear it.
[crowd cheers]
And when you hear him do this thing,
please just go totally ape shit,
because he doesn't even
like playing the drums,
he just does it 'cause we're brothers
and he's so good at it.
[crowd cheers]
♪ When everyone was out to get you ♪
♪ You can feel it all around ♪
- Here it comes.
[crowd cheers]
[indistinct].
♪ Hey don't you let it drag you down ♪
♪ Well if you ever feel neglected ♪
♪ If you think that all is lost ♪
♪ I'll be counting up my demons yeah ♪
♪ Hoping everything's not lost ♪
♪ So if you ever feel neglected ♪
♪ You think that all is lost ♪
♪ I'll be counting up my demons oh yeah ♪
♪ Hoping everything's not lost ♪
♪ Singing out oh oh oh yeah ♪
♪ Oh oh yeah ♪
♪ I know everything's not lost ♪
♪ Come on yeah ♪
♪ Oh oh yeah ♪
♪ I know everything's not lost ♪
♪ Come on yeah ♪
♪ Oh oh yeah ♪
♪ Everything's not lost ♪
♪ Come on yeah ♪
♪ Oh oh yeah ♪
♪ I know everything's not lost ♪
- Keep it going.
♪ Come on yeah ♪
♪ Oh oh yeah ♪
♪ One two three go ♪
- Come on, Johnny.
♪ A one two three four ♪
- Okay, Will.
Thank you, everybody, thank you so much.
I see you up there, I see you up there.
[crowd cheers]
Okay, Will.
♪ Call it magic ♪
♪ Call it true ♪
♪ I call it magic ♪
♪ When I'm next to you ♪
♪ And I just got broken ♪
♪ Broken into two ♪
♪ Still I call it magic ♪
♪ When I'm next to you ♪
♪ And I don't and I don't
and I don't and I don't ♪
♪ No I don't it's true ♪
♪ No I don't no I don't
no I don't no I don't ♪
♪ Want anybody else but you ♪
♪ No I don't no I don't
no I don't no I don't ♪
♪ No I don't it's true ♪
♪ No I don't no I don't
no I don't no I don't ♪
♪ Want anybody else but you ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Call it magic ♪
♪ Cut me into two ♪
♪ And with all your magic ♪
♪ I disappear from view ♪
♪ And I can't get over ♪
♪ Can't get over you ♪
♪ Still I call it magic ♪
♪ Such a precious jewel ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ And I don't and I don't
and I don't and I don't ♪
♪ No I don't it's true ♪
♪ No I don't no I don't
no I don't no I don't ♪
♪ Want anybody else but you ♪
♪ No I don't no I don't
no I don't no I don't ♪
♪ No I don't it's true ♪
♪ No I don't no I don't
no I don't no I don't ♪
♪ Want anybody else but you ♪
♪ Wanna fall ♪
♪ Fall so far ♪
♪ And I call it magic ♪
♪ Call it true ♪
♪ I call it ma ma ma magic ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ And if you were to ask me ♪
♪ After all that we've been through ♪
♪ Still believe in magic ♪
♪ Oh yes I do ♪
♪ Of course I do ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
[crowd cheers]
- Thank you, everybody.
Thank you so much, everybody.
♪ Look at the stars ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ How they shine for you ♪
♪ And all the things you do ♪
♪ They were all yellow ♪
♪ I came along ♪
♪ I wrote a song for you ♪
♪ And all the things you do ♪
♪ And it was called Yellow ♪
♪ So then I took my time ♪
♪ Oh what a thing to have done ♪
♪ And it was called yellow ♪
♪ Your skin ♪
♪ Oh yeah your skin and bones ♪
♪ Turn in to something beautiful ♪
♪ Do you know ♪
♪ You know I love you so ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ I swam across ♪
♪ I jumped across for you ♪
♪ What a thing to do ♪
♪ 'Cause you were all yellow ♪
♪ And I drew a line ♪
♪ I drew a line for you ♪
♪ What a thing to do ♪
♪ And it was all yellow ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ And your skin ♪
♪ Oh yeah your skin and bones ♪
♪ Turn in to something beautiful ♪
♪ Do you know ♪
♪ For you I'd bleed myself dry ♪
♪ For you I'd bleed myself it's true ♪
♪ Look how they shine for you ♪
♪ Look how they shine for ♪
♪ Look how they shine ♪
♪ Look at the stars ♪
♪ Look how they shine for you ♪
♪ And all the things that you do ♪
[crowd cheers]
- Okay, thank you, everybody.
So because we're here in Seattle,
we wanted to pay tribute to
both of the bands that
we fell in love with
when we were just young
teenagers in the '90s.
So this is a cover, this is
a cover version, this song.
But maybe don't upload it onto YouTube,
because it's not going to
be the best cover version.
It's really just a, it's just a tribute.
You know what I mean?
This is not Adele singing
Make You Feel My Love.
This is not what you're about to see.
This is a 40-year-old, 44-year-old man
remembering how much he fell
in love with Pearl Jam in 1991.
[crowd cheers]
And if you told that kid,
he would be here singing this song,
that kid would have said, "Are
you sure that's a good idea?"
And I would've said, "Maybe not."
But we're doing it.
And so, so for this,
please welcome from the drum kit
all the way down to the B
stage here to play piano
on a song that I only made
him learn like 25 minutes ago.
This is our incredible
anchor of a drummer,
Mr. Will Champion.
Let's bring him down the catwalk.
[crowd cheers]
♪ Once divided ♪
♪ Nothing left to subtract ♪
♪ Some words when spoken
can't be taken back ♪
♪ Walks on his own with thoughts
he can't help thinking ♪
♪ Future's above but in the
past he's slow and sinking ♪
♪ Caught a bolt of lightning ♪
♪ Wished he'd never let it go ♪
♪ Nothingman ♪
♪ Isn't it something ♪
♪ She once believed in
every story he had to tell ♪
♪ One day she stiffened
and took the other side ♪
♪ Empty stares from each
corner of a prison cell ♪
♪ One just escapes one
stays inside the well ♪
♪ And he who forgets will
be destined to remember ♪
♪ Nothingman ♪
♪ Isn't it something ♪
♪ Oh Nothingman ♪
♪ Nothingman ♪
♪ Isn't it something ♪
- Thanks, Will.
[crowd cheers]
If Eddie ever hears this,
I love you, man,
thank you for being so kind to our band.
[crowd cheers]
♪ Nothingman ♪
♪ Isn't it something Nothingman ♪
- All right, Will, hit it.
[crowd cheers]
I don't know.
Okay, I don't know how
good your Korean is,
but that's where we're going now.
All right, this is called My Universe.
[crowd cheers]
♪ You you you are you are my universe ♪
♪ And I just want just
want to put you first ♪
♪ And you you you are you
are my universe and I ♪
♪ In the night I lie and look up at you ♪
♪ When the morning
comes I watch you rise ♪
♪ There's a paradise
they couldn't capture ♪
♪ That bright infinity inside your eyes ♪
♪ [foreign language] ♪
♪ Never-ending forever baby ♪
♪ You you you are you are my universe ♪
♪ And I I just want just
want to put you first ♪
♪ And you you are my universe ♪
♪ And you make my world light up inside ♪
♪ [foreign language] ♪
♪ And they said that
we can't be together ♪
♪ Because because we come
from different sides ♪
♪ You you are my universe ♪
♪ And I just want just
want to put you first ♪
♪ And you you are my universe ♪
♪ And you make my world light up inside ♪
♪ My universe doo-doo doo-doo ♪
♪ You make my ♪
♪ You make my world light up inside ♪
♪ [foreign language] ♪
♪ When I'm without you I'm crazy ♪
♪ We are made of each other baby ♪
♪ You you are my universe ♪
♪ And I just want to put you first ♪
♪ And you you are my universe ♪
♪ And you make my world light up inside ♪
♪ My universe you you are ♪
♪ My universe ♪
♪ My universe you you
are my universe and I ♪
♪ My universe ♪
[crowd cheers]
- Okay.
Oh, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, wait, wait, stop.
Okay, wait.
Okay, so, this is kind
of our last song, but.
[crowd cheers]
Let's just go underneath
the whole bullshit.
This is not really our last song.
[crowd cheers]
But.
I always feel a slight fraud saying,
"This is our last song."
And then coming back eight times, so.
But I will say this,
if you could treat it like our last song,
that'd be wonderful.
[crowd cheers]
And then with full
disclosure, after this song,
we're going to play a 10
minute ballad, which is a,
which if you have school
tomorrow or you have a babysitter
or you're just plain bored,
I would recommend you don't
stay around for, okay?
So you're totally excused.
After this song you could say,
"They played the last song.
"It was A Sky Full of Stars.
"The confetti went
everywhere, had a great time,
"then I had to go back to bed."
It's okay if you want to
leave after this song,
but we are going to play
our favorite song to play
in the world after this.
[crowd cheers]
Okay, so with that in mind,
I'm not really sure if I'm
making any sense at all.
It's been a while since I've
spoken to this many people.
[crowd cheers]
I mean, if we were all on Zoom right now,
I'd have a lot better
chance of making sense.
So we'll start this song again.
Please give it the Seattle
like super power welcome.
[crowd cheers]
Okay.
Here it is.
Here it is, officially our last song.
Let's go, Will.
♪ 'Cause you're a sky 'cause
you're a sky full of stars ♪
♪ I'm gonna give you my heart ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ 'Cause you're a sky oh
you're a sky full of stars ♪
- I see you up there.
♪ And 'cause you light up my path ♪
♪ I don't care go on and tear me apart ♪
♪ I don't care if you do ooh ♪
♪ 'Cause in a sky 'cause
in a sky full of stars ♪
♪ I think I saw you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're a sky 'cause
you're a sky full of stars ♪
♪ I want to die in your arms oh ♪
♪ 'Cause you get lighter
the more it gets dark ♪
- Happy birthday over there.
♪ I'm gonna give you my heart oh ♪
♪ Yes sir ♪
♪ I don't care go on and tear me apart ♪
♪ I don't care if you do ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ 'Cause in a sky oh
in sky full of stars ♪
♪ I think I saw you ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ 'Cause you're a sky
you're a sky full of stars ♪
♪ Such a heavenly view ♪
♪ You're such a heavenly view ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ooh ♪
[crowd cheers]
- Thank you, everybody, thank you so much.
Can you put the house lights on sooner?
Okay.
Is it just me or is there
a kid dressed as an elephant over there?
[crowd cheers]
And did I see a sign saying
it was your sixth birthday?
Yeah.
Do you want to come up here?
Do you want to come up?
[crowd cheers]
Okay, man.
Let's do it.
All right.
Okay, let's go, yeah.
This is a big deal.
Are you sure you want to,
hey, look at these pants.
They've got the same
pants as me, that's cool.
[crowd cheers]
Do you want to come up with your mom?
Okay.
Hey man.
[crowd cheers]
All right, Patrick.
And this is your mom, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, and you're really
six years old today?
- I'm trembling.
- All right, that's okay, you're cool.
It's all right, it's okay.
We're just human people, it's all right.
Come, do you want to sit down?
Hey Patrick, come this way.
Let me show you what it's
like to be a rockstar, ready?
Okay, watch this, you go
up, you say something.
[crowd cheers]
Say, "What's up, Seattle?"
What's up, Seattle?
- What's up, Seattle?
[crowd cheers and applauds]
- Hey, is there anything
else we can do for you?
Do you want to hang out with us
while we sing this last song?
Okay, come on, Patrick, let's go.
All right, come on, come on this way.
This is Johnny.
Oh, let's introduce the band.
You could introduce the
band to everybody, okay?
I want you to say,
"This is Johnny, he's the
best guitarist in the world."
Can you say that?
- This is Johnny, the best
guitarist in the world.
[crowd cheers]
- Say, all right.
This is Will, he keeps it locked down.
- This is Will, he keeps it locked down.
- He keeps it locked down.
Look at that, it's Will, look at that.
[crowd cheers]
Are you okay?
And last but not least, say,
"This is Guy, he's just
handsome, just handsome."
- This is Guy, he's just handsome.
- He's just handsome.
[crowd cheers]
All right, Patrick, okay, man.
All right, so come on,
let's go this way, okay.
You want to sit right here?
Okay, here, ready?
Let's go.
[crowd cheers]
Okay, look at these pants.
We got the same pants, man.
All right, this is a song
that's almost as old as you
in terms of how long it lasts.
You're six and, yeah, okay.
[crowd cheers]
Okay.
You okay?
All right.
Happy birthday, my young brother.
Okay.
[crowd cheers]
Well, this really is the last song
and we want to say thank you to our crew
and to the local crew and to
the people that built this arena in time.
And we're so grateful
and happy to be here.
[crowd cheers]
We want to thank Patrick
for being six today
and introducing the band.
And I hope we'll see you again sometime.
I think we're coming through
here again at some point.
I hope so.
[crowd cheers]
This is a song called Coloratura
and thank you for having us.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
Okay.
[crowd cheers]
♪ Coloratura ♪
♪ We fell in through the clouds ♪
♪ Everyone before us is
there welcoming us now ♪
♪ It's the end of death and doubt ♪
♪ And loneliness is out ♪
♪ Coloratura ♪
♪ The place we dreamed about ♪
♪ The melodies inside yourself ♪
♪ And love come pouring out ♪
♪ We're feathered by the crowd ♪
♪ And everyone's allowed ♪
♪ And up there in the heavens ♪
♪ Galileo and those pining for the moon ♪
♪ Know it's a slow burn ♪
♪ Through Pioneer and Helix ♪
♪ Oumamama Heliopause and Neptune ♪
♪ We're a slow burning tune ♪
♪ But we'll touch down soon ♪
♪ In this crazy world I do ♪
♪ I just want you ♪
♪ In the end it's all about ♪
♪ The love you're sending out ♪
♪ And up there in the heavens ♪
♪ The explorers who've
all gathered by balloon ♪
♪ Saw the world turn ♪
♪ Through Voyager Callisto Calliope ♪
♪ Betelgeuse the neon moons ♪
♪ We're a slow burning tune ♪
♪ But we'll get there so for now ♪
♪ In this crazy world I do ♪
♪ I just want you ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ And up there in the heavens ♪
♪ Galileo saw reflections of us too ♪
♪ Pluribus unum unus mundus ♪
♪ And all the satellites imbue ♪
♪ The purple yellow green
red orange and the blue ♪
♪ Oh it's a crazy world it's true ♪
♪ Sing it out ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ In this crazy world it's true ♪
♪ I just want ♪
♪ In this crazy world I do ♪
♪ I just want you ♪
♪ Poets prophesy up in the blue ♪
♪ Together that's how
we'll make it through ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
[crowd cheers]
- Thank you so much, everybody.
Thank you, Patrick, thank you.
[crowd cheers]
Goodnight, goodbye.
[uplifting music]