Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[lullaby music]
[baby cooing]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
Come on, kid.
Just five more minutes.
[baby cooing on monitor]
Shh... It's okay.
[baby crying out]
Sophie!
Sophie...
[screaming]
[eerie music]
Good morning, beautiful.
Hi, my girl.
Hi!
Hi...
Okay, let's go.
Let's go see daddy.
How would you
like your eggs, love?
How about later?
You're supposed to
be taking advantage
Of the fact that
I don't have to go
Back to work right away.
I know.
I just have to get back
to the office.
This european deal is killing me
And they're only in the office
for a couple more hours.
Will you be home for dinner?
I'll do my best.
And what do my girls
have planned for today?
Enjoying the sunshine,
that's for sure.
Get some sun for me.
-Love you!
-Love you too.
Okay maya.
It's just me and you.
You hungry?
Okay maya.
Time for a nap.
What do you think?
[camera snap]
♪ ♪ ♪
[television news in background]
I'm sorry.
Hard day?
Interesting.
Is maya asleep?
Of course, it's after nine.
I have some good news.
And some bad news.
The european team loved my idea
For the new trading platform.
Honey, that's fantastic.
Yeah.
So much in fact,
that they want me to fly
To stockholm to
help implement it.
For two weeks.
I leave tomorrow morning.
Can you say something?
You're scaring me.
What do you want me to say?
You don't have a choice, do you?
Then I'm happy for you.
Taylor...
If it wasn't so
important for my career
And if there was any way
that I could get out of it,
You know I would, right?
I know.
You're going to be okay, right?
What do you mean?
Babe, that's behind me now.
You know that.
I know, I know.
It's just...
It's just the doctor said
that stress can exacerbate it.
Hey.
I'm fine.
I promise you.
How much time do
we actually have?
Maybe twelve hours.
Well, we better
make the most of them.
[giggling]
Oh!
You should have let us
drive you.
You kidding?
The freeways are a mess
at this hour.
You'd be pulling your hair out
Before we even
got to the terminal.
That's true.
Two weeks...
Two weeks.
Take care of our girl.
-Love you.
-Love you too.
Say bye.
Say bye to daddy.
Okay, maya.
It's just you and me.
You and me...
There are bottles in the fridge,
But she shouldn't get hungry
until I get back.
I got this.
Go have fun.
Thanks linds,
I really needed this.
Bye baby.
Bye-bye.
Let's go, come on.
[camera snapping repeatedly]
[catching breath]
[gasping]
[labored breath]
Smells good!
I knew you'd be hungry.
You want some?
Yes, please.
Maya went down easy.
I miss her little
chubby face already.
She'll wake up again
in a few hours to eat.
If you're still here,
you can see her again.
In the meantime, let's eat!
[glass clink]
(taylor)
thank you for this.
Of course.
I don't know what I needed more.
The meal I didn't cook myself,
or the run.
It's been tough
without dean, huh?
Tough...
I don't know if I'd say tough.
I mean, dean is wonderful,
you know that.
But even when he's here,
It's not like he's
the most hands-on dad.
So what is it then?
It's just... It's been weird.
Weird?
How so?
If I tell you, you're
going to think I'm nuts.
I already think you're nuts.
That's why I love you.
Okay, tell me.
Why will I think you're nuts?
For the last few days,
I've had this
really odd feeling.
Like from the baby?
No, more like I'm being watched.
The first time it happened,
we were at the park.
I suddenly got this feeling.
Then when I turned around,
I swear there was someone
in the distance watching me.
And then it happened
again today on my run.
Okay, go ahead,
tell me I'm crazy.
No, I don't think you're crazy.
But I also don't think that
there was anyone watching you.
This all started
when dean left, right?
And have you ever
been without dean before?
Not since maya was born, no.
Well, then of course
you're a little on edge.
You'll get used
to it, I promise.
Yeah, I'm sure
you're probably right.
Of course I'm right!
When am I ever wrong
about anything?
[camera snap]
[red light switches on]
Hey maya, what else
would you like to do today?
We can't stay at
the park forever.
You don't know either, huh?
Well, if you figure it out,
let me know.
[camera snap]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I hope I wasn't
disturbing your photo.
No, I was just playing around.
There's usually ducks here,
but I can't seem to find them.
Wow, that is a
really cool camera.
What kind is it?
It's just an old one I
picked up at a flea market.
It's good for the outdoors
and cute babies!
She's absolutely beautiful.
Thank you.
How old?
Actually, she just
turned six months.
Fun age.
Fun, but tiring.
You're telling me.
But I actually can't complain.
She's actually a
pretty decent sleeper.
Not my daughter.
Her first year, she didn't sleep
more than three hours at a time.
I got my revenge, though.
Now her daughter keeps
her up half the night.
And you know,
I don't feel any sympathy!
Oh boy.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, I know this
might sound weird,
But I think I've
seen you here before?
It's possible,
I'm here almost every day.
I'm cathy.
Cathy driver.
Taylor, hi.
And this little one is maya.
Well hello, maya.
So, do you just take photos
of the pond mostly?
The woods, animals.
But I'd really like to
get into portrait photography.
People...
Yeah, I prefer infants
and toddlers though,
Because they're
so much fun to shoot.
Problem is nowadays
everyone that has an iphone
Thinks they're a professional.
That's why I
still shoot on film.
It sets my work apart.
I think it gives
the photos a warmth
That you just can't
replicate with digital.
Yeah, we tried to do a shoot
when maya was born.
They put her in those
ridiculous vegetable costumes
Against a garden backdrop.
Maya wasn't having any of it.
I'm sure she was still adorable.
You know...
I'd be more than happy to setup
a photo shoot with maya.
Totally free, of course.
Oh, no. I couldn't--
Why not?
It's a win-win for both of us.
You get free photos
And I get to build up
on my portrait portfolio.
I couldn't.
I understand.
Just know the offer
is always open.
It was really nice meeting you.
And nice to
meeting you too, maya.
It was nice to
meet you too, cathy.
♪ ♪ ♪
[door slams]
[baby crying]
I'm here, I'm here.
I know, I know.
[baby crying loudly]
Shhh.
[door slams]
[baby crying]
[phone dialling]
911, what is your emergency?
I'm alone with my daughter.
I just heard a loud noise
in the house.
I think someone might be inside!
Could you please come here?
Alright miss,
please stay on the line,
We have officers on the way.
You okay?
My officers have been
through the entire house.
Top to bottom.
Twice.
Let me guess, you didn't
find anything?
I didn't imagine the noise.
It woke me.
It woke her, too.
I'm not saying you did.
But the fact remains,
We found no evidence
of a break-in.
Can't you check for
fingerprints, or something?
We really only do that when
something of value was taken.
And even then, only when
there's a strong possibility
That we'll be able to
pull prints from somewhere.
It's not like you see
in the movies.
Well, what about the curtains?
My six-month-old didn't
climb up out of her crib
And open them herself.
Show me.
When I came to check on her,
I made sure they were closed.
But when I came back,
after I heard the noise,
They were open like this.
Look, mrs. Lewis, can I
tell you what I really think?
Something woke you.
Could have been water in
the pipes, air in the ducts.
Maybe even something
falling off the shelves.
You were in a deep sleep.
You woke up
confused and frightened.
Things you wouldn't think twice
about during the day,
Now seem scary.
I promise you...
All of this will look
different in the morning.
I can have a car stay outside
your house until dawn
If it will make you feel better?
No.
That's okay, I'll be fine.
You sure?
All right.
Anything else happens,
you give me a call.
Oh, cathy!
Cathy, over here!
I thought that
was you over there.
I'm sorry.
I didn't even notice you
until you called my name.
I was tracking a lady bug,
I guess I spaced out a little.
Sometimes I get like that
when I'm shooting.
I hope I didn't disturb you.
Oh no, I got all
the shots I wanted.
I was gonna head home anyway.
Before you go, I wanted
to ask you a question.
If your offer still stands,
You know, about the photos?
I would love to
take you up on it.
Really?
Well, of course it does!
Yeah?
I just thought your offer
was so generous.
And new photos of maya would
be such a great gift for dean.
That's my husband.
Yes, they will make
a fantastic gift.
I promise you.
Great, so where do we do it?
Do you have a studio, or...?
Oh, I wish.
Actually, if it isn't
an imposition for you,
I was really hoping
to do this at your home.
I don't know--
Or not.
You know what,
I can rent a place.
Make it look as good.
I was just thinking it
might be more intimate.
Maya might feel
more comfortable.
But you know what, little maya?
Don't you worry.
You will look absolutely
adorable, no matter what.
Listen, here's my card.
It has all my information on it.
And when I find
the perfect place,
I'll let you know.
Cathy?
Let's just, let's do them
at our house.
You sure?
Yeah.
Tomorrow then?
That's not too soon?
Not for me.
How about noon?
Maya usually wakes up
from her first nap by then,
So she'll be in a good mood.
Perfect.
I am so excited, taylor!
This is going to be so much fun!
I'll see you then.
And you made sure they
all knew it was you?
That you were
the one responsible
For the new idea
for the platform?
I told them it was a
collaborative effort.
Modesty is very important
over here.
Just don't be too modest
When it comes time
for your raise.
You know me when it
comes to negotiation,
I'm as tough as they come.
I really hate to say it,
But I didn't think
I'd miss you this much.
I'm not gonna lie,
I kind of like hearing that.
And I have a big surprise
planned
For when you get back.
I've been thinking
about that every night.
Not that kind of surprise,
But I promise you're
still gonna like it.
I can't wait.
You know, you sound really good.
I have to be honest,
I didn't want to say anything,
But the last couple of days,
you sounded kind of off.
I'm sure I was just tired.
It's not so easy with you gone.
I'm going to remind you
of that when I get back.
I have no doubt.
Well, I've got to get to bed.
Maya and I have a big day
tomorrow.
Oh yeah? What?
I already told you.
The big surprise.
Oh, the surprise.
I love you.
Love you too.
Goodnight sweetheart.
Okay, bye.
[camera snapping]
[doorbell rings]
Hi cathy!
Come on in.
Thank you.
Taylor, I'd like you
to meet skylar.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Are you a photographer too?
Oh no, hardly.
I just help out
where I'm needed.
Which makes it a lot harder
for me to say no
When you ask me to help you out.
I have a nine-month-old at home.
So I know exactly
what you're going through.
Oh, no!
You were right,
she's a little princess.
I told skylar that maya is going
to make our job a lot easier.
You can't take a bad photo
of her.
So where would you
like to set up?
Just let me know.
Wherever you need.
Maybe let's take
a look around first
And then we can decide
on the best spots.
Bring the gear?
Leave the gear.
It might be nice to use
some of this natural lighting.
Oh, cathy.
You're going to be
using actual film
Like you did in the park, right?
Uh, normally yes,
but we thought
We might be taking
a lot of photos today,
So digital is just a bit more
practical.
Plus, I can play around
with it in photoshop after.
Okay.
Oh, this is going to be perfect.
Just perfect.
So skylar,
do you have a boy or a girl?
A little girl.
Who keeps me plenty busy.
You're telling me.
Nine months,
what's happening then?
I have so much to focus on,
I haven't had time to
read ahead in my baby book.
Oh, you know.
They grow up so fast.
They're doing new things
every day.
Growing like a weed,
that's for sure.
I think we should start
in here, taylor.
I already have so many ideas.
Are you okay with that?
Of course.
We're in your hands.
Okay everybody, well...
Let's get started!
You ready?
♪ ♪ ♪
[camera snapping repeatedly]
One more.
Big smile.
[camera snap]
That's my girl, yeah.
I know this might be overkill,
But I'd hate to think we brought
any germs into this house.
You can't be too careful
nowadays.
She may be a photographer,
But she's a mom and
a grandmother first.
Okay, okay.
I am... Finished.
I know, it's a little weird.
I appreciate it.
The last thing I want
is for maya to get sick.
Especially while
daddy's out of town.
Taylor, do you mind if I use
your bathroom before we leave?
Yeah, of course.
So, what happens next?
I'll call you and
we can set a time
To look at the photos together.
But from what you saw
while you were taking them,
They looked good, right?
They're great.
I'll just need to do a
little digital enhancing.
You know, play around
with color and shading.
So I'll need a
few days for that.
But then I'll put it all
on a usb stick for you.
And I'm guessing you'll want
some actual prints as well?
Oh, definitely.
She's sleepy.
Yeah.
It's about time for
the nap, isn't it?
Maybe she's not cut out
For the fast-paced,
modeling lifestyle.
Yeah, I got that.
So you'll call me?
Definitely, we'll see
each other soon.
Thank you, cathy.
Thank you.
It was my pleasure.
Don't forget what
you promised me.
Soon as I get my
website up and running,
I want maya to be
the face of it!
You have my word.
Night night, maya.
Bye bye.
-Nice meeting you.
-You too.
-Bye.
-See you.
I'll believe it when
I see the pictures.
I've never heard of a
professional photographer
Giving away their work for free.
I already explained
all this to you.
She's not really a professional.
And she's not doing this
Just out of the goodness
of her heart.
She wants to
build up her portfolio.
Still.
She's putting maya
on her website.
Front and center.
Yeah, you told me.
What?
Nothing, it's just...
Didn't you say she
had a granddaughter?
Yeah.
Maybe she had too many photos
of her already.
I will say, it's been nice
having your company.
Tell me again why you
can't just quit your job
And come and stay with me
until dean gets back.
If I could, I would.
Believe me!
For real though,
you've been feeling okay?
You and dean,
between the two of you.
Yes, I'm fine.
Hey, I'm just making sure.
I know you got
through it quickly,
But postpartum depression
is no joke.
And it can manifest itself
in a lot of ways.
I don't think
this was postpartum.
I think it was just
good old-fashioned anxiety.
That doesn't mean it
wasn't scary, though.
I've freaked myself out
plenty of times.
I mean, if I had a nickel for
every time I went to web md...
You could pay for a real doctor.
[giggles]
Yeah.
This one might be my favorite.
It's almost like she's
posing for the camera.
Like a little diva.
I don't know which one
is my favorite.
You weren't kidding,
they're all amazing.
I might have picked up a
few tricks over the years.
Cathy, when people see these,
Your business is
going to take off.
Well, from your lips
to god's ears!
Now remember, I'm giving
you all the files.
So if you ever want to go back
And print out any more,
then you have them.
Cathy, I don't
even know what to say.
This is so incredibly generous.
People would pay a small fortune
for a set like this.
Just spread the word.
That's all the thanks I need.
So have you decided which ones
you want me to print out?
All of them!
When did you say your husband
is coming home again?
Uh, a week from today.
Why?
I was just thinking
about the timing of it.
You know, if I...
But I should be fine.
I'll be able to print
them out before then.
Some of these would look great
in black and white, too.
Is that possible?
Anything is possible.
I don't know I
can ever repay you.
Okay, that's enough of that.
Oh yeah?
Okay, come on sweetie.
Okay, yeah.
Good night, girl.
Sweet dreams...
Hi...
My precious...
I'll take such good care of you.
Shhh... You're going to be okay.
[door shuts]
What the hell?
Oh my god!
It's okay baby, I'm coming.
It's okay, maya.
[screaming]
[crying out]
There's no sign of forced entry,
mrs. Lewis.
Just like the other night.
There's no sign that anybody
was ever here.
Except now my baby is gone!
Why can't you just go find her?
Mrs. Lewis, I know you're upset.
I really do.
This is a terrible situation.
But you need to trust me.
There's nothing
more important right now
Than you telling me
everything you know.
Okay.
Now, let me ask you again,
There's no one you know
who would want to hurt you?
Enemies you may have made?
Enemies?
No, I don't have any enemies.
What about your husband?
Are there any people he may have
had a business dispute with?
Not that I know of.
Did you work before
having your daughter?
Yes, I worked at a
small marketing firm.
But everyone there
pretty much got along there.
I just...
I don't understand
why anyone would do this.
What about fingerprints?
We're still dusting for them.
But assuming the person
left any,
That they didn't wear gloves,
It's going to take some time
to match them against your own.
Plus anyone else who has
recently been in the house.
Mrs. Lewis, what is it?
I know who did this.
Last week, we met
this woman in the park.
A photographer.
And she came here and she
took photos of maya.
Okay.
Okay, well she must have maya!
So why don't you go
and talk to her?
Go and talk to her, right now!
Okay, we will.
Just calm down, we will,
I promise.
Now, this woman, you
have her name, I assume?
Yes, yes, it's cathy driver.
Spelled like it sounds?
I think so.
What makes you think
she took your daughter?
Because she's the
only one that's been here.
And she's the only person
that I don't know.
And yet you let her
into your home?
She said she was a photographer.
I'm sure you've let people
into your house.
I mean plumbers, electricians...
But why do you think this
woman wanted your daughter?
I don't know.
She has a daughter of her own.
The daughter came here
to help her.
She even has a granddaughter.
This doesn't make any sense.
Do you know where
this cathy driver lives?
No, I had her card, but
I don't know where it is.
It's okay, we can find out.
In the meantime, I think
what makes the most sense
Is if I paid her a visit.
Okay.
What do I do?
You stay here in case
anyone calls
With any additional information.
And in the meantime,
if you think of anything else,
No matter how insignificant,
you call me.
I have to call my husband.
And if you have any friends
that you can call.
I don't think it
would be a bad idea
For you to have some company.
I don't understand.
There's no flights
for three days?
What kind of
weather delay is that?
They say there's an ice storm
Coming down from
the arctic circle.
No planes in or out.
He's talking to our consulate
To see if there's anything
they can do.
And in the meantime, his company
Is trying to get him home
through copenhagen.
Don't worry, taylor.
He'll be here as soon as he can.
By then it might be too late.
Hey, look at me.
Maya is going to be fine.
How do you know that?
Because I know in my heart
we will find her.
I don't know why she took maya,
But there's definitely a reason.
She doesn't want to hurt her.
How about I make you some tea?
I can't stomach anything.
Besides, detective gallagher
should be here soon.
Okay, I'll put the
kettle on just in case.
[camera snap]
Did you find cathy driver?
Mmm-hmm.
Okay, what did she say?
She said she's never
seen you before in her life.
What?
She says she's
never seen you before.
Or even heard of you.
I don't understand.
I asked her about the park.
About her coming to your home.
The baby photos, all of it.
And what did she say then?
She denied all of it.
How is that possible?
There's only one way.
Someone must be lying.
Well it's her, obviously!
Can't you see that?
My baby is somewhere!
Can't you go arrest her?
And make her talk?
You see, mrs. Lewis,
that's where we have a problem.
There's just no evidence
to support what you told us.
None at all.
I'm not saying I
don't believe you,
But I am saying
we can't just go in
And grab mrs. Driver
with no evidence.
Okay, you were in her house.
You must have found something.
We went through the darkroom.
She let us look at her computer.
There's no pictures that look
like the one
You gave me of maya.
Okay, then she must
have deleted everything!
Then there's the
biggest issue of all.
There's just no sign of a baby.
Then she must have
brought her somewhere.
Maybe to her daughter's house.
I'm sure her daughter
is on it as well!
Taylor, you're exhausted.
Why don't you go
and get some rest, okay?
And I'll talk to
detective gallagher.
I think that's a good idea.
Mrs. Lewis, I promise you,
We're going to do everything
we can to find her.
We're not going to stop looking.
It's okay.
How well do you know mrs. Lewis?
She's my best friend.
I've known her for years,
since college.
And she's never been one
to embellish things?
To make things up?
Come on, detective.
You can't actually think that
taylor is making this up?
I mean, if that were true,
where's maya?
I'll level with you, miss walsh.
There are three kinds
of these cases.
The most common, an estranged
spouse kidnaps the child.
The rarest is what
mrs. Lewis claims,
A stranger kidnapped her baby.
And what's the other one?
Oh my god.
You can't think?
I mean, you can't believe?
Taylor loves her daughter.
Unfortunately,
I've seen it before.
More times than
I'd like to remember.
But you met taylor.
Does she look like someone
who could hurt her own baby?
What is it?
Nothing, it's not relevant.
Miss walsh, right now
everything is relevant.
Now, if you're not willing to--
She had postpartum depression.
Pretty bad right
at the beginning.
But taylor is fine now.
We're going to keep
looking into her story.
But at this point,
We're gonna keep all
our options open.
All our options.
Are the police still here?
A few are still outside,
but they're almost done.
The detective,
he doesn't believe me, does he?
I think he does, actually.
But he's a cop.
They need to consider
every possibility.
But we're losing precious time!
I know.
And that's why I'm here to help.
You and I, we're
not going to stop
Until we get maya
back safe and sound.
Thanks, linds.
But right now, you need
to get some rest.
Come on.
With maya gone, I could never
sleep, you know that.
Then let's get to work.
I got you...
Skylar driver.
I got you.
Linds, linds wake up!
I'm up.
What'd you find?
It's what I didn't find
at first.
For hours, I looked online
And I couldn't find anything
about cathy or skylar driver.
Maybe that's not
their real names?
No.
The cops went to their house.
Plus, I found them.
In the white pages and on
the tax assessment website.
I hear a "but" coming up.
But that's literally all
I could find about them.
They have zero
social media presence.
Is that really that odd?
Maybe not for a
middle aged woman,
But for someone
like her daughter?
In her twenties,
who just had a baby?
It's practically impossible.
Plus, the mother, cathy.
What type of photographer,
even an amateur,
Doesn't blanket the web
with their work?
So what are you saying?
What I'm saying
is that these two
Made a deliberate
effort not to reveal
Anything about themselves.
Unless they couldn't prevent it
Because it's in
the public record.
Okay, I'll buy it.
But then...
Look at this.
Skylar driver, that's her?
Absolutely, a hundred percent.
When's this from?
A couple months ago.
She looks exactly the same.
A staffing company?
I looked it up.
They do mainly medical
and tech fields.
Near here?
Twenty minutes away
without traffic.
We're heading over?
First thing in the morning,
as soon as they open.
[car doors shut]
Hi.
Hi ladies, how may I help you?
We're here to speak
with ellen mckay.
We don't have an appointment.
It's extremely important
that we speak to her.
I'll see what I can do.
We appreciate it.
Tell her it's
regarding skylar driver.
I'll let her know.
Ms. Mckay will see you now.
That's her all right.
Just like the caption says.
That's skylar driver.
But you can't tell us how
long ago she worked here?
All I can tell you
is that she's no longer
An employee of this company.
Can you tell me if she left,
or if she was let go?
I'm sorry, can you tell me again
why you can't go to the police?
We've been to the police
and they're working on it.
But they don't have the time
to chase down every lead.
Look, I'd like to help you.
I really would.
But I'm prevented by law
From divulging any
of this information.
Unless of course,
you have a subpoena.
Do you have kids?
A boy and a girl.
Both in college right now.
Can you imagine if something
happened to them, ms. Mckay?
Look, I really
can't tell you anything.
I could lose my job.
And this is a good company.
The kind of place that people
don't usually leave voluntarily.
I'm sorry you couldn't
be more of help, ms. Mckay.
But I do appreciate your time.
She's beautiful.
You know, she has your eyes.
You think?
For sure.
I hope so.
Mom?
We did the right thing,
didn't we?
Sweetheart, of course we did.
We couldn't let this little
angel stay with that woman.
But...
She seemed like she was
taking care good care of her.
At least she did when
we were at their house.
And you know that's
what someone might have
Once said about
your biological mother.
Can you imagine if I had
left you with her?
Okay, so we know
that skylar driver
Is involved somehow,
it's not just the crazy mother.
You're sure?
I mean come on,
you heard the same thing I did.
I heard that she was let go.
We don't even know why.
But taylor, it's a long ways
from getting fired
To kidnapping a child.
It's too much of a coincidence.
She gets fired from her job
right before all this happens?
No, it has to be connected.
So what should we do now?
Go back to the police?
Not without more information.
I mean, they already
don't trust me.
I can only imagine
what they'll do
If I accuse additional people
without proof.
Okay.
What will we--
[banging on the window]
[scream]
I'm so sorry,
I didn't mean to scare you.
I overheard you
talking to ellen.
Can I get in?
Okay.
I'm jess.
-Lindsay.
-Taylor lewis.
I'm so sorry to hear
about your baby.
I really am.
What can you tell us, jess?
Well, it might be nothing.
On the other hand, if I could
help you find your daughter.
I couldn't live with myself
if I didn't say anything.
But you didn't hear
from me, okay?
Technically, I'm bound
by confidentiality as well.
You can trust us.
Okay well, skylar
was fired from here.
But before that, I worked
quite close with her.
In fact, I was probably
her best friend at the company.
So what happened to her?
Skylar, she wanted a baby.
In fact, I never met anyone who
wanted a baby more than she did.
And when she couldn't
get pregnant, it ate her up.
You know she became...
Obsessive.
The desire to have a baby
literally began to consume her.
And eventually,
her husband left.
He simply couldn't
take it anymore.
And work, work was understanding
for as long as possible.
But eventually, they had
to let her go, too.
She'd get nothing done.
She'd just sit at her desk
all day,
Looking at mommy blogs.
So after she was fired,
what happened to her?
Well like I said,
she was only a work friend.
I didn't really keep in touch.
Do you happen to know
where she lives?
I don't know the address,
but I can show you on a map.
I mean, if she
still lives there.
So this is it?
It looks just like jess
described it.
What do you think?
Go right to the front door,
try to catch her off guard?
No, if she sees me
she won't answer.
Especially if maya's inside.
Okay, then what's the plan?
Does it look like
anyone is home?
We should probably try
to get a closer look.
See anything?
No, it's too dark.
Doesn't look like
there's anyone home, though.
Let's get out of here.
We're not going to find anything
by spying on an empty house.
Think we should try and
talk with the neighbors?
See if they know anything?
No.
At this point I should probably
check in with the police.
Fill them in on what we
found out about skylar.
You want me to come?
No.
I think I should talk to
detective gallagher alone.
Besides, I'm sure
you're exhausted.
You should go home
and get some rest.
Okay.
But if you need me,
I don't care what time it is,
you call me right away.
You got that?
I do.
Thank you.
Come on.
Let's get you home.
It ooks like it's gonna
rain again.
Oh my god!
Skylar, look!
What's wrong?
Taylor, she's here.
Don't let her see you,
just turn this way.
Did they see us?
No.
How'd they find us
so quickly, mom?
[sobbing]
If they're looking for us,
That means the cops
didn't believe them.
But how'd they find our house?
I checked every search engine.
That information isn't anywhere.
I don't know, honey.
I don't know, but right now,
We have the advantage.
Okay?
I want to see what
they're up to.
Follow them?
I won't get too close,
I promise.
We'll be fine.
After all,
they're looking for us.
Shhh... Shhh...
Look at me.
What now?
We follow the friend.
I want to know who she is.
You sure you don't want me
to come with you
To the station?
No, it's okay.
You should go home.
Okay.
But I'll call you first
thing tomorrow.
We'll go out again
looking for them.
I appreciate it, linds.
But I understand you have work.
It's time for the police
to start doing their jobs.
Hey!
Don't you worry about work,
okay?
I told you, I'm with you
until the end.
I'm going to be right by
your side when we find maya.
And we will find her.
I love you.
I love you, too.
After this, I'll
take you home okay?
You can be with
your beautiful daughter.
What are you going to do?
I need to find out how
much they know about us.
What they told the police.
But taylor knows who you are.
What if she sees you?
Don't worry sweetie, okay?
Mommy's going to fix everything.
Okay?
Okay, let's go. Come on!
That's all very interesting,
mrs. Lewis,
But I wish you'd leave
the investigating to us.
My daughter is missing,
detective.
And I'm going to do anything
I can to get her back.
And with all due respect,
I haven't seen your department
doing too much investigating.
We've already put out
an alert for your daughter
And distributed photographs to
all nearby police departments.
What you should be doing
is finding skylar driver.
So first it's cathy driver,
now it's her daughter?
Exactly!
But didn't you
originally tell me
That skylar driver
had her own daughter?
Why would she kidnap yours?
Have you not been
listening to anything
I've been telling you?
According to her co-worker,
skylar couldn't get pregnant!
Well, maybe she got pregnant
and didn't tell anybody.
Maybe she adopted.
There's plenty of ways to have
a baby without kidnapping one.
Then where's my daughter,
detective?
You tell me, where's maya?
That's what I'm trying
to figure out, mrs. Lewis.
to figure out.
[phone ringing]
Hey linds.
How did it go?
He's not going to be any help.
He completely dismissed
everything we discovered.
And worst of all,
I can't tell
If he thinks I'm crazy
or if I'm a suspect!
You're not crazy.
We'll figure this out.
We'll start again
first thing tomorrow.
Get some sleep.
[doorbell rings]
Yes?
Lindsay walsh?
Yes.
Hi there, I'm detective
cindy winters.
I work with jim,
detective gallagher.
Do you mind if I speak with you
for a moment?
Come in.
Thank you, miss walsh.
Please, call me lindsay.
Can I get you
something to drink?
Water, soda?
I can make coffee if you'd like?
No, I just had dinner.
Thank you.
I assume you don't
have any good news?
I'm afraid not.
I would never ask this
in front of taylor,
But is it true that
if the child isn't found
Within the first 48 hours,
Well, the prospects
aren't so good?
Well, we're not there yet.
So let's try to
keep an open mind.
Did you speak to taylor today
when she went to the station?
Uh no, I didn't.
I was working on something else.
That's why I came
to speak to you.
Jim, detective gallagher,
wanted me to.
He said you and mrs. Lewis
Had discovered something
very interesting.
Well, I have to be honest,
we thought we did.
But according to taylor,
Detective gallagher
didn't agree.
Between you and me...
Detective gallagher can get
a little stuck in his ways,
So why don't you try me?
Well, the main thing
we found out
Is where cathy driver's daughter
used to work.
We spoke to a former
co-worker of hers.
And it turns out skylar driver
didn't have a kid.
I was under the assumption
that she had a daughter.
That's what we thought.
That's what she and
her mother told taylor.
But according to the coworker,
this wasn't true.
Skylar wanted a baby,
but she never had one.
Crazy.
I know, tell me about it.
And did you tell all of this
to detective gallagher?
Taylor did, yeah.
Didn't he tell you that?
I'm sorry lindsay, to make you
go through all of this again.
I know it's frustrating.
But with cases like this,
We have to corroborate
everyone's stories.
So tell me, did you
find anything at the house?
No, we just looked
around the outside.
But it didn't look
like anyone was there.
So then taylor, umm...
Detective winters,
How did you know we went
to skylar driver's house?
Oh, well detective gallagher
told me, of course.
Please continue, go on.
You know what...
Do you mind if I use
your bathroom?
No, of course not.
It's right on the left.
Just be a minute.
[music accelerates]
What now?
We follow the friend.
I want to know who she is.
You sure you don't want me
to come with you
To the station?
No, it's okay.
You should go home.
Okay.
But I'll call you first
thing tomorrow.
We'll go out again
looking for them.
I appreciate it, linds.
But I understand you have work.
It's time for the police
to start doing their jobs.
Hey!
Don't you worry about work,
okay?
I told you, I'm with you
until the end.
I'm going to be right by
your side when we find maya.
And we will find her.
I love you.
I love you, too.
After this, I'll
take you home okay?
You can be with
your beautiful daughter.
What are you going to do?
I need to find out how
much they know about us.
What they told the police.
But taylor knows who you are.
What if she sees you?
Don't worry sweetie, okay?
Mommy's going to fix everything.
Okay?
Okay, let's go. Come on!
That's all very interesting,
mrs. Lewis,
But I wish you'd leave
the investigating to us.
My daughter is missing,
detective.
And I'm going to do anything
I can to get her back.
And with all due respect,
I haven't seen your department
doing too much investigating.
We've already put out
an alert for your daughter
And distributed photographs to
all nearby police departments.
What you should be doing
is finding skylar driver.
So first it's cathy driver,
now it's her daughter?
Exactly!
But didn't you
originally tell me
That skylar driver
had her own daughter?
Why would she kidnap yours?
Have you not been
listening to anything
I've been telling you?
According to her co-worker,
skylar couldn't get pregnant!
Well, maybe she got pregnant
and didn't tell anybody.
Maybe she adopted.
There's plenty of ways to have
a baby without kidnapping one.
Then where's my daughter,
detective?
You tell me, where's maya?
That's what I'm trying
to figure out, mrs. Lewis.
to figure out.
[phone ringing]
Hey linds.
How did it go?
He's not going to be any help.
He completely dismissed
everything we discovered.
And worst of all,
I can't tell
If he thinks I'm crazy
or if I'm a suspect!
You're not crazy.
We'll figure this out.
We'll start again
first thing tomorrow.
Get some sleep.
[doorbell rings]
Yes?
Lindsay walsh?
Yes.
Hi there, I'm detective
cindy winters.
I work with jim,
detective gallagher.
Do you mind if I speak with you
for a moment?
Come in.
Thank you, miss walsh.
Please, call me lindsay.
Can I get you
something to drink?
Water, soda?
I can make coffee if you'd like?
No, I just had dinner.
Thank you.
I assume you don't
have any good news?
I'm afraid not.
I would never ask this
in front of taylor,
But is it true that
if the child isn't found
Within the first 48 hours,
Well, the prospects
aren't so good?
Well, we're not there yet.
So let's try to
keep an open mind.
Did you speak to taylor today
when she went to the station?
Uh no, I didn't.
I was working on something else.
That's why I came
to speak to you.
Jim, detective gallagher,
wanted me to.
He said you and mrs. Lewis
Had discovered something
very interesting.
Well, I have to be honest,
we thought we did.
But according to taylor,
Detective gallagher
didn't agree.
Between you and me...
Detective gallagher can get
a little stuck in his ways,
So why don't you try me?
Well, the main thing
we found out
Is where cathy driver's daughter
used to work.
We spoke to a former
co-worker of hers.
And it turns out skylar driver
didn't have a kid.
I was under the assumption
that she had a daughter.
That's what we thought.
That's what she and
her mother told taylor.
But according to the coworker,
this wasn't true.
Skylar wanted a baby,
but she never had one.
Crazy.
I know, tell me about it.
And did you tell all of this
to detective gallagher?
Taylor did, yeah.
Didn't he tell you that?
I'm sorry lindsay, to make you
go through all of this again.
I know it's frustrating.
But with cases like this,
We have to corroborate
everyone's stories.
So tell me, did you
find anything at the house?
No, we just looked
around the outside.
But it didn't look
like anyone was there.
So then taylor, umm...
Detective winters,
How did you know we went
to skylar driver's house?
Oh, well detective gallagher
told me, of course.
Please continue, go on.
You know what...
Do you mind if I use
your bathroom?
No, of course not.
It's right on the left.
Just be a minute.
[music accelerates]
[phone dialling]
Hi, you've reached the
voicemail of lindsay walsh.
You know what to do.
[beep]
Hey linds, it's me.
I just woke up.
I thought I would have
heard from you by now,
But I guess you're sleeping?
I'm gonna text you,
But call me as soon
as you get up.
Okay, bye.
Hi, you've reached the
voicemail of linsey walsh.
You know what to do.
[beep]
Come on linds, pick up.
Hi, you've reached the
voicemail of lindsay walsh.
You know what to do.
[beep]
[door knocking]
Linds!
[door bell rings]
Lindsay!
[phone ringing]
Hi, you've reached the
voicemail of lindsay walsh.
You know what to do.
[beep]
[crying]
Mrs. Lewis?
How are you feeling?
I...
I can still see her
looking at me.
I'm sorry.
Do you have any idea
which one of them did this?
Which one of who?
Cathy or skylar driver,
obviously.
What is it?
We're treating this
as a suicide.
What?
We have no reason
to believe otherwise.
Other than the fact that lindsay
would never kill herself.
She was happy.
She loved her life.
She was helping me find maya.
We may know the reason
she did it.
What?
We believe that it was lindsay
who kidnapped your daughter.
You must be joking.
No, this is the most ridiculous
thing I've ever heard.
Do you recognize this?
Yes, this was what maya was
wearing when she was taken.
That's what I figured.
This item of clothing was
found in lindsay's bedroom.
No...
Mrs. Lewis, listen to me.
Did miss walsh have
any children of her own?
No.
Any nieces or nephews?
Young cousins?
Did she do any babysitting?
Not that I'm aware of, no.
Why?
We found bottles.
Baby bottles.
In her dishwasher. And formula.
This doesn't make any sense.
Look, mrs. Lewis,
in cases like this
We usually look at
the mother because, well,
Unfortunately that's
what history tells us.
You really think I could
do something like this?
To my own daughter?
No.
No, I didn't.
That's my point.
But this...
This makes sense.
Right now we don't know
Why miss walsh
took your daughter.
Out of jealously, anger.
Something else.
But I think we need to
entertain the possibility
That maya wasn't just taken.
We need to consider
that she might be--
I don't care what you say.
Lindsay did not
take my daughter.
Cathy and skylar driver did.
And she's still alive.
I can feel it.
And I'm going to find her.
[phone dialling]
Hi, you've reached the
voicemail of lindsay walsh.
You know what to do.
[beep]
Hey linds, it's me.
I just woke up.
I thought I would have
heard from you by now,
But I guess you're sleeping?
I'm gonna text you,
But call me as soon
as you get up.
Okay, bye.
Hi, you've reached the
voicemail of linsey walsh.
You know what to do.
[beep]
Come on linds, pick up.
Hi, you've reached the
voicemail of lindsay walsh.
You know what to do.
[beep]
[door knocking]
Linds!
[door bell rings]
Lindsay!
[phone ringing]
Hi, you've reached the
voicemail of lindsay walsh.
You know what to do.
[beep]
[crying]
Mrs. Lewis?
How are you feeling?
I...
I can still see her
looking at me.
I'm sorry.
Do you have any idea
which one of them did this?
Which one of who?
Cathy or skylar driver,
obviously.
What is it?
We're treating this
as a suicide.
What?
We have no reason
to believe otherwise.
Other than the fact that lindsay
would never kill herself.
She was happy.
She loved her life.
She was helping me find maya.
We may know the reason
she did it.
What?
We believe that it was lindsay
who kidnapped your daughter.
You must be joking.
No, this is the most ridiculous
thing I've ever heard.
Do you recognize this?
Yes, this was what maya was
wearing when she was taken.
That's what I figured.
This item of clothing was
found in lindsay's bedroom.
No...
Mrs. Lewis, listen to me.
Did miss walsh have
any children of her own?
No.
Any nieces or nephews?
Young cousins?
Did she do any babysitting?
Not that I'm aware of, no.
Why?
We found bottles.
Baby bottles.
In her dishwasher. And formula.
This doesn't make any sense.
Look, mrs. Lewis,
in cases like this
We usually look at
the mother because, well,
Unfortunately that's
what history tells us.
You really think I could
do something like this?
To my own daughter?
No.
No, I didn't.
That's my point.
But this...
This makes sense.
Right now we don't know
Why miss walsh
took your daughter.
Out of jealously, anger.
Something else.
But I think we need to
entertain the possibility
That maya wasn't just taken.
We need to consider
that she might be--
I don't care what you say.
Lindsay did not
take my daughter.
Cathy and skylar driver did.
And she's still alive.
I can feel it.
And I'm going to find her.
I don't like this.
I don't like this at all.
I say we leave for
the cabin tonight.
You need to relax, sweetheart.
Guilty women run.
Women who have nothing
to hide, they stay put.
The police know too much.
The police don't know anything.
They originally
suspected taylor,
Just like we assumed,
And now they're making
a case for lindsay.
Besides...
The police aren't the ones
we need to worry about.
What do you mean?
You two are so perfect together.
Just like I knew you would be.
What do you mean, mother?
Who do we need to worry about?
Taylor lewis.
You need to take care of
her tonight, once and for all.
Then the three of us,
we can be a family.
We can move away and start over.
Just like I did
when I found you.
I say we leave her alone.
Enough people
have been hurt already.
Unfortunately, we can't do that.
Why not?
Because if there's
one thing I'm certain of,
It's that if we don't
get rid of taylor lewis,
She will never, ever stop
looking for her daughter.
How do you know?
Because I wouldn't.
[eerie music]
Where's my daughter?
Where is she?
[phone vibrating]
Oh skylar.
We did it.
Where's my daughter?
[eerie music]
Cathy...
If you let maya go now,
you can still get away.
Skylar needs you, cathy.
Think about her.
I don't like this.
I don't like this at all.
I say we leave for
the cabin tonight.
You need to relax, sweetheart.
Guilty women run.
Women who have nothing
to hide, they stay put.
The police know too much.
The police don't know anything.
They originally
suspected taylor,
Just like we assumed,
And now they're making
a case for lindsay.
Besides...
The police aren't the ones
we need to worry about.
What do you mean?
You two are so perfect together.
Just like I knew you would be.
What do you mean, mother?
Who do we need to worry about?
Taylor lewis.
You need to take care of
her tonight, once and for all.
Then the three of us,
we can be a family.
We can move away and start over.
Just like I did
when I found you.
I say we leave her alone.
Enough people
have been hurt already.
Unfortunately, we can't do that.
Why not?
Because if there's
one thing I'm certain of,
It's that if we don't
get rid of taylor lewis,
She will never, ever stop
looking for her daughter.
How do you know?
Because I wouldn't.
[eerie music]
Where's my daughter?
Where is she?
[phone vibrating]
Oh skylar.
We did it.
Where's my daughter?
[eerie music]
Cathy...
If you let maya go now,
you can still get away.
Skylar needs you, cathy.
Think about her.
[baby cries]
Maya!
[baby crying on speaker]
You should have stayed away.
[screaming]
She's my daughter!
(baby cries)
Maya!
Hi, baby.
Thank god.
[baby crying]
Mr. And mrs. Lewis,
please sit down.
She looks healthy.
Healthy and happy,
when she's awake.
Otherwise, she sleeps
like a champ.
And you?
I'm okay.
Better than last week, at least.
We're getting through it.
That's good.
Detective gallagher,
You didn't just
invite me down here
To see how I was feeling,
did you?
No, no I didn't.
Skylar driver was released
from the hospital this morning.
Don't worry,
she was released directly
To the care of marlboro.
What's marlboro?
A place where she'll
get the care she needs.
Where she'll stay
until the trial.
A sanitarium?
They don't really say
that anymore, but...
I also wanted to apologize
to you in person.
I should have listened to you.
I should have believed
you earlier.
Over the past week,
we've learned a lot more
About both cathy
and skylar driver.
It seems skylar driver
Isn't cathy driver's
biological daughter.
We're almost certain
that cathy driver
Kidnapped skylar driver.
[screaming]
...When she was
just a few weeks old.
What about her actual parents?
Aren't they looking for her?
It looks like they died
soon after.
Whether it was an accident,
Or cathy driver had something
to do with it.
And then skylar, she
wanted the same thing.
Best we can figure
from the interviews
We've had with people,
It was really cathy driver
who convinced skylar
That she needed
to have the baby.
For her whole life
she worked on her.
Drilled it into her head.
And what does skylar
have to say about that?
On the advice of her counsel,
she's not saying anything.
But when she gets out,
she could come back after maya.
Trust me, mrs. Lewis.
You have nothing to worry about.
By the time skylar driver
is released,
If she ever is,
maya will be all grown up.
You'll never hear
from skylar driver again.
Shhh...
I love you, maya.
-Yeah!
-Yes, good one!
Come on, maya!
[camera snap]
[eerie music]