Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Sonny...
It's Christmas Eve,
you gotta stop
rearranging the tree.
I know, I know.
I just--
[grunts]
I want it to be perfect
when we take our Christmas
Morning pictures.
I don't know who's more
obsessed with Christmas,
you or Ari.
Oh! Speaking of,
is she's sleeping?
Yeah, finally.
Okay, great.
I can start wrapping gifts.
Okay, wait,
hold on, let me--
Let me check something quick.
Oh, boy.
What?
What is it?
You know how that
streaming service
bought the rights
to my article
about The Alamainian Peacock?
[chuckles]
Of course.
How can I forget?
You helped them turn it
into a miniseries.
Yeah, I also agreed
to do a one episode special
for them.
Oh, my God, honey.
That's great.
Well, yeah, I mean,
it would be, except
um, I was expected
to turn in a draft
by midnight tonight
and I haven't written a word.
Oh, my God, what?
Why not?
Well, I got
deadlines at the paper,
and there's chaos back home.
I mean, can you ask
for an extension?
I tried.
And according the e-mail,
they didn't buy my grandmother
is possessed
by the devil excuse.
I-- I'm afraid they're not gonna
want to work with me again.
I mean, you still have a couple
of hours left until midnight.
I can't write a whole movie
in that time.
I mean, what if I help you?
I don't even have a story idea!
What about a Christmas movie?
* *
- Where would we start?
- Okay, well--
All the best Christmas movies
always take place in quaint
little towns,
full of mom-and-pop shops,
and lots of holiday cheer.
* *
DELICIOUS EATS
TIS THE SEASON
THANK YOU
SALEM INN
Christmas cookies,
get your free sam--
Hey, you!
One per customer!
Uh, enjoy it, sir,
and merry Christmas.
Don't be a Scrooge, Dupree.
What? I'm just saying
we have a business to run.
- Come on, come on!
- Let-- just wait, just wait.
- What?
- These cookies smell really,
really, really good.
- No, no, no, no.
- Really good.
Excuse me, oh, we have
so much work to do, come on.
Gabi!
Dear.
It's my order ready?
Oh, yes, uh...
Your order.
I'm so sorry, I have been
swamped and...
I've been going crazy
trying to find
those VR goggles
that Ari wants from Santa so...
I will have those dresses
to you by Christmas.
Well, hopefully you do.
Or I'll have to take
my business elsewhere.
[people chattering]
[sighs]
Hey, honey, I was thinking.
You know, might just
increase our business
if we were to decorate a little
bit more for the holidays.
Make it more festive.
Mom, you know
how I hate Christmas.
Okay, wait, why do
she hates Christmas?
Because there's always
some tragic backstory,
like someone she loved
died on Christmas
many years ago.
[chuckles]
Someone she loved...
[sighs]
You know, your dad would hate it
if he knew he was the reason
for you losing
your Christmas spirit.
It's not just that,
um, Christmas is not
the way it used to be.
It's all been coopted
by big businesses now,
it's all about materialism
and greed.
Doesn't have to be.
It can be about...
love, caring.
Merry Christmas.
Oh, Sydney, merry Christmas!
- Look at you--
- Oh.
Can I have a hug?
- Sure.
- Oh!
Hello, Samantha.
Merry Christmas, EJ.
[chuckles]
Aw, look at you.
Mm.
What a pretty dress you have.
Thanks, my mommy
bought it for me.
[sing-song]
Custom made for her in Italy.
Hi, sweetheart.
[kiss]
Sorry I'm late.
[chuckles]
Looks like you bought out
the entire haul
in town square.
Oh, well, what can I say,
I was in the holiday spirit.
I mean, who doesn't
love Christmas?
Oh, sorry.
I mean, I know it's a hard
time of the year for you.
If I remember correctly,
Sami, your father died
on Christmas,
and, Marlena,
your beloved husband.
[laughing]
Merry Christmas, kids!
How's the cookie business?
Well, dad,
you gotta try these.
These are fantastic, right here.
Maybe later, son.
I have got an inn to run.
[phone ringing]
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa...
Salem Inn,
John Black speaking.
Sure, I think we may have an
opening for that weekend.
Just a second,
hold on a second.
Honey, do you know where the
reservation book is?
WOMAN: Hold your horses,
I've got it right here.
Ah...
What would I do without
my darling wife?
* *
WOMAN: Like sands
through the hourglass,
so are the Days of Our Lives.
A VERY SALEM CHRISTMAS
SANTA: Ho, ho, ho,
ho, ho!
Okay, so,
EJ is married to Nicole...
Mm-hm.
And then John
is married to Kristen
and your grandma Marlena is...
Is the lonely widow.
Are you intentionally
trolling your family?
Is for the benefit
of the story.
Yeah, but all these
Christmas movies,
they're about, you know, love.
Yeah, what's a good love story
without some twist
and turns?
Mm-hm.
Those look good.
Hey, you're eating
all of our samples.
I'm so sorry.
They're just really good.
Okay, why don't you come inside
and buy a dozen or so?
I should, but I'm--
I'm actually late for something,
I gotta go.
Take this one for the road.
Merry Christmas, thank you,
these are so good.
- Hey--
- Cheap-ass mother...
Eh-eh-eh... Mm.
Hey, look, it is your boyfriend.
Ah, what happened
to all the samples?
Brady cleared us out.
- Oh, that's cold.
- Yeah.
But, don't worry, I saved
something sweet...
for my man.
[sighs]
Gross.
You said it, sis.
You'd think Sydney
doesn't have any dresses.
Did you see how many
bags Nicole had with her?
Lot of bags.
All right.
Cappuccino?
With a touch of cinnamon.
- Oh...
- Just the way you like it.
You're a lifesaver.
What are best friends for?
Mm.
Ah...
Wait, okay, I'm-- um...
Gabi and Nick?
- They're best friends?
- Yeah.
Why is Nick even
a character in the story?
Well, because he's part
of the family, you know?
And, uh, he moved back
to get to know us Hortons
and I saw a kinder,
gentler side of him.
Before he tormented
you and Gabi
and completely went
over the edge?
Yes, obviously before that.
Okay, you--
you are the writer.
Yes, I am the writer
who's on a roll thanks to you.
Thank you, okay, so,
moving right along.
Okay, so, uh...
This new and improved
and sweeter and gentler Nick
is secretly in love
with his best friend.
Yes, and even though
he's perfect for her
and he's right under
her nose, she can't see it.
Because...
Because she has a crush
on someone else.
Christmas greetings one at all.
- Brady, you're here!
- Why, why--
Why are you here?
Oh. I'm here for my fitting,
of course.
I'm making him
a bespoke suit.
- Oh, now?
- Mm-hm.
Well, no, it's just, um...
She was just--
she was talking about--
You were talking
about how swamped--
We're really swamped.
No, I always have time
for my favorite customer.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, you're gonna look
so handsome.
Even more handsome.
I don't even know
if that's possible.
You....
You're so kind.
Ah, let me get
my measuring tape.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
Sydney, I was cleaning
out some closets upstairs.
I found all these supplies
for making homemade ornaments.
I'm not gonna
have a Christmas tree
so I thought
you might like them.
Thank you, Sami.
Okay...
Is there a problem?
Oh, we don't have room
for homemade ornaments.
Mom.
Honey, you know
how we feel about glitter
and it takes
months to clean it up.
Oh, the horror.
[chuckles]
Sorry.
[clears throat]
I-- I should have asked first.
Uh, how's-- how's business?
Oh, um, yeah.
Well, um, you know,
it's just hard staying
afloat these days.
I'm so sorry, I know how much
this pub means to you.
Yeah.
Yeah, my grandparents
built it from nothing and...
passed it on to my dad.
[clicks tongue]
It must be rough.
Letting down multiple
generations of your family.
Nicole.
I'm just saying,
you must feel an enormous
amount of pressure.
Ooh.
You know what?
Sami's been doing
a fabulous job
and-- and Sean, Caroline,
even Roman would be so
proud of you.
Thanks, mom.
Oh, I found this outside,
it's-- it's got
your name on it.
Oh, I'm sure
it's just a bill.
[chuckles]
The heck is this?
What the heck is this?
Wait, what the heck is it?
It's an eviction notice.
What?
It says that I have
to close up the pub.
I have to be outta here
before Christmas.
[breathing heavily]
SONNY: Mm, okay.
Okay, harsh,
but I see what you were doing.
The eviction connects
the stories together.
Exactly.
So who is the big bad Scrooge?
The evil villain trying
to toss our heroes
out onto the streets?
Well, it needs
to be a total diva.
[laughing]
I know who it should be.
Wow, wow.
[chuckles]
Watch out, Salem.
Price Town is back.
It'll be
the best Christmas ever.
[laughing]
Mary, I need you
in my office now.
1001, 1002, 1003, 1000--
Yes, Miss Price.
You're not Mary.
You fired Mary last week.
I'm Leo, her replacement.
Wait, okay, I'm sorry.
Leo Stark is in the story?
Yeah.
Every villain needs
a weaselly henchman, right?
And they don't make 'em
any weasellier
than Leo Stark.
No lies detected, proceed.
- Mary!
- [gasps]
Leo, ma'am.
Whatever.
Did you deliver
all the eviction notices?
- I did.
- [chuckles]
Wish I could've seen
the look
on the faces
of all those losers.
Wah, wah!
[laughing]
Ah, once they're out,
there will be nothing
to stop me
from leveling this town
and achieving my dream.
'Cause who doesn't love
a big impersonal discount store?
[laughing]
You silly little elf,
Price Town isn't just
a store anymore,
it's a concept.
It's luxury condos,
exclusive restaurants,
a whole new way of life,
not just rinky-dinky
mom-and-pop shops.
Price Town is going
to reinvent Salem, USA.
And make me hella rich
in the process.
That does sound fabulous, boss.
But if I may, there's just
one teeny tiny hiccup.
You're going to give me bad
news?
'Cause I don't like
bad news, Mary.
Leo, and it seems
that the property
stretching from the Horton
Town Square
all the way to the Brady Pub
sits on specially
designated land.
Designated by whom?
The Office
of Historic Preservation?
That doesn't sound like
a teeny tiny hiccup.
That sounds like a biggie,
largie hiccup.
Well, I'm sorry, but I--
[grunts]
Ow!
What was that for?
I don't like hearing problems!
I like hearing solutions!
Fix it, Mary!
- How?
- Well, uh--
By doing what I do
with everything.
Throw money at it.
EVICTION NOTICE
Why would your mother
be shutting us down?
Ever since Abe ended things
with her,
Mom has gone
full blown Cruella.
We put our heart and
soul into that bakery.
I'm sorry, guys.
I mean, this is just--
This is devastating.
Is it though?
What do you mean?
Look, don't get me wrong,
opening the bakery with
you has been amazing, but...
I don't know, I--
Real talk?
I'm tired of waking up at the
butt crack of dawn every day?
And, I don't, know I've been
itching to travel again.
You know the, uh, Italian Alps
are breathtaking
this time of year.
Ooh, I've always
wanted to go there.
I'm not sure if I can
get time off.
I understand.
They must really
rely on you
down at the free clinic
you're helping
so many people.
For free.
Aw, it's not
about the money.
Mm, kinda is, though.
I mean, I-- I just want
the world to acknowledge you
for your talents.
You know, the way I do.
Aw.
- Thanks, pookie
- Of course, pookie.
I think I'm gonna pukie.
You and me both.
I think I'm going to throw up.
There must be
some way to fight this.
Miss Price owns this property.
I don't know what I can do.
We, Gabi, all right?
No matter what happens,
we're in this together.
Yep.
Look at me.
You're a talented,
bright young woman.
Okay?
You have so much promise,
you're gonna
weather this storm.
You really think so?
I know so and I'm rarely
if ever wrong, okay?
All right.
Um, about my fitting,
can we?
You know what?
I'm just thinking
the timing on that
might not be perfect.
Yeah, I noticed the mood
has changed a little bit,
Oh, do you really know
how to read a room?
We'll reschedule.
I-- I'll call you, yes,
I will call you,
so we can figure out
the fitting.
Are you sure you're gonna
be able to get it done
by Christmas Eve, though?
I mean, just in case
you close--
Okay, that's like
a week from now.
[laughing]
I mean, it's just--
There's-- there's higher things
on-- on your priority list.
Okay, no problem,
I'll get it done.
Gabi.
Yes?
You are the best.
Oh...
JOHN: Booted out at Christmas?
Honey, I know how much
you love our little inn.
We still have each other.
And we'll get through it.
Together.
Oh, get a room you two,
but you got plenty
to choose from.
Not for long.
We just found out
we're getting evicted.
You too.
What do you mean?
I just heard that Gabi,
she and Sweet Bits,
they got eviction notices too.
Seems Paulina Price is dumping
all of her tenants at once.
I wonder if that means
the pub is getting
shut down too.
I'm so sorry, Samantha.
Bad things happen at Christmas.
You know?
It's when my dad died.
It's when Lucas ran off
with a drippy Chloe
to Antarctica.
Well, I for one, love Christmas,
the extravagant parties,
the lavish gifts.
That's not really
what it's about, mommy.
I can't wait to see
what EJ gets me this year.
Oh, I have my eye on this
exquisite sapphire necklace.
Nicole, maybe we should
be a little more sensitive
to what Samantha and
Marlena are going through?
I'm sorry,
am I being insensitive?
Yes, I love the pub and I don't
want it to go away.
Oh, neither do I, Syd.
Excuse me, I'm--
I'm gonna make a call
and see if I can get
some help with this.
[sighs]
Oof, oof!
We're going to need
some help down here.
Maybe even a Christmas miracle.
John.
Hello, Marlena.
Oh, I see.
You got the same eviction.
Yeah.
Certainly was
a kick in the gut, but...
thankfully, I have
Kristen lean on.
KRISTEN: Brady.
I thought you left
with your father.
I forgot
that I have a gift for you.
You wanna open it?
[moaning]
* *
SALEM INN
ONE WEEK LATER...
[door opens]
MARLENA: Oof!
Good morning, Marlena.
John.
What brings you
by the Salem Inn?
Uh. Oh, I was in
the neighborhood and...
I-- I thought I would drop off
your Christmas card in person.
Oh, thank you.
That's so nice.
Yeah.
Kristen and I
have one for you also.
Oh, thanks.
Where is your wife
this morning?
She wasn't feeling well.
Took the morning off.
Nothing serious, I hope.
No, no.
I'm sure she'll be
feeling much better
after she spends
some time in bed.
[moaning]
Merry freaking Christmas!
[Brady laughing]
And happy freaking New year.
[moaning]
You know what?
I know Christmas Eve
isn't till tomorrow.
I think now is a good time
to give you your gift.
Oh, come on,
what are you talking about?
You have been giving me
fantastic gifts all week long,
not to mention the amazing
gift you just gave me.
- You know--
- Just, please,
let a girl catch her breath?
I'm talking--
I'm talking about...
an actual
gift.
[sniffles]
- What's that?
- Open it and find out.
No.
What do you mean "no"?
Why not?
Because...
our relationship
is built on lust.
And, um, romantic
gestures just...
complicate things.
[sighs]
Look.
Kristen, I know that's
where we started.
John is my husband
and I love him.
Do you?
I mean, do you?
Do you really?
He makes me feel safe.
Safe.
When did safe become
a priority of yours?
Come on, what about--
What about passion?
What about--
I like things
the way they are.
Are you really ever
going to be content
with just being
an innkeeper's wife, Kristen?
I mean, come on,
you want more.
Don't you want more?
Not from you.
I'm sorry.
I just don't want your gifts.
I don't want your money.
I don't want anything else
that's going on
in that brain of yours.
- I see.
- All I want is this.
So, basically, what I am
to you is just a hard...
Body.
Yeah.
And if you can't accept that,
then I guess you're just
gonna have to move on.
- Looks pretty good.
- Yeah.
How you doing?
I-- I mean,
I know this is a...
a rough time of year for you.
Well, I miss Roman.
I guess they always will.
May I ask you something?
Of course.
Why haven't you moved on?
I mean, I'm--
I'm sure there are...
Must be someone out there
for you somewhere.
[door slams]
[laughing]
Good morning people.
How we feeling today?
Well, not great,
Miss Price.
Fabulous, fabulous.
Just passing through
with a friendly reminder
that you need
to be out by Christmas.
We hadn't forgotten.
Mm-hm, good, good.
[chuckles]
You know, Paulina.
You can evict us.
You can...
throw us out on the street,
but the city will never
let you destroy
these historic sites
for your precious Price Town
and that's a fact.
[chuckles]
Well...
I wouldn't
be too sure about that.
OFFICE OF HISTORIC PRESERVATION
MAN: Come in.
I'm sorry to bother you, sir.
My name is Leo Stark
and I was hoping
we could have a little chat.
Hello, Mr. Stark.
How can I help you?
Oh, so, so, Xander
runs the Office
of Historic Preservation.
- Yeah, I like casting its type.
- Mm.
Plus, Leo's always
had a crush on Xander
and I thought
it might be fun for those
two to cross again.
- Yeah, fun for Leo anyway.
- Yeah.
[sighs]
There's something wrong,
Mr. Stark?
No, it's just--
Office of Historic Preservation,
I was expecting
some old creaky relic,
not a big strapping hunk.
Is there something
I can do for you?
I want to answer that
in so many ways.
I'm sorry?
Let me start over.
My boss, Paulina Price--
Oh, you work for
Miss Price.
Yes, and she submitted
a proposal for new construction?
Mm, I'm-- I'm aware,
I'm afraid that
I'm going to have to...
decline her request.
What, why?
Why?
Your boss's plans for Salem
are unethical and offensive.
She'd be tearing out
the very heart of this town.
Okay.
So what if she made
a donation to your office?
A very generous one.
Cash.
Is this a bribe?
More like an incentive?
A gift for a job well done?
I'm afraid I'm going to
have to ask you to leave.
It's a lot of money.
Some things are
more important than money.
Like what?
Are you aware that some
of these businesses
have been around for over
50 years?
Then isn't it time
for a change?
New businesses
can be cheaper to run.
Look, I'm all for progress
and innovation.
But it must honor the--
the history of this town.
These places that your boss
wants to tear down,
they aren't...
just relics of the past.
They're the soul of Salem.
They're bringing
the community together,
uniting people from
all walks of life
and those experiences
and traditions are
passed down from
one generation to the next,
providing a common
thread for all the people
that live in this town.
So your boss wouldn't
just be tearing down buildings,
she would be demolishing
the connective tissue
of Salem itself.
So...
Is that a definite no?
DENIED
NICOLE: Sydney, honey don't run,
you're gonna ruin your shoes
EJ can you please
talk to your daughter
and ask her to please
act more like--
What?
What are you doing?
EJ.
I'm just helping
the poor man out.
He's just gonna spend it
on drugs and alcohol.
You don't know that.
Where's your Christmas spirit?
Or perhaps I would be
more festive
if we didn't have to keep coming
to this dreadful hole
in the wall
that is run by her ex.
Sydney loves it here
and she loves spending time
with Samantha.
Sydney.
Santa pancakes!
I made them especially
for you.
Okay...
You got this, and we have--
That's for you.
[Nicole gasps]
Sydney DiMera
put that fork down.
What's the problem?
Uh, it's loaded with sugar
and carbs is the problem.
Sweetheart, it's almost
Christmas
and Samantha already went
through all that trouble.
Well, she could have asked me.
Come on, Sydney,
honey come over here
and we'll get you
something healthy to eat.
Good girl.
Uh, sorry...
about overstepping again.
No, no, you didn't do
anything wrong.
You're wonderful with her.
I just think Nicole gets
a little threatened
by that sometimes.
What is it?
It's-- it's just sometimes
when I look at the date.
Can't help but think about...
Our daughter?
Grace would have been
the same age.
I'm so sorry, Samantha.
I miss her too.
SWEET BITS BAKERY
CLOSED
Hey, isn't it a little early
to pack it in?
Well, we're getting
evicted anyway
so I was in the mood
for some shopping.
That is an excellent idea.
I have my eye on this new watch.
Ooh, I want a new watch too.
It's Christmas.
You're supposed to get gifts
for other people.
Okay, but isn't loving yourself
the greatest gift of all?
See?
Now, she gets me.
How about we go
ice skating at the park?
Ooh, yes, yes.
I like the way you think.
Okay, but I don't want
to miss the last minute sales.
Well, we can do both, pookie.
Okay, pookie.
But shopping first.
All right, we'll
catch up with you later.
Mm-hm.
Drives me crazy.
What?
Tripp putting
Chanel's needs above his.
Just so typical of him, right?
So kind and unselfish.
Wait.
Are you in love with Tripp?
What no,
no he's my BFF's boyfriend
Look, Allie, it's okay,
no one's judging you.
I--
If I'm being honest, uh...
I'm kind of in the same boat.
Are you in love with trip?
No.
But I'm totally
in love with Chanel.
PAULINA: Denied?
Nobody denies me.
He wouldn't take the money.
You're a disgrace,
get out of my office!
Ay!
I'm sorry, Miss Price,
I tried!
But did you know that some
of these buildings
have been here for over 50 years
and Mr. Cook he made this
impassioned speech about--
Out, I said.
Wait!
Where's my money?
Oh, right.
[thud]
Hm.
Textbook Mary.
Oh, well, if you want
something done right,
do it yourself.
At least find
the right partner in crime.
Hello, this is Paulina Price.
We need to talk.
You cannot be serious.
"Die Hard" can't be the best
Christmas movie ever.
Well, it takes
place on Christmas Eve.
But it's about
a guy killing terrorists.
To save the woman
that he loves.
It's about family
and friendship...
- And bloodshot...
- And bloodshed?
Yes, okay...
Okay, what's a better
Christmas movie?
Oh, I don't know.
"It's a Wonderful Life," maybe?
Oh come on, boring,
so boring.
Basic.
"Home Alone"?
"Home Alone" is--
is just "Die Hard"
for-- for kids.
Okay, "National Lampoon's
Christmas Vacation."
Everybody loves the Griswolds.
Griswolds, brilliant.
Absolutely brilliant.
Cousin Eddie,
obviously the best character
"Save the neck
for me, Clark."
[laughing]
What do you--
what are you doing tonight?
Uh. Nothing.
Literally nothing, why?
Do you wanna go to the pub?
There's this cookie
decorating thing.
- Be my partner.
- Yes.
Absolutely, you're on.
I knew I could count on you
to be my bestie.
Yeah.
Actually Gabi, there's--
there's something that I
wanted to talk to you about.
Ah, good.
They didn't close it down yet.
Brady!
Is the suit-- is it ready?
Oh, yeah, just right here.
[chuckles]
Oh, God, it looks great.
I knew I could count on you.
Hot date tonight?
Uh, sadly, no, no.
The woman I'm into
is not into me the same way.
Are you sure, have you--
Who told her how you feel?
No, I don't know.
I mean, I-- I hate rejection.
I'm not used to it, so I'm--
not really great
at expressing my feelings.
I tend to trip over
my words a little bit.
Maybe you can, uh,
write her a letter.
That's--
Actually a great idea.
[zipping]
- I like that.
- Yeah.
Oh, this suit looks great.
How much do I owe you?
Oh, we're-- you know what?
It's nothing.
Gift for Christmas.
- Really.
- NICK: Really?
Yeah, you've been such
a wonderful customer
and the store is gonna
close down anyway.
Well, at least let me--
let me send you a
little something in return.
Can I have your address?
Oh, yeah, kidding me?
Of course you have...
my address.
Thanks, thanks.
Um, suit looks great.
Thank you.
[exhales]
You think
he was talking about me?
What do you mean?
The woman
that he said
he has feelings for,
that he's afraid
to open up to.
He said he might
write her a letter and
then he asked me for my address.
To thank you for the suit.
I don't know, I just, I--
I kind of feel a vibe.
I don't know if it's
the Christmas spirit but...
Kind of feel like all
my dreams are coming true.
[steps receding]
[sighs]
PAULINA:
Yes, well, thank you.
I'm glad we could
come to an understanding.
Oh, yeah, be in touch.
[laughing]
Well, Mary,
I did it.
The city has approved
the construction of Price Town,
But Hottie McHotFace
wouldn't accept the bribe.
[laughing]
Oh, I found a way around that.
It's all happening.
Nothing could stop me now.
Are you sure about this, boss?
Those places, they mean
a lot to this town.
This calls for a celebration
of epic proportions,
steak, lobster, champagne.
Well, that does
sound divine.
Shall I make a reservation
at the Penthouse Grill?
Yeah, for one,
since it was a little old me
who sealed the deal and you,
you did diddly squat.
So you know what?
You get to stay here
and clean up my office.
And don't forget
to email one last reminder
about the evictions.
Ta-ta, Mary.
It's Leo.
It was so good of you
to think of this.
Oh, wow, I may not
like Christmas but
I do enjoy spending time
with my family and friends
and it's nice to be able
to lift their spirits,
especially given
the circumstances
that we're about
to lose everything.
Snazzy shirt I bought him, huh?
Looks a little tight.
It's fine, as long
as I don't exhale.
I love the way it shows off
your muscles, pookie.
Well, hey, if
he doesn't want it.
Looks like it might
fit me, so...
See, now Johnny here
has excellent taste.
I feel like you're more
of a flannel kind of guy,
maybe a size too big.
I do enjoy breathing.
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, look who's here!
Oh, mom, we have a real life
princess here tonight.
We just got back from seeing
The Nutcracker, didn't we?
Did you like it?
Boring.
Nobody even talks.
- [laughing]
- Oh, dear.
Nicole stayed behind
for the official gala.
I thought this
might be more Sydney's speed.
- Yeah, of course.
- Well, yeah, good, you can--
You can be a team.
I want Sami on our team.
It's pairs of two, honey.
Oh, wait, wait,
I'm judging.
I think I can make an exception.
- SAMI: Yay!
- Yay!
[laughing]
Why don't--
Why don't you find a place?
We're about to get started.
Yeah, uh, all right,
why don't you go there?
I'll meet you in a minute.
Take your coat off.
[inaudible]
Something wrong?
Oh, no.
No, I-- I was just...
hoping John might
be coming by.
Now, are you sure
that you don't want to go
to Marlena's party?
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry,
I'm just really--
I'm just really
not in the mood tonight.
It's all right.
Hey, maybe we can
just snuggle up in bed,
watch a holiday movie,
Maybe the one with
Hugh Grant when he plays
the Prime Minister and
a guy from the zombie show.
I just love it when
he comes to the door holding
those big signs.
Really?
Don't you think
it's just a little sappy and...
kind of stalkery.
No, it is romantic
and it's sweet.
Oh, come on, give it another
chance,
I guarantee...
it will melt your heart.
[sighs]
[clicks tongue]
This is interesting.
[paper rustling]
Yeah.
[laughing]
- I think this border--
- There, there.
Yeah, what do you think?
[indistinct chatter]
Is it too much?
[sighs]
Damn it.
What?
- What's wrong?
- I just--
I lost another bid
for the VR goggles
that Ari wants
for Christmas.
What am I gonna do?
They're sold out everywhere.
- Really? Hmm.
- Yeah.
Well, that might be because
I bought the last pair?
Wait, you bought them?
Why?
For you to give to Ari.
I mean, I heard you
talking about
how hard it was
to find them and...
And you did that for me?
Of course I did.
Gabi, I'd--
I'd do anything for...
Um, uh...
Ladies and gentlemen,
children of all ages,
I have made my decision
but first let me say that you
are all winners in my book.
[laughing]
I should say on these
very trying times,
you brought Christmas cheer.
And that fills us all with joy.
- Hear, hear!
- [cheering]
Now, there can
only be one champion.
So the winners of this year's
Brady Pub Christmas
Cookie Decorating...
is...
Nick and Gabi!
Ooh!
Nick, we won!
[overlapping chatter]
[laughing]
- We did it.
- We sure did.
And you make quite a team.
[laughing]
[sighs]
Yeah, yeah.
I'll give it to him.
Hey, what kind
of devilish judge
doesn't pick
her own grandkids?
Well, I calls them
like I sees them.
In fact,
Allie's gingerbread man
looks a lot like Tripp's.
And yours looks
a lot like Chanel's.
Hm.
Maybe y'all should
have switched partners, hm?
Let me help you with this,
you got a little--
- [laughing]
- [door closes]
[Nicole clears her throat]
Look, Mommy,
we made a gingerbread man.
Oh, wow.
Oh, and got frosting
all over your new dress.
I'm sorry.
EJ: It's okay, honey.
It'll come out in the wash.
That is her answer
for everything.
Can we talk about this
in private, please?
Be right back, Syd.
Daddy is in trouble, ugh.
[chuckles]
You know what?
I think I can get it out.
Let me just see if
I can fix this real quick.
Yeah, look, see?
Yeah, ha! Perfect.
Perfect.
Sami, can I tell you a secret?
Of course you can.
I wish you were my mommy.
Oh...
JOHN: Kristen,
what are you doing in there?
My favorite scene
is coming up.
Be right there!
God, I'm gonna need this
to get through the rest
of that movie.
[knocking on door]
[mouthing]
Shh.
What the world?
JOHN: Who's at the door?
SAY IT'S CAROLERS
It's carolers!
* O holy night, the stars
are brightly shining *
I'M SHOPPING AROUND
FOR A GIRLFRIEND
* It is the night
of out dear Savior's birth *
HERE ARE A FEW OPTIONS
* Long lay the world *
* In sin
and error pining *
* 'Til He appeared and
the spirit felt its worth *
I'D RATHER BE WITH YOU
* A thrill of hope
the weary world rejoices *
BUT TO YOU,
I'M JUST A HARD
* For yonder breaks
a new and glorious morn *
BODY (WHICH, FINE,
I'M OBVIOUSLY HOT)
* Fall on your knees *
BUT I HAVE TO SAY THIS
* O hear the angel voices *
I LOVE YOU, KRISTEN
* O night *
* Divine *
PERHAPS ONE DAY
YOU'LL LOVE ME BACK?
* When Christ was born *
* O night... *
I'm sorry,
just can't.
* Divine *
* O night *
* O night divine *
YOU MADE ME
THE HAPPIEST MAN ALIVE!
* [vocalizing] *
I UNDERSTAND
GOODBYE
* Fall on your knees *
* Oh, hear the angel voices *
[sighs]
* O night *
* Divine *
* When Christ was born *
* O night *
* Divine *
* O night divine *
[yawning]
[sighs]
Wow.
That was fun,
wasn't it?
I think I'm gonna go upstairs
and wash my face,
put on some flannels
and watch my favorite
Christmas movie.
The-- the one with Hugh Grant.
Oh, my God.
What is it?
Mom.
I think I have a way that I can
save the business after all.
* *
How did they find out
about that damn loophole?
No idea, boss.
Explain it to me again.
[grunts]
Apparently,
a Salem law from 1965
states that any small
business owner
operating in
an historic district
for at least a year
has the right to buy out
their lease.
So that's it?
Price Town is dead
in the water?
Oh, hell, no, hell, no, Mary,
they only have until
midnight tonight
to raise the money
and those deadbeats
over there
they're barely
making ends meet.
So if they can't
scrounge up the cash,
it's eviction time in Salem.
[laughing]
Full speed ahead!
[chuckling]
Oh, a Christmas Eve deadline.
Just like your script.
- Very meta.
- Yeah.
Gotta push on the climax,
Our characters
are running out of time.
Ooh, and so are we.
SAMI: [clears throat]
Okay, everybody,
thank you all for coming.
I know you'd rather
spend Christmas Eve
with your families but, um...
but we are running out of
time to save our businesses.
John, have you been
able to pull together enough
money to buy our leases?
Even pulling our resources
we're coming up short.
So pooling was a mistake.
But maybe we can still save
a couple
of the businesses, right?
MARLENA: No, no.
We have to stick together.
It's all or nothing.
I have to agree with Marlena.
Couldn't you ask your mom to
give us an extension?
I can try.
But I doubt
she'll change her mind.
GABI: Damn it, you guys,
I mean,
there must be a way to get
that money by midnight, we--
we can't just give up.
SAMI: You're right.
You are right, Gabi, we can't.
So...
I have an idea.
CHRISTMAS EVE
TALENT SHOW FUNDRAISER
So, what do you think?
How's it look?
Perfect.
You know, for someone
who's not a fan of Christmas,
you've certainly
gotten into the spirit.
[laughing]
I know, right?
I don't know
what's come over me.
[chuckles]
So, do you think
this fundraiser
will get you over the line?
I hope so, that's our
last best shot.
I talked to WXIR and
they're going to broadcast
the whole thing, so that'll
bring a lot more eyeballs too.
- That's great!
- Yeah.
And I'll donate
as much as I can.
Oh, no, EJ.
I'm not asking that.
No, no, no, it's my pleasure,
but unfortunately
all of DiMera's assets
are now temporarily frozen.
What?
What happened this time?
The SCC is after us again.
I'm sure it will blow over,
but not in time to donate
to your cause.
I see.
But I'm willing to do
whatever I can to--
to help out.
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
Well, I'm really glad
that you say that because, um...
Do have a costume for you.
Uh-- Costume?
[laughing]
I was told to pick up
my costume for the show.
We have to stop
meeting like this.
- What?
- Because of the suit and now--
- Here it is.
- Okay.
Uhm, you know?
I thought about what you said.
About, um,
expressing my feelings
for the woman that I love.
Yes.
BRADY: And I decided
to take your advice.
And?
And she turned me down.
Flat.
Oh, I see, I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
I guess it's time for me
to just, you know, move on.
Yeah, but then you know, maybe
you and I
can hang out sometime.
BRADY: Oh, um...
Thanks, I'm--
I'm flattered, Gabi, but...
I really think we should keep
our relationship professional.
I mean we work for
rival companies, right?
Yeah, right, yeah, of course.
But thank you, thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I'm such an idiot.
Ugh!
No.
Gabi, you're wrong.
Brady Black is the idiot.
He doesn't deserve you.
[sighs]
[guitar music playing]
[applause]
[laughing]
Wow.
Everybody,
this is Allie and Chanel.
Co-owners of Sweet Bits.
Wow, that was fantastic.
What an interesting choice
to cover the Indigo Girls.
Well, I want to thank
all of you so much.
All of you out there
for being so generous.
[applause]
[chiming]
GOAL
But, as you can see, we haven't
reached our goal yet,
so, please keep
those donations coming.
Oh, give it up, honey!
It's almost midnight
and that meter is about
as dead as this mink.
You are never gonna stop
Price Town from happening.
Oh, the show isn't over yet.
PAULINA: I beg your pardon?
There's still one more act.
How do you know that?
Because I booked it.
You did what?
Who do you think
tipped everyone off
about the loophole in the law?
You? How could you stab
me in the back, Mary?
After everything I've done
for you, Mary!
For the last time
my name is--
You know what?
Let's go with Mary,
but with an E and two Rs
as in Merry Christmas.
If you don't mind...
- I don't mind at all.
- Thank you.
Ladies, gentlemen...
or however you identify,
I would like to present
our grand finale,
the incomparable
We Three Queens.
[cheering and applause]
Please welcome to the stage
Miss Sunny Delight.
[cheering and applause]
Ow!
[chuckles]
Wilhelmina Shakespeare!
[applause]
Oh, okay, okay,
nice- nice try.
Yeah.
What?
We need a grand finale.
That's not what I meant
and you know it.
Fine.
Here you go.
Amanda Bottom!
[cheering and applause]
[laughing]
And last
but certainly not least,
the belle of the ball
with the big blue eyes
Miss Bullinda Chinashop.
[cheering and applause]
Take it away.
[whistling]
* *
* Deck the halls
with boughs of holly *
* Fa la la la la *
* La la la la *
* 'Tis the season
to be jolly *
* Fa la la la la *
* La la la la *
* Don we now our gay apparel *
* Fa la la la la la *
* La la la *
* Troll the ancient
Yuletide carol *
* Fa la la la la *
* La la la *
* [vocalizing] *
[laughing]
* Come on *
* La *
[cheering and applause]
[meter chimes]
Ha, close, but no cigar.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
No, we are not finished yet,
So, you got a gander
at us girls
but now it's time for you
to check out the boys,
ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for
Salem's Sexy Santa.
[cheering and applause]
* We Three Kings
of Orient are *
* Bearing gifts
we travel far, travel far *
* Travel far *
* We Three Kings
of Orient are *
* Bearing gifts
we travel far *
* Travel far, travel far *
[cheering]
* We Three Kings *
* *
* Join the party *
* Oh, join the party *
* We Three Kings *
* Join the party *
* Yeah *
* I love it *
* *
[cheering]
* Come on, you faithful *
* Oh, come on, you faithful *
* I like it *
* Join the party *
You know, you should know
that I always wondered
why aren't the two
of you a couple.
What? No, Nick is my
friend, I don't--
I don't see him like that.
[laughing]
* Join the party *
* [vocalizing] *
Nick.
[inaudible]
I can't believe
that perfect guy
has been under
my nose the whole time.
* [vocalizing] *
CHANEL: Horton,
I-- I was thinking
that maybe Johnny and me...
I know.
* Come on *
* [vocalizing]
Come on *
* Come on, you faithful *
* Oh, come on,
you faithful *
* Join the party *
* Oh, join the party *
* Yeah, yeah *
WOMAN: Whoo!
* We Three Kings *
WOMAN: Yeah!
* I like it *
[cheering and applause]
[meter chimes]
JOHN: Great job!
SAMI: We did it!
Mom, we got enough to save
the Horton Town Square
and the Brady Pub is saved!
Oh!
Thank you,
thank you so much!
What the--?
I can't believe
she pulled this off.
Oh, you've got to be
so proud of your daughter.
I am, I am, I am.
Don't you-- don't you want
to go find Kristen?
I'm not sure where she is,
but you'd want to tell her
the good news, won't you?
Well, to be honest,
I'm beginning to wonder
if she even cares.
* O holy night *
* The stars are
brightly shining *
* It is the night
of our dear Savior's birth *
I LOVE YOU, KRISTEN
John was right.
This is the best part.
* Sin and error pining *
[indistinct chattering]
Oh, my God.
You were amazing.
[chuckling]
Gabi.
Is this real?
I've been pining for
the wrong Santa the entire time.
I don't know
what I've been thinking.
EJ: You did it, Samantha.
This is all because of you.
Well, I had a lot of help
and I'm just so grateful.
I mean, you know, to everyone.
Oh, I should give you
back your pants.
[laughing]
Thank you.
And you should be happy too,
because you deserve it.
Thank you, EJ.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
You know, I don't think this
night could be any more perfect.
John, it's snowing.
- What?
- [gasps]
Doesn't this place have a roof?
It's a Christmas miracle.
Well, Dad, we did it.
I wired the money
just in time.
The Brady Pub is here to stay.
But you know that, don't you?
Because you were here
looking out for me
the whole time, weren't you?
[door opens]
Sami Brady, you and I are going
to get something straight.
What now, Nicole?
I saw you uglying
my husband earlier.
Uglying, really?
Yes and you're gonna
stay away from him.
And while you're at it,
stay away from my daughter, too.
[door slams]
EJ: Except she isn't
your daughter, is she, Nicole?
What?
What are you
talking about?
I just had a talk
with Rafe Hernandez.
The man is a self-righteous
Neanderthal
but he uncovered
a great injustice.
What are you saying?
Samantha.
Our child didn't die
all those years back.
Nicole switched the babies.
What?
Sydney is your daughter,
not Nicole's.
My daughter.
No, no, that is not true.
Sydney is my daughter.
She's my daughter.
No.
Oh!
Say it.
Sydney...
is EJ's and my daughter,
isn't she?
No.
Oh!
Say it, Nicole!
"She's Sami's child."
Sydney is mine
and I'm gonna
make you say it.
Sydney...
[sniffles]
Sydney is yours.
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
Horton's winding down?
Is it?
I barely noticed.
What do you want to do now?
We could, uh...
Go back to my place
and watch the Griswolds
or we could
watch Bruce Willis
kill a bunch of terrorists
in his bare feet.
I thought "Die Hard"
wasn't Christmas movie.
You know, I'm starting
to see things
in a whole new light.
So, this is...
Awkward?
It doesn't have to be.
Yeah, she's right, you know?
I-- I think we'll
all be happier this way.
TRIPP: I mean, we're finally
matched with the person
we're meant to be with,
don't you think?
Uh-huh.
Right, Dupree?
Yeah, Horton.
Totally.
LEO: Hello, Historical
Society guy.
Mr. Stark, you know you did
a wonderful thing tonight.
I was pleasantly surprised
to see you in the show.
Really, why?
Paulina convinced
somebody from the City
to approve her plans,
I was worried it was you.
No, not me.
Mm.
I wonder who helped her, then.
If that wasn't so
humiliating,
my plans foiled
by a drag show,
of all things.
WOMAN: I gave it my best shot.
I called in all my favors
to get that variance for you.
Too bad it was all for nothing.
Well, at least you don't have
to keep running that stupid inn.
Not to mention,
I think I've blown
my one chance
to real happiness.
Seems I had
you pegged all wrong.
You and the rest
of the human race.
Seriously, you should
be proud of yourself.
You helped to save the town.
I did, didn't I?
May I ask, what made you
change your tune?
Honestly, it was that
passionate speech you gave me
about tradition and some things
being more important than money.
I didn't think
you were listening.
Not listening?
Honey, I'm gonna needlepoint
that speech into a pillow.
[laughing]
Well, I'm flattered.
Somehow you got through to me
in a way nobody else ever has.
Can't quite explain why.
Merry Christmas, Leo.
This town doesn't deserve you.
You came here to gloat?
I came here to invite you
to Christmas brunch.
Me and Johnny
and Allie and Tripp
we're calling it
"A Very Swappy Christmas."
You want me there
after I tried to evict you?
Well, you're an awful Grinch.
But you're still my mom.
And I know there's a great
big heart in there somewhere.
I love you, baby.
[chuckles]
I love you, too, Mama/
- Oh...
- Merry Christmas.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Did Santa come?
Is it time to open presents?
[chuckles]
Oh, yeah, my darling.
But we do have a gift for you.
SYDNEY: Sami?
What are you doing
in my room?
Well.
Sydney...
your Christmas wish...
has come true.
I'm your mommy.
What?
You are?
She is?
She is.
Nothing could make me happier.
I love Christmas, mommy.
And I love you.
Oh, sweetheart,
I love you so much.
[sniffles]
[laughing]
- Excuse me.
- Uh, wait.
Hi.
I can't stop
thinking about that...
little performance
you gave last night.
Well, we've already
established that you...
like my hard body.
- I do.
- Hm.
I do, but it-- no,
it was more what you said.
Actually, what you wrote.
And...
I just want to tell you
that I love you, too.
- You do?
- I do.
I mean,
I really, really do.
And I want to be with you.
For real.
If you still have me.
Oh, God, Kristen.
Come on.
[grunts]
Such a big girl!
Hold on, let me
get the bed ready.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Let's take those slippers
There you go.
Now...
You close your eyes
so that Santa
can deliver your presents.
And we'll see you
in the morning.
[sighs]
[EJ exhales]
I can't believe it.
I can't believe
she's really mine.
She's our child, Samantha.
I meant to be a family.
When I fix all this mess
with Nicole,
maybe you and I can...
Maybe you and I could...
What a Christmas.
And the awful truth came out.
Oh, God.
Please, forgive me.
You know what?
I take that back.
After what I did to Sydney
and EJ and Sami,
I don't deserve forgiveness.
MAN: Everyone
deserves forgiveness.
[gasps]
[door opens]
Oof.
Oh...
John?
Ah, hey.
Is everything all right?
Kristen and I we're...
We're gonna get a divorce.
Oh.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you, Doc.
Doc.
You haven't
called me that in years.
No, I guess I haven't.
Would you like to sit
with me for a little bit?
I would.
[clock chiming]
Well, look at that.
All right...
Merry Christmas, Doc.
Merry Christmas, John.
WILL: "And as they nuzzle up
in front of the roaring fire,
"snow falling gently outside,
"the clock chimes midnight
and we fade to white."
"The end."
And?
Just under the wire.
All that's left
is to hit "send."
Shall we--
Shall we do it together?
Yes, please.
[chuckles]
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much for
helping me with this.
Of course.
We just, like,
completed a miracle.
Yeah, and you know what?
We got to spend
Christmas in Salem.
Even if we couldn't
actually be there in person,
You know,
writing all that...
it made me miss it.
You know?
Miss them.
Yeah, me, too.
We'll have to visit soon.
Hm.
It's midnight here, too.
Merry Christmas, honey.
Merry Christmas...
pookie.
[laughing]
MERRY CHRISTMAS TO ALL!
* *