Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Mr. Halley, is it true that
on the night in question
that you told the police
that you saw the defendant,
Sergei Ivanov, loading some
very suspicious looking
containers into the storage
unit that you rented him?
No, I... don't
remember saying that.
But you very clearly told
the police that you were
so suspicious that you
went there that night
-Objection. Asked
and answered.
Sustained.
Mr. Halley,
you very clearly
have changed
your testimony.
Did the defendant
threaten you in any way?
Because if he did,
we can protect you.
Okay.
Yeah.
What
happened was...
I am so sorry,
Your Honor.
I apologize to the
court, Ms. Sagan.
Mr. Halley, you
were saying?
-No. No one
threatened me.
I didn't
see anything.
Am I done here?
I'm done.
Judge: It's
getting late.
Let's adjourn
for the day.
We'll continue this
Monday morning at 8:00.
You look
horrible, Annie.
If I was you I'd get
some rest on the weekend.
Go to
hell, Larson.
Thank you.
So, I think I
should get my
public YouTube
channel this week.
I have so much
great content.
No, You have a
private channel
so your Grandpa can
watch and that's that.
Jamie's is public!
That's just
not fair, mom!
She's already
monetizing!
We could
make money!
I'd get a ton
of subscribers
and I could get
merch and sell it
and even
become famous!
Crystal, How
many times
do we need to have
this conversation?
You do not need to
worry about making money.
You should focus on
getting good grades
and being a
regular kid.
That IS being a
regular kid nowadays!
Do you know how
many of my friends
have YouTube
channels?
Yeah, well, not
you, and that's final.
I still think you're
being old-fashioned.
Great. Look, your tennis
coach is right there.
Hurry up.
Love you.
-Love you, too.
Sorry about that. Had to
drop Crystal off at tennis.
-That's fine.
How's Crystal?
Haven't seen
her in a while.
She's great.
Other than the fact she
wants to be YouTube star.
Yeah, don't lose too
much sleep over it.
She'll be on to
something else next week.
I sure hope so.
Hey, I'm sure that
as the most promising
Assistant DA
in the state
there's nothing
you can't handle.
That's not true. A
ten-year-old preteen
is definitely
more tough than
the criminals
I prosecute.
But I'm sure as the most
promising DA investigator
you already
know that.
Speaking of, how'd
the Ivanov case go?
-Ugh. Don't
get me started.
I had the prime
witness on the stand
then of course Larson
pulls one of his antics
to disrupt my
cross examination
so the judge
adjourned for the day
and I have to start
all over tomorrow.
He's
such a sly bastard.
-Yeah.
Listen, Mark...
there's something
I want to discuss.
What's up?
Who's the girl you
were with last night
at The Grove?
What, so I can't
go out with a friend
anymore just 'cuz
I'm dating you?
You kissed
her, Mark.
Danielle saw you in the
parking lot kissing her.
I don't know what
she thinks she saw,
but there
was no way-
Mark! Why are
you lying to me?
Danielle's my
best friend,
she wouldn't just
make that up.
-A garden salad
for the lady...
and the salmon eggs
Benedict for you, sir.
What do you want
me say, Annie?
The truth. It's
not that hard.
Okay.
The only time I ever
see you is at work, Annie.
And then I get a lunch
or maybe a dinner,
what, once
a week?
I miss you. I want
to be around you.
I want to speak to you
face-to-face instead of the
five-minute phone calls
and text messages we have.
You knew the
situation, Mark.
Crystal is my
first priority.
We have school and tennis
on top of trying to
juggle a career
at the DA's office.
All of which existed before
you were in the picture.
Except I'm not actually in
the picture, Annie, okay?
You say I am,
but I'm not.
So where do we
go from here?
I think you know
the answer to that.
We still have to
work together.
Well, that's
what we'll do.
Hello?
Oh, Danielle, thank
god you answered.
Do you happen to
be free tonight?
-Hmm.. let me
check my calendar.
No job, divorced,
no hot date...
Yeah, I think
I'm good.
-Well, I also just joined
the 'no hot date club'
if that's any
consolation.
-I'm sorry, Annie.
It's for the
better though.
-I know. Thanks for
letting me know
you saw him
last night.
-I hated having
to tell you.
So, what's up? You
need me to hang out
with my bestie
Crystal tonight?
-I totally forgot I have
a work function tonight
at some fundraiser
at the DA's office.
-Hey, no need
to explain.
You know I love
spending time
with that
wise old gal.
-Thanks, you're
a godsend.
So, um, swing
by for 7:00 pm?
-Yeah, TTYL.
-What?
-TTYL... talk
to you later.
It's all about the
acronyms, Annie.
C'mon, get
with the ages.
-Okay, okay.
Blue is A
favorite color of mine.
AN umbrella is
useful when it rains.
He ate A enormous
Pop-Tart.
You sure about
that one?
Yeah. He ate a
enormous Pop-Tart.
'Enormous'
starts with a vowel.
It's the grammatical
rule that counts;
not how it sounds
to the ear.
He ate AN
enormous Pop-Tart.
Good job.
-I'm here!
-Danielle!
-Hi, my BFF!
Where's Hector?
Oh, he's fine. Um,
my best pair of shoes,
on the
other hand..
It's motion-activated
so I get an alert
any time
something happens.
Wait, did you just
say that those are
your best pair
of shoes?
Hey, I'm not
pushing 40.
You know what,
I've gotta run.
Okay, so dinner's
in the oven,
it'll be ready in like
15 minutes or so.
And then just call me if
you need anything, okay?
And in bed by
8:30 this time.
Love you.
-Love you, too.
Hey, Annie.
On the cell phone
at the fundraiser.
What is that,
the new standard
at the DA's office
these days?
Yeah. Well, it's
been a long day,
so I called
my ride home.
You're leaving
so soon?
Not soon
enough, I guess.
Wait a
minute, why is it
I get the feeling
that you don't like me?
Maybe it's because
I don't like you, Larson.
-Perfect.
This place is a little too
lame for my taste as well.
I'm outta here.
So, how about I
give you a ride home
and you join me
for one drink.
What d'you say?
I'll pass. The joy
of rideshare apps.
-C'mon, Annie.
What am I gonna
do, bite you?
One drink, c'mon.
Wait a minute.
You don't wanna be
seen with me, is that it?
-Well, I have a
reputation to protect.
Your reputation
will not be tarnished.
You're opposing
counsel, yes, it will.
It's a little thing
called the appearance
of impropriety,
or did you just
skip that section
in law school?
I have a tidbit of
information about the
Ivanov case that will
make you very, very happy.
And why would
you give me that?
Oh, come on,
Annie. Really?
We both know
this case is shut
and closed in my
favor, right?
So me giving you a
tidbit of information,
a little bit of discovery
to get a drink with you,
hey, I got
nothing to lose.
But you, on the
other hand,
you have a lot to
gain.. trust me.
Fine. One drink.
So, after your
husband passed,
where'd you
go from there?
-That's about it. I,
uh, went to law school,
did my best to
raise Crystal,
and the rest, as
they say, is history.
You know, I'd like to
meet her some time.
Hmm.
So, what
about you?
You went to
Yale, right?
That's right.
-I don't get it.
You're a smart guy.
Why do you..
why are you a...
-Why am I a
drug lawyer?
Yeah.
You know, Annie, I uh..
I'm very well aware
I've got a pretty
bad reputation.
But to be honest with
you, it doesn't bother me.
Everyone's entitled
to a defense, right?
Yeah, but..
In some
strange way,
I think I'm a little
bit like them. Okay?
You know, I like to
live my life on the edge.
To be honest, I think it's
gonna be a little difficult
for someone like
you to understand.
Seems like you've lived
quite a disciplined life.
Why do you
think that?
-Well, it's just the
vibe you project, Annie.
You know, you
always seem so..
I dunno..
buttoned up, maybe.
And to be honest
with you, Annie,
I didn't even
recognize you
when you walked
in this evening.
You know, generally,
you're always so
I dunno..
prissy, maybe.
And tonight?
Well, tonight,
you look luscious.
I'm gonna go to
the ladies' room.
-Sure.
So, what about that
"tidbit" of information
about the
Ivanov case?
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
I'm gonna have
to show you.
What? No,
it's not-
I don't have it with me,
Annie. It's at my place.
Nice
try, Larson.
C'mon, I'm not
trying anything.
Really? Hey, look,
it's up to you, okay?
If you want a chance
of cracking this case,
entirely
up to you.
Finish your drink,
we'll head right over
and I'll show
it to you.
Hey, hey...
are you okay?
-Uh, yeah.
I feel like
I'm drunk.
I only had one
drink, though.
-Maybe you didn't have
enough to eat today.
I dunno.
Hey! There he is!
How you doing, Rex?
Rex, uh, Annie.
Annie, Rex.
-"Rex", that's
original.
-Hey, c'mon, buddy.
Can I get you a drink
while you wait, Annie?
-No, I'm good.
-Okay. I'll be right
back. C'mon, champ.
Hey.
-Wow, read much?
Yeah.
It is one of my
vices, actually.
So, uh, the thing
about the case?
Yeah. It's
upstairs. C'mon.
I'll give you a tour
while we're at it. C'mon.
Whoa..
My room...
Do you know I've always
thought you were
the most beautiful
thing I've ever seen?
Annie... What
do you think?
No!
No, that is
not the deal.
-Okay. Okay.
I had to try.
Nice try.
I'm ordering
a ride home.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
I'll give you
a ride home.
Let me grab you the
thing I promised you.
Oh, no.
Oh, god..
Have you seen
my phone?
Larson? Larson!
Oh, my
god! Oh, my god!
911, what's the
nature of your emergency?
911...
High-profile defense
attorney Doug Larson
was found shot to
death in his home
at 3:00
this morning.
Detectives say that the
suspect is still at large
but they will
work diligently
to bring the person
responsible to justice.
Officials are still
unsure if this was a
robbery gone wrong or
a targeted shooting.
We'll keep you updated
on the situation...
Hey, ugh, thank
you so much
for dropping her
off at school.
Again, I am so
sorry about last night.
-Hey, you have nothing
to be sorry about.
You figured out what
you're gonna do yet?
Yeah. I'm gonna do
what I should've done
last night and
go to the cops.
Get fired probably,
even disbarred.
C'mon, it can't
be that bad.
Well, it is. It's
called the appearance
of impropriety,
and yeah, it's bad.
I didn't even
sleep with the guy
but who's gonna
believe that?
I fled the scene,
wiped my prints,
which is
obstruction.
-Wait, so you could go
to jail for something?
What would
happen to Crystal?
Annie, you did
nothing wrong!
Just don't
say anything.
I can't do that.
That just makes
things worse.
Hi, Annie.
-Hi, Sarah. Is
George available?
Yeah, he said to
just go on in.
-Thanks.
George?
Hi, um... I wanted
to talk to you
about the Doug
Larson murder.
Yeah, right.
You were up against him
on the Ivanov case, right?
Uh, yeah. See,
the thing is-
Yeah, I know.
You have a
perfect record
and you want to
prosecute this case.
But so does everyone
else in the office.
No, the thing is I've
really messed up and-
Damn. Right now?
Yeah, yeah, fine.
Press conference.
Downstairs. Five minutes.
-For what?
For the
Larson murder.
I guess it's big
news whenever
a client offs
his own lawyer.
A client?
Yeah. Jimmy Perriera.
Didn't you hear?
Yeah, he
murdered Larson
because he didn't
get his son off.
Maybe this time
we'll get the guy.
-And so after fine police
work by our detectives,
at 8:00 this morning we
arrested James Perriera
a known criminal
and former client
of Doug Larson's.
-Sir, we heard rumors
that someone was spotted
leaving Larson's in
the middle of the night.
Was that Perriera?
-We don't know that yet
but we have a special
DA investigator on
the case: Mark Evans.
-Are you prosecuting
this one yourself?
-No. As you know,
I'm in the middle of
prosecuting another
major case.
This case will
be handled by
a very capable
young DA who
happens to have
a perfect record:
Miss Annie Sagan.
-Miss Sagan, is it
true that Larson was
laundering money
for Perriera?
-How do you respond to
Perriera's lawyer's claim
that he was
set up?
Um..
-How long do you think
this trial will last?
-Do you anticipate an
open and shut case?
No comment.
-Miss Sagan...
Hmm. No comment.
-We'd like to thank you
for coming out today-
Thanks for saving
me back there.
Yeah, seemed like he kind
of sprung it on you, huh?
Still, it's pretty good
for someone so young.
George must hope
that some of your
old man's talent
rubbed off on you.
Mark, I can't
prosecute this case.
What? Isn't this what
you always wanted?
This is your first
homicide case.
You've been begging for
this and now here it is.
Look, it's
complicated. Okay?
I'll tell you
about it later?
Guess who?
-Danielle!
-Hey sweetie, can you go
to your room, please?
I need to have a grownup
conversation with Danielle.
-Mom..
-Please?
Thank you.
-What's up, Annie?
Look at this.
"I'm going to
kill you bitch."
Do you know
who it's from?
Yeah. His name
is Quentin Cruz.
I put him away
two years ago and
he's been harassing
me ever since.
Okay, why haven't you
told me this before?
Because it wasn't really
a big deal before and
honestly I thought he
would just get over it
but now it's escalated
to death threats.
Have you reported
this to anyone?
Yeah, I told Judge
Miller this morning
and he told me
to tell some lady
with Judicial
Protection...
Officer Mendez,
I think.
Well, did you?
-No. Not yet.
I didn't want to make
a big fuss about it.
I just wanted someone
outside the courts
to be aware, that's
why I'm telling you.
Look, I'm here for you
every step of the way.
-I know.
-Mitch Warner, appearing
on behalf of the defense.
-Annie Sagan,
appearing for the people.
-Do you have a copy
of the police report?
-We have yet to
receive a full report
from the police,
Your Honor,
despite the numerous
attempts from my office.
Based on that,
and other factors,
we strongly recommend
that bail be granted.
Miss Sagan... Miss
Sagan, did you hear me?
I said I wanted to hear
the People's position
on the
matter of bail.
Miss Sagan? Bail!
Right. Um, sorry.
Due to the serious
nature of the crime
we request that he be
held without bail, sir.
-Your Honor, my client
has strong ties
to the community.
He's in no way
a flight risk.
He has a wife,
children, home,
and businesses
in this community.
Based on that, I
strongly feel that
Mr. Perriera should
have bail granted.
Fine. Bail is set at
half a million dollars.
Hey, don't feel
too bad about it.
-Huh?
That he
got bail.
-Oh, yeah. Right.
So, you heard
the latest, right?
Perriera has an alibi for
the night of the murder.
-It's because
it wasn't him.
Yeah. It
was him, alright.
His alibi's his mistress
who's lying for him.
I already found a
witness who'll testify
she wasn't even with
Perriera that night,
that she was
home alone.
I can't prosecute
an innocent man.
Innocent? Are
you kidding me?
Perriera's a drug
dealing, murdering scum.
Hey. Hold up.
That witness who can
break Perriera's alibi,
he wants to cut a
deal... like now.
Wanna discuss it
over a drink?
Mark, you
know it's over.
Okay, how about
a coffee shop?
Nothing romantic
about that, right?
Yeah. Well,
it can be.
Walk me to
my car?
So what did they
pick this guy up for?
-Uh, robbing
a liquor store
while high
on heroin.
Great. Sounds like
a reliable source.
I mean, this guy's
obviously a junkie
who's lying.
And it seems to me
you're trying to do
the defense's
job for them.
You know what?
Yeah, I am,
because the
defense is gonna
rip this guy apart
on the stand.
-Okay. Fine. Whatever.
You're the boss.
I will look into
other suspects.
-Great.
-I've been meaning
to track down that
mystery
blonde anyway.
-The what?
-The blonde woman
who was with Larson
the night of
the murder..
you read the
file, right?
You know they found
two long blonde hairs
on the pillow next
to Larson's body.
I dunno. Maybe
she did it.
Maybe Perriera
put her up to it.
No! I mean,
no, that's-
that's not
Perriera's style.
Larson was a
total horndog.
He probably slept with a
new woman every night.
Those hairs could've
been there for weeks.
Still, it's a lead that
we have to follow up on.
No. Listen,
Larson is no angel.
I'm sure he has enemies
against him, right?
-Yeah. You
got that right.
Larson
was a jerk.
Right. So, why
don't you work on
finding out who else
wanted him dead.
What is this? Is
this some kind of
women's intuition,
"feeling" thing?
Does George know about
this feeling of yours?
No. And he
doesn't need to.
This is my case. I've
gotta get back to work.
-Hey. You up for
a drink tonight
in a NON-romantic
setting?
Definitely not. I'll be
working well into the night.
I'll talk to
you later.
That was
so fun.
I must say, Danielle sure
is great with Crystal.
Looked like they had a
great day at the lake.
Sorry, what?
Who is this?
Crystal didn't
even wake up
when I was in
her room tonight.
Who is this?
Quentin Cruz?
Oh, come
on. Go, go, go.
Oh, come on,
Danielle, pick up.
Please, answer.
Crystal!
Hello?
Crystal? Oh,
thank god.
Baby? Hey, how are
you? You okay?
-Hi, Mom.
-Hi.
-Time to
go home?
-Yeah.
-What's going on?
Oh my god, I've been
calling you and no answer!
I've been worried
out of my mind!
Why? You know
she's with me.
My phone's
probably dead.
-You okay?
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
Did you get my
package, Annie?
I'm quite a
good photographer,
don't you think?
You're out of
your mind.
I know who this is, I'm
gonna have you arrested!
Oh, I don't think
you'll do that, Annie.
Not when I have
more pictures
I could show them
from THAT night.
Cruz, what
do you want?
Isn't it obvious? I'm
going to ruin your life
the way you ruined
mine.
Who was that?
-He knows
where you live.
Pack your bags,
we're going to a hotel.
Judge, I'm-I'm so
sorry to bother you.
-When I said any
time, I meant it.
What's wrong?
Everything.
I mean, the stalker,
the Larson case...
-Oh, right,
congrats on that.
It'll be a real
feather in your cap,
putting that
guy away.
The thing
is, um...
He didn't
do it.
Perriera, he
didn't do it.
His hands are
totally different
than the
killer's hands.
-How do you
know that?
You have a witness who
saw the killer's hand?
Yeah.
Me.
I was there
that night.
I know. I'm so sorry.
It was a total mistake.
It was the night of
the benefit and I just
got drunk and I went
over to Larson's house
and then I was there
when the killer came in
and I was
hiding and-
-And you didn't
come forward?
-I tried, okay,
but now I can't
and.. and now I
can't prosecute
an innocent man
and the guy that
they'll replace
me with is just
gonna be hell-bent
on putting him away.
-No, stop! STOP.
I don't want to
hear any of this.
I'm about to
be nominated
to the Federal
Court of Appeals.
You're
right. I'm sorry.
Actually, I didn't
hear any of it.
You have got to figure
this out yourself
before they do.
Hey, Danielle. Is
everything okay there?
Thank you again. I
won't be too much longer.
Find anything,
counselor?
-Oh, god. I didn't
realize anyone was here.
-I just went out
to grab dinner.
It's hard work
searching for a clue
to who
knows what.
Yeah, well, isn't
that your job?
Hey look, I'm satisfied
that Perriera did it, okay?
If you want to go on
some wild goose chase
based on some
women's intuition thing,
that's your business
but, you know, please,
forgive me if I don't
share your beliefs.
-You know what
strikes me is that
this place has
been trashed.
But not just
randomly trashed.
Like the drawers and
the filing cabinet,
which indicates
to me that
someone was.. was
looking for something.
I mean, if Perriera
killed Larson because
he couldn't keep
his son out of jail,
revenge pure
and simple,
but then.. what
was he looking for?
Maybe it was
another motive
or maybe it was
someone else.
Let's see...
Are you
gonna help?
Look, it's Larson's
bank statements.
He makes a deposit for
$9,000 every month..
going back
for years.
-They could be
perfectly innocent.
Yeah, but...
Alright, um..
He made the
same notations
on every time that
he made a deposit.
TOC, SM, SL?
Someone's
initials maybe?
Yeah, maybe, but
TOC and the others,
what are they
paying Larson for?
-Blackmail
comes to mind.
Yeah. That's what
I was thinking too.
But who is Larson
blackmailing?
Yeah, this is he.
Yes, that's right.
Thanks for
getting back to me.
Uh-huh...
Great.
That's exactly what
I wanted to know.
Thanks for
your help.
Remember those
long blonde hairs
they found on
Larson's pillow?
-Yeah.
That was Larson's
maid on the phone.
Turns out she changed
Larson's sheets earlier
on the day of
the murder so the
blonde hairs were left
on his bed that night.
Larson was with
the mystery blonde
the night of
the murder.
So maybe Larson
left the party
with somebody
that night after all.
Ooh, I gotcha...
Wow, that's
pretty intense.
-Oh. Yeah. It's
just a stalker
who's been
threatening me.
He got out of jail a
couple of weeks ago.
-What? Why wouldn't
you tell me?
-Because it wasn't
that serious at first.
Now it's
escalated.
He broke into
Danielle's house
the other day and left
a threatening note
next to
Crystal's bed.
-Are you kidding me?
Get out of your house!
-We did, okay?
We're at a hotel.
We're fine.
-Good job today.
-Thanks.
So how long do we get
to stay at the hotel?
-Not too
much longer.
Just until they
fix the house.
-Well, tell them to take
their time 'cuz I love it!
- Well, I
prefer our house.
-I know. I do too
but it's so much
fun at the hotel.
-Hey, sweetie,
gimme a sec.
-Mm-hm.
Hey, George.
I got a call from a lawyer
today named Simmons
and he said that his
client was willing to
testify that Perriera
wasn't anywhere near
his girlfriend at the
time of the murder
and you
wouldn't deal.
Well, George, his client
is totally unreliable.
He's a junkie
who didn't even-
-Annie, listen to
me.. very carefully.
I want Perriera.
But George, I-
Rumor has it that you
are not pursuing this
with the vigor
that you should,
that you're off on
some wild goose chase
of your own.
Listen to me, Annie.
if you cannot
handle this
I want you to let
me know right now
because I do not
want you to blow this.
The guy took
Simmons' deal,
you got a problem
with that?
-No. I..
-Good.
Are you okay, Mom?
Yeah, just some work
stuff. You ready to go?
Mm-hmm.
Ooh!
-Is Danielle
here?
-Yeah, I
think so.
Hey, Counselor.
Let's go for a ride.
How did you
know we were here?
It's what I do
for a living.
C'mon. I got something
important to show you.
-Maybe not.
Oh, come on.
What is it now?
Here I thought we'd
reached an understanding
and now you're
being all weird again.
Can you give us
a sec, sweetie?
Mm-hmm.
Are you out of your
mind? I'm being weird?
I just got chewed out
by George because
someone told him I was
on a wild goose chase.
Now where would he
get that idea, huh?
-Beats me.
Okay. So, maybe I
complained about you
to someone and it
got back to him.
I didn't mean to
get you in trouble.
-Well?
I really am
sorry, okay?
And in fact, I'm
thinking you might be
onto something, this
whole someone else
being involved in
Larson's murder thing.
If you get in the car
we can go find out.
Fine. Let me put Crystal
in Danielle's room.
-Okay.
-So what's the
big surprise?
You figure out who
Larson was blackmailing?
Wait, this isn't the
way to Larson's house.
-No, it isn't.
I thought first we'd make
a little stop at Scratch.
Scratch?
-Yeah. It's a
jazz club nearby.
I found a drinks
receipt on Larson's
credit card bill from
the night of the murder.
I'm thinking maybe
he met the mystery
blonde woman there
that night and
maybe someone got
a good look at her.
Anyway, the waiter who was
on that night is working
so, uh.. let's
go find out.
Annie? You coming?
Yeah.
Um, I'm gonna go
to the restroom.
Are you Tony?
-Yeah.
Great.
I don't know if he met
her here that night
or if he came
in with her, okay?
Annie! Over here.
Sorry, you
were saying?
-Yeah, like
I was saying,
I don't know if he met
the girl here that night
or if he came
in with her, okay?
It was a really
busy Friday night.
But you do remember
a woman being here
that night
with Larson?
-Yeah.
-Do you think
you'd recognize her
if you saw
her again?
-Maybe. Okay?
I don't know.
There were so many
people here that night.
-What about
surveillance cameras?
You guys have any kind of
security cameras in here?
-Yeah, we do but
they erase themselves
and then get re-taped
over every couple days.
-Okay,if you think
of anything else,
give me a call.
-Yeah.
-Thanks for
your help.
Mm-hmm.
It was
worth a shot.
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah...
I think I left my
phone in the bathroom.
-So how long until
we can go back home?
-Mm. Hopefully not
too much longer.
You know, I
can't stand it.
I think I'm just gonna
call Officer Mendez
with Judicial Protection
at this point.
Hopefully they'll
find him soon.
Yeah, that's
fine, I'm sure,
but you should get a
gun for your own safety.
Ever since Evan left, I
made a point to get one.
I keep it in my
nightstand and..
It just.. it makes me
feel more comfortable
being in the
house all alone.
I'm sure that they'll
find him soon enough
so cheer up.
Think of this as like
a fun girls' getaway.
At least we don't have to
cook and clean, right?
Mm. Haven't had to do
that since my divorce
so it's
nothing new.
Well, Crystal
told me that she
prefers the
hotel life, so...
Get that forehand..
Good job!
Good hustle!
Here we go...
Good job!
Excellent.
Well done.
-So what's going on
with the Larson case?
Well, I have a couple ideas
that probably all lead to
dead ends, but you know,
what scares me the most
is that they found my
hair on the pillow
and that Mark
talks about
"the woman with
blonde hair" all the time
and I know fully
well it's me.
Bring it in.
Awesome job!
-Thanks!
-Ooh!
You're Crystal,
right?
-Oh, yes, that's
me.. Crystal.
Hi!
-Well, hi
to you too!
Your mom asked
me to pick you up
and give you
a ride home.
-My mom?
Mm-hm
-Um, no she's
not coming.
My grandpa's coming
to pick me up.
Oh, hm. Well, must be
some kind of mix-up
but since I'm
already here,
why don't I just
drop you off at home?
My car's
right there...
and that way it won't
be a trip for nothing.
Hey, Crystal. Is
this your grandpa?
Oh, no. He's
on his way.
Annie's a
friend of mine.
She asked me to
pick Crystal up.
There's been some
kind of mix-up.
I'm gonna
head out.
I'll see you
next time, Crystal.
-Bye!
Bye.
He did find a
lead though. Um...
he found Larson's
safety deposit box
so maybe that'll lead to
something that we can use.
Well, is there
any way I can help?
I'll do anything
for you,
for Crystal,
for that matter.
I know.
You know...
it just
scares me...
I mean, you know
what's at stake.
I could go to
jail, or worse,
I could..
lose Crystal.
Mark, please tell me
you found something
in Larson's safety
deposit box
that'll crack this
case wide open.
-I think I did.
I'm still looking
through it all.
Oh, great. Okay.
I'm on my way.
Please tell me you
found something.
-Take a look.
These look like
docket numbers.
-That's what
I figured.
Larson had 'em in
his safe deposit box
and needless to say
his sister couldn't
make heads or tails
of 'em so I kindly
volunteered to try and
decipher them for her.
And?
-And do you
want a beer?
Yeah, sure.
So I presume that Larson
handled all the cases?
-Yeah, some of 'em.
His old partner
handled some of 'em too
and in each of the
cases the defendant won
due to some evidence
that wasn't allowed in.
-Wait, so you're
saying that the
judge was on the take?
Or the prosecutor was?
I don't know. It
could be either.
Though, that kind of
thing is particularly
hard to prove 'cause
judges, or whoever,
can always claim
they made a decision
based on the
merits of the case.
I'm still looking
through the files
but, um,
hold on a second,
I gotta grab a
bottle opener.
To finding
the truth.
Truth.
You're leaving?
Ah, yeah.
You know, I..
I forgot to feed
my neighbor's dog.
I'll see
you later.
Hi. I am here
for that video.
Hey, um, I was expecting
the guy, a Mr. Evans.
Right. Um, I
work with him
and he wasn't
able to make it
so he told me
to come grab it.
Mm-hmm. Okay. So, it's
not actually our video
but we have this guy,
Leon, who's a regular here
he was actually having
a party that night.
So he's taken a bunch
of videos on his phone
and I think that
one of them caught
the woman you guys
are looking for.
Here, I put it on a
thumb-drive for you.
Thanks.
-Yeah. You know,
it is funny though.
You do look a lot like
the woman on the film
with your hair
and your eyes.
People say I have a
common face. Thanks!
Great.
Whoa, Annie.
What happened?
Where's Crystal?
She's fast
asleep in my bed.
What happened here?
-I don't know. Quentin
Cruz, I imagine.
"I'm watching you.
Time for your
mentor to die too."
-Wow.
"Time for your
mentor to die too."
He's talking
about Judge Miller.
Oh, my god!
That means that
Cruz killed Larson.
I mean, I knew he
was following me
but I never thought
he would kill somebody
in order to get
back at me.
Oh, my god...
Oh, my god!
It's all my fault.
It's all my fault
that Larson's dead.
I have to
warn the judge.
Come on. Pick up,
pick up, pick up.
Hey, Judge,
It's me, okay,
you need to be careful.
Cruz killed Larson
and now I think
he's after you.
Can you just please
call me back. Please.
Annie, where
are you going?
-Listen, I have
to warn the judge.
I need you to take
Crystal to my dad's.
It is not
safe here.
I'll let him know
that you're on the way.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
Hi, Officer Mendez.
Yes, this is Annie
Sagan, Assistant D.A.
Um, Judge Miller
referred me to you.
I believe he spoke
to you about this and
I apologize for not
following up with you.
I just honestly was hoping
that this all would pass
but it seems like Quentin
Cruz is a bigger danger
than we
originally thought.
He broke into my
hotel room tonight
and made some
pretty serious threats.
He needs to
be arrested.
Um, can you please
just give me call back
when you have
a moment.
Judge? Judge?
Judge!
Judge! Judge!
Judge!!
Annie! What
the hell?
Oh, my god,
you're okay!
-What are
you doing?
Didn't you get any
of my messages?
-No. What
messages?
Oh god. Uh,
Cruz, you know,
the guy who's been
stalking me, right?
-Yeah. Yes.
Yeah. Well, he
trashed my place
and he threatened
to kill you
which means that
he killed Larson
and now he's
coming after you.
I'm.. I'm fine.
Everything's alright.
Oh god.
It was Quentin
Cruz the whole time.
He followed me there and
when he thought I'd left
he went in
and shot him.
-Hmm.
Probably to put
the blame on me.
It's okay.
You'll have him arrested
and turn yourself in.
Officer Mendez? Yeah,
did you find him?
Are you sure?
Yeah. Okay.
Um... Thank you
for letting me know.
What is
it? Annie?
It wasn't
Quentin Cruz.
She said that he's been
dead for three days.
His body washed up
on a beach yesterday
and they
just ID'd him.
It doesn't
make sense.
I talked to him
on the phone
the night he left the
photos in the room.
I mean, it was.. it
was definitely him.
Annie, exactly how
long has it been
since you've had
anything to eat?
I thought so.
I'm gonna go
get us something.
Also, we need to
call your father.
Hey, Mark.
-How about that? I've
only been trying to
reach you for the
last few hours.
I'm sorry, okay?
I just.. I've had
a lot going on.
Great. So, I guess
you don't care that
I finally figured out who
Larson was blackmailing.
What? You
did? Who?
Okay. So, I went
through all the
case files and in
two-thirds of them
the same judge
was on the bench.
My guess is he's
the dirty one.
Okay, who?
It's hard to believe
but in each case
it was distinguished
Judge Ryan Miller.
-You still there?
Yeah...
..and you think that
Miller killed Larson?
-Yeah. Well, I
guess he got
tired of having
Larson dogging him.
Miller wants to go all
the way to the top.
I doubt he wanted
Larson following him
and asking for more
and more money.
But this leaves us
with a problem because
no judge is gonna
issue a warrant
for Miller's
bank accounts,
not without
more proof.
What if we can link
him to the codes
in the
appointment book?
-I'm working on it
but I still haven't
been able to
figure it out.
I think I'm
gonna have to
look for that
mystery blonde again.
Maybe she has
something to do with it.
No! I mean, please,
just stay on the files.
I.. I may have
a way to get into
Judge Miller's
bank accounts.
-Yeah? What're
you going to do,
go over to his
house for dinner and
start hunting through
his personal papers?
Something
like that.
Just work on
deciphering those codes
and I'll talk
to you soon.
-Here we go.
-Great.
I'm starved.
I thought you said
you were hungry.
Yeah, sorry...
I must not be as
hungry as I thought.
Actually, can I
use your restroom?
If that's okay?
Of course. You
know where it is.
Annie? What
are you doing?
I know what
you did.
Annie, what are
you talking about?
The blackmail.
The payoffs.
Blackmail?
What are you-
Stop lying!
I know that you
fixed those cases
and that Larson was
blackmailing you
so you
killed him.
Killed him?
No, Annie.
I would never do
anything like that.
Annie, please.
Yes, he was
blackmailing me.
It was just a couple
of cases that I fixed
for the mayor's son
several years ago
but I was paying
Larson off.
I wasn't happy about it
but I could afford it.
Why would
I kill him?
I don't know.
Maybe because you're up
for an important new job
and Larson was
threatening to expose you.
I don't know
and I don't care
But I'm going
to the cops.
Annie, you can't.
You can't go without
revealing that you were
in Larson's
house that night.
If I go down,
so do you.
You stay away
from me.
What do you have
there? My files?
Are you crazy?
You're not getting
out of here with those.
I said stay
away from me.
Jesus. You
are crazy.
I trusted you!
I thought you were
my father's friend!
I drove over
here to save you
and you trashed
my place
to make it look like
Quentin Cruz did it.
No. I had nothing
to do with that.
Stop lying! I
know it was you!
And you knew I was at
Larson's the entire time
and you
acted surprised.
I'd like to think it
was because you wanted
to protect me, but
no, now knowing
that you just wanted
something on me.
You know what, it
doesn't matter anymore
I'm going to the cops
and turning myself in
right after I
turn you in!
Annie, I don't
have anything
because I
wasn't there!
Annie? Geez. Where
have you been?
I've been
worried about you.
I've been calling you
for the last two hours.
Are you okay?
-It's Miller. He
did everything -
the blackmail,
the murder...
-Shhh, it's
gonna be okay.
It's not.
Look, I've done some
pretty messed up things
and things you don't
even know anything about.
It's okay. Whatever
you did, it's okay.
WHAT THE
HELL, ANNIE!!!
I know I can't fix what
I did and I'm sorry.
Here's all
the evidence.
Miller's bank account
withdrawals, the gun...
you can check it against
the slugs that killed Larson.
-And I was about to
put Jimmy Perreira
away for this and
you said nothing!
Well, this is no
laughing matter, Annie.
This goes way
beyond impropriety.
I mean, we are talking
criminal charges here!
Starting with
obstruction of justice.
And let's just hope that
they don't slap you with
an accessory to
murder charge.
You know what I
have to do, Annie.
Because of your father
I will make the process
as easy as I
can make it
but there is only
so much I can do.
Now get the hell
out of my office.
And don't
come back!
I appreciate you
calling me over
to tell me this, Annie.
At least now we know
who the mystery
blonde is, right?
You'll be fine.
No, I'm
not fine.
I lost everything that
I ever worked for.
Not only may I
get disbarred but
I may also get slapped
with criminal charges!
Do you know what
that means for Crystal?
We'll get you
out of this mess.
Everyone's
behind you.
I know George was
hard on you today
but you know
he's on your side.
And who better to
have on your side
than the District
Attorney himself?
Is Crystal
already in bed?
No, um, she's
over at my dad's.
I didn't feel comfortable
with her staying here
ever since my
place got trashed.
About Judge Miller, I
spoke to George today
and it looks like
he's getting off
due to lack
of evidence.
What? Are kidding me?
Lack of evidence?
What about the
bank statements?
Or the gun?
I mean,
I can't believe they're
not pressing charges.
The gun
didn't match.
It didn't?
-Doesn't
sound like it.
And those withdrawals
he made every few months
he said he was buying a
lot of expensive artwork.
There's really no
definitive proof
linking him to the
blackmail or the murder.
You know, I wish we
could've figured out
what those
initials meant.
Then we could've linked
Judge Miller to Larson
to the blackmail,
and he wouldn't have
been able to wiggle
his way out of that one.
Yeah. But
we couldn't.
-You know...
I guarantee that there
are answers in that house.
-Yeah? Well, they're
releasing the house
back to Larson's
sister tomorrow and
you legally can't work the
case anymore anyway, so...
Yeah, I know.
Hey Annie, I really hate
to ask, but do you mind
taking care of
Hector for the night?
I have a date and you
know what a baby he is
about staying
home alone.
-No, of course.
Come on, Hector.
-Thanks. I
really owe you.
No, you don't.
Who's the date?
Uh... MYOB.
MYOB?
Mind Your
Own Business?
Remember
what I said:
it's all about
the acronyms?
Geez, Annie.. Seriously,
sure it's not a problem
'cause I might not
be home until late.
No, go and
have fun.
All right.
Bye, Hector.
-Say bye.
-I love you.
Let's go.
Come on.
Oh! Here
we go! Oh!
-Who was that?
It's Hector...
Hi, buddy.
I have a date and you
know what a baby he is
Who's the date?
MYOB. Mind Your
Own Business?
What?
TTYL. Talk
to you later.
It's all about the
acronyms, Annie.
Come on, get
with the ages!
-You okay?
Annie? Hello?
Oh, my gosh.
I think I figured out
what the initials could be.
What?
I have to go
to Larson's
-Whoa, no.
No way.
You can't go
back to that house.
I have to. I understand
if you don't want to
go with me but I have
to get in that house.
Come on, Hector,
let's go.
-Seriously? We
bring him too?
-Yeah, well, he's
gonna eat my shoes.
Let's go.
Okay. We're here.
So what exactly
are you looking for?
-Larson's books.
-I thought you already
checked those code books.
-I did, but I
didn't really
pay much attention
to the titles.
I have this
idea... Ah!
Dang, I could
have sworn...
-Find something?
-Yeah.
Here it is.
...so we won't have any
problem with his case?
No. No problem. It's
a felony gun charge.
I'll reduce it
to a misdemeanor.
But this is
the last time.
I can't believe
we got him.
Yeah. Judge Miller
won't be able to
weasel his way
out of that one.
How'd you know?
-I didn't.. not until
Danielle mentioned
the acronyms
thing,
the MYOB thing
or whatever it is
and then it just all
clicked that Larson
had to have hid
evidence in the house
in case the
authorities came.
What better place to
hide things than a book?
It's hidden
in plain sight.
You don't know
where it is
unless you know
where to look.
So the letters "TOC"
aren't necessarily
a person's
initials.
They could be an
acronym for anything
like the book title
Tropic of Cancer
by Henry Miller.
Wow. Looks like
you just found
the last piece of
evidence they need
to put the good
judge away.
Good work, Sagan.
-Thanks, Mark.
But where are
you going?
We still have
two more titles.
Um, I... S... SL.
Let's see...
SL.... SL..
oh, here it is!
Salem's Lot by
Stephen King.
Uh-huh.
All right. So that
means the King
would be the
name of the guy
Larson was
blackmailing, right?
-Yeah.
You know, there
used to be a very
distinguished judge
named Trevor King.
You think it
could be him?
Maybe...
Wow. Judge King.
Never would
have thought.
Okay. So what's the
other one? Um, S.M.
Here it is. Silas
Marner by George Eliot.
All right...
There's something
wrong with this,
it's not fitting in.
Goddamn!
-Oh, no. Can
your tech guys
find the information
or something?
Yeah, sure.
But for now let's
just get out of here.
-Okay. Yeah.
We finally
figured it out.
Finally be able
to prove it.
Ah. I wonder who
that third man or...
or woman is.
Well, the last name of the
person being blackmailed
would have to
be Eliot, right?
Like in
George Eliot.
-Right.
I don't know any judges
by that name, do you?
It doesn't need to be
a judge necessarily,
just someone who
could fix a case...
a judge, cop,
DA, anybody.
Yeah, then you're
probably right.
Wait, wasn't there a
lawyer named Eliot?
Yeah. A guy who wore
a bowtie and glasses.
-Maybe.
Uh, no, I think Eliot
was his first name.
-Uh, are
you sure?
-Not really.
Everything okay?
-Yeah. I just
think I may have
left my cell phone
at your place
so can we maybe
swing by for it?
-Yeah. Of course.
Man, I think my allergies
are starting to kick up.
You have allergies?
Yeah. Sometimes.
I don't have
my pills on me.
Can we just
drop him at home?
Come on, Hector.
Come on.
Gotta go in
here. Okay.
Come here.
Good boy. All right.
Go in. Good job.
Okay, while
you're finding your phone
I'm going to check
the directory and
try to figure out
who George Eliot is.
I won't be able to sleep
if I don't figure it out.
Wait.
You know, maybe we're
looking for a woman
since George Eliot
was a woman.
And George Eliot
was a pen name,
I'm pretty
sure. Right?
Yeah. I learned
it in school.
What was it? Um...
-I hate to ask, but
could you please
do something
about this dog?
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Come on
Hector. Let's go.
Go back to your
room. Let's go.
Go in, go in.
Good boy.
Um. Where
was I?
Pen name. Pen
name. Pen name.
Right, right, right.
Okay, pen name,
pen name...
You know what?
I bet it's in the
preface of Silas Marner.
Let's see.
Oh, yeah, here
it is. Okay.
So George Eliot is
the nom de plume
for Mary
Anne Evans.
Huh. The only
Evans I know is...
You...
Mark Evans.
You were the one being
blackmailed by Larson
and you
killed him?
-Guilty.
Oh, come on, Annie.
Larson was scum.
I did the world a favor
getting rid of him.
Why? Why did
you kill him?
It was one
case. One.
Early in my career, I
really needed the money
and his client was
willing to pay my price.
That case got thrown
out on a technicality.
Yeah, but after that
he thought he owned me.
He had a tape of me
accepting the bribe.
I just had to find
it and get rid of it.
And him.
That's what you
were looking for
the night that
you killed him.
You ransacked his
house.. the tape.
Yeah.
What can I say?
I don't like to be
owned by anyone.
And now thanks to you
I found the evidence.
-No.
-No more evidence.
You're psycho.
I can't believe I
didn't see it before.
I guess you
were too busy
trying to cover
your own ass.
Screw you.
-Ah, if only
there were time.
-So you knew I was
the mystery blonde
the whole time.
-Yeah.
It was really funny
how freaked out you got
when I took you
back to the jazz club,
how you tried to
change your appearance
so the waiter
wouldn't recognize you.
You should've
seen your face.
Thing was, I had
been following Larson
all night after
the charity event
and I saw you go
into his house..
and I saw
you leave.
And then I went
in and killed him
and I set it up to look
like Perreira did it.
Did you trash my place
to make it look like
Quentin did it?
Not Judge Miller?
-Yup. Guilty again.
Thing was, we were getting
way too close for comfort
with that whole
blackmail investigation
So I thought I'll just
throw a wrench in those
tracks and just derail
that train completely.
The problem was they
found Cruz's body
way too soon.
His body? You
killed Cruz too?
Yeah, I had to. After
I saw the photos he took
of you and Larson on
the night of the murder
I got worried he might
have photos of me too.
But, don't
worry, he didn't.
I made sure to search
his place really well
before I
killed him.
So what are you planning
on doing with me?
I think suicide
would make more sense.
Would you please stop
that dog from howling?
You know what?
maybe I should shoot-
-No! Stop! Okay.
Look, I'll just...
can I just take him
to Danielle's please.
-Are you serious?
Yes! It'll blow your
cover if you kill him
and if he keeps
barking, well,
the neighbors are
gonna call the cops.
Please.
Fine. Do not do
anything stupid.
I will be right
behind you.
Okay. Come
on, Hector.
I'm gonna put
him in here.
Come on, Hector.
Come on.
Good boy. Stay.
-All right.
Come on.
Let's go
over there.
Anti-depressants.
No one's gonna believe
I committed suicide.
They'll believe it.
Start swallowing.
I'm just... can I
write a note first?
Please.
Fine...
Go. Go.
Okay. That's enough.
Take the pills.
Please. Just...
Enough!!
Faster.
Mark.. please,
don't do this.
We still like each
other, right?
Are you serious?
You think I'm
gonna fall for that?
This dog...
You're
hurting me.
-Yeah, really?
No, no... don't.
You just need
to go, okay?
The cops will be
here any minute.
-I'm telling
the truth.
Danielle has a
motion-activated camera
and she probably saw
that I was in trouble
and called the
cops. Just go.
You are so full
of shit, Annie!
You should get a gun
for your own safety.
..made a point
to get one.
I keep it in my
nightstand and...
Open the
door, Annie!!
Are you okay?
Yeah...
I guess.
Is he dead?
How are
you feeling?
-Good, I guess.
'relieved' is probably
the better word.
Any issues with work
considering you were
there the night
Larson got killed?
Well, the
charges got dropped
so that's
something.
Mm-hmm. Shouldn't
you be happy?
I am. It's just..
I mean, that
job was everything
I ever dreamed
of, you know?
With everything I
witnessed, it's...
it's not what I
signed up for.
It's not the reason
I went to law school.
It's definitely
not the example
I want to set
for my daughter.
Well, I'll tell
you something.
There's no
better example
you could have set
for OUR little girl.
Yes, she's my
little girl too.
But you're the
greatest mom
she could ever
have had.
I know your dad
is proud of you.
Thanks.