The moment when someone
is consumed by their desire for revenge
is the moment they become a demon.
Now, with the traffic update.
There's a 2.5-kilometer traffic jam
at the Soma Interchange
on the Joban Expressway
heading towards Sendai.
The Shinjo bypass route is down
to one lane on the local roads.
This is due to the ongoing construction
in Ongyo Town, Shinjo City.
On the southbound lane
of the Kijo Hirai Route
heading towards Mahitotsu Town,
a car accident has caused
a 2.5-kilometer traffic jam
in Shinjo City's
Torakuma Town First District.
The estimated time
from the Ogura intersection
to the Shiroyama intersection is…
Hmm? Repeat that.
What was that?
W… Well, uh…
"Do… do you realize how much we've…
we've been… protecting all of you,
all of this time"?
Uh, that's what I told the head of
the dockworkers' union to his face.
Out of nowhere, he said,
"We can't take orders from you anymore."
So I asked, "What are you guys up to?"
Mm.
And then?
Um, and then he said,
"If you keep ordering us around
about the port area, the entire city,
uh, the entirety of Shinjo City,
its structure, its people,
its history will bare their fangs at you."
The "structure…"
Shinjo?
Yes.
Also, "people" and "history."
So, those "things"
will be baring their fangs?
Yes.
What's he mean by that, huh?
Honestly, I'm not quite sure
what he meant by that.
-Come kneel.
-Y… Yes, sir.
What the hell happened?
What made him think
he'd be able to talk to us like that?
-Uh, um…
-Huh?
Any idea?
Uh, I… I don't know, sir.
I think you need to do your job!
What the hell?
Let's go, boss.
-We're moving!
-Yes!
Upstairs!
What the hell happened here?
-Move!
-This way! Hurry!
Drive.
I said, drive!
Shit.
-What's going on?
-We need to go.
This way, sir.
Stop! Stop him!
Wait.
Please wait.
Please wait. Please wait.
Well done.
Hey, Sakata.
Maybe you shouldn't retire just yet.
I should've stopped you
from having a family.
I enjoyed working with you.
Oh!
It's Daddy!
Daddy's back.
Oh great!You are soaking wet!
Hey, Ryo, you're gonna be
all wet like Daddy. Whoa!
Oh no!
Yuck, hey! Stop it!
Normal people use umbrellas. Come here.
-Go wash up, okay?
-Mm-hmm.
Hold on, I'll be back.
Um, Ryo,
you grew a little bit, huh?
Mm, I think I grew a bunch!
A whole bunch, then?
Should we measure your height?
-Mm-hmm.
Here we go.
Okay. Right this way.
Let's wait for Daddy
to get out of the shower.
It's all done.
I'll look for a new job.
We'll celebrate.
With Ryo.
Mm-hmm.
Go away!
No!
Daddy.
Welcome home.
Who would've thought
a top-tier hitman
would have such a warm
little family at home?
So who are you?
We're going to be running
all the business in this city from now on.
The yakuza group,
who had control of the port area,
was a real thorn in our side.
So thank you for eliminating them for us.
But what I've heard,
Mr. Sakata,
you're walking away from this job
for the sake of your family.
Get off, asshole!
Doesn't bruising him clash
with the whole suicide scenario?
Nobody will notice a few bruises.
I'll handle it.
Good.
Daddy! Don't hurt my Daddy!
Ryo!
Just please…
please let my daughter leave, please!
As her mother, I'm begging.
Please. Just please let her leave.
I'm begging you,
please don't hurt my daughter!
-Time to shut up, "Mother."
-Please don't hurt my baby!
Mommy?
Please…
don't pull the trigger.
Don't do it.
Daddy…
Ryo! Run away!
Sakata.
They say in Shinjo,
a demon lays dormant.
And once every 50 years,
the demon awakens,
possessing someone in this city,
and goes on a killing spree.
Our purpose
is to protect this city from this demon
and that person.
Please understand,
Sakata.
One day…
I'll kill all of you.
I'll find all of you.
You will?
I'll be waiting.
Last night,
at around 11:00 p.m.,
a shooting incident occurred
at a residence in Shinjo City.
The suspect
has been identified as Sakata Shuhei,
the father of a family of three.
Authorities believe that
Sakata shot his wife, Aoi,
their five-year-old daughter, Ryo,
and subsequently turned
the gun on himself.
Neighbors reported hearing
several loud sounds, similar to gunshots,
one after another.
12 YEARS LATER
I'll call you later
and tell you everything.
I'll transfer the money once I get it.
I have to go.
I'll call again. Okay, bye.
Hey, let's go.
Just until
a little over a decade ago,
Shinjo City
was like any other regional city.
It struggled greatly
with financial difficulties
as well as a declining population.
Mayor Sunohara, tell me,
what is your perspective
on the changes that have taken place
from then to now?
Shinjo City stands
at a significant milestone in history.
This didn't come along by chance,
you must understand.
This was made possible
only through the absolute
hard work, perseverance, and courage
of its wonderful citizens
over the past century.
This started to become possible
when you, Mayor Sunohara,
took office as Shinjo City's mayor,
in my humble opinion.
Many would agree with me.
That's really overstating it.
Mm-hmm.
Now, we're expecting tourists
from all over Japan
and some even say from all over the world,
to gather with us all here in Shinjo City.
Is that correct?
Yes. That's right.
Esteemed media.
We are just six months away
from the opening
of the integrated resort, Mahoroba.
A theater, a shopping floor,
a multitude of restaurants,
international conference facilities,
a hotel, as well as
Japan's very first full-scale casino.
Every utopian desire
you can imagine can be achieved
here… at Mahoroba.
Do you have questions
for the mayor at this time?
Sir, you have a question?
I'm Kamiyama. I'm a journalist.
Shinjo City has seen a 15% increase
in missing persons in the last few years.
Among those is the leader in charge
of the construction's opposition.
Residents displaced due to redevelopment
have been quietly swept under the rug.
Can you keep your questions brief?
Please, sir.
Ah, apologies.
Shinjo City's transformation
into a better place was highlighted.
I'm wondering about
the increasing number of strange incidents
and unresolved cases.
I'd like to know.
Mayor Sunohara,
what are your thoughts on that?
You're bringing up things like
the increase in missing persons
and the opposing leader.
But where's your evidence?
When have you ever heard the police
make those statements?
-Well, the investigations I've conducted--
-Mr. Kamiyama.
Factual evidence matters here.
Facts only.
If your intention is to unfairly
harm this city's reputation,
I implore you.
Stop making false testimonies.
I've got it all right here--
I'm sure you're quite aware,
Mr. Kamiyama,
of the consequences of false rumors,
aren't you?
Do we have another question?
SHINJO INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX
Get out of here! No, it's not!
This place has changed quite a bit,
and it's only a decade.
Can you believe it?
Sorry… about this place.
We're working on finding
a safer place for you.
Look after him.
Yes, sir.
All right.
What the hell? Scars all over.
Mr. Sakata, time to eat.
Here you go.
He needs a lot of fresh air.
-Yes, sir.
-Take good care of him.
Huh?
Sakata!
Remember this?
You did this to me.
He can't comprehend what you're saying.
His body can't feel that!
Stop that!
Who the heck is
this crazy person?
Sakata!
Damn it!
So they're called "Kimen-gumi."
Yeah.
I've never seen them myself though.
And it was 12 years ago.
Kono-gumi,
the yakuza group you belonged to,
held the rights to the port,
but then, the Kimen-gumi wiped them out.
And ever since that time,
they've been controlling the rights
all around the port area.
That's including Mahoroba.
That's pretty much what happened.
Is that correct?
Yeah, that's right.
A hitman who was hired
by Kimen-gumi attacked us
by himself.
So the attack by the hitman hired
by Kimen-gumi happened 12 years ago,
coinciding to when Mahoroba
was granted its business license.
Which also coincides
to when Mayor Sunohara took office.
Kimen-gumi started out by doing business
in human trafficking and drugs,
so they were able to expand their power.
Trafficking humans?
Shinjo City may seem prosperous
on the surface,
but that's because of the Kimen-gumi.
Huh?
Oh, whoa, whoa.
What, what, what, what, what?
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
No, please.
I have a child to take care of.
I'll get out of here
the first thing tomorrow
and won't say anything.
I… I mean it. I swear!
A family.
All the more reason, right?
Place your finger right there.
I'll handle the rest.
Really?
That's impossible.
Sakata has a family that he loves.
He's leaving his job to take care of them,
so please let him go.
You promised me
that you wouldn't kill him!
What is it?
What?
Oh, Chief!
I wasn't expecting you.
What's going on?
Some drunk guy was picking a fight
in the neighborhood?
Yes, but… this guy here
was just released from a medical prison.
Seems like he might be
mixed up in something.
That's why we were called in
to deal with it.
You're working so hard.
It's getting pretty late, isn't it?
You deserve a break.
Head out and buy yourselves a drink.
Oh! We'll take you up on that.
-Let's get a drink. Thank you, sir.
-All right.
-Thank you, sir.
-Sure thing.
-See you tomorrow!
-Night!
-Where to?
-Someplace cheap.
It's been such a long time, Sakata.
Do you remember me?
Look at you.
It's such a pity
you've ended up as a vegetable.
That night,
when we realized
that you weren't dead yet,
our master ordered us to let you live
for some reason.
What a waste.
I should have just finished you off.
Twelve years.
Time has really flown by.
Have you seen it?
The incredible progress?
Shinjo City. Right?
That beautiful city
was nearly on the brink of death.
Do you remember, Sakata?
Ah, that's right.
I should take a picture.
I need to capture
the moment of your death.
Some resisted the changes.
Their feelings are understandable.
But what really matters
is having the courage
to overcome the fleeting grief.
Eat shit!
What the hell?
-Hands up!
-Ah! Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Uh… Oh, sir. So sorry.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm all right, yeah.
What happened?
Ah, well, he flailed and fell off the bed.
Sorry, can you two help
put Sakata back up there?
Y… Yes, sir.
Do you guys… Do you know each other?
Why do you ask?
Well, you just…
I guess
a lot just happened.
Okay, let's do this.
Sure.
Uh, I'll grab his legs.
-Okay, ready?
-Ready.
Lift.
-And swing.
-Swing.
Swing.
And… there.
Huh?
Leave the rest up to me.
I'll just say that Sakata grabbed the gun
and shot him in front of me.
Thanks.
So, what's exactly…
Oh, wait… What?
That's annoying.
You asshole!
Please move back. Move back.
You need to listen!
Seriously?
Daddy.
Please let my daughter leave.
Please.
I'm begging you!
-Start the car.
-Yes.
-Batteries. The batteries.
-They should be here.
-Okay.
Don't mix them.
And you forgot that one over there.
Got it.
Mr. Shinozuka has been killed.
What?
At the hospital.
By Sakata Shuhei.
-Sakata?
-Get over there!
-That Sakata?
-Don't be scared.
Right. That Sakata.
He was just released
from a medical prison.
He was stabbed and taken to the hospital.
Seems like
Mr. Shinozuka visited him and was killed.
How's our master?
Well…
he seemed like
he was pretty thrilled about it.
So what's your location?
At the port.
Shipping them out.
Oh, great.
The real question is,
how could he all of a sudden do all that
after being in a coma for 12 years?
Do we have any idea where he is?
Yeah.
We know where he is.
Right now, he's with Fujita.
FROM: UNKNOWN TO: AKIRA FUJITA
KILL HIM AND BRING ME HIS BODY
Sakata Shuhei.
That demon is back.
He's wreaking havoc
in our Shinjo City again.
Well…
it's time to eliminate him for good.
♪ The will of ♪
♪ The fierce gods ♪
♪ Is like the parting ♪
♪ Of the eight-fold clouds ♪
♪ That are in heaven ♪
SHINJO CLEANING SYSTEM
Okay. Sakata confirmed.
Good.
So you just take care of the body.
Let's go.
Start the car.
Yes. I'm sorry.
Don't make it obvious.
Yes, sir.
You're full of crap.
Three times a week? Where at?
Not a prostitute.
-What?
-She's not a prostitute.
-I bet you're lying.
-Why?
-She's your girlfriend?
-Yeah.
-No freaking way.
-Why's that so hard to believe?
'Cause it's you.
You're full of crap.
-For real.
-Yeah, right.
-This old man has a girl.
-For real?
-It's the truth.
-Show us, then.
Uh, fine, I'll show you guys later.
You're totally lying.
-Why would I lie about that?
-Yeah, right.
Huh?
-Who the hell's that?
-Whoa!
You are a traitor, Fujita!
Hey.
Son of a bitch! Hey!
Yeah?
It's not like you
to use such a forceful tactic, Ikkaku.
Were you watching the whole time?
I apologize.
I made you sacrifice your factory.
Don't worry about it.
I planted a bomb in case of emergencies.
I'm actually relieved that it did its job.
Great. Thank you.
It's nothing at all,
Master.
What?
What is it?
Impossible!
Excuse me a moment.
That was impressive.
Sakata…
I'm sorry…
about your wife and daughter.
I'm the one…
I betrayed you.
I deserve… to die.
Take care
of them all how you want--
Sakata.
Tell you what.
You have a narrow view of the world.
You have a tiny little point of focus,
not like me.
I almost feel sorry for you.
We, on the other hand,
are looking ahead
to the distant future of this city,
and, even more so, this country.
We plan ahead and do
what we need and--
Hit me as many times as you want!
Yeah! Sakata!
'Cause my loyalty is to our master.
I swore that I would devote my body
and my soul for a better world.
Can you even understand what that means?
Ah, Sakata!
MASTER
That's the person whom
you've probably been dying to meet.
Is that you, Sakata?
Finally, we speak.
Master,
I didn't say a single word.
Please be rest assured!
Not even once!
I believe you.
Thank you.
Sakata.
Stop murdering people for no reason.
We need Takemoto.
-He's the man next to you.
-No. Not my mask!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
If you don't stop
hunting people,
you'll end up killing
every single resident in Shinjo.
All these people need us.
The people of this city survive
on the money we make.
This world
is a bit more complex…
MAYOR RYU SUNOHARA
…than you could ever imagine.
Oh, by the way, Sakata,
uh, your daughter…
she's alive.
She's healthy and lives like
any ordinary high school girl.
Although…
I'm letting you know that if you keep
insisting on your petty revenge,
I'm sure your little pea brain can imagine
what'll happen to your daughter.
It was a miracle
that little girl survived.
Sakata.
It's Daddy!
Come on.
It's time to release me.
Or else, your precious, lovely daughter
will be just a piece of meat.
Ryo.
Last night in Shinjo City,
where preparations are steadily
in progress for next year's opening
of the integrated resort Mahoroba,
a series of terror attacks occurred.
Yesterday, at around
seven o'clock in the evening,
four police officers
were brutally murdered at…
Thank you for your patience.
It's very hot.
-Thank you. Looks good.
-Here's your miso.
…a bomb suddenly exploded
in the Shinjo Cleaning System factory,
destroying the building.
The suspect, identified as Sakata Shuhei,
was caught in the explosion
and has now been confirmed dead.
Police are currently investigating
the suspect's motive
that led to this terrible reign of terror.
I imagine that our residents
had an incredibly restless night
last night, didn't you?
We're collaborating along with the police
and have already begun analyzing
the presumed suspect's behavior
leading up to the events that occurred.
Shinjo City is up against
a tall and very thick wall,
the likes of which
it has… never faced before.
Good morning.
…a sign that this city of ours
will grow and transform…
Seems like
things are getting kinda crazy.
Mm-hmm.
…keep striving against
this predicament we are in…
Oh crap!
-Practice?
-Yeah.
Oh, hey.
You didn't come home last night, did you?
I put the leftovers in the fridge, okay?
Eat them when you get hungry.
Thank you.
INCOMING CALL
MASTER
-Can you do the dishes?
-Yeah.
Oh no. Oh no.
Have a safe trip, Ryo.
Thanks!
Hello?
When will you find Sakata?
I'm sorry.
All of the employees are out there
searching the neighborhood for him still.
It's quite possible that
he's already gone and left Shinjo.
Sakata is still in Shinjo now.
He won't leave the city.
Right.
-He'll be filled with rage…
-Good morning.
…when he finds out
that his own precious little daughter
is being kept alive
just for your pleasure.
I will get him. You'll see.
I'm counting on you.
SHINJO POLICE
-See you tomorrow.
-Yeah.
I'm finally home.
Why is that open?
Oh!
What?
Oh my God.
It's been quite a while, Mr. Sakata.
I ended up working
at a local police station.
I really went through a lot.
Honestly, it's not gonna be as easy for me
to give you useful information
like I used to.
But look at this person right here.
Look familiar? Right?
That's the man you killed at the hospital.
Mr. Shinozuka.
I worked
directly under that man back then.
He treated me
to a lot of meals and drinks.
It was great.
He was basically the best boss ever.
He had a lot of drive when he was young.
Always eager to protect the citizens.
We were pretty similar in that way.
Look at her.
This woman, she was his wife.
Hiromi.
She was a classy lady.
She was modest.
Didn't really match this guy.
Hey!
That one's private.
He snuck out in the middle of the night.
Apparently, he did this more than once,
and Hiromi got suspicious.
She figured he was cheating on her.
So I decided to take it upon myself
and hired a detective to tail him.
Use the evidence against him.
That way, Hiromi and I could be together.
Right here. Watch closely.
I'm scared.
-Please, please.
-I'm begging you.
Please don't kill us.
Bang.
Let me live! Let me live!
Guess what he did.
A few days after that incident,
Mr. Shinozuka gifted me this.
Look.
It's Hiromi's finger.
He gave me Hiromi's finger as a warning.
"Keep your hands off my wife."
The man's insane.
I mean, come on.
Ugh, the nail polish started peeling off.
Later on,
the detective I hired went missing too.
The guy in the video who got shot
was the CEO of the security company
that handled most of the public facilities
around this area at that time.
After he died,
a company by the name of Shinjo Security
came into the picture.
They became the security
in charge of Mahoroba.
Stop!
Hey! You can't go in there!
What the hell are you doing in my house?
You can have my money.
There's no need for violence, all right?
What have you done?
Huh? What'd you say?
To Ryo.
What have you done with her?
Get off, asshole!
What the hell?
Dad!
Ryo.
Ryo, are you all right?
Are you okay?
You're insane.
You rampaged at the hospital and factory,
and stormed into that building,
and came back with an arrow
sticking out of your shoulder.
You're out of your mind.
Don't hurt my Daddy!
All right. Here we go.
Okay.
Hang in there a little longer.
Okay? I'm pulling it out, okay?
One, two, three!
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
This will help.
I am not gonna let you die.
You saved my life once,
and now it's my turn to save yours.
Press down on it with this.
Who's calling me?
Hello, who is this?
This is
Officer Takigawa Yoshifumi, correct?
Yeah, who is this?
I've been told that
you used to work under Shinozuka.
Yeah, that's right.
Put Sakata on the phone.
You got a call.
How was it?
You haven't seen each other
for quite a while.
She's grown up well, hasn't she?
Pay attention.
If you want your daughter
to live much longer,
…come to Mahoroba.
I'll be waiting for you.
Don't be moving right now.
Wait, you're driving?
You're trying to drive?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't be reckless.
Careful! Be careful!
Whoa.
You've been living here?
Wow.
Whoa.
Delta 1. One car.
Shoot him!
Just fucking die!
Why don't you ever
just stay dead?
Why now? Why, after all this… time?
She's finally starting to look hot.
Enough!
Stop interfering!
Ryo
is mine.
She's mine.
I'm the one who raised,
clothed, and fed her.
Ryo!
Ryo.
Ryo, I'm your dad.
Do you remember me?
We meet again,
Sakata.
Since time immemorial,
this place has been known as
"The Town of Demonic Possession."
There's a demon in Shinjo.
Your school teach you that?
Or not?
I'm sorry.
Disregarding local legends
like this is… so disrespectful.
I'm going to have to reprimand
the Board of Education.
Actually,
we're on a similar page now, in a way.
To be completely honest,
I've never seen a demon myself.
It would be great if I could see one.
But somehow…
I'm not sure why you haven't
let the demon out yet.
Don't do it.
I'm begging you.
Well then, Sakata…
let's see the demon.
Ryo!
Run away!
Come on!
Does it hurt?
You poor thing.
Ryu.
This is your twin brother,
Jin.
Help each other out.
Be there for each other from now on.
Oh, whoa!
Look at that.
They're all dead.
All right, follow me.
My dad.
What? Hey, come back!
Do what you want. You're on your own.
They say in Shinjo,
a demon lays dormant.
And once every 50 years,
the demon awakens,
possessing someone in this city,
and goes on a killing spree.
Our purpose
is to protect this city
from this demon and that person.
It's time.
Bring out the demon.
Are you…
You are.
The demon…
of Shinjo.
I knew it.
Ryo!
Are you all right?
Thank goodness!
What?
Ryo!
What's wrong? What is it?
This isn't right.
What do you mean?
What's "not right?"
You tricked me.
You're the one. You killed my mother!
Ryo!
I'm your father.
Daddy?
You can't die, okay?
Ryo.
Your mother…
…I couldn't protect her.
I'm sorry.
Look how much you've grown.
I wish I could've been there.
Dad? No!
Please don't die!
Dad, you can't die.
Daddy.
I just got you back!
Daddy!
Please don't leave!
Turn all the lights on.
Coming through.
1 YEAR LATER
Mayor Sunohara,
congratulations on defeating your rivals
and winning reelection.
I'd like to address the citizens
and express my gratitude.
Last year,
a number of incidents occurred,
one after another.
Being mayor,
I feel somehow responsible for it all.
But Mayor Sunohara,
I have heard quite the opposite.
You put your life on the line and fought
and even sustained
a serious injury at the crime scene.
Right.
Perhaps it's because
I'm experienced in martial arts.
I didn't think twice about intervening.
I just…
And the opening of Mahoroba,
which had been delayed,
is going to have its grand opening.
Yes.
People will be coming from all over.
Shinjo City will be reborn
and represent Japan on the world stage.
It was
the dearest wish of all who perished
in that series of unfortunate events.