Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[powerful music playing]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
["Underestimated" playing]
♪ Flashbulbs fill the air ♪
♪ Frenzy fills the night ♪
♪ A lonely girl aswirl ♪
♪ Lost in blinding light ♪
♪ Living rather large ♪
♪ Yet feeling rather small ♪
♪ Step up to the mic ♪
♪ But you're not heard at all ♪
♪ Your prison has been built ♪
♪ Your downfall's been devised ♪
♪ Won't they be surprised? ♪
♪ When you're underestimated ♪
♪ They minimize your thoughts ♪
♪ They maximize your flaws ♪
♪ The trouble you can cause ♪
♪ When you're underestimated ♪
♪ Underestimated ♪
[woman] Lady Diana, is it?
His Royal Highness was wondering
where you went. He sent me to find you.
Oh, I just needed a little air. [chuckles]
-[woman chuckles]
-It's such a posh party.
I'm used to talking to five-year-olds.
What?
I'm a kindergarten helper.
I don't even know why I came.
So not my scene.
Well, His Royal Highness
is certainly glad you came.
I can tell he's taken
quite a liking to you.
Has he really?
When you come back in, I'll make sure
you two have some time alone.
Oh, thank you--
Mrs. Parker Bowles. But call me Camilla.
Charles and I are old chums.
♪ Nineteen and naive ♪
♪ Shy and insecure ♪
♪ Thinking princes never lie ♪
♪ Believing love is pure ♪
♪ Suddenly, a chance ♪
♪ Why not have a go? ♪
♪ The danger you don't see ♪
♪ The sorrow you don't know ♪
♪ So summon up your nerve ♪
♪ Fairy tales exist ♪
♪ And this one has a twist ♪
♪ 'Cause you're underestimated ♪
♪ You never once stood out ♪
♪ Hardly passed a test ♪
♪ Sometimes, though, it's best ♪
♪ To be underestimated ♪
[grand orchestral music playing]
["The Worst Job in England" playing]
♪ The headline of 1980 ♪
♪ "Playboy Prince Needs a Lady" ♪
♪ His mother grew quite upset ♪
♪ For he hadn't found her yet ♪
♪ It was fine when you were new ♪
♪ But, good God, you're 32 ♪
♪ What's a monarch to do? ♪
There must be someone appropriate,
Charles.
You'd be surprised by how few, Mummy.
We are in crisis!
Our popularity is declining,
the public trusts us less and less.
And you're saying that's my fault?
I'm saying your philandering
isn't helping matters!
♪ You're the heir to the British crown ♪
♪ You were bred to settle down ♪
♪ Our future queen should have no past ♪
♪ Find her, Charles, and find her fast ♪
♪ The boy just can't decide ♪
♪ I swear to God, I've tried ♪
♪ This is matricide ♪
Well, there is one possibility.
[ensemble] ♪ Daughter of a British earl ♪
The youngest Spencer daughter, Lady Diana.
♪ Lovely as an English pearl ♪
♪ Seemingly, the perfect girl ♪
♪ For the worst job
The worst job in England ♪
But didn't you used to court her sister?
Sarah, yes, until she started mouthing off
to the press about our relationship.
-How stupid of her.
-But Diana's different.
She's… very shy,
and I'm certain she'll be discreet.
But I'm not certain
this is what she wants.
♪ How could she not?
She'll be Britain's heart ♪
♪ Though time to time
She'll be torn apart ♪
♪ She'll have a staff all her own ♪
♪ And not another moment alone ♪
♪ She'll be celebrated
Our country's pride ♪
♪ And spend her life objectified ♪
♪ She'll have a place
In our history books ♪
♪ And forever she'll be judged
By her looks ♪
♪ Britain won't be mollified ♪
♪ Till we have a princess bride ♪
♪ A country unified ♪
♪ A girl like her is hard to find ♪
♪ A princess we could get behind ♪
♪ Then again, keep in mind ♪
♪ It's the worst job ♪
♪ The worst job ♪
♪ A royal couple casts a spell ♪
♪ A royal wedding serves us well ♪
♪ A fairy tale born in hell ♪
♪ She's the best girl ♪
♪ The best girl ♪
[ensemble] ♪ For the worst job ♪
♪ The worst job ♪
♪ It's the worst job ♪
♪ The worst job in England ♪
The Princess of Wales?
Me? Imagine. [chuckles]
I know. I'm as amazed as you are.
But I hear
the Queen's become your biggest advocate.
God, that woman hated me.
I don't know, though,
he seems rather melancholy.
[gasps] You've been hanging pictures
of Charlie boy on your wall
since you were 12.
He's your Barbara Cartland fantasy
come true.
All right, fine.
But do you think
he even likes me all that much?
[doorbell ringing]
As if that matters!
You meet all the requirements:
the right family, no pesky ex-boyfriends,
and, against all odds,
you're still a virgin.
In their eyes,
you're the perfect bloody princess.
This just came.
Yeah, I'd say he definitely likes you.
Bloody hell.
[phone ringing]
-The sod never gave me one of these.
-Well, that says a lot, doesn't it, Sarah?
-Hello?
-Ah, Lady Diana.
I was just checking if you received
the necklace I sent over?
Oh, yes, sir, and I…
I love it.
I thought you might wear it tonight.
Oh, and I hope you don't mind,
I've invited a few friends to join us.
Well of course not,
I enjoy all your friends.
And tell me, Diana,
do you enjoy Bach?
-Yes, sir, I adore Bach.
-[Sarah scoffs]
Splendid. Tonight, then.
He really does have
many appealing qualities.
Such as he's in line
to be the King of England?
She really couldn't be more charming.
-I hope she likes the necklace.
-Have you met Mrs. Parker Bowles yet?
I spent a lot of time
picking it out for her.
Yes, they're good friends. Why?
You'll see. I'll be borrowing this a lot.
-Enjoy Bach.
-And you truly think she may be the one?
[Camilla] I do.
I've really enjoyed getting to know her.
Her simplicity is so refreshing.
Not to mention, she's remarkably pretty.
And you know I've never cared about that.
-No, darling. I didn't mean--
-Someday I'll forgive you for that remark.
All right, forgiven.
Do you know what she suggested
we do this weekend?
-Hm?
-Go and see Dire Straits.
I hadn't the foggiest idea
what she was talking about.
-They're a pop band.
-Yes, I've been well educated on that now.
As well as on The Culture Club
and Duran Duran Duran.
-Oh, no, there are only two.
-Only two what?
Durans. It's simply Duran Dur--
Never mind.
I'm merely pointing out she has
the musical tastes of a teenage girl.
She is a teenage girl.
-So she's malleable.
-[Charles] Mm.
You and I would have
great influence over her.
Now go and grab her before she runs off
with a member of Air Supply! [chuckles]
Well, I've engaged us a cellist
for tonight. You will join us?
Charles, perhaps Diana would prefer
some time alone with you?
I was actually hoping you could come
and offer her, um, a spot of guidance.
[orchestral strings playing]
Wow.
[Charles] Diana.
-I'm so thrilled you could come tonight.
-Well, it was a tough decision.
It was either this
or Trivial Pursuit with my flatmates, so--
And you look absolutely stunning.
Really? I feel like
an overdressed Barbie doll.
-Oh, no--
-Oh, that necklace is perfection!
Camilla?
-Oh, I didn't realize you'd be here.
-[Camilla chuckles]
Then again, you seem to pop up everywhere.
My dear, may I offer a spot of advice?
You see, I feel as if I've become
a bit of a big sister to you.
Well, I already have two big sisters,
so I actually don't need another.
Well, this, uh, situation you're in,
the favored girl of the prince,
it's rather unique.
So do try to be as clever
as you can about it, all right?
-Charles likes clever girls.
-[Charles] Ladies?
Ah.
Oh, here! A little thank-you gift.
Uh, for me?
You seem surprised.
Don't girls usually give you gifts?
No. Never.
Cuff links. How lovely.
-I'm sure you have dozens.
-Actually, hundreds.
Well, I saved the receipt, so--
-Oh. [clears throat]
-[applause]
That's Mstislav Rostropovich.
He is, in my layman's opinion,
the greatest cellist in the world today.
-["This Is How People Dance" playing]
-You see? It's sublime, darling, isn't it?
♪ Soak it in, feel the strings ♪
♪ Hear the sound of angels' wings ♪
♪ This is heaven's music
Fit for kings ♪
♪ The Russian plays on and on ♪
♪ Like an endless telethon ♪
♪ How I wish that he were Elton John ♪
Charles likes clever girls.
♪ All right, I'm no intellect ♪
♪ But maybe there's a discotheque ♪
♪ Where the prince could hear some Prince
And we'd all get Funkadelic ♪
♪ Then again, don't create a scene ♪
♪ You're auditioning to be his queen ♪
♪ And if Queen were playing now
Freddie Mercury would slay it ♪
♪ This is how your people
This is how your people dance! ♪
♪ Pet Shop Boys!
C'mon, c'mon, make some noise! ♪
♪ This is how your people
This is how your people dance! ♪
♪ Rave and rant!
Give it up for Adam Ant! ♪
-Where are you, Diana?
-Huh?
You seem a million miles away.
The music is transporting me.
♪ I guess it's the royal drill ♪
♪ To smile a lot and sit still ♪
♪ Though I don't know why she's here
And I'd really like to sock her ♪
♪ And then there's Charles
Who's happy when ♪
♪ He hears music by dead white men ♪
♪ Perhaps his girl
Can turn him into a rocker ♪
♪ This is how your people
This is how your people dance! ♪
♪ Young and free
Everything I wanna be ♪
♪ This is how your people
This is how your people… ♪
♪ Perhaps this girl
Can turn him into a rocker ♪
♪ Young and free
Everything you wanna be ♪
♪ Feel the groove
Even royals need to move ♪
♪ This is how your people
This is how your people ♪
♪ This is how your happy goddamn
Bloody people dance! ♪
[orchestral cello music playing]
♪ She has youth
She looks the part ♪
♪ To have such charm is quite an art ♪
♪ And all you have is the prince's heart ♪
♪ She is what the people ♪
♪ She is what the people want ♪
["Snap, Click" playing]
Excuse me,
how about a quick snap there, luv?
Of me? Why?
You're that new friend
of the prince, ain't ya?
Come on, luv. One shot.
♪ Snap, click
Snap, click, give a smile ♪
♪ The prince will enjoy you
At least for a while ♪
♪ Snap, click
Snap, click, Lady Di ♪
♪ Damn, I see why
You caught Charlie's eye ♪
Cheers.
♪ Snap, click
Snap, click, just one peek ♪
♪ You're the hottest one
He's had all week ♪
♪ Snap, click
Snap, click, have a blast ♪
♪ God only knows how long you will last
Snap, click ♪
Thank you, that's enough now.
♪ Ain't nothin' like the hunt
Ain't nothin' like the thrill ♪
♪ Find the right bird
Then go in for the kill ♪
♪ Better than a Guinness
Better than a wank ♪
♪ Snatch a few pics
It's money in the bank ♪
♪ Honey, you are money in the bank ♪
Lady Diana Spencer
calling again for the prince.
I called earlier, so--
All right, yes, but please tell him
I really need to speak with him,
please. I--
♪ She teaches kindergarten ♪
♪ She really ain't that bright ♪
♪ I hear she's still a virgin ♪
♪ So Charlie's got it right ♪
♪ Charlie's got it right ♪
Please, sod off!
♪ Snap, click
Snap, click, ain't this rich? ♪
♪ The kindergarten teacher
Is also a bitch! ♪
♪ Come on
Come on, just one go ♪
♪ Then we'll go away for an hour or so ♪
♪ Hey, why can't you see
That we're your friends? ♪
♪ Baby, our love is real ♪
♪ We know that your aim is
To be friggin' famous! ♪
♪ Well, honey, we are part of the deal! ♪
♪ Snap, click
Snap, click, earn your pay ♪
♪ All you gotta do is all that we say ♪
♪ Front page
Front page, you're the lead ♪
♪ Another hundred pictures
Is all that we need ♪
♪ We provide a public service ♪
♪ We do it every day ♪
♪ And if you think we're vultures ♪
♪ We dare you ♪
♪ To look away! ♪
-♪ Snap, click, snap, click! ♪
♪ Snap, click! ♪
-Charles, this has gone far enough.
-Are you suggesting it's my fault, Mummy?
I'm suggesting it's time
you make up your mind!
-The way the press is hounding her…
-I am fond of Lady Diana.
I am, but…
what if there were someone else?
Isn't this "someone else" already married?
Right. Of course, but--
Lady Diana and I,
we've only been out a dozen times or so,
and we don't have much in common.
You're the Prince of Wales.
You don't have much
in common with anybody.
-["Whatever Love Means Anyway" playing]
-But what if I'm simply not certain?
I mean, were you certain when you married?
Well, uh…
[sighs]
Quite.
♪ He got down on one knee ♪
♪ Yes, he did it properly, and, well ♪
♪ That was it for me ♪
♪ But love evolves and bends and… ♪
♪ Men take other friends ♪
♪ It doesn't mean devotion ends ♪
♪ Love's not what you expect ♪
♪ Love rarely is direct ♪
♪ Love changes every day ♪
Well…
♪ Whatever love means anyway ♪
Diana, it's time
we have a serious discussion.
-My cuff links.
-[Charles] Hmm?
The ones I gave you, you're wearing them.
Yes, uh, they're now my favorite pair.
I was so touched by
your kindness and your generosity and…
-[Diana titters]
-And, I've grown quite fond of you.
But I'm not even sure
if any of this is what you want.
Sir, my mother deserted
our family when I was five.
Ran off with her boyfriend.
Horrible, really,
so I spent the next few years
reading nothing but romance novels,
mostly by Barbara Cartland.
[both chuckle]
She's written, like, 400 books,
and I'll argue they're all brilliant
because they're all about the same thing.
Finding the one person
you're meant to be with.
Before you snicker at me again,
you should know
that when my father remarried,
he married her daughter.
So Barbara Cartland
is now my step-grandmother.
[both chuckle]
I met her when I was 14.
[fantastical music playing]
Darling Diana!
Barbara Cartland, oh, just look at you!
I know, I'm delicious.
Your stories are the only ones I read!
How many are true?
True? Oh, no.
♪ My books are spry with fantasy ♪
♪ Their endings tie up happily ♪
♪ It's what we long for in our youth ♪
♪ But here's the honest truth ♪
♪ Men are liars and dire cheaters ♪
♪ Passion expires and true love teeters ♪
♪ So don't be blinded by good looks ♪
And most of all, read other books.
-[Charles chuckles]
-And I did read other books.
But she makes you believe love can
overcome whatever problems you have and…
If my parents
had just believed that fantasy,
maybe they'd still be together.
So that's what I want.
A fantasy?
[Diana] No. [chuckles]
[exhales] Just the possibility of it.
Lady Diana…
you are remarkable.
So, then…
♪ I could get down on one knee ♪
♪ And do it properly ♪
♪ And ask you to marry me ♪
Did you just-- Is this a proposal?
Well, it is.
Oh, my God.
♪ I'd guard you from that bloody mess ♪
♪ Known as the British press ♪
♪ Well, that's it… more or less ♪
What a terrible proposal.
♪ And though you're just-- ♪
-Nineteen.
-Thank you.
♪ Someday you'll be crowned Queen ♪
♪ The loveliest queen we've ever seen ♪
♪ Though it happened fast ♪
♪ This feeling unsurpassed ♪
♪ Our affection grows ♪
♪ Day by day ♪
♪ A fairy tale formalized ♪
♪ A nation mesmerized ♪
♪ Let's put our fantasy ♪
♪ On full display ♪
And you're truly in love with me?
I am.
♪ Whatever love means anyway ♪
Oh, sir.
[ensemble] ♪ Whatever love means anyway ♪
♪ Anyway ♪
♪ Say the word, and I'll stop it now ♪
♪ But the girl is quite the "wow" ♪
♪ I'm sure that she will satisfy ♪
And we're certain?
♪ We found one young and pure ♪
♪ Somehow, you will endure ♪
♪ When you get bored, just come on by ♪
♪ You do your duty
For your country and your honor ♪
-♪ I often think happiness is a luxury ♪
♪ Was there ever ♪
♪ A greater tabloid tale? ♪
♪ She was common, she was dim ♪
-♪ She was far from worthy of him ♪
-[camera shutter clicking]
♪ A fairy tale about to turn grim ♪
♪ Diana, Diana ♪
I've been assigned to take care of you,
m'lady, if you'll come with me?
No, I must go back to my flat.
Impossible.
It's engulfed in photographers.
♪ The Queen and prince decree ♪
♪ That you must follow me ♪
♪ We'll keep the outside world at bay ♪
But my kindergarten class,
I didn't even say goodbye.
♪ Behind these noble gates ♪
♪ Your palace staff awaits ♪
♪ For safety's sake, let's lock you away ♪
♪ A fairy tale formalized ♪
♪ A nation mesmerized ♪
♪ Could they be more in love
Than they are today? ♪
-♪ Love took us by surprise ♪
-♪ You do your duty for your country ♪
-♪ Happiness in disguise ♪
-♪ Duty for your country and your honor ♪
♪ Could they be more in love
Than they are today? ♪
-[gates clatter shut]
-♪ Whatever love means ♪
♪ Whatever love means ♪
♪ Anyway ♪
♪ So love evolves and bends ♪
♪ And men take other friends ♪
-♪ It doesn't mean devotion ends ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
I can't go through with it, Sarah.
Don't be daft, you're walking
down the aisle in two hours.
But you were right
about that Camilla woman.
Well, it's too late now.
Your face is already on all the mugs
and the tea towels.
You're a national holiday.
That dress doesn't lack volume.
[gasps] Oh, God, I'll look enormous!
Hey, now.
["I Will" playing]
Listen to your sister.
Every girl wanted him,
but you're the one who nabbed him.
And how many people's childhood dreams
actually come true? [snickers]
♪ Don't give in to your doubts ♪
♪ They'll find out who you are ♪
♪ An unknown nervous girl ♪
♪ How did she get this far? ♪
♪ So push those nerves aside ♪
♪ Time to get a grip ♪
♪ Just hold your head up high ♪
♪ And pray that you don't trip ♪
♪ I will make him love me ♪
♪ I will prove that I can ♪
♪ And I will be all that they require ♪
♪ All that they require and demand ♪
♪ I will ♪
♪ Try my very best
As I stumble in this dress ♪
♪ I will ♪
♪ Represent the Crown
No time now to back down ♪
♪ A bad time to back down ♪
♪ I will ♪
♪ How did you become ♪
♪ This global fantasy? ♪
♪ No pressure, none at all ♪
♪ I'll plead insanity ♪
♪ I will ♪
♪ Make them love me ♪
♪ Prove that I can ♪
♪ And I will be more than is expected ♪
♪ More than is expected
Here I stand ♪
-♪ I will ♪
♪ Rise above their fears
Deserve their deafening cheers ♪
-♪ I will ♪
♪ Be all they've dreamt and more ♪
♪ Somehow better than before ♪
♪ I'll be better than before ♪
[ensemble] ♪ I will ♪
♪ I will ♪
I will.
[ensemble] ♪ I will ♪
♪ I will ♪
I will.
[ensemble] ♪ I… ♪
♪ Will ♪
Darling, are you okay?
Of course.
Seems as if your friend
had a memorable wedding.
[Camilla chuckles] Hm.
Well, for what it's worth, I thought
you were a far more beautiful bride.
[scoffs]
And now you've gone completely mad.
-[both chuckle]
-On the contrary.
♪ We will always have each other ♪
♪ And we will make this marriage work ♪
♪ And we know it's surely for the best ♪
♪ Yes, I'd say it's for the best ♪
-[Diana] Our first official appearance?
-A week on Sunday, yes.
-Are you certain I'm ready, Mummy?
-Now, now, it's all set.
-We shall present you in Wales.
-But what exactly will be expected of me?
No need to worry, darling,
all you have to do is follow by my side.
But I feel as if I received more training
when I was a preschool helper.
No training in the world
can prepare you for what's in store.
Darling, we'll simply
greet our subjects, shake their hands--
Wear gloves.
But what on earth do I say to them?
[speaking Welsh]
What?
It's Welsh for,
"I'm happy to be here. Thank you."
-[Queen chuckles]
-So, then…
♪ All will be fine
Just move down the line ♪
♪ Excessive display of emotion is rude ♪
-♪ Show your smile-- ♪
-♪ But just for a while ♪
I've never been so nervous.
♪ Never let any feelings intrude ♪
♪ So go with Windsor fortitude ♪
I will try my very best.
And I'm so sorry if I disappoint you.
Charles, this will be her first time
interacting with a crowd.
-Stay close to her, will you?
-Yes, of course, Mummy.
["The World Fell in Love" playing]
♪ Came out here to bitch and gripe ♪
♪ Guarantee she ain't my type ♪
♪ Ain't no way she'll match the hype ♪
-♪ I don't know, she seems real nice ♪
-[man laughs]
♪ Want to bet she's cold as ice? ♪
♪ Let's go home ♪
♪ That's good advice ♪
Now, you remember
the Welsh lesson I gave you?
Not a word.
Hello.
I'm Diana.
♪ I hardly know what I'm doing ♪
♪ I'm just glad to be with you ♪
♪ Sharing handshakes, hearing stories ♪
♪ What a lovely thing to do ♪
♪ But I'm truly no one special ♪
♪ In fact, I'm less than what I seem ♪
-♪ Years of royals ♪
-♪ So standoffish ♪
-♪ Who'd have thought? ♪
-♪ Something new ♪
♪ Over here, Princess Di
I want to catch your eye ♪
♪ Take this rose, this bouquet ♪
♪ Diana, make my day ♪
♪ Won't you please take my hand?
I am now your biggest fan ♪
♪ With no bother and no fuss ♪
♪ It's like she's one of us! ♪
♪ Pretty as we've ever seen ♪
♪ Like a living magazine! ♪
♪ We'll be proud to call you Queen ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ And just like that ♪
♪ They fell in love ♪
♪ All of Wales ♪
♪ They fell in love ♪
-♪ And with joy ♪
-[ensemble] ♪ And with joy ♪
[Charles] ♪ Undreamed of ♪
♪ All of Wales ♪
♪ They fell in love ♪
Her press coverage is extraordinary.
♪ She hardly knows what she's doing ♪
♪ But she does it awfully well ♪
-♪ She's a natural ♪
-♪ They adore her ♪
As for me?
Hard to tell.
I was wondering if some of you
might say hello to my husband.
He adores Wales.
[crowd clamoring]
♪ I was crowned in this country ♪
♪ How that day lives in me ♪
♪ Here I flourished, here my heart lies ♪
♪ Here in Wales, I feel most free ♪
♪ Charlie, thanks for all you do ♪
♪ But right now
You're blocking our view! ♪
♪ Step aside, let the lady through ♪
♪ I learned their language
Served their country ♪
♪ Over here, Princess Di ♪
♪ Loved my subjects, played my part ♪
♪ I want to catch your eye ♪
♪ Then a preschool helper
With no training ♪
♪ Steals away their heart! ♪
♪ And the world ♪
-♪ The whole world ♪
♪ We fell in love! ♪
Darling, they're simply fascinated
with her because she's new.
Not to mention, she's a pretty young girl
with the hair and clothes, and you're a…
I'm what?
A man, in a suit.
A very handsome man in a suit,
but nevertheless--
So I should simply hover nearby
and hold her handbag?
Well, wasn't that the goal?
We should be happy!
Darling, we've succeeded
beyond our wildest imaginations.
I'm beginning to think she may be
the best thing that's happened to you.
[scoffs] And where do you fit in, then?
[snickers] Funny, my husband
recently inquired about that too.
So, I've been wondering,
are you still seeing your friend?
He calls you my friend.
Yes.
I just hope you're aware of the risks now.
I can't imagine his wife
or the Queen would be too happy about it.
And are you still seeing your friend?
Or should I say "friends"?
[chuckles] Actually, no.
No?
Oh, well… Charles and I, is it a problem?
It just seems at some point, perhaps,
we should start paying
more attention to each other.
[regimental music playing]
-We can't continue on as we've been.
-What do you mean?
[ensemble] ♪ You do your duty
For your country and your honor ♪
You're now married
to the most beloved woman in England.
If we were ever found out,
I would be the most despised.
[ensemble] ♪ You do your duty
For your country and your honor ♪
I don't think I could stand that.
Go to your wife.
We both have marriages
we need to attend to.
[Diana] Charles?
I have something to tell you.
-Charles?
-Hmm?
-Are you all right?
-What?
Uh, yes, of course.
-You seem distracted.
-I've had much on my mind of late.
-Well, I have something to tell you.
-[Charles] This isn't a good time.
-Can we speak later?
-It's good news, I think.
Christ! All right.
You're not still upset?
-About that newspaper coverage?
-[Charles] Of course not.
I'm simply trying to do
what everyone expects of me.
It's rather difficult, isn't it?
What is it you wanted?!
-If you're in another one of your moods--
-What is it, Diana?
["Happiness" playing]
♪ A baby, Charles ♪
What?
♪ I'm going to have your baby, Charles ♪
-A baby?
-Yes.
So quickly?
♪ Are you happy, Charles? ♪
♪ Please tell me
That you're happy, Charles ♪
Well,
I have always dreamed of having a girl,
but it would be quite helpful
if this first one were a boy.
[giggles]
I will do my very best.
I love you.
What?
I do.
Love you.
And we married so quickly.
So perhaps this
is a proper beginning for us.
And Mrs. Parker Bowles, whatever we had…
I've ended it.
[chuckles] A baby?!
Oh God!
[music continues]
♪ William, my dear little prize ♪
♪ It stops me to look in your eyes ♪
♪ My gorgeous heir to the throne ♪
♪ Do I dare call you my own? ♪
♪ To me, you're much more than an heir ♪
♪ You're simply my heart, lying there ♪
♪ And can't we forever be ♪
♪ This happy new family? ♪
♪ Happiness ♪
♪ You find the way to face the day
When you find happiness ♪
[gasps]
♪ Darling, I'm holding our son ♪
♪ So let me say, jolly well done ♪
♪ Never thought I was the type to cry ♪
♪ Or sing a sweet lullaby ♪
-♪ Happiness ♪
♪ After all we've both been through ♪
♪ Have we found happiness? ♪
[Diana inhales sharply]
[servant] Sir?
It's Mrs. Parker Bowles.
Should I tell her
you're otherwise engaged, sir?
Charles?
How have you been?
All is well, I suppose.
Though my husband is being stationed
overseas more and more. And you?
William brings me
an impossible sense of joy.
And Diana and I are getting along
better than ever.
But it is lovely to hear your voice.
Is it?
[inhales] ♪ I will always love you ♪
♪ You still haunt my dreams ♪
♪ And we will be there for each other ♪
♪ Always be there for each other ♪
-Is that…?
-It was a phone conversation, that is all.
-You're still in love with her?
-I am not.
-But you--
-You misunderstood! That is all.
-You just said you were in love with her!
-I said nothing of the kind!
Now if you don't mind,
I'd rather not have this conversation
again and again!
["Simply Breathe" playing]
♪ Stop ♪
♪ Breathe ♪
♪ I feel so unprotected ♪
♪ Hopes ♪
♪ Fade ♪
♪ This is not what I expected ♪
♪ A princess unperfected ♪
♪ If no one's listening ♪
♪ A husband barely there ♪
♪ Can't grab a gasp of air ♪
♪ Don't forget this was your dream ♪
♪ So simply breathe ♪
[ensemble] ♪ Simply breathe ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
She hardly eats.
Her mood changes by the minute.
She's even been
threatening to harm herself.
It's postpartum depression.
I'm afraid it's grown quite severe.
She needs rest, as well as
the full support of those around her.
Especially from His Royal Highness.
Well, good luck with that.
-And when she has her next child?
-It will likely grow worse.
[ensemble] ♪ Simply, simply ♪
♪ Simply breathe ♪
♪ Harry, my ginger-haired son ♪
♪ You'll always be second to none ♪
♪ Perhaps, at last, finally ♪
♪ Your dad will be so proud of me ♪
Another boy, then. Seems
you've ignored my request for a girl.
So now our own son
isn't good enough for you?
Christ, Diana, don't overreact to a joke.
You haven't made a joke since I met you.
Why must every conversation we have
turn into a bloody argument?
She's still in our marriage.
She will always be in our marriage.
Is it your intention
to drive me back to her?
Because that is exactly what you're doing!
♪ Wounds heal ♪
♪ But scars can last forever ♪
♪ Hearts bend ♪
♪ Break, and burst, and sever ♪
♪ A dangerous endeavor ♪
♪ Avoid the flashing glare ♪
♪ Undone yet undeterred ♪
♪ Defy this life absurd ♪
♪ I think it's time to change your dream ♪
♪ So simply breathe ♪
♪ I could use a prince
To save me from my prince ♪
♪ How does one survive
When it hurts to be alive? ♪
-[glass shattering]
-[Diana gasps]
♪ Wounds heal ♪
♪ But scars can last forever ♪
♪ And you can't breathe ♪
-[ensemble] ♪ Breathe ♪
-♪ Breathe ♪
♪ Simply breathe ♪
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Look, please don't fuss over me.
-Are you sure the boys are all right?
-They know you're unwell, that's all.
You ask me, you're just doing all this
to get your husband's attention.
I say you cut your losses and drop
the sod. That's how I handled him.
You did not, he dropped you.
Please, I already had
one foot out of the door.
And let's face it, you know
all they really wanted from you.
A baby prince.
And you've already popped out
a perfectly good pair.
-Pop, pop.
-[chuckles]
-You've done your duty, now move on.
-Move on?
Do you think I can simply pack up
my tiaras and rent a flat in Kensington?
The country would go mad.
The Queen would have to approve,
good luck with that.
-And perhaps…
-Perhaps?
-Perhaps I still love him.
-After the way he's treated you?
M'lady, I think Her Royal Highness
needs some rest now.
She's rested long enough. I say
Her Royal Highness gets up and fights.
If only
he wasn't still seeing the Rottweiler.
She calls Camilla
"the Rottweiler," I just love that.
You know what the latest talk is?
That you've gone completely mad.
-I must reiterate my plea for rest.
-She should know this.
They're saying you're officially bonkers.
Unfit to be seen in public.
You have got to get out there
and show them otherwise.
Once they think
you're another unhinged woman
driven mad by her unfaithful--
Charles.
I hope you don't mind.
Hello, Sarah. [clears throat]
You just…
be good to yourself. Okay?
I already had one foot out of the door.
It's lovely of you to come, Charles.
Of course. I'm--
My God, Diana!
You know, the first time that you…
harmed yourself, I thought,
"Well, merely an aberration."
But then the second time,
and the third, and now--
Sarah thinks I do it
to get your attention.
Is that true?
How are the boys?
I told them you're anxious to see them
as soon as you're recovered.
Thank you.
I'm really glad you're here.
Listen.
What we need to do is come together and…
And get you well,
and somehow make this marriage work.
-May we at least agree on that?
-Yes, of course.
It's grand to hear you say so.
Well, is there anything
that will lift your spirits, then?
Yes.
When we do our walkabouts,
people often tell me their troubles.
I don't even ask. They just… volunteer.
And I know there's so much
I can do for them. So…
I'd like to get involved
in more charities.
[chuckles] Fine, we'll arrange
a few more appearances.
No, more than appearances,
and more than a few.
-You're truly not well enough.
-But I would be, if you'd just let me try.
["She Moves
in the Most Modern Ways" playing]
My mother generates much goodwill
when she goes out among the people.
But she likes to do things her way.
And I'd like to do things mine.
♪ A monarch must give, but not too much ♪
♪ There's danger
When one shares one's access ♪
♪ One's comfort and one's touch ♪
♪ Talking to a child on bended knee ♪
♪ Her smile holds the truth ♪
♪ She's all the things that I cannot be ♪
♪ She enters with style ♪
♪ Then moves with such ease ♪
♪ Anxious to connect ♪
♪ And desperate to please ♪
♪ She shares all her feelings
And deflects all their praise ♪
♪ She moves in the most modern ways ♪
This amazing new facility
for cancer care is a true inspiration.
And I can't wait to visit
each and every one of you.
-Just pace yourself, darling.
-Why?
♪ No matter the cause ♪
♪ She moves with such skill ♪
♪ She seems to know secrets
Which I never will ♪
♪ She stands still and listens
For what seems like days ♪
♪ She moves in the most modern ways ♪
Isn't it marvelous, darling?
They view me as one of them!
But the point of our existence
is that we're not one of them.
We are symbols, if you will.
Who the bloody hell wants to be a symbol?
We represent their aspirations.
So what you're doing, darling,
is coming across as a bit, rather, well--
-What?
-Common.
When His Royal Highness feels so strongly,
I find it best to listen to him.
Why? When I'm just
beginning to feel as if I matter.
Paul, we have the event for
the Royal Ballet coming up, don't we?
Always one of your favorites.
Well, I'd like to be
of greater help this year.
You could give a speech
before the performance.
They'd adore that!
No, I've given enough speeches.
Let's show them what else I can do.
["She Moves in The Most Modern Ways"
continues playing]
♪ We wear our fancy jewels
Escort our fancy spouse ♪
♪ Thanks to Princess Di
Another sold-out house ♪
♪ The Royal Ballet Gala ♪
♪ Rich in romance ♪
And do you know
the whereabouts of my wife?
I believe
she's still using the facilities, sir.
A fine way to treat her husband.
♪ We sit here in the dark
None of us are wise ♪
♪ In about a minute
We're in for a surprise ♪
And now, to conclude
the Royal Ballet Christmas Gala,
please welcome one of our brightest stars.
[applause]
And the most special of guests.
[applause continues]
♪ There she was, unconfined
Everybody lost their minds ♪
♪ Once again, quite the scene
Unbefitting of a queen ♪
♪ Every move was on point
She electrified the joint ♪
♪ Every step, every twirl
What's the matter with this girl?! ♪
[ensemble]
♪ She moves in the most modern ways ♪
♪ Moves in the most modern ♪
♪ She moves in the most ♪
♪ Modern ways ♪
-[cheering and applause]
-[indistinct chatter]
Would you please give us some privacy?
["The Rage" playing]
Everyone leave, now.
A public dance performance
by the Princess of Wales?
-Have you lost your bloody mind?
-It was a present, I did it for you.
-This was entirely about you!
-No!
To get your picture
in the bloody paper again!
No, to make you proud of me.
You live inside a photograph!
-Listen to me, Charles, I--
-I have finished listening!
♪ You speak and you speak
With the world at your feet ♪
♪ As you soak in every last cheer ♪
That's not true!
♪ Stay still and listen to your husband
For once-- the man who put you here! ♪
♪ You demean us all, Diana ♪
♪ Each time you cause a scene ♪
♪ Have you forgotten, Diana? ♪
♪ You're in line to be Queen ♪
Charles, please calm down.
♪ A gala affair
And look who's there, Diana! ♪
♪ The cameras whir and--
"Hey, it's her! Diana!" ♪
♪ You only enter center stage ♪
♪ There's more to life
Than the bloody front page! ♪
♪ Diana ♪
I just want you to notice me
how you notice Mrs. Parker Bowles.
What?
I know you still see her.
♪ There are centuries
And centuries of protocol ♪
♪ The damage you've done
By ignoring it all ♪
♪ Don't blame me for your antics! ♪
♪ Don't blame me for this dance ♪
♪ I'm through with giving you
One more chance! ♪
♪ If my heart has strayed, Diana ♪
♪ If our marriage has come to a halt ♪
♪ You never once obeyed, Diana ♪
♪ God damn it, it's all your fault! ♪
How is it my fault?
♪ How 'bout for a start
Don't act like a tart, Diana! ♪
♪ Stop being a martyr!
Why can't you be smarter, Diana? ♪
♪ With all you do
How can I be proud of you? ♪
♪ When any fool can see ♪
♪ Your life's greatest achievement?
You married me! ♪
♪ You married me! ♪
♪ All you've ever done
You married me! ♪
♪ You married me
You married ♪
♪ All you've ever done ♪
♪ Is marry me! ♪
[panting]
["As I Love You" playing]
♪ Another night ♪
♪ Another brawl ♪
♪ How do you not understand me at all? ♪
♪ Don't you ever tire ♪
♪ Of this mess? ♪
Yes.
♪ All of the harm we do to our boys ♪
♪ Living inside this castle of noise ♪
♪ Can they survive
Our royal horror show? ♪
I don't know.
♪ Maybe for them ♪
♪ We could start once again ♪
Diana--
♪ Te amo ♪
♪ Te quiero ♪
♪ I'll say it every way I know ♪
♪ It's always been true ♪
You are worshiped by the world, Diana.
Isn't that enough?
♪ Once we seemed like destiny ♪
♪ Why can't you love me? ♪
♪ As I love you ♪
♪ He went abroad but promised his heart ♪
♪ Was he a fraud right from the start? ♪
♪ How come I seemed to be
The last to know? ♪
♪ Wasn't I the most beautiful bride? ♪
♪ A glittering jewel, right by his side ♪
♪ Serves me right for marrying a Scorpio ♪
♪ Well, fantasies die ♪
♪ Who knew princes lie? ♪
♪ Te amo ♪
♪ Te quiero ♪
♪ I'll say it every way I know ♪
♪ It's the best I can do ♪
♪ Je t'aime ♪
♪ We could end so happily ♪
♪ If you would love me ♪
♪ As I love ♪
♪ Why do I still love you? ♪
[knocking on door]
Well, then.
I'll get her.
-Sir, we should go.
-No.
-I'm sorry to come at this hour.
-It's all right.
But the worse things get with Diana,
the more I miss you.
Every day, more and more,
I miss you. I can hardly bear it anymore.
-[sobs]
-Don't you think I feel the same?
-All these months apart…
-["I Miss You Most on Sundays" playing]
♪ I miss you most on Sundays ♪
♪ That idle day when little gets done ♪
♪ Just lazy walks and silly talks ♪
♪ A kiss before the week's begun ♪
♪ I miss you most on Sundays ♪
♪ When time stands still and we are one ♪
♪ An easy chat about this and that ♪
♪ A cuddle as we watch the setting sun ♪
♪ Why can't we have more Sundays? ♪
But how could we possibly?
If I am to be King,
divorce is out of the question.
We have friends, dear friends,
who are sickened of
this continuing charade.
They'll lend us their flats.
Hell, they'll lend us their castles.
♪ One day we'll escape ♪
♪ Two castaways ♪
♪ Our passion once again ablaze ♪
♪ I miss you most on Sundays ♪
♪ That idle day when little gets done ♪
♪ Just lazy walks and silly talks ♪
♪ A kiss ♪
♪ Before our future's begun ♪
♪ No more missing you on Sundays ♪
♪ No more missing you ♪
♪ On Sundays ♪
["Pretty, Pretty Girl" playing]
♪ I know what they both want ♪
♪ For me to fade away ♪
♪ Obey each new command ♪
♪ Do as they say ♪
♪ Pose for a photograph
Smile for the press ♪
♪ Simply be a pretty girl
In another pretty dress ♪
♪ Too many smiles, too many yeses ♪
♪ Too many dreams
Which Charles depresses ♪
♪ He was the one who they'd devour ♪
♪ But you won their love ♪
♪ And doesn't love give you power? ♪
♪ A pretty, pretty girl ♪
♪ Wears a pretty, pretty dress ♪
♪ The press has always used her ♪
♪ So now, she'll use the press ♪
♪ This pretty, pretty girl ♪
♪ Was raised to strike a pose ♪
♪ Perhaps she should fight ♪
♪ The only way she knows ♪
-Paul!
-Yes?
Is something wrong?
Very much so.
Have you looked in my closets lately?
It's as if the Queen
selected my entire wardrobe. [scoffs]
♪ Too many bows!
Too many ruffles! ♪
♪ Too many frilly, frumpy fruffles! ♪
♪ A girl can look rather skittish ♪
♪ When her designers are boring
And British ♪
♪ This pretty, pretty girl ♪
♪ Dresses quite demure ♪
♪ It's time she found her fashion ♪
♪ And her fashion is couture ♪
♪ A pretty girl ♪
Look at these pictures.
They fawn over her because of her gowns
and her shoes and her hairdos.
♪ Hardly takes a genius
To make the front page ♪
♪ It just takes someone pretty
Think when Twiggy was the rage ♪
♪ But you were born with brilliance
You drip with intellect ♪
♪ She may have won their love
But you won their respect ♪
♪ Too much noise
Too much distraction ♪
♪ How on earth
Did she gain such traction? ♪
♪ Take a stand ♪
♪ Go out and lecture
On painting or politics ♪
Architecture! Modern buildings
really are quite ghastly, you know.
No, you're the one who knows.
So you must push back, darling.
♪ A handsome, handsome prince ♪
♪ With a worthy, worthy cause ♪
♪ Can captivate a nation ♪
♪ And turn around its laws ♪
♪ A lucky, lucky man ♪
♪ With his woman by his side ♪
♪ Can satisfy his subjects ♪
♪ And supersede his bride ♪
♪ My handsome prince ♪
I'm here to speak to you tonight
about the necessity
and glory of older buildings.
While we may prize the new,
we must cherish the established.
It would be a tragedy if St. Paul's
is dwarfed
by yet another giant glass stump,
a monstrous carbuncle on the face
of a much-loved, elegant friend.
♪ A pretty, pretty girl ♪
♪ Grows more famous than before ♪
♪ When she decides to wear
The latest from Dior ♪
♪ A pretty, pretty girl ♪
♪ In a pretty, pretty frock ♪
♪ Can set the world awhirl ♪
♪ And send the prince a shock ♪
[crowd clamoring]
I have begged and pleaded with her,
but she refuses to listen to a word I say.
And now all of Diana's showboating
is making matters worse!
♪ She doesn't need to make matters worse
You've done a fine job on your own ♪
It's her doing!
♪ Don't blame her, Charles
Tame her, Charles ♪
♪ She's embarrassing the throne ♪
[Diana] ♪ A pretty, pretty girl ♪
♪ To a round of great applause ♪
♪ Can use the press at will ♪
♪ To illuminate a cause ♪
♪ The stories
Girls are taught to believe ♪
♪ Are not the stories
That a girl should believe ♪
♪ A pretty, pretty girl
With a charitable heart ♪
♪ Can turn a photo op into a work of art ♪
♪ A pretty, pretty girl
In a pretty, pretty dress ♪
♪ The stories
Girls are taught to believe ♪
♪ Are not the stories
That a girl should believe ♪
♪ She'll take on the monarchy ♪
[ensemble] ♪ She'll take on the monarchy
And cause a royal mess ♪
-♪ A pretty, pretty girl ♪
-♪ Pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty girl! ♪
♪ In a dress ♪
[snare drum playing]
[powerful music playing]
No, it's me again,
Barbara Cartland. [chuckles]
Now, where were we?
Oh, yes. [clears throat]
["Here Comes James Hewitt" playing]
♪ If your prince leaves you wanting more ♪
♪ And royal life is a royal bore ♪
♪ Why not score a man of war? ♪
♪ Here comes ♪
♪ James ♪
♪ Hewitt ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ James Hewitt ♪
Ladies.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ James Hewitt ♪
Other ladies.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Let's do it ♪
♪ Ladies
If your life has gone off course ♪
-♪ Oh, oh ♪
-♪ You don't need no messy divorce ♪
-♪ Oh, no! ♪
-♪ All you need is a man on a horse! ♪
♪ Here comes, here comes ♪
-♪ James, James, James ♪
-♪ I can take you for a ride ♪
♪ All your troubles cast aside ♪
-♪ You'll dismount satisfied ♪
-Ooh!
♪ Here comes, here comes ♪
♪ His stomach is slim
His muscles are tight ♪
♪ A he-man like him
Who cares if he's bright?! ♪
♪ You'll sing his hymn
When the lights are dim ♪
♪ Here comes ♪
James Hewitt, Your Royal Highness.
Officer Hewitt, I hear you offer lessons.
There's only one type of lesson I offer:
riding lessons.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, James Hewitt ♪
I assumed your husband
gives you riding lessons.
He's tried. He's not very good.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, you go, girl ♪
Perhaps he just doesn't have
the proper horse.
And do you have the proper horse?
Your Royal Highness,
I think you'd adore my horse.
Oh, all right, all right!
I just made up those bits of dialogue,
but aren't they delicious?
They are! They are! [chuckles]
Now, listen.
♪ Soon he hoists her up on a mare ♪
♪ Then the stallion takes it from there ♪
♪ He dared go where few men tread ♪
♪ James Hewitt ♪
♪ Did do it ♪
♪ In our princess's ♪
♪ Bed ♪
From the moment we met,
I felt this… electricity, right?
Like, destiny,
like this really intense sense--
Stop it, James. You're beginning
to sound like a Barbara Cartland novel.
[chuckles]
Well, her novels do end happily,
right? [chuckles]
Do you truly want me?
-What?
-Do you truly desire me?
Aren't you the most desirable woman
in the world?
I'm not even the most desirable woman
in my own marriage.
-Oh, my love.
-["Him and Her (and Him and Her)" playing]
♪ It still comes as a surprise ♪
♪ To see such sadness in your eyes ♪
♪ You're overdue for a man loving you ♪
Trust me.
♪ I'm one of the good guys ♪
♪ Who knew that a commissioned lad ♪
♪ Would give me more than I've ever had? ♪
♪ Kindness like this
I forgot it exists ♪
♪ Guess I'm not stark raving mad ♪
♪ Now there's him ♪
♪ And her ♪
♪ And him and her ♪
♪ Yes, sir, it's a blur of him and her ♪
Look at the time,
you've made me late. [chuckles]
♪ I'd like to make you even later ♪
♪ Will this be a long evening, Charles? ♪
♪ Don't you know by now? ♪
They're all long evenings.
♪ Another night, another bore ♪
♪ All right, fine, I don't mind at all ♪
♪ How jealous I'll be to see you on TV ♪
[James and Camilla]
♪ When you come home, please call ♪
-♪ Damn him ♪
-♪ There's him ♪
-♪ Damn her ♪
-♪ There's her ♪
♪ There's him ♪
♪ There's her ♪
♪ Tonight, I defer ♪
-♪ To him ♪
-♪ To her ♪
♪ Look at me here, watching them glow ♪
♪ I sometimes think she's an angel ♪
♪ Just another mistress stuck at home ♪
♪ I wonder if she's thinking of me ♪
-♪ Yes, there's him ♪
-[James and Camilla] ♪ There's him ♪
-♪ There's her ♪
♪ There's him, there's her ♪
♪ Yes, sir, it's a blur ♪
♪ Of him and her ♪
Shall we, darling?
["Just Dance" playing]
♪ Let's dance ♪
♪ It's nice to be with you, Charles ♪
♪ May we speak a bit? ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ You still look so handsome, Charles ♪
♪ How nice that you've kept fit ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ My mother left me ♪
♪ I never understood ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ She broke up a family ♪
♪ I vowed I never would ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ William's so innocent ♪
♪ He needs his dad and mum ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ Harry's a funny one ♪
♪ As goofy as they come ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ We are a family
Let's hold on for the boys ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
-♪ I still do want you, Charles ♪
-♪ Just… stop! ♪
[music halts]
That's quite enough, darling.
Thank you.
["Just Dance" continues playing]
♪ I'll steal you away from here ♪
♪ The Queen and her palace guards ♪
♪ We'll go to America ♪
♪ The cowboys and the movie stars ♪
-♪ Just dance ♪
-♪ It's more than a fantasy ♪
♪ We'll take your boys and disappear ♪
-♪ Just dance ♪
-♪ We could live openly ♪
♪ With nothing to hide
And no one to fear ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
I'm sorry to disturb you, sir,
but I have rather upsetting news.
The princess has apparently
grown close to a cavalry officer.
How close?
♪ Here's him ♪
♪ And her ♪
♪ More him, more her, more… ♪
-Wait.
-[music halts]
Doesn't he give my boys riding lessons?
[sighs] Yes.
And they are quite fond of him.
Perhaps I should give
the princess a warning.
Is everything all right?
No warning. Let them carry on.
What is it?
["Just Dance" continues playing]
♪ I'll steal you away from here
We'll bask in our romance ♪
-♪ Oh, Charles ♪
-♪ As my uncle before me ♪
♪ I'll hide us away in France ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
[Charles]
♪ The things I would do for you ♪
♪ Give up the crown and disappear ♪
-♪ Just dance ♪
-♪ A life filled with honesty ♪
[men] ♪ With nothing to hide
And no one to fear ♪
♪ Fantasies come and fantasies fade ♪
♪ We live with the choices
That we've made ♪
[all] ♪ So let's not be afraid ♪
-♪ To just dance ♪
-[James] ♪ Dance ♪
-[Camilla] ♪ Dance ♪
-[Charles] ♪ Dance ♪
♪ Dance ♪
♪ We could break free right now ♪
♪ Say "farewell" to all we are ♪
♪ Perhaps we could flee somehow ♪
♪ Though, in truth, we won't get far ♪
♪ Or we could just dance ♪
I know where you're going
and I beg you to reconsider.
Oh, for God's sake, someone
has to be there for these people.
Especially after what
Margaret Thatcher has done.
So now we have political opinions?
It's not an opinion, it's a fact.
Since Mrs. Thatcher
has taken her claws out…
-Oh please!
-…there are far fewer social services
-for those who need it most.
-[Paul] M'lady.
Thank you, Paul.
What you're doing is simply unwise.
Charles, what's the point of having power
if we don't use it to help people?
AIDS is a growing crisis in Britain
and no one's paying
the least bit of attention to it.
But there are more appropriate causes.
You should know people
are beginning to suggest
that you revel in being
the pretty face of all this suffering.
I bet those are the same people who
call Mother Teresa an opportunist, so…
All I'm saying is,
if you insist on playing martyr, fine.
But for the sake
of your sons, protect yourself.
Wear gloves, wear a mask,
wear whatever you need to wear.
But protect yourself.
What a joy, Your Royal Highness.
No one near your stature has ever
even inquired about us, much less visited.
-Your Royal Highness.
-Those gloves aren't necessary.
I really must insist.
We've been desperately
trying to educate the public.
There are doctors in this very hospital
who won't even touch these men,
much less treat them.
The men have been
instructed not to touch you.
So everyone will feel comfortable.
We have orders from the Queen.
And where's the Queen now?
Buckingham Palace, I presume.
Pity.
Hello.
I'm Diana.
["Secrets and Lies" playing]
♪ They said you would come ♪
♪ It seemed so absurd ♪
♪ We all had our doubts ♪
♪ Well, I'm a girl of my word ♪
♪ Here, take my hand ♪
♪ We'll have a nice time ♪
♪ An honor to meet you ♪
♪ The honor is mine ♪
[ensemble] ♪ All pretense falls
Every line blurs ♪
♪ She sees all our pain ♪
♪ And we see all hers ♪
I brought along
a photographer from the papers.
-I thought some pictures might give--
-Oh, no. No.
I couldn't possibly.
But it will bring attention to your cause.
♪ My parents don't know ♪
♪ There's really no way ♪
♪ They'll find out I'm sick ♪
♪ They'll find out I'm gay ♪
♪ I could lose my new job ♪
♪ Be tossed from my flat ♪
♪ Of course, let's forget it ♪
♪ Or how about we chat? ♪
♪ I do like your suit ♪
[chuckles] ♪ Well, how very kind ♪
♪ Perhaps not the collar ♪
♪ I'm sick but not blind ♪
[all snickering]
♪ Are you getting good care? ♪
♪ The best anywhere ♪
♪ Although my eyeliner's run low ♪
♪ Oh, well, no need to fear ♪
♪ I'll send a case here ♪
♪ Makeup is one thing I know ♪
♪ Then, like a good chap ♪
♪ Sure, I'll take the snap ♪
♪ For what is there really to lose? ♪
♪ I may be unwell
But I'm handsome as hell ♪
♪ So I bet we get good reviews ♪
♪ You might think me mad
But the lighting's not bad ♪
♪ Now let's make us some news ♪
♪ I'm so glad I came ♪
♪ I enjoyed your jokes ♪
♪ Well, you always did like
Sexy young blokes ♪
♪ You know I'll be back ♪
♪ You've opened my eyes ♪
♪ The damage that's done ♪
♪ Through secrets and lies ♪
[ensemble] ♪ It's time to be done ♪
♪ With secrets and lies ♪
Actually, I wouldn't mind a photograph.
Me too.
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah ♪
Our problems are so minuscule
compared to the rest of the world.
I sometimes wonder
if I could do more for people.
More?
There isn't an unwell person in England
whose doorbell you haven't rung. [scoffs]
-Sarah!
-Sorry.
I came here for dinner
and there's still no sign of it.
Will Captain Hewitt be joining us?
-In Kensington Palace? Are you mad?
-[both chuckle]
Well, I'd just like to meet him
before you two ride off into the sunset.
Oh, he would make
a wonderful father, he truly would.
Wait, you're not really considering it.
Don't be daft.
[sighs] Good. To have to put up
with your husband's nonsense
and then not be crowned Queen?
I'd have to kill
both you and the Rottweiler.
I don't even think
she's been around much of late.
Maybe he's finally over her.
You do know where
your husband's going tonight?
One of his pretentious friends
is having a party or something.
It sounds dire.
Are you aware it's a birthday party
for the Rottweiler's sister?
What?
Those two go together
to their friends' flats all the time now.
It's not exactly a secret.
Except, apparently, to you.
Think you could ring a bell
or something so we could eat?
Change of plans, no dinner.
-Paul?
-Oh, come on.
Locate my husband, will you?
There's a party I'd like to attend.
["The Main Event" playing]
♪ Another night with Charles' friends ♪
♪ I pray to God that it soon ends ♪
♪ Nights like this, I envy the poor ♪
♪ Their parties can't possibly
Be such a bloody bore ♪
We had the most marvelous time,
but we must get going.
Oh, no, he'll be here soon.
♪ We stand and chat, try to look alive ♪
♪ While we wait for the prince to arrive ♪
♪ His mistress smiles and does her bit ♪
♪ I wonder how
She puts up with this shit ♪
-I'm here.
-Darling, finally!
And I'm here too.
Surprise!
[saxophone plays]
♪ Good night
And goodbye to my discontent ♪
♪ I just got a ticket to the main event ♪
♪ It's the "Thrilla in Manila"
But with Diana and Camilla ♪
♪ "Thrilla in Manila" with Camilla ♪
♪ Hold on to your hats
These cats are gonna fight ♪
♪ This suddenly became
One hell of a night ♪
♪ Now let's start the show ♪
♪ Ready, set, here we go ♪
♪ Go, go, go! ♪
-[music halts]
-Diana.
Actually, it's "Your Royal Highness."
You swore you wouldn't cause a scene.
And you swore you wouldn't see her again.
Perhaps we should go somewhere private.
How about the basement?
Love to.
["Main Event" continues playing]
♪ A rather tough night
For our beloved sir ♪
♪ Between him and his wife
I'd put my money on her ♪
♪ I'd swallow my pride ♪
♪ To have a seat ringside ♪
♪ Ringside, wanna be ringside ♪
♪ Here we go, a chance to chat ♪
♪ You and me
How about that? ♪
♪ Tell me, then, will this take long? ♪
♪ I'll be brief, I want you gone ♪
♪ Here's a truth about royal life ♪
♪ A prince has his lover
As well as his wife ♪
♪ Don't you know?
Must I make it clear? ♪
-♪ I picked you out ♪
-♪ What? ♪
-[Camilla] ♪ And put you here ♪
-♪ No ♪
♪ I love Charles for who he is ♪
♪ For his strength
And the noble life he lives ♪
♪ You love Charles for who he's not ♪
♪ Some fantasy prince
In some storybook plot ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, you're completely mad! ♪
♪ Such delusion and confusion
How bloody sad ♪
-♪ You're a fool! ♪
-♪ You're a fling! ♪
♪ You're a thing on the side! ♪
♪ While I'm his celebrated bride ♪
♪ I've been discreet
Stayed out of your way ♪
♪ You showed up to the church
On my wedding day ♪
-♪ At least I have class ♪
-♪ Well, you hide it well ♪
[both] ♪ Just so you know ♪
-♪ I'll fight like hell ♪
-♪ I'll fight like ♪
-♪ Hell ♪
♪ I'll fight like-- ♪
♪ Stop this now! ♪
♪ You've had your goddamn fun! ♪
♪ We'll take our leave ♪
♪ Your little stunt is done ♪
♪ Thought I was a ninny
You could mold me as you like ♪
♪ Well, the skinny on the ninny
Is she's really rather bright ♪
♪ I've suffered through divorce
I know how it destroys ♪
♪ I've had it done to me
I won't do it to my boys ♪
♪ Ladies and gentlemen
Now, this is a show ♪
♪ And I'm front row for the blow-by-blow ♪
♪ It's the "Thrilla in Manila"
But with Diana and Camilla ♪
♪ "Thrilla in Manila" with Camilla ♪
♪ For years, this story
Will drip off my tongue ♪
♪ I was part of the party
Where the mud was flung ♪
♪ Who will the winner be ♪
♪ In a marriage of three? ♪
♪ Three, three, three! ♪
♪ And while we're all here
Shall we clear the air? ♪
♪ You aided and abetted
Their entire affair! ♪
♪ You lent them your flats
You hid them out! ♪
♪ Don't say you don't know
What I'm talking about! ♪
♪ That's enough, that's enough
Now you've gone too far ♪
♪ No, it's not, no, it's not ♪
♪ Now call the car ♪
♪ That's right ♪
♪ Time you go ♪
♪ Grab my bag, grab my coat
Grab my feeble little husband ♪
-♪ Good night ♪
-[ensemble] ♪ Good night! ♪
♪ And cheerio! ♪
I'll ring you.
No, no, he won't!
♪ Well, thanks for the party
It really was fun ♪
♪ I wish we could stay
But I'd say that we're done ♪
♪ Now I'm leaving with my man ♪
Oh, my gosh, this was fun.
♪ Fun, fun, fun! ♪
[traffic passing]
Did seem like a lovely party.
I know about the stable boy.
Hewitt is his name, correct?
I know what you do, the men you see.
You've been spying.
I have a responsibility to know
what goes on in my family.
Especially when my wife acts
as if she's escaped from an asylum!
For the record, he's not a stable boy.
Do you love him?
Don't answer.
I don't even care.
I will end it with him
if you end it with her.
When will you come to your senses
and stop trying
to make this marriage work?
What?
Well, let's be honest.
-I owe this Hewitt chap my gratitude.
-["Whatever Love Means Anyway" playing]
♪ Thanks to him, you're good as gone ♪
♪ Feel free to carry on ♪
[chuckles]
♪ The fun you two will have ♪
♪ Enjoy your grand affair ♪
♪ I could not care ♪
♪ Go ahead and call him night and day ♪
♪ The center shakes ♪
♪ The contract breaks ♪
♪ A selfish child at play ♪
♪ An army bloke!
Your dirty joke! ♪
♪ Go ahead and love him ♪
We will continue to play our roles
in public, but in private,
do as you must.
And our boys?
We will both always love them.
They'll be fine.
♪ Whatever love means anyway ♪
So you and I can be together
as much as we like now!
-Diana--
-You'll spend more time with my boys.
And perhaps we'll even visit America.
Don't you see?
We can make plans for our future.
I didn't want to tell you
until my orders came through,
but I believe I'm about to be reassigned.
To where?
Germany.
Oh, for how long?
Two years.
No.
-I'm sorry, but no.
-I'll be back from time to time.
How could you agree to this?
-What choice do I have?
-Me, you could choose me.
-No, I'm sorry, you simply can't go.
-Germany isn't far.
-I'll come back as often as I can.
-Do you think Charles is behind this?
What?
I bet he did all he could
to have you sent away.
Or perhaps he had nothing to do with it
and I'm just good at my job.
-I can arrange things so you can stay.
-Diana--
If I make a phone call,
they'll have to let you stay.
You can't interfere
with my career, my life.
[regimental music playing]
♪ I do my duty
For my country and my honor ♪
I thought I was your life.
♪ We both know happiness is a luxury ♪
I've been receiving calls from reporters
inquiring about our relationship.
I'm only surprised it took this long.
Then let's tell our story before they do!
I'm ready to tell the world!
And do you know what they'll call me?
The randy stable boy.
The plaything of the princess.
You know, sometimes I think it's
impossible for any man to be with you.
I'm sorry.
If you leave, you and I are no more.
Did you just give me an ultimatum?
No.
No, no, just please don't go, James.
Please. Look…
I… I won't let Charles get away with this.
I'll… I'll make a phone call, and then--
No, James!
James, please!
-["Pretty, Pretty Girl" playing]
-♪ Another lesson learned ♪
♪ A girl grows wise ♪
♪ I'd say she's finally done
With secrets and lies ♪
♪ So much is left unsaid ♪
♪ Yet she remains discreet ♪
♪ The tabloids tell her story ♪
♪ But that story's incomplete ♪
♪ A clever, clever girl ♪
♪ With so little left to lose ♪
♪ Can rewrite her own story ♪
♪ For her story's hers to choose ♪
♪ A clever girl ♪
["Snap, Click" playing]
[ensemble] ♪ Snap, click
Snap, click, give us a quote ♪
♪ Come on, play the game
Or we'll go for your throat ♪
You are truly awful people.
♪ Snap, click
Snap, click, won't you admit? ♪
♪ Your storybook marriage
Is going to shit ♪
That is utter rubbish!
♪ Snap, click ♪
-Andrew, there's a phone call for you.
-Bad time.
-It's the Princess of Wales.
-Yes, this is Andrew Morton.
Mr. Morton, I hear
you're writing another book about me.
I suppose I am, Your Royal Highness.
Well, I was wondering
if you'd care to interview me for it.
No, truly?
Though you'd have to agree
never to tell anyone we spoke.
We must never meet,
and all quotes must be anonymous.
Perhaps you could send me the questions
and I could record them
into a tape recorder
and then a third party
could deliver you the tapes.
[chuckles]
That sounds rather like a spy novel.
Well, I suppose
that's what my life's become.
["The Words Came Pouring Out" playing]
♪ There are powerful men ♪
♪ There are vindictive people ♪
♪ Who won't sleep at night ♪
♪ Till they see me destroyed ♪
♪ All those friends of the palace ♪
♪ Who are nothing but callous ♪
♪ Who track me everywhere ♪
♪ Yet call me paranoid ♪
♪ They've all taken his side ♪
♪ They've all made their choice ♪
♪ They chose their prince, so now ♪
♪ I need a voice ♪
♪ Then the words came pouring out ♪
♪ Yes, the words came pouring out ♪
♪ A dam that burst, a Windsor first ♪
♪ When the words came pouring out ♪
♪ So now, the truth about Charles ♪
♪ And yes, his mistress, Camilla ♪
♪ He's a third-rate Henry VIII
And she's Godzilla ♪
[typewriter clacking, dings]
♪ He loved me for a bit ♪
♪ When I delivered his heir ♪
♪ But Harry was soon born
He even got his spare ♪
[typewriter dings]
♪ He longed for a girl ♪
♪ I gave him a son ♪
♪ And just like that ♪
♪ The marriage was done ♪
♪ And the words came pouring out ♪
♪ Yes, the words came pouring out ♪
♪ It makes one wince and pity the prince ♪
♪ When the words came pouring out ♪
♪ A marriage built on lies
The depression, the bulimia ♪
♪ Each day I'm brutalized
Assaulted by the media ♪
♪ My suicide attempts
A Kensington estrangement ♪
♪ We're leading separate lives
In this royal rearrangement ♪
♪ And the truth came pouring out ♪
♪ Yes, the truth came pouring out ♪
♪ A tabloid war never seen before ♪
♪ When the truth came pouring out ♪
♪ A kingdom fooled by a girl unschooled ♪
♪ A monarch maligned
Has she lost her mind? ♪
[ensemble] ♪ Our eyes are opened
To say the least ♪
♪ Our Beauty married a princely Beast ♪
♪ A life of desperation
In the Windsor corporation! ♪
♪ Oh my bloody Christ
We caused a sensation! ♪
[ensemble] ♪ Every revelation
A brand-new sensation! ♪
♪ Sensation! ♪
-[servant] Your morning paper, sir.
-Well, put it down.
[ensemble] ♪ Sensation! ♪
As long as you're prepared, sir.
♪ A marriage built on lies
The depression, the bulimia ♪
♪ Nothing justifies
Her assault by the media ♪
♪ Her suicide attempts
A Kensington estrangement ♪
♪ They're leading separate lives
In this royal rearrangement ♪
♪ This certainly preempts
All our other entertainment ♪
God damn her!
♪ Then the hate came pouring out ♪
♪ Yes, the hate came pouring out ♪
♪ A nation beguiled by a spiteful child ♪
♪ I'll strip the prince
Of all his pretenses ♪
♪ Petty tyranny has consequences ♪
[ensemble]
♪ Then the words came pouring out ♪
♪ Yes, the words came pouring out ♪
♪ A palace conned by a cunning blonde ♪
♪ And the words came pouring out ♪
♪ All the drama she creates
Without our permission ♪
♪ The lies and the hate
And the borderline sedition ♪
♪ All the drama she creates
Without our permission ♪
♪ The lies and the hate
And the borderline sedition ♪
♪ All the drama she creates
Without our permission ♪
♪ The lies and the hate
And the borderline sedition ♪
♪ I suppose it's time
For a reality check ♪
♪ The pretty, pretty princess
Just stuck out her neck ♪
[ensemble] ♪ And the words ♪
♪ And the words came pouring ♪
♪ Out! ♪
Of course
she was interviewed for the book.
Those words are her words.
Doesn't she understand by now?
We don't speak to the press.
-She understands next to nothing.
-Doesn't she?
She's portraying herself as a woman
cruelly betrayed
by her unaffectionate husband.
Half the women in England
can relate to that scenario.
Now, how much of the book is true?
And how am I supposed to answer that?
For a refreshing change,
let's try honestly.
Well, I've only seen
excerpts in the paper, but…
seems to be not untrue.
-Oh, for God's sake!
-Mummy, Mrs. Parker Bowles--
-I don't want to hear it!
-She is quite wonderful--
I don't care if she's Joan of Arc!
-If you'd spend time with her--
-Absolutely not!
If I was interested
in this type of sordid drama,
I'd turn on Coronation Street.
Now, get on with it, Charles,
and mend your marriage.
For your children and for your country.
And maybe even for your mother.
And if I simply can't?
That's not an option.
[orchestral strings playing]
She said that? Your mother
truly has no interest in meeting me?
After that book?
After Diana's been
dominating the airwaves?
I'm sorry, Charles,
but the Queen has gone mad.
Darling, I could use
a moment's quiet right now.
How can you be
so calm at a time like this?
Well, I need to finish this landscape.
-It's going to be on a stamp.
-Let me see it.
It's not one of your best.
Perhaps because it's been
rather difficult to concentrate!
She has no sense of propriety.
No sense of what should
and shouldn't be said.
Exactly!
So we must convince the press
to begin seeing this through our eyes.
She is out there
making a fool of you, and me.
And demeaning the monarchy in the process.
How do you react? You paint.
Leave us, William.
Well, there is one thing
I've been considering.
But it's rather drastic.
At this juncture,
we could use a bit of drastic.
What if…
Well, what if I went on television?
And owned up to the truth, told my story?
No.
Our story.
No Windsor has ever admitted
to having a mistress before,
but I could speak to the nation,
unfiltered,
and tell them how I've tried my very best.
What do you think?
-["I Miss You Most on Sundays" playing]
-♪ The truth revealed ♪
♪ We'll bask in praise ♪
♪ Candor cuts both ways ♪
♪ We'll have a life of Sundays ♪
♪ We'll live as one with hardly a care ♪
♪ Just you and me, endlessly ♪
♪ Imagine that ♪
♪ If we dare ♪
♪ A lifetime full of Sundays ♪
♪ We'll have years and years ♪
♪ Of Sundays ♪
Are you certain, Paul?
I'm sorry, the newspapers
leaked the content of the interview.
And my husband truly--
…will admit his infidelity
on national television tonight, yes.
The stupid sod.
At least I had the good sense
to speak about it for a book interview.
Anonymously, I might add, anonymously.
For people to actually see him sit there
and say those things out loud. [scoffs]
They claim I'm the one who's mad.
I'm afraid the headlines tomorrow
will be quite… humiliating.
Christ. And there's nothing
I can do about it?
There's not.
That is-- Well, unless…
-Unless?
-Unless--
We did receive one invitation
for this evening, an art gallery opening.
No, decline it, please. I couldn't--
Of course, you absolutely couldn't.
-Unless--
-Unless?
Unless!
-Please stop saying that.
-Of course.
-Unless…
-["The Dress" playing]
♪ What can a princess do ♪
♪ When her prince takes to the air? ♪
♪ And tells his gobsmacked subjects ♪
♪ He's had a love affair-air-air-air ♪
♪ She could moan on her throne ♪
♪ And sob and say boo-hoo ♪
♪ Or find a frock designed to shock ♪
♪ Designed to say
"Eff you-oo-oo-oo" ♪
What?
♪ She could try something sly ♪
♪ A bitch on wheels in six-inch heels ♪
♪ You'll rock the place in silk and lace ♪
♪ That maybe lacks a bit of taste ♪
♪ What better way to impress? ♪
♪ Than to show a flash of flesh ♪
♪ So how about this feck-you dress? ♪
♪ This feckity-feckity
Feckity-feckity feck-you dress ♪
[music halts]
Perhaps I've said too much.
My apologies, and good night.
-Unless…
-[music continues]
♪ What can a woman do
When her life goes off the rails? ♪
♪ She wonders why she married ♪
♪ The priggish Prince
Of Wales-ales-ales-ales ♪
♪ She could frown in her crown
And accept her Waterloo ♪
♪ Or flash her smile and use her style ♪
♪ To tell the prince
"Screw you-oo-oo-oo" ♪
♪ She could sport something short ♪
♪ Even bolder
Off-the-shoulder! ♪
♪ Black chiffon will turn them on ♪
♪ And tick this prince right off ♪
♪ When a girl needs to express ♪
♪ Her proper state of distress ♪
♪ Revenge looks best in an eff-you dress ♪
♪ A feckity-feckity
Feckity-feckity feck-you dress ♪
[both giggle]
Now then, the most damaging charge
is that you were persistently
unfaithful to your wife.
Did you at least try
to be faithful and honorable
to Lady Diana Spencer
when you first married?
Yes, absolutely.
And were you?
Yes.
Until the marriage became
irretrievably broken down.
["The Dress" continues playing]
♪ My son is on the telly ♪
♪ Pouring out his heart ♪
♪ While his wife is on the town ♪
♪ Dressed up like a tart ♪
♪ It's no surprise that
This is a royal tabloid mess ♪
♪ Not the first Windsor
To prefer another missus ♪
♪ Just the first one to confess ♪
♪ Her Majesty is in distress ♪
♪ This travesty, she must address ♪
♪ A princess in a mm-mm dress ♪
♪ A mm-mm, mm-mm
Mm-mm, mm-mm, mm-mm dress ♪
♪ Girlfriend in a feck-you dress ♪
♪ Feck-you dress ♪
♪ When a girl needs to express ♪
♪ Her proper state of distress ♪
♪ Revenge looks best in an eff-you dress ♪
♪ A feckity-feckity-feckity-feckity ♪
♪ Feckity-feckity-feckity-feckity ♪
♪ Feckity-feckity-feckity-feckity
Feckity-feckity ♪
♪ Fuck-you dress! ♪
["The Servant Quartet" playing]
♪ Every sexy revelation ♪
♪ Helps the tabloid circulation ♪
♪ The Windsor wars are growing rough ♪
♪ And all you sods can't get enough ♪
♪ We don't say you're to blame ♪
♪ Then again, you fan the flame ♪
♪ Have you no shame? ♪
-I'm sorry, Charles made it impossible--
-Oh, stop whining, Diana.
Every time I pick up a newspaper,
there's another personal revelation
by you or my son.
The both of you would do well
to acquaint yourselves
with the concept of discretion.
We both know the prince
certainly didn't help matters.
And neither did the princess.
In the old days,
we'd have simply chopped off your head
and been done with it.
Sometimes I miss the old days.
[Charles sighs]
Do you have anything else to add, Charles?
I will say this.
I tried my very best
to make this arrangement work.
Arrangement? Funny,
I thought it was a marriage.
If I could've known our ending
before our beginning, I never would've…
But then again,
we wouldn't have had the boys. So…
You are a wonderful mother.
No one can deny you that.
So, Diana…
What is it you want?
To be on my own again.
To be free of it all.
That is a fantasy, Diana.
Don't be foolish.
I realize I must have disappointed you.
No argument there.
Then again,
you never really understood me.
-That is not true.
-I'm afraid it is.
You never listen, Diana.
In fact,
at this moment,
I understand you more than ever.
["An Officer's Wife" playing]
♪ A long time ago ♪
♪ A princess like you ♪
♪ Was young and so scared
Of all she must do ♪
♪ She married a prince ♪
♪ A captain at sea ♪
♪ The King sent them away ♪
♪ So the princess could be
An officer's wife ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Just an officer's wife ♪
They were stationed
at a naval base in Malta,
which was then part
of the King's vast empire.
♪ The day she arrived ♪
♪ She knew things had changed ♪
♪ She was one of the girls ♪
♪ Which seemed rather strange ♪
♪ She made her own plans ♪
♪ She wrote her own rules ♪
♪ She'd drive into town
And leave home her jewels ♪
♪ An officer's wife ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Just an officer's wife ♪
And for a time, her life seemed
as ordinary as the other wives'.
♪ At night, she would sleep so soundly ♪
♪ In the arms of her sailor prince ♪
♪ He loved her so profoundly ♪
♪ They haven't felt such happiness since ♪
♪ She and her prince ♪
[ensemble] ♪ But then the King died ♪
♪ And she was crowned Queen ♪
♪ Now wherever she went ♪
♪ She caused quite a scene ♪
♪ Photographers snapped ♪
♪ Her every move ♪
♪ This frightened young girl
With so much to prove ♪
♪ An officer's wife ♪
♪ Whatever became
Of that officer's wife? ♪
All right, Diana.
You and Charles are to be divorced.
You will no longer be known
as "Her Royal Highness,"
but you shall retain
your protection services.
No, if I'm to be released,
I'm to be released from everything.
But the way you're hounded by the press.
If I retain my protection services,
they'll only continue to spy on me.
And then report back to you.
Would you care to deny that?
Very well.
No protection services.
And your plans now?
Once the boys are older,
I'd like to go to America.
A country unafraid
to express its every emotion.
You'll fit right in.
[Diana chuckles]
And they don't have princesses,
so they'll allow me to be who I truly am.
And perhaps this queen,
perhaps one day she too may rediscover
a bit of who she once was?
As I said,
don't be foolish.
♪ Now she sometimes reflects ♪
♪ On her unusual life ♪
♪ And that unusual year ♪
♪ She was ♪
♪ An officer's wife ♪
♪ She never complained ♪
♪ She was good English stock ♪
♪ And her citizens saw ♪
♪ She was their rock ♪
♪ The country she loved ♪
♪ Loved her in return ♪
♪ Her subjects became ♪
♪ Her major concern ♪
♪ An officer's wife ♪
♪ Whatever became
Of that officer's wife? ♪
-[ensemble] ♪ Oh, oh ♪
-♪ Oh ♪
-♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Just an officer's ♪
♪ Wife! ♪
["If" playing]
[Diana] ♪ I offer my goodbyes ♪
♪ Without compromise ♪
♪ A princess moving on ♪
♪ Beyond the palace staffs ♪
♪ Beyond the photographs ♪
♪ A fairy tale, come and gone ♪
♪ All I shall do again ♪
♪ Stand in a queue again ♪
♪ Here's to not making news ♪
♪ A mother full of pride ♪
♪ Her princes by her side ♪
♪ Her life finally hers to choose ♪
♪ And I choose happiness ♪
♪ I choose a fresh new start ♪
♪ I choose whatever lies ahead ♪
-[ensemble] ♪ If… ♪
-♪ If I can carry on ♪
-♪ If… ♪
-♪ Stay calm and simply breathe ♪
-♪ If I devote my soul ♪
-♪ If… ♪
-♪ To every child in need ♪
-♪ The Queen bestows her grace ♪
-♪ If… ♪
-♪ And places me in charge ♪
-♪ If… ♪
-♪ To represent the Crown ♪
-♪ Ambassador-at-large ♪
-♪ If… ♪
-♪ I'll be their English rose ♪
-♪ Their proudest shining knight ♪
-♪ And I'll light the world ♪
-♪ If… ♪
♪ I'll light the world ♪
It's finally time, Mummy.
Your Majesty, it is an honor to meet you.
Well, I admire your patience.
[Diana] ♪ But how does one begin ♪
♪ To shed her royal skin? ♪
♪ Be better than before ♪
The princess will auction off
dozens of her most famous dresses.
♪ She discards her past ♪
♪ And all that she's amassed ♪
♪ Set free, she'll do even more ♪
Her dress sale has raised millions
of pounds for childhood cancer research.
The National AIDS Trust thanks
Princess Diana for her invaluable contri--
The princess' work for
The Leprosy Mission has revolutionized--
Her work
on the international landmine crisis
has already been credited
with saving thousands of lives.
In an act of extraordinary courage,
the Princess of Wales
walks through a minefield in Angola.
♪ I choose happiness
I choose a fresh new start ♪
♪ I choose whatever lies ahead ♪
-[ensemble] ♪ If… ♪
-♪ I'll have another child ♪
-♪ If… ♪
-♪ An answer to my prayer ♪
-♪ Perhaps a baby girl ♪
-♪ If… ♪
-♪ Or, better yet, a pair ♪
-♪ If Charles steps aside ♪
-♪ If… ♪
-♪ And lets my William reign ♪
-♪ Then all this suffering ♪
-♪ If… ♪
-♪ Will not have been in vain ♪
-♪ My future's my design ♪
-♪ If… ♪
-♪ My story, finally mine ♪
-♪ And I'll light the world ♪
♪ I'll light the world ♪
There is breaking news
coming out of Paris.
♪ Flashbulbs fill the air ♪
We are hearing of an automobile accident
involving Princess Diana.
[man] We have no word
on the extent of her injuries.
♪ Frenzy fills the night ♪
A mob of paparazzi
followed her car into a tunnel.
We are getting reports
Princess Diana may be seriously hurt.
♪ A lonely girl aswirl ♪
We are being told now
to prepare for the worst.
There is shock and horror
as the West wakes up to the news.
♪ Lost in blinding light ♪
We can now confirm…
that Princess Diana has died.
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
[voices echoing]
[silence]
[footsteps clacking]
[orchestral strings playing]
♪ The people who will change the world ♪
♪ Are not the ones you think ♪
♪ Will change the world ♪
[sounds fade]
["Underestimated" playing]
♪ Flashbulbs fill the air ♪
♪ Frenzy fills the night ♪
♪ A lonely girl aswirl ♪
♪ Lost in blinding light ♪
♪ Living rather large ♪
♪ Yet feeling rather small ♪
♪ You step up to the mic ♪
♪ But you're not heard at all ♪
♪ Your prison has been built ♪
♪ Your downfall's been devised ♪
♪ Won't they be surprised? ♪
♪ When you're underestimated ♪
♪ They minimize your thoughts ♪
♪ Then maximize your flaws ♪
♪ The trouble you can cause ♪
♪ When you're underestimated ♪
♪ Underestimated ♪
♪ Nineteen and naive ♪
♪ Shy and insecure ♪
♪ Thinking princes never lie ♪
♪ Believing love is pure ♪
♪ Suddenly, a chance ♪
♪ Why not have a go? ♪
♪ The danger you don't see ♪
♪ The sorrow you don't know ♪
♪ So summon up your nerve ♪
♪ Fairy tales exist ♪
♪ And this one has a twist ♪
♪ 'Cause you're underestimated ♪
♪ You never once stood out ♪
♪ Hardly passed a test ♪
♪ Sometimes, though, it's best ♪
♪ To be underestimated ♪
♪ Underestimated ♪
♪ Expectations will grow ♪
♪ They'll prey upon the weak ♪
♪ They'll say they love you so ♪
♪ Just as long as you don't speak ♪
♪ So summon up your nerve ♪
♪ Fairy tales exist ♪
♪ And this one has a twist ♪
♪ 'Cause you're underestimated ♪
♪ You never once stood out ♪
♪ Hardly passed a test ♪
♪ Sometimes, though, it's best ♪
♪ To be underestimated ♪
["I Will" playing]
[Diana] ♪ Don't give in to your doubts ♪
♪ They'll find out who you are ♪
♪ An unknown nervous girl ♪
♪ How did she get this far? ♪
♪ So push those nerves aside ♪
♪ Time to get a grip ♪
♪ Just hold your head up high ♪
♪ And pray that you don't trip ♪
♪ I will make him love me ♪
♪ I will prove that I can ♪
♪ And I will be all that they require ♪
♪ All that they require and demand ♪
♪ I will ♪
♪ Try my very best
As I stumble in this dress ♪
♪ I will ♪
♪ Represent the Crown
No time now to back down ♪
♪ A bad time to back down ♪
♪ I will ♪
♪ How did you become ♪
♪ This global fantasy? ♪
♪ No pressure, none at all ♪
♪ I'll plead insanity ♪
[Diana and ensemble] ♪ I will ♪
[Diana] ♪ Make them love me ♪
[Diana and ensemble] ♪ I will ♪
[Diana] ♪ Prove that I can ♪
-♪ And I will be more than is expected ♪
-[ensemble] ♪ I will ♪
[Diana] ♪ More than is expected
Here I stand ♪
-♪ I will ♪
-[ensemble] ♪ I will ♪
-[Diana] ♪ I will ♪
[Diana] ♪ Rise above their fears
Deserve their deafening cheers ♪
-[Diana and Charles] ♪ I will ♪
-[ensemble] ♪ I will ♪
-[Diana and Charles] ♪ I will ♪
[Diana and Charles]
♪ Be all they've dreamt and more ♪
♪ Somehow better than before ♪
♪ I'll be better than before ♪
[ensemble] ♪ I will ♪
♪ I will ♪
[Charles] I will.
[ensemble] ♪ I will ♪
-♪ I will ♪
[Diana] I will.
[ensemble] ♪ I ♪
♪ Will ♪