Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
First of all,
let me get something straight.
This is a journal, not a diary.
When Mom went out to buy this thing,
I specifically told her not to get a book
that said "Diary" on it.
But, of course, she didn't listen.
It's been hard enough getting through
the first week of middle school
without carrying this thing
around with me.
Hey, this kid's got a diary.
A-Actually, it's a jour--
If Mom's expecting me to write down
my feelings or whatever,
she's gonna be disappointed.
The only reason I agreed
to write in this thing at all
is because one day
I'm gonna be rich and famous.
And people'll wanna read about my
early years. So I'm doing this for them.
-Greg is so smart.
-So handsome.
-So brave.
-And he smells terrific.
But for now, I'm stuck in middle school…
…surrounded by morons.
But luckily, I'm not alone
in this middle school thing.
My best friend, Rowley,
is in the same grade as me.
I doubt he's ever gonna be
rich and famous,
but it's good to have him around
for laughs.
Did you know
if your hand is bigger than your face,
it's a sign that your brain is shrinking?
It is?
Gotcha.
But does this mean my brain is shrinking?
Not sure.
Let's check the other hand.
I'm glad Rowley's along for the ride,
because everything else
about middle school stinks.
And I can't believe it was just a week ago
that me and Rowley were actually
looking forward to this.
Heads up!
That was a good one.
You almost hit the front tire that time.
You just need to slow down a little
so I can get locked in.
-Let me get this straight.
-Come on, Rowley.
So in middle school,
do you just go to a different room
for each class?
Come on. You got it.
And you just carry all your stuff
around with you all day?
No, no. No, no, no.
They give you a locker
so you can just ditch the books you
don't need in between periods.
W-w-what about recess?
There's still recess, right?
I told you, like, a million times, Rowley.
Recess is an elementary school thing.
Aw. But I like recess.
Are you gonna go,
or are you just gonna sit there?
Don't you want a turn riding?
I've gone three times in a row.
But you're way better at riding than me.
I can never do it as good as you.
Woo-hoo!
-
Oh, come on, Rodrick! You made me miss!
I'm okay.
One of the reasons
I'm friends with Rowley is
there aren't a whole lot of boys my age
in the neighborhood.
In fact, aside from Rowley,
there's only really--
Fregley!
Why, hello, Greg Heffley.
Hi, Fregley. I was just, um,
getting-- getting my football.
Wanna come inside my house for a playdate?
I can show you my room.
You know, I'll definitely take you up
on that offer sometime.
Wanna see my…
secret freckle?
-
Should we do that one over?
Who's hungry?
So, did everyone have a good day?
Frank, don't do that with your food.
It's weird.
-It tastes better this way.
-
Hey! Oh!
I'm still gonna eat it.
Greg, is that dirt
on your back-to-school clothes?
Please don't call them that.
What on earth were you doing
to get so filthy?
I was throwing a football in the street
with Rowley.
You were playing a sport with
your feet and hands and not a device.
Wo-- Wow.
I guess.
Mark the calendar, Susan.
Greg here played a sport.
You weren't playing that game
with Rowley, were you?
You know you're banned from playing that.
Somebody is going to get hurt.
What?
Oh! Oh, that game?
No. No way.
You said we couldn't play that anymore.
Right. And Rowley's parents
are in full agreement.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, there. All clean.
Speaking of Rowley,
how's he feeling about Monday?
Is he looking forward
to his first day of middle school?
Hmm. I'm not sure.
I think he might be
a little nervous, actually.
Well, he's lucky to have you
as a best friend.
You know, that's all you need to get by
in this world.
One good friend.
Yeah.
And you're lucky to have a big brother
who's already gone through
the middle school experience.
Right, Rodrick?
-Rodrick!
-Huh?
Take off your headphones.
You know the rule.
Why don't you give Greg a pep talk
about middle school?
Greg's going to middle school?
Yes, Rodrick.
Why don't you tell him
what he can expect on his first day?
Here's what you need to know.
First of all, watch where you sit
on the first day of school,
because your teacher might make that
your permanent seat.
Next, don't use the bathroom
on the second floor,
no matter how bad you have to go.
-There aren't any doors on those stalls.
-
And finally, whatever you do,
don't get the Cheese Touch.
'Cause if you do,
you might as well be dead.
Thank you, Rodrick,
-for that wonderful pep talk.
-
Greg, please forget
everything that you just heard.
Especially the nonsense about the cheese.
But wha-- what's the Cheese Touch?
It all started
in my first year of middle school.
No one knows where it came from
-or who put it there.
- Don't do it!
One day…
- Stay away!
…a slice of Swiss cheese
appeared on the blacktop.
Ew!
At first,
-no one would go near it.
-Ugh!
And then one day…
-Hmm.
…a kid named Darren Walsh got curious.
No way!
-
And that's what started
the Cheese Touch.
The only way to get rid of the Cheese
Touch is to give it to someone else.
Then one day…
-
…a kid named Abe Hall moved to California.
He took the Cheese Touch with him.
But the cheese remained.
And to this day, it sits on the blacktop,
waiting to strike again!
Well, that's terrifying.
Don't let Rodrick scare you, Greg.
Middle school's gonna be fun.
Oh, and please don't mention
the-- the cheese thing to Rowley.
Honestly,
it-- it'll scare him half to death.
Who's Rowley?
Greg's best friend.
You know, the kid who's over here
almost every single day.
Oh, him.
I thought you were babysitting that kid.
We're the same age.
He's the same age as y--
Oh, man. I thought he was, like,
in kindergarten or something.
Middle school's gonna eat him alive.
Rodrick.
Let me give you
one last piece of advice, Greg.
Middle school is every man for himself.
You don't need some overgrown baby
weighing you down.
Rodrick!
That's enough.
Greg, come on, man. Trust me.
Cut him loose now or you both drown.
-You lose!
- Woo-hoo!
In your face, Greg! That's three in a row.
Wanna go again?
No, that's okay. We can shut it off.
What's the matter?
Afraid to lose?
No, I'm just not in the mood.
Rowley, cut it out!
I mean--
Don't you think
it's time to start acting our age?
But you always do the chicken thing to me.
It's not just that, Rowley.
Look around this room.
All these stuffed animals, that bedspread,
and what's with this Joshie guy anyway?
Joshie's from Europe.
And you're just jealous
because I discovered him first.
Yeah, I'm jealous that you discovered
some stupid pop star
whose fans are only six-year-old girls.
Joshie says,
"Follow your dreams
and respect your parents."
Don't you think
it's time to grow up, Rowley?
You're in middle school now.
Well, not yet.
"Be friendly to one another, yes?"
Come on, Rowley.
Middle school's no joke.
There's bullies, and bathrooms with
no stall doors, and permanent seats,
-and-- and--
-And what?
And the cheese!
What's the cheese?
Please don't mention the cheese thing.
It'll scare him half to death.
You know what?
Forget I said anything.
Middle school's gonna be just fine.
In fact, it'll be great.
Yeah, 'cause we're in it together.
Right, Greg? Friends till the end.
Yeah, friends till the end.
Hi, how was your summer?
- My summer was awesome.
No, I hate camp.
Oh, my gosh, I love your backpack.
Did your mom
dress you this morning?
Look at those high waters.
I heard that Peter Mud and Alicia
Tango got their braces stuck together
-over the summer.
-Move to the side, shrimp.
-Come on. Let's go. I don't wanna be late.
-But what about the-- the cheese?
That's just some stupid fairy tale
Rodrick made up.
Stop trying to copy my style, please.
Nice mom jeans, Kelsey.
Hair color…
You know,
maybe this isn't such a good idea.
Maybe my mom can homeschool me.
-Come on, Rowley.
-
You can do this.
We can do this. We just need
to find our lockers and we'll be fine.
Heads up.
- Whoa!
Ugh!
But I gotta go to the bathroom!
-
Ugh!
…sanitary.
Yep. Homeschool for sure.
One step at a time.
Don't make eye contact,
and they won't even notice you're here.
You better not be looking
at my boyfriend, Kelsey.
-
Come on. I was eating that.
Help me.
Mm-mmm.
That was close.
Kindergarten's
down the street.
Not so bad.
And look.
Our lockers are right next to each other.
Yes!
Look. They keep our schedules in here.
Cool. Let me see yours.
But they don't match.
Well, we've got lunch together.
We'll see each other then.
Oh, hey!
- See ya!
What do we do now?
We go to homeroom.
Mine's right here.
Yours is upstairs, I think.
-There's an upstairs?
-
-Out of the way, runt.
-Move to the side, shrimp.
-Step aside, little man.
-Yes, not for long, little man.
Greg! What do I do? What do I do?
There was no time
to worry about Rowley,
because I needed to focus
on my own situation.
I was glad Rodrick gave me
a few pointers, so I knew what not to do.
Oh, hey.
- Yeah. Awesome.
Uh…
-
Exactly!
But it turns out…
- Shh.
…having an older brother
who went to the same school
isn't such a good thing after all.
-Greg Heffley?
-Huh?
-As in Rodrick Heffley's brother?
-
You'll be sitting
in the chair in front of my desk.
-
Oh!
Bro, dude's with the weirdo.
-
Just about everything's different
from elementary school.
Wouldn't want to be him.
Mm-hmm.
And the biggest change
is who's popular and who's not.
-Back in elementary school, it was simple.
-
If you were the fastest runner,
you were the most popular.
-In fifth grade…
-
…the fastest runner was Ronnie McCoy.
But now, all the rules have changed.
Now it's all about whether or not
you have cool hair
and how many followers
you have on social media.
In middle school,
a kid like George Deveney
is at the top of the food chain,
and Ronnie McCoy is scratching his head
wondering what the heck happened.
So what I'm trying to figure out
is where I fit into all this.
I'm sure I'm not at the top of the ladder,
but at least I'm not at the bottom.
Does this scab smell funny to you?
But there's one way for sure
to get to the bottom.
Come on!
Run! Yeah!
-Yo, get in there for the rebound, dude.
And nobody's risking that.
-
What are you standing around for?
Get the ball!
Ew. It's so gross.
-
Hey, what did you get for lunch?
- Today I have a jacket.
Looks pretty full up.
Oh, hey.
Try your luck with someone else.
Maybe try the table next door.
-Eighth-graders only, newbies.
Should we sit with the girls?
We're out of our league here.
Hey! Over there.
-Take a hike.
-Hey.
Band members only.
- Not today, guys.
Over there. Let's go!
Yeah?
Check back when we're not so busy.
Uh…
There's two!
-
And another thing.
Don't use the bathroom
on the second floor.
That was a big mistake.
Yeah, I probably
should have warned you about that.
I can't deal with this.
I need to be sitting at a table.
But you said only popular kids
get seats at the table.
Well, I heard Charlie Davies
is getting braces next week,
so he'll definitely
drop a few spots for sure.
But that's only one spot. We need two.
That's all the time we get?
I didn't even get to finish my juice box.
We gotta go to fifth period, Rowley.
I'll meet you back here
at the door after school.
But I don't want to go back out there.
Keep a low profile and you'll be fine.
Think good thoughts, Rowley.
Good thoughts, Rowley. Good thoughts.
Hey, Greg!
After school, wanna come over and play?
Play, play, play, play, play…
Play.
-Play.
- Play.
-
-Hey, kid. Wanna come over and play?
-Huh?
Um, no, thank you.
Psst! Rowley!
There you are! You said we were gonna
meet at the back door.
"Hang out," Rowley.
You say "hang out" in middle school,
not "play."
I've told you that a million times.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Seriously,
you gotta start listening to me, Rowley.
You're gonna get us both killed.
So, do you wanna hang out
and "do" video games?
Better.
Thankfully,
Rowley did start listening to me.
We made it through
the next few weeks alive.
But by the time Halloween rolled around,
Rowley started to slip again.
Do you think our teachers will let us
wear our costumes to school tomorrow?
No, Rowley. No!
Have I not taught you anything?
They had a costume parade
in elementary school.
Right, elementary school.
We're in middle school now, remember?
Yeah, you keep reminding me.
Listen. The only reason
I'm trick-or-treating this year
is for the candy.
And I really don't want anyone
knowing we're doing this, okay?
-I guess.
-Listen, things are hard enough at school.
I just don't wanna put a target
on our backs, you know?
Fine.
So wear something
that doesn't attract too much attention.
-Seriously, we have to be invisible.
-Got it.
Ooh!
Is that our first trick-or-treater?
-Can someone get the door?
-I'm on it.
What? Huh?
Rowley, what are you doing?
I thought we said we were being invisible?
-My mom made me add safety stuff.
-We can deal with costume stuff later.
Bubby.
- Greg?
Let's get out of here before--
You weren't gonna leave without Manny,
were you?
-Rowley, you look adorable.
-Come on.
-Mom, can't someone else take Manny?
Well, Rodrick's at the high school party,
I'm going to be handing out the candy,
and Dad is doing that thing
that he does on Halloween.
Okay. Man your stations.
Well, I'll man mine.
Just making sure we're not getting
toilet-papered this year.
It takes too long to get that off.
No, no. It's not happening.
Good thoughts. All positivity.
But Manny will just slow us down.
We're trying to double our territory
this year, Mom.
Well, there are only so many houses
in our neighborhood.
Wait a minute.
You're not planning to take the shortcut
through Snake Road, are you?
-What? No.
-
That-- That would be crazy.
Good. Because you would be in big trouble
if you did.
-Right, Manny?
-
Keep to the sidewalks,
and I want you back at 8:00.
It's a school night.
8:00? 8:00 a.m.?
All right. I-- I mean, I'm fine with that.
-
Fine. 8:30 and not a second later.
Oh, Rowley, you know what?
Those glow sticks are a great idea.
Let me see if I have any in the pantry.
Okay, time to go.
-Come on, Manny. You wanna get some candy?
-
Arr!
Thank you.
- Isn't he in your class?
That's a kiddy costume!
-All right! Let's go!
It's the Prince of Preschool.
What a dork.
Trick or treat.
-Candy.
-Aw. Here, take five.
-Yay!
-
Thanks.
Aren't you too old for trick or treat?
What the heck?
Aw.
Bye.
Unbelievable.
Come on, guys.
We need to pick up the pace a little.
You guys are killing me.
-
Hi.
Is that a cute little pirate I see?
Mm-hmm.
Aw.
Here's some extra booty for your bucket.
-Biggie!
-Seriously?
King-size?
It'll take you a week to get through that.
Bubby!
Hmm…
-Do you see what's happening here, Rowley?
-Hmm? Aw.
This kid's our golden ticket!
-
-Hmm?
Aw.
There you go.
-
Oh, yes!
Yay!
Bubby! Candy!
I can't believe we never thought
of bringing Manny.
-This kid's a gold mine.
-Yeah.
So we'll stop by my house,
empty these bags in my room,
then head back out for another round,
okay?
I don't know. I mean, Manny looks tired.
He's fine. Aren't you, Manny?
See? That was a nod.
-Actually, I'm kind of tired too.
-
Come on, Rowley.
We can stock up on candy for the year!
We can't let this opportunity go to waste.
But we don't need that much candy.
Seriously?
You can never have too much candy, Rowley.
Candy's like money in middle school.
We can buy someone's lunch seats off them.
How about just like
a couple more houses, okay?
It's the end of the night.
Everyone's looking
to get rid of their candy.
-We can make a killing.
-I don't know.
Okay, here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna hit Whirley Street.
Whirley Street?
But that's like a mile from here.
-Not if we take a shortcut.
-Snake Road?
-Don't you remember what your mom said?
-She'll never even know.
Twenty more minutes and we'll be back
at my house eating our candy. I promise.
We're not little kids anymore.
All right. That's my boy.
I-- I think we made a mistake.
It's gonna be worth it, Rowley.
Just think about all the candy.
I don't even like candy all that much.
Rowley, do not say that.
Don't even joke about it.
Do you think the Goat Man is gonna get us?
Are you kidding me, Rowley?
That's obviously a made-up story.
-Rodrick was just trying to scare us.
-That's what you said about the cheese.
And that was real.
Yeah, well, a half-man, half-goat?
It's not even physically possible, Rowley.
-
But--
But if the Goat Man was real,
do you think he's a goat on the top
and a person on the bottom?
Or the other way around?
Or do you think
he's got a split down the middle
with a goat on the left side
and a person on the right?
Can we stop talking about this?
I think I hear some--
-
Teenagers!
♪ Breaking the law, breaking the law ♪
Whoa! That was close!
Yeah. Um, let's just keep moving before--
-
♪ Breaking the law, breaking the law ♪
♪ Breaking the law, break-- ♪
-
Look at these little nerds,
out past their bedtimes.
Yeah. Shouldn't you be getting
a good night's sleep?
Actually, we're in middle school.
My bedtime's not until 9:00.
Mom let me stay up extra tonight.
Yeah, we-- we better head home.
Have a good night, fellas.
Ooh! Look at those bags.
Is that all candy?
Mostly. But my parents handed out
miniature toothbrushes this year,
so we've got those too.
We-- We'd really better get going now.
It would be a real pity
if that candy got wet.
-
-What?
-Huh?
-
Greg, run!
Let's go!
Hang on to Manny!
Whoa!
-Yeah!
-
Yeah, baby!
Not so fast!
Whoo!
-
Whoa!
Oh, yes!
You'll pay for this!
We know where you go to school!
-Whoa!
-
Is this…
My yard! We made it, Rowley.
We're alive!
I told you, Rowley.
If you just stick with me,
everything will be fine.
Now let's get inside
and enjoy some of this candy.
Ha ha! Oh!
Sorry. I-I thought you were teenagers.
Are you all right?
You're all right.
We were worried sick about you two.
-Mama.
-Where were you boys?
Snake Road.
Busted.
Mom grounded me
from playing video games for a week,
which is her go-to punishment.
That meant I had to figure out something
else to do with my time after school.
Woo-hoo!
I'm thinking I might either
run for student council
or maybe sign up for the dance committee.
Or maybe I'll try out for the play.
-They're doing Wizard of Oz this year.
-Uh-huh.
Chirag Gupta wants to be Toto,
and Patty Farrell says
Mrs. Norton already promised her Dorothy.
I'm trying to decide if I wanna try out
for the Scarecrow or the Cowardly Lion.
Sounds great, Rowley.
Can you go now?
Well,
aren't you gonna sign up for anything?
My mom says, "It's important to belong to
something when you're in middle school."
Belong to something?
Rowley, I can't even get a seat at lunch,
and I'm sick and tired of it.
But if we were in the play,
we could make friends who could invite us
to sit at their lunch table.
That's a lot of work, Rowley.
And it'll take too much of my time.
I need to change my situation now!
Oh, yeah!
Whoa!
Hey, oh!
Rowley!
You okay? I feel so bad!
I really didn't mean to flip you.
I think I hurt my arm.
Yeah, I think I might have pulled
something myself.
Can you believe that throw though?
I mean--
Ow.
Oh, man. You're really hurt.
I think I'd better go home.
Okay. But you can't tell your parents
how this happened.
If my mom found out
we were playing this game, she'd go nuts.
-I'm already grounded.
-What am I supposed to tell them then?
Just say you were playing tag
and that you tripped on the curb.
But whatever you do,
don't mention the Rumble Trike.
Got it?
Got it.
So what happened at the hospital?
- They took a bunch of X-rays.
The doctor says my arm is broken.
Broken?
Oh, man. I thought it was just
bruised or something.
Nope. I've got a cast and everything.
A cast? That's serious!
Yeah, I know.
I mean,
that's really awful and everything.
-But do you know what this means?
-Yeah.
I have to put a plastic bag over my arm
in the shower for a whole month.
No! What this means for school.
I guess I can't do
the wrestling unit in Phys Ed?
Rowley! A cast is the greatest
thing that can happen to a kid.
-It is?
-Yes, Rowley.
-Everyone's gonna wanna sign it.
-What? They will?
Yes. Kids will be begging you
to sit at their lunch table.
Yeah.
And I hope you'll remember
who your real friends are, Rowley.
The people who helped you get
to where you are.
-Yeah.
-What about your parents?
Are they suspicious?
I told them I tripped on a rock
playing Duck, Duck, Goose, like you said.
Like I said?
We were playing tag, Rowley!
And you tripped over the curb.
It doesn't even make sense for two people
to play Duck, Duck, Goose. Come on!
-Oh, yeah. Sorry.
-We gotta get our story straight,
or they're gonna find out
about the Rumble Trike.
Did you say, "Rumble Trike"?
I don't know
what to do with you, Greg.
First you disobey me and go to Snake Road.
Then you play that-- that game.
I told you someone
was going to get hurt playing that.
I'm sorry, Mom. I just…
Lying to me is bad enough,
but telling Rowley to lie to his parents
is just-- just--
Mom, I know I messed up.
You can take away my video games
for the month.
The year if it makes you feel better.
Punishing you doesn't make me feel better,
Greg.
I'm trying to raise a good kid.
I do wanna be good, Mom.
Well, then here's what you need to do.
You need to figure out a way
to make things right by Rowley.
You owe that to him.
That boy is such a good friend to you.
Yeah, Mom.
I can't tell you how to make things right.
That part is up to you.
-But Mom…
-Listen to that inner voice, Greg.
I know it's in there.
Do the right thing.
Okay,
I know what my mom wanted me to do.
She wanted me to tell Rowley's parents
the truth about what happened.
But here's the thing.
Rowley's dad has never really liked me.
I knew if I told him what really happened,
it was just gonna make him
like me even less.
That wouldn't make things any better.
I don't wanna get Rowley in trouble
for lying,
'cause then he'd be in trouble too.
So, I decided the right thing to do
was to just let things be.
Because telling the truth
would make things worse for everybody.
-Ooh.
-Oh, my gosh. What happened?
-It looks so cool.
-Oh, you're so great.
Can I sign it?
And I'll tell you another thing
that I was right about.
That cast. In fact, it worked even better
than I thought it would.
It's so cool.
Just like I predicted, getting
a seat at lunch was no problem at all.
Well,
at least for Rowley it wasn't a problem.
Here comes the airplane.
-
-Nom!
-Here comes the train!
Chugga chugga chugga, choo choo!
He can feed himself just fine, okay?
Mmm.
You know Rowley's left-handed?
Who are you?
I'm Greg Heffley, Rowley's best friend.
I'm the one who broke his arm.
You jerk!
Get out of here.
- Heads up!
I couldn't have Rowley
hog all the attention,
so I decided to whip up
an injury of my own.
It's just an infection caused by
a splinter that was left untreated.
-Hey.
-
Can I peek at your infection?
Ew.
I realized I couldn't compete
with Rowley's stupid injury.
So that meant I needed
to find something of my own.
And just like that, I did.
Hey, Greg.
I couldn't find you after school.
Huh?
Sorry. I wanted to go home
and start working on my comics.
Your comics? For what?
The school paper.
One of the cartoonists quit,
so now there's a spot open.
Can I help?
Sorry, Rowley. There's only one spot open.
Zoo-Wee Mama!
This is funny!
"Oops. I've stepped in a puddle!
Well, at least it's not an acid puddle!
Ah! It is an acid puddle!
Zoo-Wee Mama!"
Zoo-Wee Mama!
Do you have any more like this one?
I'm working on something better.
Check this one out.
It's called "Creighton the Cretin."
"Hiya, doc! Can I get a new butt?
My old one has a crack in it."
"Everyone's butt has a crack in it,
you idiot!"
"Oops."
But when does he say, "Zoo-Wee Mama"?
He doesn't.
I think it'd be funnier if he said,
"Zoo-Wee Mama!"
You know what? If you wanna draw
your own comic, be my guest.
But we always do everything together.
Yeah, well, not this time. Sorry.
But can we be partners?
You can write the comic,
and I can draw it.
No offense, Rowley,
but you don't even draw noses on people.
Sorry. This is kinda my thing,
like the way Joshie's your thing.
Okay. Well, I guess I'll go work
on my comic at my house.
Sounds good.
See ya.
-
After I turned in my comic,
all I could do was wait.
But after a whole week went by,
Mr. Humphreys made an announcement.
Attention, students.
After careful consideration,
we've made a decision
on the cartoonist for the school paper.
And the new cartoonist is…
-Greg Heffley.
-Yes! Yes!
This is possibly the biggest thing
that has ever happened to me.
-That's the dude?
-He wrote that?
Is that cartoon kid?
For the first time since I stepped
through those double doors,
I wasn't invisible.
-Teacher's pet!
Aren't comics supposed
to make you laugh?
"Creighton the Curious Student."
Did you think that was funny?
-What the--
"Teacher, if x plus 43 is 89,
what would x be?"
"Why, it would be 46!"
"Thanks! Kids,
if you'd like to learn more about math,
have Mr. Humphreys show you around
the newly expanded
math and science section of the library."
"And thanks to the Parent-Teacher
Organization for funding the new section.
Our old books were badly outdated."
They changed it?
-Teacher's pet!
-Thanks for ruining my day.
-What a waste of ink.
-Nerd!
Boo!
Teacher's pet!
See? That's what happens
when the school librarian
is in charge of the newspaper.
They've always gotta get pushy
with their books.
One week after I quit,
Mr. Humphreys chose someone to replace me,
and you'll never believe who he picked.
Zoo-Wee Mama!
-
-Zoo-Wee Mama!
Zoo-Wee Mama!
"Hey, pretty lady.
Do you wanna go on a date?"
"I'm actually not a lady.
I'm one of those dogs with long hair.
So, no thanks to that date."
"Zoo-Wee Mama!"
So a kid who can barely draw
got his comic in the school paper?
It's totally unfair.
Why didn't they censor Rowley's work?
You stole my comic.
You said you didn't wanna do it anymore.
Well, couldn't you come up
with something original for once, Rowley?
Well, I can't help it
if I'm just naturally funny.
Zoo-Wee Mama!
-Zoo-Wee Mama!
- Zoo-Wee Mama!
You know what? I hope you enjoy all this,
because I'm tired of carrying you.
Maybe it's the other way around.
This comic, this lunch table, that cast.
You wouldn't have any of it
if it wasn't for me!
Yeah, because you broke my arm.
Yeah. You're welcome.
Rowley deserves your respect.
-
-Zoo-Wee Mama!
- Oh!
Okay, I'll admit.
Maybe I could have handled
the situation at lunch a little better.
But I figured, after a while,
me and Rowley would cool down,
things would go back to normal.
So do you like DinoBlasters?
No.
I love it.
Thing is, that hasn't happened yet.
Rowley's been hanging out
with this kid Chirag every day.
You know the only reason he's doing it
is to make me jealous.
But two can play at that game.
-You wanna see my room?
-Yeah.
Yes! Come on!
The one and only Greg Heffley
is on my front step.
Yeah, I guess I am.
So I was thinking,
me and you are neighbors.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
But we barely even know each other.
How'd you feel about a sleepover?
Tonight?
Yeah. Right now.
You and me. Just a couple of pals.
Woo-hoo! Come on in.
-
You know, maybe we should take this
one step at a time.
How about if we just play
a quick game of cards and call it a night?
-
Hey, Greg.
Oh, Fregley.
Do you have a playmate over?
Would you like for me
to knit him some socks?
Yep. I'm pretty sure
I'm gonna be in therapy over this.
Whoo!
Greg Heffley's in my room.
Woo-hoo!
Yeah, but just for a short visit.
In fact, I really need to be--
You wanna play make-believe?
You can be the church organist,
and I'll be the school hygienist.
You know, that's tempting.
But I'm not really into--
How about a tickle fight?
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle.
I'm gonna tickle, tickle.
I got you. I'm tickling you. Ha ha!
Hey! What are you doing?
Give me some space here.
Can't you just stay over there?
Well, what do you wanna do then?
I don't know. I thought if we…
Mmm.
Fregley! That's the only candy bar
I had that wasn't wet.
Mom never lets me have chocolate.
Says it makes me hyperactive and unstable.
-Fregley, are you okay? Fregley!
-
I've blocked out big parts
of that night.
Hey, Greg.
I'm so glad I can't remember
every little thing that happened.
-Hey!
But what I do remember
is that I ended up
locked up in Fregley's bathroom
while I waited
for his sugar high to wear off.
Dear Gregory,
I'm sorry I ate your candy
and chased you with a booger.
Here, I put it on this piece of paper
so you can get me back.
Signed, Fregley.
What the--
But if I could, I would forget everything.
-
Hey, Greg. Hey!
Oh, hey. Hey, Rowley. What's up?
I was wondering
if I could stop by your house today
and pick up my copy of Twisted Wizard.
Me and Chirag want to play it.
Yeah, well, I've had it for a while,
so it's kind of mine now.
I guess you and your new friend
will have to find something else to do.
Oh, yeah? Well, I'm not the only one
with a new friend.
You mean Fregley?
I'm permanently scarred from that night.
And it's all your fault for ditching me.
I ditched you?
More like the other way around.
You haven't been the same ever since
you got that stupid cast.
-You've changed.
-Fight!
-Oh, yeah?
- They're gonna fight.
Well, you're the one who broke my arm.
You can take him. Knock him down!
Guys, come over. Come check out the fight.
Why don't you make a move?
- Unless you're chicken.
Fight, fight, fight!
Fight, fight, fight, fight!
Where'd you learn to fight?
Ballerina school?
If you don't do something,
I'm gonna fall asleep.
Who taught you how to fight? Your granny?
Are you two gonna fight
or keep dancing with each other?
Do they even know how to do this?
-
-Let's get out of here!
-Come on. Let's go!
Well, look who it is.
Our little friends from Halloween.
We told you we'd find you.
And now you're gonna pay
for busting my tire.
But, like, how are they gonna pay?
Yeah. Do you mean, like, with money?
'Cause not everybody
carries cash these days.
No, you morons.
Pay, as in, like, revenge.
Okay. Now we're all on the same page.
Okay. Now what?
I am thinking.
Ooh! Ooh!
-You still got that fire extinguisher?
-
Nah. My mom made me
put it back in the house for "fires."
What's this one looking at?
Uh, it looks like…
Cheese!
-
Now, I really can't say
what happened next.
Because if Rowley ever tries to run
for president when he grows up
and people find out
what those teenagers made him do,
he won't have a chance.
So all I'm gonna say
is that the teenagers made Rowley
-blank, blank, blank the cheese.
-
Okay. You're next.
No. But I just had lunch.
I'm not even really that hungry.
You're not getting out of this.
But, um, I'm lactose intolerant.
It'll make me gassy.
-Huh?
Get out of here, you punks!
You boys okay?
What happened?
-They're gone.
-What's going on?
-What's going on over here?
The cheese!
Look! There's--
There's a piece missing!
What?
- What?
-Disgusting!
- Ew!
Trust me, I was tempted to tell
everyone the truth about what happened,
but then
I heard that annoying inner voice.
Do the right thing, Greg.
That's all you need to get by
in this world, you know?
One good friend.
Somebody has the Cheese Touch.
Rowley Jefferson ate the--
No!
It was me! Those teenagers
dared me to do it, and I did it!
So what? No big deal.
-Greg Heffley has the Cheese Touch!
-
He has the Cheese Touch.
- Oh, ew!
The Cheese Touch!
Okay, so I might have
bent the truth a little,
but sometimes you have to do
that sort of thing to help a friend.
So, uh…
you, uh, wanna go to my place
and, I don't know,
play some Twisted Wizard?
Yeah. That'd be good.
Oh, man. I totally would've had you.
Are you kidding?
You were totally about to start crying.
I had something in my eye.
I could've taken you
with my eyes closed.
I could've beaten you
with my little pinkie.
Having the Cheese Touch
hasn't been as bad as I thought.
Cheese Touch!
The kids at school
give me plenty of space.
And it's not just in the hallways.
I've pretty much got the run of the place.
And the best part is,
getting a seat at lunch
is not a problem anymore.
-Run!
-
In fact,
I've got a whole table to myself.
Well, maybe not entirely to myself,
but I'm fine with it.
And things are good with me and Rowley.
In fact, they're better than good.
But if Rowley ever steps out of line,
I'll let everyone know
who really ate the you-know-what.
Come on. Almost there.
-
-I got you.
-Eat my dust! Get out of my way!
-Oh, you got lucky that time.
How are you this bad?
-Oh!
-Best of three!