Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Hello.
You probably
recognize my face.
Let me introduce myself
in another role.
Not as the actor,
but Omar Sharif
the bridge player.
In recent years,
my partners have included
not only great players
but famous people,
royalty, cabinet
ministers,
famous entertainers.
From my perspective,
nobody cool doesn't play bridge.
Like everyone who plays bridge
is super cool
so cool
that people don't even
understand it.
When I play bridge
I feel that
I maximize my talent.
You're earning a lot of money.
You're living the life.
You're traveling a lot,
hanging out with the richest
people in the world.
Bill Gates, Warren Buffett.
People told me I can be
a good programmer.
I can be
a good financial analyzer.
But to be the best in bridge
in the world,
only one.
Yes,
it's me.
He was great.
For his generation,
he may be the best
bridge player in the world.
He could have been,
the next Michael Jordan
of bridge.
He was that good.
They just kept winning major
events, him and his partner
on whatever team they played
almost to the point,
it was kind of unbelievable
such a young pair,
winning everything.
They were the new stars,
all the way they were
like in the front seat.
Nobody could touch them.
They were at the top.
They had everything
you could want in bridge.
They were making great money.
They were winning
all kinds of things.
What more could you want?
[Crowd cheering]
They were accused
by another player
on another team of cheating.
I see people the writing
that he's a cheater,
he is a cheater,
he is a cheater.
They put it inside my head.
It was all coming to a boil.
There was too much cheating
going on.
And it had to stop.
Like the shit
had to hit the fan.
I didn't cheat,
but I brought it on myself.
Bridge is all my life.
They took my baby,
they took half of me.
I cannot forgive for that.
I came from a family
who liked sports.
My father was
a soccer goalkeeper,
and my mom,
she was a basketball player.
And me,
I wasn't into bridge at all.
When I was about 11 years old,
I saw two girls from my class
and I was asking them
where are you going?
They told me,
"We are going to the mall.
Then we're going
to a bridge lesson."
One of them I really liked.
So I was trying
to make some impression,
I decided, okay I want to go
to the bridge lesson.
So I went up to the lesson,
I entered,
we were learning a little bit
about the rules
and then we started to play.
He was shocked.
He told me,
"Go out! Come with me out."
I thought he was going
to kill me or something.
Maybe he thought
I'm cheating or something,
I didn't know.
And of course
he was speaking to my father
and my father told him,
"No way,
my son will not play cards.
He's playing handball.
He's playing soccer, no way."
"I can make him number one
in the world."
He said it.
When I see numbers,
phone number, credit card,
I close my eyes I can see it.
I can see how you wrote it.
I can hear your voice
when you told it to me
there is no way
I will forget it.
So basically this is
how my memory works, yes.
It was
the 20th of January, 2005.
I was playing
some tournament in Israel.
When I went to the main table
to take a board,
I probably took it
very quickly
because I was excited about
the match, we played very well.
And then when I took the board,
one of the notes
which was on the top
fell on the floor.
So I picked it up
from the floor,
I didn't look,
I hold it in my hand,
I put the board on the table
and I was sitting
on my right hand
which holds the note.
And my right opponent,
he saw that I'm holding
something in my hand
before I even had the chance
to say something,
he got crazy,
he started to shout.
He started to call me
some names.
He called the director
and he said that I'm holding
something in my hand.
They told me,
"Okay, just stand up.
We wanna see what do you hold
in your hand."
I was crying.
I wanted to tell my story.
I wanted to explain
what happened.
I just freezed out.
I had an ethic committee,
I said that I had no intention
to take it.
And I had no intention
to look.
I took responsibility
and I admitted that I could
behave a little more wisely,
when it fell on the floor
to call immediately
to the director.
Everybody knew
that it was something that
I didn't try to hide it
or something like this.
They decided that I didn't cheat
but I might had
some intention to.
And I was suspended
for two years for that.
That is very,
very heavy penalty.
They said
it's because I'm young.
And because I have to learn
how to behave.
When you watch
a really good ballet dancer,
it's this fabulous image,
a mirage almost, right?
And that's what
good bridge is.
It takes anyone
a very long time to kind of
grasp the brilliance
of the game.
Not you, you're not brilliant.
The game itself
is so fantastic, really.
Do you play bridge?
I don't play bridge-
-You don't play bridge.
Well, you have to learn to play.
Welcome to the magical world
of bridge.
It's actually
an extremely complicated game
requiring decades to master.
Our system
will be five card majors,
all jumps
by responder forcing.
Stayman, blackwood,
and weak two-bids.
This means two clubs
will be the old--.
But we really don't have time
for that.
So here's
all you need to know
in order to not look stupid
in front of your friends.
Step one,
you're dealt a hand of 13 cards.
The goal in bridge is to win
the most rounds
holding the highest card.
Here, for example,
the lucky bastard holding
the ace has won the round.
Winning a round
is called a trick.
Step two, you and your partner
sitting across you
must declare how many tricks
you're going to win together
and what's
your strongest suit.
One spade.
We call this a contract.
Now here come
a gazillion more rules
that have nothing to do
with our story.
So let's just forget them
all together.
Oh, wait a sec.
There is one rule
you must remember.
When playing bridge,
you can't just ask your partner
if he's got some diamonds.
In fact, you can't talk to him
at all.
No coughing, no winking,
hell, you can't even
kick him under the table.
Illegally communicating
with your partner
is the one mortal sin of bridge.
That pretty much sums it up,
cheerio.
So I didn't play bridge
for two years,
but always in my mind,
I knew that I want to
go back and play bridge.
It was already
inside my blood.
After I came back
from the suspension,
I wanted to play professionally
and I needed a partner.
Everybody had
a partner already
and Ron was the one
to be available.
So I offered him
to play together.
At the beginning
of our partnership
when I was very, very confident,
some people will say arrogant,
I used to be very aggressive.
I'm looking for someone
to be perfect
as I thought I am,
and it's impossible.
I remember after one tournament,
he told me I quit.
I don't wanna play
with you anymore.
And I needed to apologize.
And then we played again.
I told him
I will never do it again.
I did it again
even worse than that.
I made him cry
a million times.
It's terrible to play with me,
but with time he got stronger
and I was trying
to be more calm,
we improved as partners.
If you want to be good,
you have to put a lot of effort.
We were practicing
10, 12, 15 hours a day.
And once we started to think
about the game the same
and we understood each others'
thoughts about the game,
it was very difficult
to stop us.
They won the Cavendish.
They won the most prestigious
European championship.
And they won the main
tournaments in the USA
some of the biggest that even
some of the players ranked
in the top 20 players
in the world
have never won in their life,
and are dreaming of winning,
they had won already
two or three at their age.
Here we have a Lotan Fisher.
One of the young star players
of Israel.
They just kept winning
major events,
him and his partner.
It seemed like
they never lost almost.
They were considered
one of the very best
partnerships in the world.
And they were in all
of the bridge magazines
on the covers
of the bridge magazines.
And they were famous, yeah.
Me and my partner
had a very nice defense
at the first day
of the tournament
the declarant was very surprised
when my partner
won with the queen.
It was nice.
When I play bridge,
I see nothing than that.
This is something
that is in my blood.
The game takes out of me,
the best part of me.
I think he liked winning.
And I think
he liked being right,
and I think he liked
being smarter,
being better.
You just sort of felt
that way by looking at him
just the way he walked around
and carried himself
that he seemed arrogant.
Like he had an "I'm better
then you" kind of look to him.
You can tell at a young age,
he was very full of himself.
Like you need to be the best.
You're smarter than everyone
because they're idiots
and you're a genius.
This is gonna sound
very, very fucked up.
But if you invest too much
in the idea
of other people adoring you
or liking you or loving you,
you're never gonna win.
You're never gonna get anywhere.
And this is the best lesson
in the world playing bridge
because it's not
about others approving.
It's a little bit arrogant,
but I don't want to compromise
and to be one out
of thousands programmers,
one out of thousands
financial analyzers.
I want to be the best,
the best in the world.
And the winners
of the Gold medal
is the team of Israel.
[Crowd cheering]
I remember I spoke to our
sponsor Richie Schwartz,
and he said, oh, he had
this new team from Israel.
They had really good results.
So that's, to me,
sounded like really good idea.
So I remember speaking
to Lotan on the phone
on Richie's phone.
And I was like wow.
I knew Boye from books.
I knew Boye from stories.
He was a big star
in the bridge world
and he offered us
to join his team.
We just said, yes.
We were just waiting
for that chance.
What I remember was that Lotan,
he was very keen on playing
on that team with us
with me and my partner Espen.
I was calling my friends
and my parents,
my girlfriend, I told everybody
that Boye called me.
I think he's one of the
biggest talents in bridge.
Top top player to me.
From the first moment
we became good friends.
In 2013, 2014,
when we were playing
on the Richie Schwartz team,
we had an amazing run,
[Crowd cheering]
we won three nationals.
We won a lot of European events.
We played well.
You are very young.
You're earning a lot of money,
staying in expensive hotels,
going to expensive
restaurants,
hanging out with the most
richest people in the world.
They're like your friends,
at some way
they are admiring you,
your bridge skills
and they're coming to you
to ask you questions
and they want you
to be part of their team.
If you're a very good
bridge player,
you can be pretty rich,
you get paid
over 2000 bucks a day,
just playing bridge,
travel around.
If you're extremely good,
making a six figure salary
is not that difficult to do
as a professional player
and the best ones making
half a million dollars a year.
There's a lot of money
at stake here.
The difference between
being one of the top pairs
in the world
and just being pretty good
is worth tens, hundreds of
thousands of dollars a year.
So there's definitely
a financial incentive
to win at all costs.
This is something
very, very good,
but could be very dangerous.
In 2015, we got another offer
from Jimmy Cayne.
He called us and he said,
"I'm Jimmy Cayne."
And when he said it
I already knew
he is Jimmy Cayne.
James Cayne, a notorious CEO
of Bear Stearns
was worth more
than a billion dollars
but it all came crashing down,
when Bear Stearns subprime
investment bubble burst in 2007
critics claim that while
Bear Stearns was burning up,
Cayne was literally
playing bridge.
It was a big compliment for us
to get an offer from Jimmy.
And I knew
that we're gonna be his.
Boye was a little bit
angry with me.
He felt that he was the one
to deserve
to get this kind of offer.
It's a better offer and better
money, better teammates.
He said, I played 10, 15 years
more than those guys.
"When they didn't know
how to hold cards,
I was already been
Bermuda Bowl champion.
How come they get it?"
I felt really bad.
First for him.
Second for our friendship.
Third for me, my partner.
No matter what is going
to happen with this story,
things are not going to be
the same again.
Mike Benson live
from the 2015 Spingold.
We've had some intense days
here in Chicago
featuring a record number
of over 10,000 players
and 64 international teams.
I remember,
on the way to Chicago,
I was very excited.
The whole flight,
you talk about bridge.
My heart was pumping.
We had a lot of pressure
on our shoulders.
You're gonna see
10,000 players
the best players in the world,
and you're gonna compete
against them.
As higher that you get
in the stages
your opponents gonna be
tougher and tougher
and tougher and tougher.
Ex-world champions,
ex-nationals champions.
This guy won
the national 14 times.
This guy 20 times,
no matter where you go
you see champions, champions,
champions around you.
You have to bleed
if you want to survive.
On Spingold,
you start a round of 64
and you're gonna play
the whole day.
And then you qualify
for the 32 and 16 and 8.
You're bleeding and bleeding.
And I already saw
that if we are going to qualify
for the quarters,
there is a chance
that we are going to play
against Boye Brogeland.
It's all coming
down to the quarter finals
with the eight
top ranking teams fighting
for their spots in the semis.
All eyes are on the Cayne
and Schwartz knockouts tomorrow
where title holder Lotan Fisher
and Boye Brogeland
are facing each other
for the first time as opponents,
right here in Chicago.
The Cayne team
that Lotan and Ron had gone to
and our team
we both reached quarter final.
And then this quarter final,
we are actually going
to play each other.
That night before the match
against them,
that's the only thing
that people were talking about.
The two had
a fantastic last season
playing alongside
for Richie Schwartz.
But now Brogeland and Fisher
are in a showdown
for a place in the finals.
It was like a match
to decide who is bigger
LeBron or Michael Jordan.
I felt like all my body, like
you know...
I remember that
I looked at myself in the mirror
and I shouted,
"Showtime baby.
It's showtime baby,
now it's time
to prove yourself."
When I play bridge,
I feel like I'm fighting
in the ring boxing.
Fisher and Schwartz
walking a tightrope
as they declare a contract
of five no trump.
Sees someone who's very sharp.
His eyes shining,
like he's not going to give up
A very interesting kickoff
with Lotan leading
with the king of diamonds.
I think it's very interesting
how something as unimportant
in a way as a card game,
how deeply it can get
rooted in yourself.
Playing a hand
and knowing that I played
that hand perfectly.
That's the greatest excitement
for me.
And Boye is back in business,
as he tackles
this three hearts contract
with a finesse made in heaven.
So one of the things
that you you need to do
is to analyze the situation
and you need to calculate it
very quickly.
And this is something that
people think that I'm the best.
Lotan just throwing
a hail Mary
as he plays a seven heart
just to be saved
by his partner's ace.
I mean, sometimes they
don't understand as well
how my brain works,
'cause people like to think that
bridge is only about math.
You cannot use any instincts
and you cannot use
any reading of the situation
which I don't agree.
An absolutely
remarkable move.
You have so many choices
to make in bridge.
When you make choices
of the choices of the choices
and you play
day after day after day
it's very easy
that you make mistakes.
You sit there and you know
you made like a silly mistake.
It's a really emotional game.
You know
that it's really hurting.
You feel it to your bone.
Another gutsy play
by Fisher-Schwartz
making bold moves that
turn out paying off big time.
The two teams
are headed for collision
under now,
just pounding each other.
It becomes
a very very tough match,
like very tight much.
And you start getting tired.
That was ruthless,
Lotan dropping the ball here
as he loses this contract.
It will come down
to single digits,
as both Fisher and Brogeland
refuse to give up their place
in the semis.
And it's finally over.
Both teams
are now holding their breath
as the tournament directors
calculate the final score.
What always frightens me,
is the day that I will feel
that I get worse
that I'm not on top
of my game anymore.
The day I really realized now
it's just downhill from here.
and that will be
extremely tough.
At this moment, we're still
waiting for the results
of the last matches
in the final round
of the open teams.
After 12 hours of playing bridge
with high pressure
the score was 159, 158.
We lost by one IMP.
I believe.
Gutting. Gutting.
There's no smallest margin
than that.
That happens maybe once
in 1000 matches
I felt so bad.
First tournament I'm losing
on the quarterfinals
and not just losing on the
quarterfinals for being unlucky
or whatever it is.
I'm losing to Boye Brogeland.
It was very interesting match.
And I thought we played
like me and my partner,
I thought we played great,
it was really
one of our best matches.
Good luck, guys.
-Thank you very much.
He was so excited,
he was so happy.
He went out like high five
every person he saw,
he was so proud of himself,
but he didn't know one thing.
In our table,
we called to the director
about some move
that our opponents made
that we thought that might
change some decision
in the game.
And that might change
the all result of the match.
And we went
to the appeal committee.
Our teammates told me that
they never won an appeal before
all the time they were
playing for 50 years,
they lost the European
Championship, World Champions
all the tournaments
because of appeals.
I told them, you never played
with Lotan Fisher.
I'm going to appeal.
The appeals committee
is in a tough spot.
No one wants to have
to decide the fate
of a match like that.
I was away from the table.
So this appeal now
goes on about midnight.
I think the final result
I think is about
1:30 in the middle of the night,
and we wait and suddenly I see
Lotan coming out of the room.
The appeal committee
decided that we were right
about some of our arguments.
So they decided that we
deserved to get two points.
I couldn't believe it.
I just won Boye Brogeland.
We started to shout...
Yes!
We won, we won, we won.
I've had a few bad losses
in my life,
but that was one of the
toughest, and I was so hurt.
I remember just looking at Allan
and Richie we had all played,
we all fought,
yeah that felt really,
really bad.
So it was 1:30 in the morning
and I couldn't sleep
because I was so gutted.
And I said, okay,
I'll go and have a look
at the other table,
how we lost this match.
So I just went to my computer,
and had to look what happened.
And yeah, I just scrolled
through and look at some,
and that was strange.
There was a hand where
it was so clear in my view.
And I think that of the top
hundred players in the world
at least 99 would have led
a heart.
But Ron, led something else,
I said that was strange,
I said why is this happening?
I know how good a player
he is.
And that's how it kind
of really got started.
We felt that something
was astray.
I thought, okay
I'll go to the bar.
While I was talking to people
and then I met Bobby Levin,
they said, "Oh did you
see how they cheated you
"on that board?"
I see this hand,
that Lotan Fisher cheats Boye,
so blatantly, it's unbelievable.
And he is going through
the hand and furious.
To me, here something was wrong.
An Israeli guy, he asked me,
"Oh, have you seen the hand
"under they played
against this Dutch pair."
"No, I haven't seen any hand",
"Oh, you should see that hand,
it's clearly,
clear that they're cheating."
They mentioned YouTube videos
that I could go and look at.
You see Lotan coughing to give
certain information to Ron.
Is it cheating?
So you can't have a way of
communicating with your partner
that your opponents
have no knowledge about.
These are the most important
rule about ethics in bridge
and what everybody thinks
that they had a way
to communicate
to each other information
the people wouldn't know.
There were rumors about it
among expert bridge players
for a long time.
It seemed like everybody knew
that these guys were cheating.
When you know
they're cheating,
why haven't you
done anything?
You must do something
when you know they're cheating.
You can't accuse people
of cheating
unless you can absolutely
prove it.
Let's say I turn to them and go,
"You fucking guys are cheating.
You think I don't know it?"
The organizers will immediately
ban us from the tournament.
There's too much cheating
going on.
And it had to stop.
It had to go outside
of the official channels.
Like the shit
had to hit the fan.
If other people are not doing,
I need to do something.
This cannot continue.
I remember that after we beat
Boye on the quarter finals,
he came at the middle of
the match to our opponents
and he told them,
"You have to withdraw.
You have to stop playing."
It was at the lunch break.
Brogeland came to me,
starting to shout at me,
"You're a cheater, cheater.
You know exactly
what I'm talking about."
It was almost
a fight over there.
I wanted to tell him like,
"Boye, the match is over.
We can be friends again,
it's over.
You don't have to keep with
the trash talk and everything."
And sometimes you just
got to do the right thing.
They shouldn't have
played there.
They should have been
disqualified.
I don't think
the organizers realize
how much the players
care about fair game.
He went to each bridge player
and spoke to him
and told him
we have to kick them out.
This is very, very important
for the players.
So what is the proof
against them?
I saw it just-
When you know you see
Even if other people
can't see it,
When you know it yourself,
you investigate it thoroughly
and you just know it.
As a bridge player, you know it.
I don't understand
cheating in bridge,
I just don't understand.
It's such a darn hard game
to learn.
And then you have to learn
the game
and then learn how to cheat.
I mean, that just seems
impossible to me.
When we lost
to Jimmy Cayne's team
that was the quarter-final.
And they went on to playing
against the Zimmermann team
in the final.
It had Fantoni and Nunes,
number one, and number two
in the world rankings.
And they play Cayne in the final
and Cayne won.
So Lotan and Ron
won that tournament.
This Spingold of 2015.
[Crowd cheering]
I see him out in front
of a crowd of people.
I go up to him.
I say, "So Lotan,
this hand you had the other day.
What were you thinking
when you made this play?"
And he couldn't
even answer me,
this fast thinking smart guy.
There are many things
that I cannot explain.
And this is one of the
problems that people
they can't accept it.
Like, why did you do that?
Why did you know to do that
and I didn't?
My intuition made me do that
but this is not an answer
that people accept.
So I said to him,
in front of a lot of people,
"You just proved
what a fucking cheat you are."
And he said, "I will sue you
for a million dollars."
And I said,
"When they find you guilty
you won't be able to collect."
So now, I went back home
and I spoke to my wife.
She had talked to Lotan
when I was in Chicago
and Lotan said,
"Oh Boye's crazy.
"He's accusing me
of this and that."
"And I never seen him like this
before", Lotan told my wife
she said, "Oh he just needs
to calm down a bit
after losing to you,"
or something like that,
that he's, yeah.
So we're going back home
from Chicago
we know that there is
a little buzz.
People are gossiping,
but this is not something
we weren't aware before.
People were talking about us
all the time.
But every time they were
speaking about us for a week
and it's passing,
week, passing
and that's what we thought
is gonna be this time.
And now, I started trying
to get to people that I knew
in the bridge world and saying
that this is what's going on,
We need to do something.
The problem here is that
everybody denies everything.
Nobody wants
to take any blame.
I sent emails,
I phoned really all my contacts
in the bridge world.
"It's Boye Brogeland
calling here."
"Hi, Steve, it's Boye here."
Have you heard anything from
the ACBL or from other people?
I spoke to the federations
to a guy in the European
Bridge League.
And his answer to this was that,
"Well, file a complaint.
We'll see what we can do."
Well,
you need to do something,
we can't have this happening.
The World Championships
are coming up in two months
from here in Chennai.
Like we need
to stop this before,
we cannot have
the World Championships
be tainted by cheats.
Now we have a chance,
we have a great chance
Lets get the Israelis
and that's fine.
The case with Israelis
that is almost case closed,
I would say.
Stop covering up here.
But Bob, speak to them,
speak to them
and let's do something
that's good for bridge.
I got some people here
from a town where I lived.
They helped me.
We were able to set up a site
called bridgecheaters.com
where we provided what we
thought was information,
but of course it was also
accusations about
something illegal going on.
I didn't think
of the consequences, really.
I just thought
we need to do something
and we know
we need to do it now.
First day that we launched
the website,
I think we had a 100,000 hits.
I was the Australian captain
played the transnationals
in the Netherlands
and our team lost the semifinal
to Fisher-Schwartz.
I didn't really think much of it
but when this thing broke with
Fisher and Schawrtz from Boye
I went back and I watched
the match against our team.
And there were at least 15 hands
where weird things happened.
It was like, man, you're one
of the best players I've seen.
You didn't need to cheat.
Like, I didn't know
why you would do it.
Like, why would you cheat
when you're so good?
There was such an uproar.
It was almost like a revolution.
Top players, medium players
maybe not so good players,
but very keen passionate
bridge players
express the same feeling.
Cheating should not be part
of a game.
It exploded for sure.
I'm gonna talk about
the cheating scandal,
that's been all over
the internet.
You know where to look
in websites.
So last month, two players
that Cayne had hired
for his competitive team.
They were accused by
another player on another team
of cheating.
Fisher and Schwartz are denying
the charges vigorously,
but the damage has been done
for the moment at least.
They're not playing.
Cayne, now 81
is out two top teammates.
And at this point
in their season,
it could be hard
to replace them.
And he may even have
to give back
a big trophy that he won
in Chicago, in August.
Few days ago,
Mr. Brogeland published
some special gift for me.
He opened a website,
bridgecheaters.com
The greatest scam
in the history of bridge.
Basically the whole website
is like story of our life
and also Brogeland
and is saying that
for the two years
he played with us,
people keep telling him,
"They are cheaters,
how can you play with them?"
And he's saying that he was
checking the hands all the time
and he didn't find
anything suspicious.
And still Boye
is claiming now,
that we cheated
on those hands.
It's easy for me
to speak about it. But...
inside my heart,
you have no idea
what I'm going through.
It's not so easy.
I'm trying to show
business as usual
but it's not like that.
It's very difficult to sleep.
It's in your mind 24/7.
I don't know.
It's not so easy
as it looks like.
I got a warning letter
from Lotan and Ron.
"Stop all actions on your
part which are harmful
including publication
of any claim
which is defamatory.
Immediately publish
a correction, denial,
and apology on any platform
on which you made
the original publications,
including
on the designated website."
They write compensation
in the sum of $1 million.
It is to be clarified
and nothing in this amount
expresses anything other
than a small part of damages
and mental anguish
which has been caused to me."
To me, this is what's so sad
about the whole thing
that we were friends
in my view, like good friends.
We were all like one big,
and I hope like a happy family
kind of.
So that's also what's so hard
when you, like
when you realize
that actually your friends
are willing to do this
against you.
They're entitled to a process.
I know, but...
Don't you think that I think
they are entitled to it?
Absolutely.
But when you know it,
you know it.
If someone came
into your house
and you saw that guy,
you knew him.
It was a friend of yours,
okay?
And he stole your things
and he went out.
He stole,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no,
I can't put him in jail.
I'm not putting anybody in jail.
I think that you have
because you-
I'm having, how can I?
You have convicted them
in a public forum.
You've convicted them.
So you're not entitled
when you saw this thief
that you know, you knew
it was your neighbor.
I know the process,
just go and have a trial.
What do I? I have no power
to judge, no power.
But you have judged.
-No, I haven't judged.
You have judged
in the public arena.
There's a huge difference
in today's world.
Hello, Giannarigo how are you?
Are you ready now?
It's impossible to take
any sanction
without the decision of a judge.
If found out something
got in here, okay,
there's the prosecutor
where they can be guilty or you.
I know a 100 precent
maybe you don't know,
but I know.
And I understand the game,
I can tell you that.
I understand the game,
and I know
that these guys have been
cheating big time, big time.
You can be as much lawyers
as you want to
but if you think that Fisher
and Schwartz didn't cheat
then I must say,
you don't understand the game.
And the problem here
if there is any case,
the decision has to be
taken by a judge, a judge.
Why?
-Why, because is the law.
My attitude is to say that
if they are cheats,
someone sanctions them,
because I can't believe that.
I couldn't believe,
I couldn't believe myself.
It's just,
yeah, okay thanks.
Yeah, thank you.
See you later in the week.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, hope so.
When the federations saw
how much buzz this created
and saw the uproar
by the players,
I think they realized that
we need to do something.
And then the day after
I got an invitation
from the Israeli
Special Committee.
All of them were
well known bridge players.
Two of them were lawyers,
they put on the table
all the allegations.
Spoke loudly about
what is going on.
And I remember one guy
of the committee said,
"You two are done with bridge.
The only place that you two
can sit in front of each other
is in the restaurant
downstairs."
And we we're starting
to get ready for a war.
The war of our life.
These two young players
come to me
and they say, "Don't believe
anything you're going to read.
We didn't cheat."
"Okay, why should I believe you?
They said,
"Take us to a lie detector."
I said,
"Are you willing to do that?
You know if you're going
to fail the lie detector
I would find it very hard
to keep on defending you."
They said,
"Take us to a lie detector."
So we decided we gonna do it.
It wasn't an easy decision,
especially not for Ron.
Because sometimes
even when you're correct
if you're very emotional,
the results can be different.
So I had to explain him a lot,
that we are innocent
and don't worry.
Lotan is a, I mean,
I wouldn't trust him
as far as I could far as
I could throw him obviously,
he's a fast talking,
fast thinking guy,
who is always looking
to impress everybody
with his quick talking,
quick analysis.
And Ron Schwartz was very
soft-spoken, almost didn't speak
like a nitwit.
While Lotan was
a gifted player, no question.
Ron is not, not even close.
He wasn't, I don't even know
if he was a good player.
You could tell that he just
didn't quite have the instinct.
He would every now and then
make a play
that we would say no,
like it cannot win.
It can only break even
at best.
The kind of thing that a real
expert player would just not do.
It was the cup in Moscow.
Schwartz lay down contract
on the last board
that 99% of player in the top
100 in the world would win.
He made incredible mistake
and went down with the contract
on the last board
to give us the title.
Ron Schwartz,
he's a terrible bridge player.
It was just impossible
he was winning
all those tournaments.
So you ask yourself,
why would a guy
like Lotan Fisher
play with a schlub
like Ron Schwartz?
Well, there's only
one logical conclusion,
here's a guy that's willing
to cheat with him.
They were both caught cheating
many times in their youth.
Obviously when he was
allowed back,
his plan was,
I wanna become rich and
famous playing this game.
Who's gonna do this with me?
He needed to find someone
he could control the brain of,
saying, I think Ron Schwartz
was a perfect victim for this.
What I did to humiliate Ron,
was against us
because when I came in front
of everybody, shouting at him
and tell everybody
how bad he is,
people started to think,
"How come he's that bad,
and they are
so good together?"
Sometimes I made mistakes
as well.
Again, I'm not perfect,
I just thought I am.
And my best way to deal
with that was shouting at him.
And sometimes he was playing
really perfect.
Sometime I was shouting
at him for over tricks
for mistakes that didn't
even cost us nothing.
But when people saw it,
they thought like
how come they are that good?
How come they're
so successful?
They must be cheating.
They were asked three questions.
Have you ever at any time
received from your partner,
Mr. Schwartz Ron
information during a bridge game
by means of coughs?
He answered in the negative.
Have you ever at any time
during the bridge game
provided improper
or illegal information
to your partner,
Mr. Schwartz Ron?
He answered in the negative.
Have you ever at any time,
during a bridge game,
provided improper
or illegal information,
by means of a bottle of water?
He answered in the negative.
I remember,
I didn't want to think about
what comes up
with the results.
The only thing on my mind
is to clear my name.
I got a phone call
from my lawyer.
He was asking me if I'm alone.
So I told him, wait a second.
And I went out.
And the lawyer told me
that we passed it, absolutely.
The results were absolutely,
that they're telling
the truth.
I was so ashamed,
so embarrassed
about all the situation
because my parents were
so proud of me
when I was so successful
and then something like that
comes up
and it's in the newspapers
and everywhere.
Every place they used to go,
"Oh, your son is a cheater,
your son is a cheater."
And we both started to cry.
I don't know.
I don't know that a lie
detector test is a 100%.
I've seen situations
in my lifetime
where innocent people
have failed lie detector tests.
So I don't see why guilty people
shouldn't pass them.
Isn't a doubt in my mind
passing the lie detector test
doesn't mean a thing to me.
I'm absolutely sure that somehow
they cheated that too.
So what happens,
more evidence coming every day.
Yeah, yeah, we have more
evidence coming every day
because a lot of people
like digging into it.
Like everybody can see that
they're cheating, like big time.
And what do they have left?
The only thing they-
Some people are beside them,
but you know-
I don't know about that,
I think like 98%.
The information from these hands
he had looked at
was not enough.
He had damning hands.
He had lots of stuff.
But in of themselves
were not sufficient.
My wife and also friends
that I had said,
oh you need
to find the evidence.
And to me that wasn't
so important.
To me the evidence
were clear through the hands,
through all the irrational
non-logical
actions that they took.
This is not like
proper bridge.
It almost feels like the car
is not in the right gear.
It's like we're playing,
but we're not,
we're just revving that
there's just something wrong
at the table.
I can't tell you what it is.
Of course
we couldn't prove anything
but we knew
they kept doing things
that were impossible.
The hand, that my partner
was very upset with him about
was a hand
when Lotan led a club,
a correct play based on math
would be to play a diamond.
A club was actually
a very bad bridge play.
It happened to be right
because his partner had
an unusual combination
that made it correct.
How, how is this possible
if they weren't cheating?
So we played once or twice
with Mr. Alder
and his wife kitty.
And he wrote a column
about bridge,
for years
for "The New York Times".
And this one time
we were playing the hand
and I finessed a card
in a certain direction.
And he literally
almost started screaming
in the middle of the game.
He's like, "Excuse me,
that should not work."
And I was like,
"Well, it did, it worked."
And you could see
his mind just go
like tha, you know?
But I tried something
and it worked
which wasn't supposed to work.
All bridge players do
illogical things,
but they also end up
most of the time
looking really stupid
when they do.
These guys ended up
winning world championships
by doing illogical things.
You can almost think
about it in the same way
as someone who does
too well at the stock market,
they probably know something
that they shouldn't.
And one defense could be.
I'm just better than you are.
I'm just smarter.
You don't understand
because you're not at my level.
I'm so much better
at playing bridge.
Of course, it looks illogical
to you, but I'm so good,
you don't even understand
my brilliance.
I remember
that I was very emotional,
and I came there
with heavy feelings.
Even though I felt
that the bridge community
are a little bit biased,
I was happy.
I was happy
to have the first time
to tell my side of the story.
I remember their face.
They didn't even understand
what I'm saying.
Not because I was talking
Chinese or something like that,
because they don't even
understand the logic,
how I think about the game.
I led the hand
because I'm a genius
but he is a cheater.
Hi this is Steve,
please leave a message,
thank you.
It's Boye here,
I just wondered
if there was any more news
about the video footage.
If there's nothing to cover up
then just send those tapes so
we can check them with experts
and go over the tapes
with experts.
And if I find out that,
okay, the tapes are for real,
okay,
that's everybody's happy.
We just go, we'll get
the Israelis and that's fine.
We all lucked out
in that the year before
the European championships
had been filmed
for the first time.
What it meant was
that for the first time ever,
we had data.
Watching 100 hours of hell
is hard work.
And probably it takes
a particular character flaw
to enable you to do it.
None of us got paid.
I just, I worked nonstop
for the better part of a month
just going through hand after
hand after hand and just
getting evidence and looking
at what they were doing
and watched thousands of hours
of video.
And then when I worked
out yet, some of the time,
you had to actually watch
in slow motion
to see what was happening.
Some hands we thought
there was signaling
but you can get paranoid
at every little thing
that players do
and what means something
and what doesn't mean something.
And that's where
it gets difficult.
Placement of cards on a board,
the way things were turned.
To drinking bottle
on the table, on the floor.
The way you do
with your hands.
The bidding cards
wide or narrow.
You can do like this on
your shirt or move your watch
or do your fingers.
But if you move the bidding box
this way or that way
that could mean something.
If you wanna cheat
you can find a way.
Sounds were a big issue
we looked at,
sniffles, scratches, coughs.
I suspected that
whenever they coughed,
they had a very bad hand.
We were all making fun of it
'cause they were wearing
scarves in June
and stuff to pretend
that they were ill
but we all knew
it was not the case.
All over the world,
I got thousands of emails
and phone calls from China,
to Australia, the U.S, Europe.
And we felt, we knew,
we didn't know how.
Stopped mowing the lawn,
stopped paying the bills
like this, to me, this was
going into a kind of a bubble.
I wasn't afraid of losing
any, like my money.
They could take my money.
They could take my house,
they could take anything.
It was very strange for me
to get a lot of phone calls
from Brogeland.
[Phone rings]
During the day he's writing
those kinds of stuff.
And then later in the evening
he's calling me.
"Hey, Lotan, how are you?
How are you hanging on?
I am not mad at you.
I think you should come up
for the game.
You need to do
the right thing.
Everybody will appreciate
that you came forward
and you admitted."
I hope that he would come out
and say,
sorry, guys, we cheated.
And then we can build
on something from there.
And they would have to take
the certain number of years off.
And hopefully
that they could come back
and play a clean game.
Maybe not together,
but at least come back.
He would call them
and always give them a chance
to come clean and always say,
"If you admit what you've done
we would support and help
in whatever influence
we may have."
The ACBL encouraged people
to come forward
to say, "Hey, if you
come forward and admit this,
there will be leniency for you."
To come and say that I cheated
in bridge, when I didn't
is like, say
I worth nothing.
Bridge was
and still is everything.
I breathe bridge.
I go to sleep bridge.
My whole life is bridge.
And coming up and say
that I cheated in something,
which is everything for me,
is like giving up
everything inside me.
He never really
admitted anything.
It was still that we were wrong,
and we just put out accusations
that were just nothing in it
that we was just making up stuff
destroying their career
with this.
To me with this, like
with the "Me Too" campaign,
these kinds of things like,
sometimes people need
to wake up.
Like we need to see
that the culture we have here
is just wrong,
we need to do something.
And...
And when the authorities,
when the bridge federations
organizations
are not willing
to do anything,
what's the alternative?
What alternatives do you have?
I went to a cabin of ours
to try and get some sleep
and relax a little bit
because I had been working
so many hours.
I just slept like maybe
three, four hours a night.
And I couldn't sleep
because I was so gutted
and felt really really bad.
There was a Swede with
the name of Per-Ola Cullin
that in the middle of the night
sent me a text message
saying that,
"Wow, I know their code."
The normal thing is
to put it in the middle.
So here he puts it
very far left.
You could see
that it just couldn't be
random placement of the board.
This is huge evidence.
I remember I was crying.
And I phoned Ishmael Del'Monte
in Australia
and said this is
what comes here.
Can you have a look at this?
I remember like,
when he told me the code,
I was like, "My God,
that's so simple."
And he sent this
to Kit Woolsey in the U.S.A
And he looked through it
and tested it.
Because of the videos,
it is red-handed the evidence
is right in front of you.
This is the action,
the physical action
that was taken.
This is the hand
that the person actually held,
do they match?
In my opinion
that was a 100% evidence
that they were
doing something.
You wouldn't have to even
know the rules of bridge
to be able to look
at these videos
and say, yes
this is what they were doing.
I saw that and I was like, okay,
we nailed them a 100%.
Oh my God, yes, like
how did I not notice that?
How can I miss this?
It seems so obvious
once you know it.
[Laughing out loud]
You hear my evil glee,
the evil happiness in my laugh.
It's almost like those
"Where's Waldo?"
If you're looking for Waldo
and you get,
then when you find him,
you're like,
"Oh, he was right in the middle
of the page all along."
I remember the morning
when I woke up
was one of the most
happiest days of my life.
That finally we will get rid
of those bastards.
Poof...
Honestly, I can say
that it's very easy to believe
that we cheated.
Let's say I'm not Lotan.
And I'm not the one
who is in the story.
And I hear like
over and over again,
over and over again
no matter where I go
on the internet,
I read about it,
I read about it.
I see people writing that,
"He's a cheater, he is cheater,
he is a cheater."
They put it inside my head
and then I see
those kinds of videos.
I need nothing more than that.
I will be sure 100%
that they are cheating.
And no matter what people
will try to show me after,
I will still have it in my mind.
At that time I worked at CERN
the biggest lab of particle
physics in the world.
I was one of the main developers
of the statistical framework
of the search and discovery
of the Higgs boson,
so-called the god particle.
This is the particle
that gives all other
particles their mass.
And in a way,
one can show that
this is one of the basic things,
thanks to which we are living,
we exist.
I got a call from a lawyer.
And he asked me if I'm willing
to check some statistical issue
that has to do with bridge.
I told him, I don't understand
anything about bridge.
Turned out that this problem
of bridge has a lot to do
with what we do
when you search
for new particles
because it asks
the same question.
What is the probability
that the phenomenon
that we observe
is a fluctuation of nothing?
Or is it a real thing?
Are they cheating
or not cheating?
When I looked at the numbers,
I told them,
That I think the analysis
the people did on the case
is wrong.
I don't think there
was enough data to make
a fair statistical analysis
here.
The one that was done
was not kosher.
It's stinking.
We were filmed
over 250 boards,
they picked only 37 boards
out of those 250.
37 boards.
And from those 37 boards,
we showed them
and we proved them
that only six boards
confirmed their code
that they claimed
that we are cheating.
Now six boards out of 250,
this is not the pattern.
This is totally random.
I told them
"You look at the data
and you throw away
the cases that disturb
the hypothesis
you want to claim."
This is something
you don't do in statistics.
I felt like I'm talking
to a void.
Talking for nothing.
Nobody cares
about the statistics.
You look, and it looks
like they were cheating
and this is it.
Nobody cares about
probabilities, et cetera.
It just smells bad,
so it's bad.
This is it.
Unfortunately, there are
some cases that my memory
is not good for me,
because if I can
remember numbers
or if I can remember
credit cards,
I can also remember
the bad moments
that I had in my life.
Even if I want,
and even if I try to delete them
from my mind,
it will be impossible.
I remember everything.
So I remember
it was February, 2017.
I got the message from
the Israeli bridge chairman.
He told me that
I got an email
with the decision,
and I have two hours
to prepare for the media.
And probably some people
will call me.
So I'm reading this email
and I feel my heart
is pumping so quickly.
I'm putting my hand
on the screen
and starting to read
word by word.
And then I get to the paragraph
that they found us guilty
and I see: coaching -
banned for life,
watching - banned for life,
playing bridge -
banned for life.
It's like losing part of you,
like something inside you
is dead.
Like they take your heart
outside
and they break your heart.
I hate to lose.
I was very, very disappointed
from the results
very dissapointed.
I think they really hoped
that people will listen to me
but I understood
that I'm not gonna help them
because it's been
decided already.
In the middle of my interview
some point they stopped
the interview,
a guy comes and take the trophy
away from them.
And it is such
a humiliating moment.
It took every achievement
away from them.
It was like a murder,
they murdered them
from the bridge point of view.
They completely, they killed
the career completely.
They were not guilty
beyond any doubt.
No way, no way.
I didn't feel like
it was a satisfaction.
Not at all, I would say. It was,
I thought it was very difficult,
to go out against my friends.
I looked at them as friends
and in a way destroy
their bridge career.
I think at some point,
you have to make a stand
when you see
that things are wrong.
I was angry.
How dare a couple of people
try to take down our sport.
I felt that they were really
trying to take down bridge.
Do they understand
that they're unique
in the sense that they're
the only ones cheating?
Well, are they unique?
I mean, that's the fear.
I mean, that was my fear
as CEO is how unique was it?
Did we just uncover
the top layer of something?
And then
when you dug down deeper,
we would find
it was more rampant.
How deep does this go?
I think it kind of happened
when people saw
that it was actually possible
to prove
that someone was cheating
based on the videos.
And what did we do?
That people got
interest in maybe
in looking at other pairs too.
Now that we realize
what a gold mine,
these videos from the
European Championships are,
we get somebody
who's cracked the code on
Fantoni and Nunes.
Fantoni and Nunes,
was number one and number two
in the world rankings.
Boye called me and he told me,
"Pierre, may I kindly
request you to withdraw
from the Bermuda Bowl?"
I say, "What, whom,
what happens?"
He say, Fantoni and Nunes
are cheating.
There was a Dutch woman,
and she'd started looking
into Fantoni and Nunes.
And she came up with
was a very strange,
the way they put their cards.
They were very deliberate
about whether they would put
the cards vertically
or whether they put
the cards horizontal.
They were giving
their partner information
from the angle of the card
when it was on the table.
So I phoned up Fulvio Fantoni
after this came and I said,
you need to come out
and admit to some wrongdoings
and say that, sorry, yeah
we have been doing something.
Hello Fulvio,
it's Boye calling you,
Hi, Boye.
I'm not sure really
where to start yet,
but yeah, that I came over
things that I think,
with you and Claudio
that I thought was suspicious.
Yeah, he said
that he didn't cheat.
Like they didn't cheat.
It was all something
that we just cook together
and that we were jealous
and nobody admitting anything.
Good day, it's Peter here and
today I'm gonna talk
about another
cheating scandal
that's rocked
the bridge world.
The number and number two
ranked players in the world
were accused of cheating.
It's all shaken up the bridge
community in a big way.
Wow, this is all coming down.
Boye was a man on a mission.
Once we had people,
and even sometimes before,
he confronted them,
gave people a chance
to tell the truth.
And in all cases but one,
everyone denied and lied.
What happens now
when we clear
that our pair is not cheating?
No, that's not clear.
That's not clear at all.
Someone sent me a file yesterday
and when I looked
at that file,
I would say
it doesn't look good.
So why did people cheat?
Because they couldn't take
the rigors of brilliant play.
They couldn't take it,
I guess.
And they're the wrong people
the wrong people
cheat at bridge.
You just don't want them
in the world.
You just want them to go away
and play their own game.
I talked to Lotan
during this process,
I said, I hoped that he would
do something actively,
maybe that he could help
the bridge community
when maybe catching
other cheats also.
He's incredibly smart.
The guy, this Lotan
and we actually had
quite a long talk
and he gave me a lot of
information on the other pairs.
And he said if you wanna know
who I think is cheating
Fantoni-Nunes,
Balicki-Zmudzinski,
Piekarek-Smirnov,
and there was a Bulgarian pair
who they actually no longer
play together.
He even told me
an exact hand to go
and look the video
of Piekarek and Smirnov.
And I went and watched this hand
and he told me exactly
what he thought
their code was.
Lotan is laughing
because he knows exactly
what he's done
and because of how
he had placed the bid
and what Lotan thought
their code was.
He was pretty sure
he knew what he had.
Yeah.
Good day, it's Pete here,
I'm here to discuss
the breaking news of a
third pair, cheating allegation.
Good day, it's Pete here,
and I'm back to talk about
the new recent installment
of the cheaters.
Good day, it's Pete here,
today I want to do
a bridge cheating update.
And there is a new cheat.
New development and another pair
has been accused of cheating.
Do you think
some of the sponsors
might have been looking
the other way?
Absolutely,
and the professionals too.
I mean, there will be some
that will deny it
and say it never occurred to me
that they were cheating,
but I don't believe them.
Were they aware?
I can't say
what's in someone's head,
but I think it's impossible
they weren't hearing
the same rumors I was hearing.
So if they hired them,
they did it at their own risk.
These people don't wanna know
if they're cheating or not
and don't really maybe care.
They just wanna win so badly.
Maybe they don't care
how they win.
Maybe you get addicted to it.
Maybe you get addicted to
that winning and you can't stop.
A great player
had his sponsor hire a pair
that was highly suspected
to be cheating.
And his comment was,
"We couldn't beat the cheaters,
so we had to hire them."
Well everybody else
is hiring cheaters,
why shouldn't I hire cheaters?
It was very sad
for me personally,
but for for
the bridge community,
you have so many decent players.
You have so many
nice people around.
Some of those people
are being robbed
of their chances to win.
People had put in
their heart and soul
and their energy
and their life
into trying to become great
at something
and really caring
were playing on this field
that wasn't leveled.
And they were losing to people
that were not doing it fairly.
We were looking at the World
Bridge Federation's website
and they showed past winners
of various events.
And we were looking okay,
cheaters, cheaters, cheaters.
There was so many cheaters
accepting awards
and then this pictures.
And it was just really sad.
We got phone calls and emails
from people that said
they didn't want
to play the game anymore
because they were devastated.
They flew
to foreign countries.
They competed for days
and days and sweated, and tried.
And then you find out
that the team that you lost to
in the finals or semi-finals
were convicted.
It's almost like losing
to Lance Armstrong
in a bicycle race.
You worked all your life
to win the Tour de France,
[Crowd cheering]
you finished second or third
to somebody
that's later found to have
been gaming the system.
[Crowd cheering]
Every single world championship
of the last 30 years
has been invalidated
because we now know that
there were cheaters that
were in those tournaments.
And in most cases did very well
in those tournaments.
It's like invalidating 30 years
of bridge history.
It's like saying, you know,
Wimbledon didn't happen
over the last 30 years
because we now know that,
all the great players
were cheating.
I think that there are
a couple more pairs
that I would like to see
not play together.
And people of interest.
Are there suspicions going on
against new players
or now we're in this magic hour
in which nobody
suspects anybody?
I can't comment on that.
I play every day,
like three or four hours
sometimes till the late hours
of the night.
There are more
than 10,000 players online.
Some of them professionals,
you can see they have stars.
You can watch them
if you want.
You can see here,
now playing in other table
Jimmy Cayne is practicing
with his partner.
I'm playing with
a Bolivian partner
and he's playing so bad.
I would assume he is playing
bridge less than one year.
And if he's playing more
than that, he should quit.
If I was playing with him live
I will probably shout at him
like I used to do.
And sometimes
I really miss it,
what can I do?
Some people are not
that talented and it's okay.
I mean,
oh my God.
The things that he did
just right now,
it's like unbelievable.
This is embarrassing.
I can try to get
to play with some pros
or something like that,
but usually nobody will want
to play with me online.
You go with like an alias
or you go with your real name?
Usually I play with my own name,
lately people don't like
to play against me.
So I'm playing sometimes
on my friend's account.
And this is sad
but this is the reality
and I need to face it.
Do you ever play with Ron
as a partner online?
No, I mean, Ron hurt a lot
from the story and he lost
his passion to bridge.
I'm even afraid to ask
if he wants to play
because I know the answer.
Now I'm going to be dummy.
So my partner
he bought the contract
and he's going to take
responsibility for my cards.
And of course
it's better
that I will close the computer
with what he is doing.
And no, it's like sometimes
I take it as a nightmare
and sometimes I take
it just like a comedy.
Like you go to,
oh, my God.
I don't want to be rude
and ask him like,
to leave the table.
But it's like, it's a nightmare.
I mean,
I can be even very cynic
and tell him that,
well done partner.
I miss playing bridge.
I miss it that much,
that I don't even care
who I'm going to play with.
There is a screen anyway,
so I'm not going
to see my partner.
I don't care if you put Boye
Brogeland behind the screen,
you're going to put
the committee behind the screen.
I don't care,
I just play the cards.
And whoever I found out after
the game behind the screen,
Like, who cares?