Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[knocking on door]
Oh, Alex. Hi.
Come on in.
Hey, sorry to interrupt you.
I thought I'd catch you
before you went home.
Oh, no problem. What's up?
I just wanted to talk to
you real quick about the test.
What is it, Alex?
I just...
think you might have misjudged
some of my essay questions.
Alex...
I'm sorry.
I just-
I can't get a C in this class.
I'm a senior.
It's going to bring
down my average,
and I need a great average
for college applications.
Plus my father is...
Look...
I stand by the grade I gave you.
If you want to do some-
No, I deserved a better grade!
[tense music]
Alex, settle down.
No, I'm no going
to settle down! Okay?
You're going to take this test,
reassess your grading system,
and give me the
grade I deserved!
-Alex.
-Now!
[tense instrumental music]
Here we are again, Alexander.
The fifth outburst
this year. My own son.
Charles, stop.
I'm just saying.
If he wants a better
grade, he has to earn it.
Not whine about it in
front of the whole school!
[tense music]
Shut up.
What did you say to me?
I said shut up!
[grunting]
Alex! What are you doing?
[tires squeal]
[mother screams]
Alex! What are you...
[mother screaming]
[car crashing]
[unsettling instrumental music]
You could stay home.
Mom, stop!
I can teach you
things from here.
Oh yeah, because you
double-majored in business
and anthropology.
Sorry.
We just had such a great summer.
The best.
Okay, I can't take
this. I'm coming with you.
Okay, enough. Let's just...
Let's rip off the bandaid!
Best friends?
Forever.
Christmas break
for sure, right?
Yeah.
And text every day, even
if it's just an emoji.
Every day.
I will, I swear.
Okay, I'm ripping the bandaid.
I love you, Mom.
And I had the best summer!
And thank you.
I love you too, sweetie.
Good luck on your
presentation! Okay?
You're going to kill it.
[car starts]
[emotional piano music]
[car horn honks]
Okay.
Pull yourself together, Maya.
Big day for her.
Big day for you.
[upbeat instrumental music]
Hey, how'd it go?
I'm going to miss her.
She's such a sweetie.
She brought me a gift
bag and thanked me
for finding time in your
schedule this week. [chuckles]
Are you good?
Yeah. I'll be fine.
Let me have it.
Okay.
Board meeting presentation's
in 15 minutes.
Jason will be there.
Perfect.
Look, he likes you!
You get this deal
with the hospitals,
you're looking at
an easy promotion.
Which means I get a promotion,
so get yourself together.
Hi!
Morning, Jane.
Well that's a
little presumptuous.
Look, I'll get you a coffee.
Presentation is queued
in the board room.
Anything else?
What would I do without you?
That would be a sad sight.
Before I forget, the
new intern is in today.
I'll bring him by
after the presentation.
You can meet him.
You take just good care of me,
I don't think there'll be
anything for him to do.
Exactly. Remember that.
Besides, all project
managers get fall interns.
We're stuck with him, but
he can do the dirty work.
All right.
As you can see, our
software is years ahead.
Health Ridge Hospitals
isn't just a
billion-dollar businesses.
It's 20 billion.
With locations stretched
from coast to coast,
border to border, millions
of patients' records.
Nobody has the
connectivity, speed,
and resources
Newmark can provide.
Newmark will allow hospitals
easy, simple access
to their patients' records
in a seamless fashion.
Thank you so much
for being here today,
and we look forward to
doing business together
in the future.
[bright instrumental music]
[applauding]
Thank you for that.
You made me look good in there.
So when can we meet with them?
Couple of weeks.
Presentation's
already in the works.
Good. I want you
to head it off.
Jason...
You do what you did in
there, it's a sure thing.
I'm not a pitch man.
I just write the code.
This deal goes through, I
want you on point for it
the whole way through,
national and international.
I appreciate it.
Thank you!
You've earned it.
And Becky and I will have you
over for dinner to celebrate.
Sounds good.
Alex?
Hi. I'm Kate.
Hi.
Maya Taylor's
project coordinator.
Ready?
Yes.
Okay.
Well she's pretty busy, so
report to me with questions.
I have her schedule
down to the last minute.
No need to ask her if she
wants coffee or anything.
She likes to get out of the
office a few times a day.
You with me?
Yes. 100%.
Sorry if I'm just
rattling all of this off.
I don't mean to be short.
No, it's okay. I can tell.
I can learn a lot from you.
Let me show you
where you're working.
You know, I was actually
her first intern.
I've been there. You'll be fine.
The internship is three months.
We've got an expansion
office in the works.
Any jobs or promotions
will happen through there.
This is you.
You put in the work,
I'll make sure you get your
chance at the new office.
Cool?
Cool.
[knocking on door]
It's Emma.
Tell her that her sister
from another mister says hi.
Kate says hi.
Okay, sweetie.
All right, well, I
just wanted to call
and see if you were okay.
Yeah. Drive safe.
Text me when you
get there, okay?
All right, love you. Bye.
[gentle piano music]
Maya Taylor.
I'm a project manager here.
Hi.
Okay, let's see
what we got here.
Impressive.
Business major. I was too.
And you went to
Eastwood University.
My daughter is on her
way there right now.
Oh, she'll love it
there, Mrs. Taylor.
Miss. And, please, it's Maya.
So you graduated...
Three years ago.
Then I signed up for
two-year active duty
with the Army Reserves.
University's ROTC helped
me get ready for that.
Wow. Appreciate the sacrifice.
My father was in
the service. Army.
Hooah!
[Maya chuckles]
I just flashed
back to my childhood.
Heard that a lot in my house.
Did he serve in Vietnam?
Yeah. Tough war.
Much respect to him.
I...
I didn't see any action.
Spent most of my
time in an office
fetching coffee for
a Lieutenant Colonel.
They have me on
reserves for now.
Your family from around here?
No!
Uh...
A few hours away.
That's where I grew up.
Well, this looks great.
Happy to have you for
the next few months.
It'll be mostly go-fer duties.
Kate runs a pretty tight ship.
But we'll do our best
to give you some more
important things to do
so you can learn a bit.
Yes, Ma'am.
Okay. Ma'am is
even worse than Miss.
Sorry.
Force of habit.
But I am very excited.
My last internship, it was...
Wait. I don't see it on here.
Oh, uh...
unfortunately they went under,
so I wasn't sure
if I should add it.
All right.
Well, did Kate tell you
about the company perks?
Uh, no. There's...
There's perks?
Mm-hm.
Lunches are on the company.
We have an account at most of
the restaurants in the area.
And on the first floor
we get full access
to the Athletic Club.
I'm there every night
trying to turn back the clock.
[Alex chuckles]
I think that's it.
You can go talk to
the receptionist.
She can help you finish
off your paperwork.
Paperwork?
Yeah. Just the basic stuff.
I mean, I know the
internship doesn't pay much,
but we still got to get your
address, bank information
background check,
that kind of thing.
Is that an issue?
Uh, no, no. It's just...
I closed my accounts at the
last just before the move,
and I haven't had a chance
to open a new one yet.
You can work it out with her.
We have that call with
the hospital in a few.
Ah, completely lost track
of time. That's right.
Okay, well, great meeting you,
and enjoy those free lunches.
And the Athletic Club.
Yes. [chuckles]
Maya?
Yes?
Can I get you a
coffee or anything?
No. Thank you though.
Here you go. Just
fill these out.
Okay.
Yeah, I need to grab some
information for these two.
Kate said it would okay
to hold off for now.
Let me just get her
approval on that quick.
[phone ringing]
Hey, hey.
Jeez!
Listen, you earn
your paycheck.
Let me earn mine, all right?
Hey.
Hey, Kate.
Alex said he needed some time
on the bank information and...
Yeah, don't worry
about it, Jane.
Thanks.
Look, he's already
causing problems.
Oh stop.
He seems sweet. Here.
Okay.
Just fill out the
rest of the stuff
and get those to
me when you can.
Sounds good.
Can a grab you a coffee?
Easy, go-getter. I'm
just the receptionist.
Never know when you're
going to move on up.
Mm-hm. Yeah.
[clattering]
I am so sorry! I...
No, no, no. It's...
It's okay. I shouldn't
walk and read.
Well, they taught
us in the service
to keep our head on a swivel.
If my Drill Sergeant saw me now
I'd be doing
pushups till sun-up.
Thanks.
[chuckling]
Well, I-
Ah, yeah, yeah.
Don't let me keep you.
I just finished up.
Have a good workout.
See you tomorrow.
[upbeat rock music]
[treadmill beeps]
[metal clanging]
[anxious music]
[shower running]
[door slams]
[unsettling music]
Hello?
[clunk]
There's still someone in here!
[unsettling music]
[door clunks]
[nervous music]
[car beeps]
[uneasy music]
[security system beeping]
[security device beeping]
[phone buzzes]
[Home Security Network Agent]
Home Security Network here.
Are you having trouble
with your system?
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm
entering in the right code.
It's my daughter's birthday,
but it's just not taking it.
[Home Security Network
Agent] Not a problem, Ma'am.
We just need the
last four digits
of your social security
number as your pin,
and I'll clear it up and arm it.
Sure. 1187.
[Home Security
Network Agent] All set.
We'll just need to
reset the password.
Do you still want
the same password
for the door and the
inside alarm box?
Yes. Same for both, please.
[Home Security Network
Agent] If you could enter
the four digits on the
keyboard it should arm.
[security device beeping]
[security device chirps]
Got it. Thank you so much.
[Home Security Network
Agent] No problem.
Have a good night.
Goodnight.
[gentle instrumental music]
Maya?
I got those files
you were asking for.
Great. Thank you.
Hey, whoa!
Sorry.
I had to change the
security password, by the way.
What is it?
What?
The password.
If I'm going to have to
water your plants again.
Oh. 0511.
Same for both
inside and outside.
Your birthday? That's secure!
[Maya chuckles]
Lunch is in five minutes.
Okay, boss.
The old taco joint
has a new owner.
They had the best
tacos! It's a tragedy.
Ooh, I smell coffee! You game?
Uh, yeah. Am I ever not?
You go in. I just want
to enjoy the fresh air.
Sure.
You know what I like.
Yeah.
[Ben] We did that one
for a meat packing company.
Sorry.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to scare you.
It's okay. I'm just
naturally a little jumpy.
Meat?
Oh. Yes.
That is a meat packing
company design for their logo.
We're a graphic design company.
Oh! I thought it
was an art gallery.
We design logos and other
graphic art work for businesses.
It's a booming
business district.
About 50 new companies.
I thought, why not show our
portfolio for all to see?
That's clever. I like it.
Ben Johnson.
Right.
I'm-
About to be late for
your board meeting.
I'm sorry. She's right.
No problem. You
know where to find me.
I'll give you the grand tour.
[ominous music]
[bright instrumental music]
I think we killed a
generation of trees.
This is the only way
I memorize this stuff.
I'm analog dependent.
Don't judge me.
We'll recycle it.
It's like a desk
of tree genocide.
[both laugh]
[Alex clears throat]
I have some more for the pile.
What are you still doing here?
I thought you left hours ago.
Good at being
invisible I guess.
Thanks, but we
have all the copies
we need of these figures.
Oh, I color-coded it.
Blue are figures
for two years ago.
Red are last fiscal year.
And green are projections.
[mumbling]
Figured I'd...
I was trying to find green.
'Cause Maya, you're
going to be making
a lot of green for this
company in the next few days.
Wow.
Wow indeed.
Thanks, Alex. Have a good night.
I can grab you some
food if you like.
Oh, no. I need to get
home and get some rest.
I can give you a ride.
Alex...
No, sorry, I just...
I don't think you should be
driving if you're this tired.
That's all.
Besides, it's on my way.
And how do you know?
No. I just...
Sorry, I mean I don't mind.
No.
I appreciate the
sentiment, Alex.
I'll be fine.
Big gulp for the road.
[tapping on phone]
That'll be all,
Alex. Thank you.
Okay.
Night.
That is one
over-achieving kid.
Oh, stop.
He's not that much
younger than you.
And he reminds me of my
intern in her early years.
Besides, you never
color-coded my files for me.
[scoffs]
Look how beautiful that is.
I hate you.
[Maya chuckles]
Okay.
You okay?
[crickets chirping]
Yeah.
I know that look.
We just really need
to close this deal.
Maya, you could do
this presentation tonight
and you would nail it.
You're over-preparing.
That's what you do.
It's something else though.
Come on! I'm not leaving
till you spill the beans.
It's just...
the house, the career...
the divorce.
Emma's gone. It's lonely.
I mean, I have you. I love you.
You're amazing, but...
It's been awhile since
you've seen some action.
[Maya gasps]
Katelyn Nash!
[Kate laughs]
What? Come on!
It's us. It's me.
I mean, I haven't
seen any in months.
Months, wow. Okay, now
I'm really depressed.
Try a couple years.
You have got the
art gallery guy.
That's a prospect.
It's not an art gallery in...
Wait a minute?
How do you know?
Why do you think I
came and pulled you away?
Makes you look all
mysterious and intriguing.
What would I do without you?
Well, you wouldn't get laid.
Part of my job apparently
I've been slacking on.
You have no idea how badly
I want to knock those papers
out of your hand right now.
Oh, come on.
You have to admit
color-coding is next level.
And now I'm leaving. Okay.
Drive safe.
Goodnight.
Night.
[laughing]
[ominous music]
[car starts]
[car humming]
[upbeat music on radio]
[car engine revving]
[tense music]
Whoa!
[tires squealing]
[suspenseful music]
[breathing heavily]
Oh my god!
[cars crash]
[horn blaring]
[emotional music]
[Kate whimpers]
[suspenseful music]
[car horn honking]
[Man] Hey! Are you okay?
[Kate groaning]
[tires squealing]
[anxious electronic music]
[Alex] Hey, what's going on?
You okay?
It's Kate.
[Alex] Maya?
You heard?
Yeah.
Not much but-
It was a car accident.
She ran into something.
Is she...
Okay? Yeah.
Have you talked to her?
No, not yet.
I'm waiting for them
to say it's okay.
She's pretty banged up
I guess. Bad concussion.
I overworked her.
Maya.
No, I did.
She said it herself. I
over-prepare, it's my thing.
My thing almost killed her.
This is not your fault.
She was wide awake
when she left here.
Or at least last time I saw her.
This is not your fault.
Okay?
Accidents happen.
Thanks.
[phone ringing]
I got it.
Maya Taylor's office.
How can I help you?
Hey.
Where are you going?
You've got that call.
I moved it.
I heard back from Kate.
She can take visitors.
I'll...
I'll go with you,
if that's okay.
She's just been
so helpful for me.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'm sure she'll be fine.
I still feel so bad.
It must have been so scary.
Most people in car
accidents don't remember.
The mind has a way
of protecting itself
from that kind of stuff.
Hopefully she doesn't
remember anything.
I've never been
in an accident.
Have you?
Yeah.
One.
[uneasy electronic music]
[Alex's Father] What
did you say to me?
I said shut up!
We're here.
Alex, Alex, we're here.
[tires squealing]
[knocks on door]
Knock knock.
Hey.
I'm okay.
We shouldn't have
worked that late.
Are you kidding? I
was on a coffee high.
This wasn't your fault.
It's not your fault.
It was...
my damn tires, I think.
It's a blur. I
don't remember much.
Doctor says it's the
concussion clouding my memory.
I love that car.
[chuckling]
Well, maybe it's something
you don't want to remember.
Maybe it's for the best.
The important thing
is that you're okay.
Thanks for coming, Alex.
I'm just glad you're okay.
And Maya's right.
Probably best you
don't remember.
Yeah.
I can stay all night.
No.
I'm fine.
I'm just tired.
And I need to get some rest
so I can get back to work.
Stop. Don't worry about that.
You said it yourself.
I could do the presentation
today and nail it.
I just said that to
make you feel better.
[laughing]
I'm kidding.
You're going to be great.
All right.
Well, rest up.
Okay.
Love you.
You take care of her.
She's got that final
presentation, board
and everything.
Oh, don't worry.
She's in good hands.
[uneasy electronic music]
I just don't know what to do.
I mean, I feel horrible.
I shouldn't be worried about
some stupid presentation, but-
[Emma] Mom. stop.
None of this is
your fault, okay?
And if I know you,
you're already prepared
to make this deal happen.
Kate's going to be okay.
And so are you.
I thought I was the Mom here.
I should be telling
you everything's
going to be all right.
And why aren't you
crying, missing your Mom,
and begging me to come home?
[Emma] I miss you, I
love you. Can I come home?
No. Suck it up.
[both chuckle]
All right, goodnight, sweetie.
I love you, and thank you.
You always know what
to say to your Mom
when she's losing it.
[Emma] Ditto.
Love you too. Goodnight.
Night.
[chatter on TV]
[ominous music]
[camera clicking]
[breathing heavily]
[car beeps]
[uneasy music]
[grunting]
[car beeps]
[soft electronic music]
Well, needless to say,
I think you're ready.
They'll love it.
Anyone else have any comments?
Frank, yeah, go ahead.
Welcome back by the way.
Appreciate that, Jason.
It was a great golf trip,
but I missed you guys.
So I know I missed the
initial presentation Maya had.
It's great.
I've actually be looking at
that hospital since I got here,
which is when you started this
company, Jason, am I right?
A few guys, dream,
and a single bag of
golf clubs between us.
[chuckling]
You brought this old guy in
'cause I could charm investors.
And I did.
I just wonder if maybe I should
make first contact on this.
I've got a couple of connections
there I've been working on.
No disrespect, Maya.
No, none taken.
Jason, if I could...
By all means.
Hi, Frank. I hope
the vacation was good.
While you were gone, I put
the whole package together.
And I've got contacts of my own-
And, again, I
mean no disrespect.
You did the leg work on this.
I'm just think maybe
we need a closer.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, Frank and Maya.
I'll tell you what.
Frank, you put your
approach together for me
by lunch when we reconvene.
Everyone get your
orders in to Jane.
We think better
when we eat, right?
Coffee?
Oh!
Wow. The office looks great.
Whole system's
color-coded now.
Yeah, that's a lot of color.
You don't like it.
No, no, no. It's great.
Oh, I'm good.
I need to crunch before
the lunch meeting.
Nope.
You got a whole hour of nothing.
How is that possible?
I figured you
could use a breather,
so I moved a couple calls.
Now you've got time to
relax, enjoy your coffee,
go over everything before lunch.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm fine.
Thank you for this.
Come on.
It's me.
It's just this guy.
Guy?
Frank.
In the meeting.
Oh.
I guess I was enjoying the
extended vacation that he took.
Anyways, now he's back
and back to his old self.
What do you mean?
Let's just say
he's old-fashioned.
And by old-fashioned, I mean
he's a blatant sexist jerk
that can't handle a woman
making a better deal
for the company than he
could have ever done.
[uneasy electronic music]
I don't mean any
disrespect to her,
but I leave for three weeks
of hard-earned vacation
and she stumbles on a
multi-billion dollar deal
that I would have
likely closed on by now.
Hey guys!
Hey beautiful.
You miss me?
No.
Did your wife? Probably not.
[laughing]
Taking orders for
the lunch meeting.
We're getting Rizuto's.
Sure, I'll take their
chicken breast salad
with extra Italian
dressing, don't forget that,
and no peppers.
[Ralph] Can't handle
the heat there, Frank?
[Frank] That's
not it, wise guy.
Serious allergy.
What about you?
[Ralph] Thanks, but
I'm headed out in a bit.
[Jane] Okay!
[ominous electronic music]
Lose your appetite?
Sorry?
You didn't get anything.
Thought of something better.
Hey, did you want me to pick
up the lunch order for you?
I'm heading out anyway.
[Jane] Are you sure?
Yeah. I don't mind.
That'd be great.
You're a lifesaver.
Thanks.
[Alex] Happy to help.
[phone ringing]
Newmark.
[ominous music]
[shaking salad]
Lunch is here.
We've got...
That's for you, sir.
Extra dressing, right?
Mr. Meyer, pasta
special I assume.
Wow.
Thanks. How'd you know?
A good intern always
knows or tries to at least.
What was your name?
Alex.
Mm.
Missed this place.
All right. Dig in and
we'll get to business.
So...
Frank...
What have you got for us?
Well, I've been playing
golf with two guys that...
[coughing softly]
[ominous music]
I've been playing golf...
[choking]
Oh my God!
You okay?
Frank!
[choking]
Frank?
[Jason] Call 911!
[suspenseful music]
Frank...
[unsettling music]
Hey.
Is he okay?
No.
He wasn't that responsive
when they took him out.
They gave him some
shot or something.
I feel so horrible for him.
Well, that's karma, I guess.
Alex.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
I just think out loud sometimes.
That's okay.
I can't lie.
Same thing crossed my mind,
which is why I feel so bad.
Why don't you call it a night.
I'm going to get some
more work done here
and then take the
rest home with me.
It's been a strange day.
Did you want any help?
No. I'm good.
It'll be nice to have the
office to myself for a bit.
Have a good night.
Big day tomorrow.
Mm-hm.
Hey...
You'll do great.
[security system beeping]
[anxious music]
[security device beeping]
[car pulling into driveway]
[security system beeping]
[relaxing piano music]
[crickets chirping]
[floorboard creaking]
[tense music]
[security system beeping]
[security device chirping]
Shoot!
[lock clicks]
[phone buzzing]
[gasps]
Hello?
[Alex] Hey, it's Alex.
Just wanted to remind you
that your favorite
show premiers tonight.
Might be good to settle
your nerves a bit.
How...
How did you know?
[Alex] I heard Kate and you
talking about it last week.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I...
I'm fine.
[Alex] Well, you
don't sound fine.
It's just...
It's this security system.
I can never figure it out.
The back door was open.
I heard some strange sounds.
[Alex] I'm coming over.
No, Alex.
[Alex] I insist.
You're on the west side,
right? I'm not too far.
What's the address? I'll
just do a walk through.
Just to make sure
everything's okay.
[doorbell rings]
It's so stupid. I'm sorry.
Oh, that's okay. Nobody
could have been up there.
Well, you never know.
I closed it,
but that's the door that
was open is down there.
Mm-hm.
[uneasy music]
[door clunks]
Okay, good as new.
[security device beeping]
Silly security system.
It's more hassle than help.
No, no. It's good to be safe.
I think what happened is
just sometimes one door opens
it can cause the other
one to suction in and out.
It's like an air pressure thing.
Back door must have been
unlatched just enough to give.
Well, I should get some sleep.
If I can.
[gentle piano music]
You know, I could stay.
Alex...
No, I just I mean, you know...
down here.
No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
You've gone above and
beyond intern duties.
And thank you.
It made me feel better.
[gentle piano music]
Well...
Goodnight.
[gentle piano music]
How'd it go!
Jeez!
What are you still doing here?
I couldn't take the suspense.
How'd it go?
Amazing.
We went through everything.
The board loved it.
The CEO was outstanding.
Really nice.
She has a daughter
same age as Emma.
After that, it was just
about the logistics,
and then we had
an amazing lunch,
and then more logistics,
then an amazing dinner.
I'm exhausted.
And?
They said they'd call.
[Alex sighs]
What's in the bag?
Wine.
Client gifts.
[phone rings]
Maya Taylor's office.
Sure, I'll put you through.
It's them.
[Maya sighs]
This is Maya.
Great.
Wonderful.
I appreciate the call.
Thank you.
And?
[soft music]
We did it.
What!
We did it!
They're sending the
contracts tomorrow.
I can't believe it! We did it!
[laughing]
You! You did it!
I got to call Kate.
Well, she's probably
asleep, don't you think?
Yeah, you're probably right.
Maya, Maya! We
have to celebrate!
With what?
And that was the moment
I knew it was really over.
Best day of my life
for both Emma and I.
Well, his loss.
What about you?
What's your family like?
I'm sorry. I didn't...
No, it's...
It's okay.
I don't really have one.
Everyone has family.
My folks died in a
car accident when I
was in high school.
I was in the car with them.
My dad just lost control.
They said it was a
miracle I survived.
Doesn't feel like
a miracle though.
Alex, I'm so sorry.
If I'd known, I-
No. How could you?
I keep to myself.
I was in the hospital for
a while with a head injury,
and then it was just me.
No...
Aunts or uncles?
Nobody, no.
But that's okay.
I graduated high
school. Top of my class.
Eastwood University.
Army Reserves.
Now I'm here with you.
All is well.
Do you miss them?
My Dad was...
hard on me.
He was very successful.
Difficult shoes to fill.
He was a military guy
before he got into business.
Stern.
High expectations.
I get that.
My dad was similar.
My brothers in the military too.
It was kind of expected.
But with me...
Daddy's girl?
Exactly.
[both laughing]
I could do no wrong.
Yeah, I put up with
a lot of crap from him.
I think he was a little
jealous of my Mom
'cause she owned
her own company.
She was...
beautiful.
Successful.
Like you.
I suppose that's why I am
the way I am. I just...
I want to be successful.
You must have felt so...
Alone.
[soft electronic music]
Alex, we shouldn't...
[Alex] Morning.
Alex, we need to-
Okay. Don't be mad.
What do you mean?
[clapping]
[staff cheering]
I had to tell them.
Tell them what?
About you closing a
multi-billion dollar client!
[staff cheering]
Maya, you killed it!
You absolutely killed it!
We did it!
Thank you.
[uneasy electronic music]
Look, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have tried
to grab your hand
in front of everyone.
Alex, look-
No, no.
You right.
When we're in the office,
we should be professional.
When we're in the office?
Alex, last night was a mistake.
It wasn't you. It's me.
What do you mean?
It was a mistake.
I was a little drunk,
a little lonely.
Maya...
Last night was...
It was amazing.
I mean, you liked it. You-
I did.
I mean...
It doesn't matter. It doesn't.
This can't...
We can't.
Can't what?
Alex, you're an amazing
guy. You're an amazing intern.
Intern?
Yes, Alex. That's what
you are, and I'm your boss.
And if you know
anything about business,
which I know you do, this
stuff, it isn't right.
[anxious music]
Alex, listen. It's
just not appropriate.
Okay? And that's my fault.
Look, we need to forget this
ever happened. That's all.
Please.
Let's not make this-
What?
Difficult?
After everything I did for you?
I know, and I'm sorry.
You've been an amazing-
Intern! Yeah!
I got it.
Intern.
I have a breakfast
meeting with Jason
to go over the contract details.
I'll talk to you later.
[unsettling electronic music]
Hey.
Coffee? Bagels?
No. Thank you, though.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
So the numbers are fantastic.
Lawyers are happy
with the contract.
Barring any horrible
turn of events,
we're looking at hundreds
of millions in capitol
over the next five
years to start.
All thanks to you.
And that intern of yours.
He's a sharpshooter.
I'm sorry?
Alex, right? He's a keeper.
Once Kate comes back I may
steal him from you. [chuckles]
Actually, I think
he had his sights set
on the new location.
Something about
a better commute.
Anyways, how's Frank?
Ah, shoot. You didn't hear?
No.
I suppose with
all of this going on
the last couple days.
He's in a coma.
Medically induced.
Something about an
allergic reaction.
Oh my god. An
allergic reaction?
I know.
It was bad enough that it
caused swelling in the brain.
Ralph, one of the lawyers,
said something about
an allergy to peppers.
From what I hear from
his wife, he'll be okay.
It's just precautionary
until the swelling goes down.
He's one lucky SOB. And just
when we got him back too.
[Maya laughs]
Hi.
How 'about that tour?
Sure.
[tense music]
So that's it.
We've had 20 clients
sign already.
It's a brilliant idea.
Impressive.
So the mystery is killing me.
I'm sorry?
Well, last we talked some
girl came and whisked you away.
Yeah, that was Kate,
my overbearing but wonderful
project coordinator.
She was just-
Trying to make you
seem more mysterious.
I have three sisters.
Well all three of them
said that your friend,
your project coordinator, was
trying to do that for you.
You asked them about me?
Yeah.
Yeah, sorry.
No, no, no. It's okay.
Kate can be too smart for
her own good sometimes.
Which reminds me,
I owe her a call.
I should get going. Thank you.
Hey. Can I ask
you if you'd like-
I'm going to ask you to finish
that sentence another time,
at a much better time.
But I look forward to it.
Hey. I...
got your favorite.
Oh.
That's sweet.
So sorry. I have lunch
with a client today.
I didn't see that
on your schedule.
Oh, it was last minute. Bye.
[uneasy electronic music]
[clattering]
Really.
[phone buzzing]
[uneasy music]
[phone beeps]
Hi, Jane.
Hi!
Hey.
Good morning.
You up for some breakfast?
[upbeat instrumental music]
Absolutely.
You want to go someplace
a little more quiet maybe?
There's a place down the road-
So, great news.
Jason, the CEO, is opening
the branch across town
to handle the growth.
He's fast-tracking it,
and he's hiring a new
executive for that location.
They're going to
need an assistant.
I told Jason that you
would be perfect for it.
And even though you're still
in your internship program,
he agreed to hire you.
You impressed him, Alex.
Kate's coming back to
work in a couple of days.
She's finally feeling better,
so it's perfect timing.
This is what you wanted, Alex.
It's exactly what you wanted.
You're going to be so,
so successful. I know it.
This is about that night.
Stop.
It is, isn't it?
No. It's not.
[tense music]
It's him, isn't it?
The gallery owner!
What? Lower your voice.
I've seen you two. Staring,
smiling at each other.
Okay, this isn't right, Alex.
The behavior, the phone calls.
It's not professional.
Yeah, neither is
sleeping with your intern!
Be quiet. Quiet, please.
I'm just trying to do
what's best for you.
What's best for you, for us.
[Alex scoffs]
The last company I worked
for, the one that went under.
Why do you think it did?
[tense music]
I don't-
Because a project
manager, a woman,
sexually harassed an intern.
In this day and age,
can you imagine?
Once word got out, financial
backers pulled out.
All those people lost their jobs
because of her one
little mistake.
Are you threatening me?
Of course not.
I just know you'll come around.
You might not know
this yet, but...
we're meant to be together.
We both know what it's
like to be lonely.
Have a good weekend.
I'm going to take the day
off and give you some time...
to think about it.
[tense music]
Hey, Maya.
Hi, Jane.
I'm just going
through Alex's file.
I'm getting him going for
this new assistant position
at the other branch.
There's some key
information missing.
He still hasn't gotten
me his bank account
and background check info.
Wait. We didn't do
a background check?
He said he needed to
get some information.
I called your office
and talked to Kate.
Yeah, I remember that.
His college transcripts
weren't in there either.
He mentioned something
about the university's
server going down.
He'd have 'em by next week.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
I'm just getting him going
for this new promotion.
It can wait till next week.
I'll be in my office
making a bunch of calls.
If I don't see you,
have a great weekend.
You too.
Hi. My name is Maya Taylor.
I'm a project
manager at a company
that is looking to
hire Alex Preston.
I'm just wanted to
confirm his enrollment,
graduation, and major.
You don't have no Alex
Preston in your records?
Are you sure?
[mysterious music]
Um, no, that's fine.
I'm sure it's just
a misunderstanding
on his paperwork.
Thank you.
Alex Dales?
[unsettling music]
[sniffing]
[dramatic electronic music]
[gung clicking]
Don't quit.
Do something about it.
Don't be a quitter, Alexander!
[uneasy music]
[chatter on intercom]
[anxious music]
Alex, what are you doing here?
I was in the area.
[door closes]
I wanted to make
sure you were okay.
Visiting hours are over.
I know.
Security sucks here.
[Kate chuckles nervously]
Well, I appreciate the visit.
I'm fine.
I actual get
discharged tomorrow.
No internal bleeding.
Head's good.
They're worried about
the trauma, but all good.
Helps to have a
hard head, I guess.
[chuckling]
Yeah.
The head.
So...
are you remembering anything?
The accident?
Still cloudy.
Well, best forgotten I guess.
[Kate gasps]
[door opens]
I'm sorry, sir.
Visiting hours are
just getting over.
You're going to have to-
No problem.
Sorry.
I...
just wanted to make sure
Kate rests peacefully.
[Nurse] Sorry,
honey. Rules are rules.
[breath shaking]
Diana?
Yeah, hi. It's nice
to meet you, Maya.
Have a seat.
I feel bad dragging
you out here.
We could have done
this over the phone.
I'd just put it behind me.
I think I needed some time.
Are you okay?
He's a charmer, isn't he?
I'm sorry?
Alex.
Alex Dales.
But you said you know him as-
Alex Preston.
And yes.
He is a charmer.
At first.
I'm sorry.
I closed the door on
this a long time ago.
I didn't think-
If this is too hard,
we don't have-
No.
No, actually it's good.
'Cause maybe you can
do what I couldn't.
What's that?
Stop him.
Before he ruins your life.
[tense music]
Missed you this weekend.
Alex.
Alex Preston, right?
What do you mean?
I'm just going to rip
the bandaid off here.
Your real name is Alex Dales.
[Alex grumbles]
You didn't graduate from
Eastwood University.
You tried and came close, but
your grades weren't up to par.
Your senior year you got
kicked out after an internship
with the registrar's
office manager.
They complained about
inappropriate behavior.
She said you were stalking her.
After that, you made
your way to a company
a few hours away from here.
Answered an online internship
ad, forged transcripts,
something that you
probably learned
at the registrar's office
during your internship there.
At first you were
a model intern.
Until some inappropriate
behavior surfaced
towards your manager.
A female manager.
She came on to me.
I talked to her Alex.
[tense music]
You did what?
I talked to her.
We had a candid discussion.
I also called the
Army Reserves office.
You were dishonorably
discharged a few months in.
Mental health concerns.
Inappropriate behavior towards
a female Lieutenant Colonel.
Threatened blackmail.
Conduct unbecoming.
Maya-
Was that your next
step with me, Alex?
Blackmail? Extortion?
It doesn't have
to be this way.
Let me tell you how
it is going to be.
You're going to go back to the
office and gather your things.
Then you're going to
leave and never come back.
Do you understand?
It's important that
I hear you say it.
[emotional piano music]
I understand.
[chatter on police radio]
[tense music]
His M.O. is pretty consistent.
He latches onto a
female authority figure.
Someone that's...
Successful.
Yeah.
He showcases obsessive
compulsive behavior.
Did he ever make any
advances towards you?
No.
Nothing like that.
Just calls and strange behavior.
I am so sorry.
I can't believe he
would do this to you.
Listen to me,
okay? It wasn't you.
It was him.
You didn't do anything wrong.
[tense music]
[chatter on police radio]
[camera clicks]
[relaxing piano music]
I'm glad you showed
up at the gallery.
It had been over a month.
I was starting to get
worried about you.
You quit drinking
coffee or something?
[Maya laughs]
No.
It's just been a busy month.
Well, I was happy to see you.
Me too.
I'm sorry if I'm
a little nervous.
This is my actually my first
date since the divorce,
which has been a few
years, if you can imagine.
Ever been married?
[clears throat]
Can we make a deal?
Sure.
Let's not share
our lonely stories.
Is that okay?
That's perfect.
So...
Tell me about your job.
[tense music]
Unless you want to
remain a mystery.
Everything okay?
Sorry. Yes.
I'm fine.
Looked like you saw a
ghost there for a second.
Maybe.
[mysterious electronic music]
[phone chimes]
Emma friended me.
Consider yourself lucky.
Emma and I are close,
but she does not want
to share social media
with her mother.
[chuckles]
I can't wait to see her.
Says she has a big surprise.
I think she aced her exams.
She's a smart girl.
[Maya] You ready
for a takeout feast?
I can't wait! Thank
you for inviting me.
I just might be a little late.
My boss is horrible.
[chuckling]
[cheerful guitar music]
[knocking on door]
[screaming with joy]
I missed you so much!
Oh, I missed you too!
Hey, Ben.
Emma!
It is so great to
see you in person.
I mean, those Zoom
calls are great and all.
Where are your bags?
Okay, don't be mad.
So I said I had a
big surprise, right?
[laughs]
Hey, babe!
[tense music]
Mom, this is Andrew.
Andrew, this is my Mom.
[phone beeps]
[tense music]
[typing on phone]
We've been seeing each
other for a while actually.
I just didn't want you to think
I was distracted from
school or anything.
Far from it actually.
I aced all of my exams.
Mom?
Oh, sorry. That's...
amazing.
That's great, Emma.
Why don't we set another
spot at the table.
Yeah.
No problem.
I'll help.
Be nice.
[tense music]
[suspenseful music]
Please don't hurt them.
That's entirely
up to you, Maya.
Okay. So what's for dinner?
[laughing]
So, Andrew, Emma says you're
starting a new internship.
Yes, at Health Ridge Hospital.
They have locations border
to border, coast to coast.
They're even expanding to-
Europe and Asia?
[uneasy music]
Yeah, that's right.
How did you know?
Maya's company provides
software for them.
Small world, huh?
Too small.
Oh my gosh!
How did I never put
two and two together?
Maybe you guys will get
to work together sometime.
That'd be cool.
[phone beeps]
[phone ringing]
Come on, Maya. Pick up.
[phone buzzing]
So, Mrs. Taylor...
Or, sorry, is it...
[phone buzzing]
Do you need to get that?
[tense music]
No.
It's probably Kate.
She said she was running late.
So is it Mrs. Taylor or...
You can call me Maya.
Maya.
The software Ben
is talking about...
it's Newmark, right?
Amazing stuff.
Thank you.
Must have taken a lot of work
to get connected with a
hospital chain like that.
[anxious music]
Mom? Are you okay?
Yeah, you don't look so
good. It's not the food, is it?
[Emma] Mom, what's wrong?
M?
I was hoping you'd
play along, Maya.
I've been waiting
for this a long time.
You're Alex.
[unsettling music]
What?
Please don't.
No, no, no! That's far enough!
Andrew! What are you doing?
[tense music]
Sorry, babe.
It's been great though.
Oh, and...
it's Alex.
Oh, oh.
Don't worry.
Emma's not really not my type.
A little young.
We never really...
You know.
Enough!
What do you want?
Quiet!
[Emma gasps]
All I want is answers.
[phone buzzing]
[slams phone]
[phone beeping]
[phone ringing]
[Dispatcher] 911.
911?
I have an emergency.
What answers do you want?
I want to know why!
Why not me?
Why him?
[tense music]
What are you talking about?
I said...
quiet!
Oh.
You never told him...
the whole story.
Please stop.
[tense music]
Or her.
Mom?
Why are you doing this?
Your girlfriend
slept with her intern.
She didn't tell you that.
No, she didn't tell
her best friend that.
She didn't tell her daughter.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no!
You should be apologizing
to me, not them.
Me!
Why? Why should I-
No!
It was one night.
We were celebrating.
I was lonely. It was stupid.
You tried to kill Kate.
You tried to kill her. Why?
Over some stupid internship?
Because I love you.
Love?
You don't know what love is.
You don't.
You're just some
confused, messed up kid.
I'm sorry your parents died.
No! Don't talk about them.
[Maya] I'm sure
they loved you.
Don't talk about them!
Love me?
My father never did.
He saw nothing but flaws in me.
I was either too stupid
or too disorganized.
Nothing was ever
good enough. Nothing!
He was ashamed.
The day of the accident...
I snapped.
I grabbed the steering
wheel, and we flipped.
I went out the window and
I landed in some bushes.
When I came to...
she was gone.
My Mom.
The seatbelt snapped.
She was laying in a...
Broken.
Covered in blood.
30 feet away.
But him...
He was fine.
Hurt but fine!
The airbag saved
him. Not her, him!
So I...
I finished it.
I finished him.
[tense music]
With a tire iron from the trunk.
Alex...
[Alex screams]
[gun clatters]
[groaning]
[suspenseful music]
[knife slashes]
[Ben screams]
Stop!
[Emma crying]
Alex, no.
This isn't about her.
[Emma crying]
No.
This is about you.
It's always been about you.
All you had to do was love me.
Like she did.
My mom.
All I wanted was for her...
for you...
to love me.
She loved you, Alex.
She did.
Until she died because of me.
I just wanted to succeed.
I just wanted you
to succeed too.
Like she did in whatever
thing she tried to do.
I know.
I get that now. I do.
You're an amazing worker.
And I know that your mom
thought you were amazing too.
[tense music]
No.
[Emma screams]
You're lying again, aren't you?
Alex, no!
This has nothing to do with her!
Everything I
did, I did for you!
All that work.
That jerk, Frank.
That was you?
Yes!
I did it for you!
Everything I did, I
did for you, for us!
I need you to
realize that, Maya.
I'm not a bad person.
I'm not a bad person! I
need to hear you say it!
How could I?
Look at yourself.
You're nothing but
a disappointment.
[Emma screams]
Maya!
[suspenseful music]
[smack]
[gun bangs]
[body thuds]
[Emma screams]
[police sirens blaring]
Maya.
[calm orchestral music]
I'm sorry I disappointed you.
[gentle instrumental music]
To a new beginning.
For us all.
Yeah.
And I know I've said
these a thousand times
these past few days.
I promise I will never-
Hey.
Let's not tell our
sad stories. Deal?
Deal.
Deal!
[glasses clinking]
[gentle instrumental music]
[dramatic electronic music]