Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
AIR TRAFFIC: Lion Inter 610
cleared for takeoff, runway 2-5 left.
CO-PILOT: Lion Inter 610
cleared for takeoff, 2-5 left.
CO-PILOT: Indicated Airspeed Disagree,
Captain.
CO-PILOT: Feel Differential.
CO-PILOT: Altitude Disagree, Captain!
AIR TRAFFIC: Lion Inter 610?
CO-PILOT:
We have a flight control problem!
CO-PILOT: Fly up! Fly up!
PILOT: These guys didn't even know
the damn system was on the airplane,
nor did anybody else.
BOEING: We try not to overload the crews
with information that's unnecessary.
PILOT: I would think
there would be a priority
on explanations of things
that could kill you.
BOEING: We take your point.
We really do.
PILOT: Is there something being done
where Boeing might address
ways to make sure it doesn't happen again?
BOEING: Well, we're looking at relatively
straightforward software changes
that we expect we can get out
in a fairly short period of time…
maybe six weeks.
BOEING: Because no one has yet concluded
that the sole cause of this
was dysfunction of the airplane.
Between me and you,
they didn't put a shim
on the landing gear yesterday.
On the lugs. Night shift didn't.
They said we don't have time
to fucking put it on.