Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
They say Bene Gesserit only exists
to serve the greater good.
I mean no disrespect to your mother,
but they also pursue their own interests.
What are you saying?
Be careful.
Don't talk to anyone.
Remember your training.
Prepare for violence.
What is the Emperor's message?
He will strengthen your hand.
With his Sardaukar army…
I know who you are.
He will know his uses
as if he was born with them.
Why does Baron need us?
The Harkonnen outnumber Atreides.
The Baron doesn't need us.
We are the Sardaukar -
Emperor's blades.
Those who stand against us
meet their death.
As the Emperor commands,
it will be done.
We will drop them in the desert.
And leave them to the worms.
Why not just cut their throats?
They could be the Truthsayers.
We can say we didn't kill them.
The one with the scar is deaf.
No! You're not ready.
Find the right tone.
We are far enough.
Throw the boy out.
We are not alone.
How can he be Lisan al-Gaib?
He hasn't proved himself.
The sun is about to rise.
We must reach Sietch Tabr.
The fate of the strangers
will be decided there.
Until then,
they are under my protection.
I give you my word.
We must go.