(gentle music)
(gentle music continues)
(wings fluttering)
- I can't see anything, Dad.
(Craig laughs)
- Well, yeah, that's
kind of the point
of the blindfolded,
isn't it, birthday girl?
(both chuckling)
- All right.
- Here, right up there.
- [Grace] Oops.
(gentle piano music)
- This is all mine?
- That's right, Little
Ladybug. Your very own garden.
- And you can grow
whatever you want.
(Craig chuckles)
- This is the best
birthday ever.
- Oh, how could I forget?
You're gonna need this if you
plan on planting any seeds.
- My very own trowel?
- Amanda, remember this
when you use that trowel,
the key to any garden's success
is the love that
you put into it.
- I have plenty of love to give.
- Yeah, you sure do.
- Dig, dig.
(all chuckling)
(trowel rasping)
(gentle music)
(people chattering)
(gentle music continues)
(oven bell dings)
- Mom!
(footsteps pattering)
(Amanda sniffs)
Hmm, (sniffs) smells
like snickerdoodle?
- Cinnamon give it away?
We've sold out every week
since the new pastor let me
sell them after Sunday service.
- Good because every
cookie sale counts
when the flowers
aren't blooming.
(Grace sighs)
So much for frost being over.
The bloom is so far
behind this year,
the only thing we'll be
harvesting for Easter is dirt.
- The harvest calendar
is just an estimate.
It's been off in the past.
Can't control the weather, but
we can control other things.
I should hear back soon about
our business loan application.
- Can't we just refinance?
- Not with the
mortgage in arrears.
Your dad would be proud
of how hard we're
trying, I know that.
- We have enough to make it
through Easter, though, right?
- Let's see what the bank
says about our emergency loan.
- I don't know what we'd
do without the farm.
- Well, we won't give up.
I can still hope for
an Easter miracle.
- Can I take a few of
these for the road?
- [Grace] Mm.
- Maybe the tips of the
cafe will be extra big
on this extra cold morning.
(Grace chuckles)
Okay, I'm gonna go. I love you.
- I love you too.
* Whoa, oh
* Yeah, I've been
through it all *
- Okay. Right behind you.
Here's your coffee.
- Cool.
Awesome. Muffin.
I have a regular latte and
a double espresso mocha.
- Thank you. Have a good day.
Thanks. Your regular.
Hi.
- Hey.
- What can I get you?
- Good morning.
I'll have a large lavender
latte with a dash of cinnamon,
some agave, and almond
milk, only if you have it.
- Yep, sure. Give
me two minutes.
- Thank you.
Hmm.
- Effie, I'm pretty sure
I need another two sets of hands
to make it through
the morning rush.
How do you do it?
- When in doubt, more caffeine.
- Ah.
- Cheers.
(both slurping)
Wow.
- Uh-huh.
- Mm.
Thank you, again, for
letting me pick up
some extra shifts at the cafe.
Things are pretty
tight at the farm,
at least until the
spring bloom comes in.
- Well, I know you'd do
anything to save the farm.
For example, used to
love our play dates.
You know, the ones
where you just basically
got me to help you weed?
(both laughing)
- My dad always said that
pulling weeds built character.
- Uh-huh.
(Amanda sighs)
- Almond milk, lavender latte,
two pumps of agave,
dash of cinnamon.
- Thanks, Amanda.
- Have we met before?
- No, you just have a nice,
beautiful, labeled name tag.
- Oh, (chuckles) I
forget that's there.
- Mm.
Mm.
This might be the best
latte I've ever had.
Mm-mm, nope. That's all yours.
- Um, that's a $14 tip.
- And I'd give you a
15th dollar if I had it.
You see, some
people drink coffee
to, you know, drink coffee.
I drink coffee because
it's an experience,
and yours, it has
just the right amount
of lavender and agave. (slurps)
Mm, not too sweet,
not too floral,
and just the right temperature
for a cold day like today.
All right?
- Well, um, well, thank you.
- [Derrick] No, thank you.
- I've never heard anybody
talk about coffee like that.
- Well, that's
because we just met.
- Right.
- I appreciate your artistry,
your effort, most
of all, that smile.
Have a good one.
- Have a good day.
- Um, okay, that was adorable.
- What? He appreciated
my artistry.
- Uh, that was a $14 tip.
Think he was appreciating
more than just your artistry.
Just saying.
Hi, Gladys.
- Oh, hi, Gladys.
- Amanda Raymond. You're
in the coffee business now.
- Uh, just temporarily, until
the spring bloom comes in.
- Fingers crossed that spring
is hiding around the corner.
I'll just take a black.
- Oh. Yeah.
- You know, I really
do miss seeing
those dedication
arrangements from your farm
in the church
lobby every Sunday.
- That was really more
of my dad's thing.
- I know you two were close.
Just know how much those
arrangements lifted my spirits.
I sure hope we get
to see them again,
and we hope to
see you again too.
- Um, I'm sure you'll see
my mom in service on Sunday.
- Thank you.
- Have a good day.
- Bye.
Everything good?
- Uh, yeah, just...
It's hard, sometimes, when
people talk about my dad.
Brings up a lot.
- Everyone has nothing
but love for him.
I do too.
Except some of those gardening
puns were way too cheesy.
- Um, what was a good one? Oh.
"You grow, girl."
- Uh, "What incarnation?"
(both laughing)
(bell jingles)
- Oh. Here she comes again.
- Who?
- Someone who seems to lack
a little sunshine in her life.
Hi.
- I'll take the usual.
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
(Effie clears throat)
- Muffin. Muffin.
Nice day we've been having.
Thank you.
- Here you go.
- Keep the change.
- Oh.
- Have a good day!
Not one for conversation
much, is she?
- Yeah, she's a
real tough cookie.
- Speaking of cookies-
- Oh?
- I think we deserve a
little cookie celebration
after having survived
that morning rush.
- [Effie] Mm.
- My mom made a fresh batch of
snickerdoodles this morning.
- Oh my gosh, oh my
gosh, oh my gosh.
Mm.
(snickerdoodle crunching)
Mm!
No words. I have no words.
- Yum?
- Yes, that.
Mm! Wait.
Idea. How many of these
can your mom make?
'Cause we could sell
them in the cafe.
- I was hoping you
would say that.
- You set me up?
- Mm, little bit.
- Oh.
And whatever profits we make
can go right back to the farm.
- Okay, you don't go that far.
- Uh-huh, Amanda, um, I just
died and went to cookie heaven,
so, yeah, we should do that.
(snickerdoodle crunches)
(both laughing)
Hi. How can I help you?
(shovel thudding)
(Amanda sighs)
- Come on.
(shovel thuds)
(Amanda sighs)
(shovel clatters)
(Amanda sighing)
(gentle music)
How come they
haven't come out yet?
- [Craig] Because they
still need time, Ladybug.
- But what if something is
wrong? I'm getting worried.
- You know what I do
when I'm worrying?
I say a little prayer.
- Why do you do that?
- Because it lets me
give my worries away
instead of letting
them weigh me down,
and I know God will
take them from me.
- You really think so?
- Yeah.
- I guess I'll try.
Hi, God. It's me,
Amanda Raymond.
I'm really nervous
about my garden.
Please help them grow to be
big, beautiful, and healthy.
Amen.
How was that?
- That was perfect.
(Craig chuckles)
(gentle music)
(Amanda sighs)
- I know that you'd probably
be praying right now.
Prayers can't melt ice,
they can't bring you back.
(tires screeching)
(car crashes)
(door clacks)
Hey, are you okay?
- Oh, I think so.
Yeah, no bumps, no bruises.
Oh, thank goodness.
- Do you live nearby?
- Closer to town. My husband
and I just moved here.
Yeah, I'm gonna call him and
he's gonna come and get me.
- Okay, okay.
Um, I can also get your
car out with our tractor.
But, um, should we go inside?
It's freezing out here.
- Oh, you're a godsend.
- Amanda.
- Oh. Lori.
- [Amanda] Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just watch your step there.
- Yeah.
I'm just a little shooken up.
- [Amanda] I'll
put the kettle on.
- Nothing better than a hot
cup of cocoa on a frigid day.
(Amanda chuckles)
- Cheers to that.
- Oh, you have a lovely home.
You live here with your husband?
- No, I am single. (chuckles)
It's my parents' house.
Well, um, actually,
it's my mom's house.
My dad died last year.
- Sorry to hear that.
I did see the sign on
your farm out front,
The Raymond Pick Your
Own Bouquet Flower Farm?
- Yeah, that's our
family business.
I know, it doesn't look
like much right now,
but, hopefully, in a few weeks,
it'll be a cornucopia
of color out there.
- Oh, yeah, the weather.
It's either they're a gardener's
greatest ally or worst enemy.
(both chuckling)
Let me guess.
Pink peonies and maybe a
row of purple hyacinths
to complement them, and, oh,
I can imagine a wide array
of tulips, perfect
Easter flower,
and, maybe a hybrid or two
when they cross-pollinate.
- Okay, Lori, most people
don't know the difference
between a daisy and a daffodil.
What's your secret?
- My whole life has been the
business of flowers, dear.
- So you're a florist?
- Was for 40 years.
I'm officially retired
now. It's just a hobby.
I don't even compete
in the annual
Easter Flower Arranging
Competition anymore.
- But you have.
Have you ever won?
- Oh, I haven't, but I
placed second last year.
My highest finish.
- So, um, I'm sitting
with floral royalty,
is what you're saying.
- Certainly not the queen, but
perhaps in her royal court.
(Amanda chuckles)
- Um, I can go get my tractor
and we can get you
back on the road?
- Mm. Oh, I certainly
appreciate that.
Thank you so much.
Amanda?
- Hmm?
- Is there anything that
I can do to repay you
for your help with my car?
- Um, well, can
you pull a miracle
and melt the ice out there?
(Lori chuckles)
- You really need a bloom, huh?
- You know the flower business.
We make most of our money
during certain seasons,
and with the Easter bloom
being so far behind-
- Well, sadly, my alter
ego isn't Mother Nature,
but what about that Easter
Flower Arranging Competition?
I mean, the prize is $20,000.
- Wow, I mean, that
would be enough
to get us through the season.
Except there's just
one tiny, huge problem.
I'm a farmer, not a florist.
I mean, that's why we
have our customers pick
their own bouquets.
- Well, that's where I come in.
I mean, I know six weeks
is not a lot of time,
but I can teach you
what you need to compete
if you're willing to learn.
- The cost of flowers alone-
- No, no, no. I can handle it.
And we can always practice
with silk flowers.
I mean, think about it,
we might even dethrone
Queen Constance Hughes.
- Constance?
- Yeah, she's won
10 years in a row.
Oh, oh, Amanda.
Come on, (chuckles) just
take my number here.
(pen scratching)
Here you go.
(paper rustles)
- This is a very generous offer,
and I'm sure it'd
be fun to learn,
but I couldn't compete.
I'd be going against people
with years of experience.
Thank you, but I'll
just have to find some
other way to keep us afloat.
- Okay.
But call me if you
change your mind.
- I will. Come on,
let's go get your car.
- Yes, please.
(gentle piano music)
- No, I understand.
You're just doing your job.
Thank you.
- Hey. Is everything okay?
- That was the bank, Amanda.
Our last two years of
sales just aren't enough
to give them confidence
to approve the loan.
- But that was our Hail
Mary to get caught up.
(somber music)
I have to do it.
- Do what?
- The statewide Easter
Flower Arranging Competition.
The first prize is $20,000.
It's at least enough
to keep us afloat
until the bloom comes.
- Flower arranging?
Is this a skill that
you've been hiding from me?
- Hiding from everyone,
including myself.
But I met a florist
yesterday and she's retired,
but she's competed before,
and she said she'd teach me.
- Your dad would
love to hear that.
- I have to at least try.
Maybe our last hope.
- Well, little bit of
hope is all we need.
- Amanda, I have to ask,
what made you change your
mind about the competition?
- Our business loan
application got denied,
so winning the
competition prize money,
it feels like maybe
the farm's last hope.
- Well, then let's
not waste any time.
Take a look at
your blank canvas.
(Amanda sighing)
Oh, I know that look.
- The "I have no idea
where to begin" look?
(Lori laughs)
- Yeah, that one.
Let's just have fun to start
and we'll see what
we're working with.
- Uh, so peonies and
ranunculus, iris,
and, go to a classic,
got some roses.
- Yeah, you do
know all the names
of the flowers
and how they grow,
but I wanna see you
actually create something.
- I think that my
creative side is
still hibernating for winter.
(Lori chuckles)
- It's a good thing
there's no pressure.
Come on, just have fun.
- Okay. You asked for it.
(hands patting)
(gentle music)
Do some...
And, um, mm-hmm.
Roses.
(Amanda claps)
I call it "A Thorn
Amidst Roses."
- [Lori] Mm-hmm.
(Lori chuckles)
- It's rough, I know,
but I am ready and willing
to do whatever it takes.
- That's the spirit.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
You got a lot to learn.
There are five principles
to floral design.
You master those, you
got a chance to win.
They are harmony, contrast,
purpose, balance, and...
Uh, I'm gonna keep
the last one a secret.
- A secret?
Well, I mean, don't I need all
five to win the competition?
- A secret for now at least.
I mean, it's something
that you can only learn
after you've succeeded
at the first four.
But let's get on with it.
Now, the first
principle is harmony.
- Harmony?
- Yeah.
We're going on a field
trip for this one.
Come on, let's take a walk.
- Okay.
(gentle music)
- Your lesson awaits.
- [Amanda] Inside?
- Oh, is everything okay?
- I, I haven't been back
inside since my dad's funeral,
and that was over a year ago.
- So it brings back a lot.
(door thuds)
- A lot.
(alarm chirping)
- [Derrick] Hey, Mom!
- Oh, Derrick.
- Hey.
- Perfect timing.
Meet Amanda Raymond.
She's the flower protege
I was telling you about.
- We've met. Uh,
Mr. Lavender Latte.
- Mm-hmm. It's good to see
you, minus the name tag.
(Amanda chuckles)
I'm Derrick, the new pastor.
It's a pleasure.
Well, I don't wanna get in
the way of flower training.
Uh, late for choir
practice myself, so...
* La la la
- Oh.
(Derrick clears throat)
- As you can hear, I need
all the help I can get.
- Well, we're on our
way there as well.
- All right, I'll
see you inside.
- Um, only if, of
course, you're ready.
- Yeah.
(door thuds)
(door clacks)
(choir vocalizing)
(choir continues vocalizing)
- I just need a moment.
- Take your time.
(choir vocalizing)
(gentle piano music)
(gentle piano music continues)
- Thank you. Just thank you.
Pink was Sonya's
favorite color. Yeah.
(gentle piano music continues)
- Lori, I just can't.
(door clacks)
I know, I'm ruining the lesson-
- No, no. Don't feel
bad for one sec.
You know, it's not one
of the five principles,
but the key to any
successful arranger
is the ability to adapt.
It's not...
Not every arrangement's gonna
go exactly as you want it to.
(door thuds)
- Amanda, everything okay?
- Yeah, I'm just not ready
to go back in there, Pastor.
- Please, it's only Pastor
on Sundays. It's Derrick.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
If you're not ready,
it's on your time. Okay?
And I'd be happy to
open the door for you
if and when that time comes.
- I appreciate it.
Um, it's very chivalrous.
- Well, I was raised well.
(Lori chuckles)
Well, I'll let
you two get to it.
Hope to see you again.
(gentle guitar music)
(record clatters)
- [Amanda] This
is like a antique.
- It's very retro.
Now, for your lesson, I want
you to pay special attention
to each person's solo.
* As I went down to the river
- Soprano.
* Studying about that
- Alto.
* And who shall
- Tenor.
* The starry crown
- The bass. (chuckles)
- Right, okay. I'm following.
(Lori chuckles)
- Here's the best part.
* Let's go down, come on down
- The harmony.
- Yes.
So, I think we can agree
that, individually, these
flowers are lovely, right?
- Right.
- Now, I want you
to close your eyes.
Close your eyes.
And I want you to imagine
that the quartet is singing.
* Let's go down, come on down
* O sisters, let's go down
* Down in the river to pray
- Voila.
(Amanda chuckles)
- How did you...
- Your first
lesson, Grasshopper.
- I'm more of a Ladybug person.
- Noted.
See, the key is to look
for ways for the flowers
to complement one another.
Now, you give it a try, Ladybug.
(both chuckling)
- Okay.
- So as you can see, we've
substantially upped our offer,
really taking into consideration
the value and
acreage of the land.
- Tom.
We've told you before, and
we will tell you again-
- It's not for sale. Hi, Amanda.
Your father was a
good friend of mine,
and I'm trying to
help you and your mom
by providing
another alternative.
- That a letter from
the mortgage company?
- We're getting more
and more behind,
and without the business loan-
- It's a notice for foreclosure.
- Again, I don't wanna
be in this position,
but I'd like to
give you the option
to earn something
substantial and fair
based on what you've built,
as opposed to other options.
(Grace sighs)
- We still have time, Tom.
And you're right, you
and Craig were close,
so you'd know that he would-
- Decline my offer.
Respectfully.
I'm rooting for you.
Reach out to me before you
hear from the bank again.
You know where to find me.
(door clacks)
(door thuds)
- Foreclosure?
How did this happen?
- No reserves and bad weather,
and your dad was the
flower whisperer.
- I should have moved back
here when Dad asked me to.
Maybe then I would know
more about the business and-
- Listen to me. This
is not your fault.
Have faith that things
will turn around.
- Why would God do this to us,
after everything we
went through with Dad
and frost and, now, foreclosure?
- God doesn't work
like that, Amanda.
I tell you what,
I'll get more hours
at the accounting firm,
and I'll keep baking,
and that'll give
you time to practice
so you can win that competition.
How'd it go today?
- Yeah, um, sorry, but
I wouldn't count on
winning the competition.
(Grace sighs)
- God wants us to be joyful,
but that doesn't mean we have
to be happy all the time.
There will be times in our
lives of struggle, of loss.
But even when there are tears
rolling down your cheeks,
there can still be
joy in your heart.
Ultimately, I want you
all to remember that
during the Easter season.
Joy can be steadfast in sorrow
and triumphant in tribulation.
Amen.
- [Congregation] Amen.
- Amen.
- Ah, James, pleasure.
Thanks, Jimmy. Good to see you.
- Sweetheart.
Oh, sweetheart, great.
- Ah, thank you.
Papa, thank you.
- Wonderful sermon today, D.
Or should I say, Pastor D?
- Samuel Stevens in the flesh.
It's good to see you, my friend.
Don't tell me you came all this
way just to hear me preach?
- I know you're busy
now, but hear me out.
I'm starting a new
venture that could be
a really exciting
opportunity for you.
A way to connect to
your two passions.
- Okay, all right, well,
we should find time
to chat, catch up.
- We'll talk soon.
- Good to see you.
- [Samuel] You too.
- [Derrick] Hmm.
- Pastor.
- Ah, (clears throat).
- It's still Sunday.
- Okay, you get a hall pass.
- Uh, lavender latte?
Just the way you like it?
- And what did I
do to deserve this?
- You know, token of
my, um, appreciation
for your very generous
tip the other day.
But I don't wanna keep
you from the congregation.
- Please, my congregation's
too busy gobbling up
your mama's banana bread.
- Mm.
- So, um, I've got an hour
until my next service.
Do you care for a walk?
- Uh, sure.
(dog barking)
So how are you
liking town so far?
- I love it, although,
for me, it's a bit cold.
(both chuckling)
Yeah, my parents grew up in
Vermont, so they're used to it,
but I was raised
mostly in the south.
You know, come to think of it,
people here are like
the weather there, warm.
(Amanda chuckles)
- [Amanda] Your mom
said that are a bit
of an outdoorsy type.
- That's my mom, loves
talking about her son.
(Amanda chuckles)
But she's right, I do
love being outside.
It's my happy place.
- She also, uh,
mentioned four-wheeling?
- Did she?
- And ax throwing.
- Of course she did.
- Mountain biking.
- What else?
- Uh, skydiving.
- Well, that's
actually a lot of fun.
(both laughing)
- If I'd met you today,
I never would've guessed.
- Is it the clean-shaven,
tailored suit jacket,
polished dress shoes thing?
It's not your typical
mudding outfit.
- Can't say I've
met too many pastors
who like ax throwing
and skydiving.
- Well, if you can't tell, it
means I'm doing a good job.
- What does that mean?
- I'm new to this town,
so I don't want people,
you know, knowing about
my extreme adventure
side, just yet.
- You think that
they'd really care
what you do for fun
when you're not working?
- They have a lot
of trust in me.
And being a pastor is
a big responsibility.
I don't want people
thinking that I'm reckless
and irresponsible
during my downtime.
I hope you can understand.
Can we just keep
this between us?
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
- Uh, sure.
Only if you tell me
more about skydiving.
- [Derrick] I never
prayed so hard in my life.
(gentle music)
(soil rustling)
- Amanda. It's six
in the morning.
What are you doing?
- I couldn't sleep and wanted
to start prepping things
before heading
Lori's later today.
- Well, let me help.
(bag rustling)
Saw you got to meet her son.
- Mom, it's not like
that. He's the pastor.
And, I don't know, we're
just in two different places.
- You know, when I met your
father at the farmer's market,
we were both searching
for the perfect bouquet
and both found it
exactly the same time.
And he insisted on
buying it, and I let him.
(Grace chuckles)
Only to have him purchase
it and give it to me.
But while your father was a man
who was incredibly
firm in his faith,
he was also a man who was
always willing to meet me
wherever I was in
my faith journey.
- And I just met Derrick. I
don't know that much about him.
- Well, and I'm sure he has
a lot to learn about you too.
Just do yourself a favor,
don't let your own
fears get in the way.
(wings fluttering)
(Grace gasps)
You were always Dad's Ladybug.
- The ladybugs are returning.
There's a slight bit of hope
that the ground
will soften soon.
(wings fluttering)
- Well, a slight bit
of hope is all we need.
(Amanda chuckles)
Mm.
(birds chirping)
(patrons chattering)
- Amanda. Are all of these
table arrangements yours?
- Uh, yeah, I'm practicing
for a flower
arranging competition.
- Why are you
using fake flowers?
- Well, the frost,
and I don't have the
budget for fresh ones,
so I've just been using
fake ones to practice.
- Practicing with fake
flowers? That just won't do.
Please, let me donate
to your flower fund,
and I'll take all of
your mom's cookies too.
- No, no. No, you can't.
Um, that's too generous.
- Of course I can.
Consider it an investment
in you and your talent.
My reward comes in the
beautiful arrangements
I get to see from you,
here and at church.
- Thank you, Gladys.
(Gladys chuckles)
* Running into freedom
* Dancing barefoot
like it's Eden *
(bell jingles)
(door thuds)
(Amanda chuckles)
- Okay, as much as I would love
to take a break and go shopping,
shouldn't we be
focusing on flowers?
- Oh, Ladybug, you
have much to learn.
- Lori. Right on time.
- [Lori] Tiff.
- Amanda, so good to see you.
I am so excited that
you came in today.
Our spring line just came out,
and let me tell
you, it is amazing.
- Feels like you should be
focusing more on pushing scarves
and jackets with
the current weather.
- Well, you know what,
if you think spring,
then it will come.
But what do you say we
try on some outfits?
- Yes. Amanda, I want you
to pick out an outfit.
- Any outfit?
- Whatever moves you.
* Yeah, yeah
* You plant the seed of love
* You plant the seed
of love in my heart *
* And it's bursting in
and out of my chest *
(curtains rattling)
(Tiff gasps)
- [Tiff] Very cute, bright.
- Oh, it's bright.
Mm-mm!
- No, no, no.
- What do you think?
- It's lovely, but...
No, follow me.
* Follow where the junk goes
(Lori humming)
- There you go.
(curtains rattling)
(Tiff gasps)
- Ooh.
(camera snaps)
- Yes.
(curtains rattling)
- It's really cute.
(Lori chuckles)
Ooh, angelic, yes.
(camera snaps)
(curtains rattling)
- Ooh.
So I think...
(Tiff laughs)
Okay.
(curtains rattling)
Oh.
- No, I'm not...
(Amanda laughs)
Try something else.
(curtains rattling)
- [Lori] Oh my.
- Oh my gosh,
looks very, very...
(curtains rattling)
- Ooh.
- [Lori] Please, twirl, twirl.
(camera whirs)
(curtains rattling)
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah, baby.
(Amanda chuckles)
(curtains rattling)
So, what seems like a fun
fashion show is actually
a valuable lesson
in floral design.
You're gonna learn
that very soon.
(gentle piano music)
Come on.
- So is there a reason you're
avoiding the Constance?
- Constance and I, well,
we used to be best friends.
- Used to be?
- Yeah.
We worked in the same
floral shop for years.
Why, she had such
an eye for design.
Yeah, there was
so much laughter.
We worked so many
hours in that shop,
creating arrangements
for every occasion.
It's missing something.
- Something bright.
- And yellow.
- [Both] A sunflower.
- There was a signature
to all our designs.
It was a single sunflower.
I like to think
that it represented
the brightness of our friendship
until, um, circumstances
changed that forever.
You see, we had a plan.
We were going to open
our own floral shop.
And then I, then I met Don,
fell in love, got engaged.
He relocated for work.
And I had to make a choice,
follow my fiance or keep my
promise to my best friend.
Broke Constance's heart.
She stopped talking to
me, and I did the same.
There was no coming
back from it.
- Sorry to hear that.
- You can imagine
how tense it is
when we see each other every
year at the competition.
And, now, I mean,
thanks to my son,
we're practically neighbors.
- Why haven't you ever
tried to reconcile?
- I think we're both just
too proud to forgive.
(gentle piano music)
So, take a look at
this first outfit.
You see how the black
skirt really makes
the red top stand out even more?
- Yeah, it pops.
- Yeah. It doesn't
have to be just color.
I mean, look at this one
with the free-flowing skirt
and the fitted top.
- So shapes.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
And the stripes here
with the solid color?
- Patterns.
- Yeah, that's right.
You're learning.
The second principle
is contrast,
how contrasting colors,
pattern, shapes, textures,
can all make things
stand out even more.
Now, look, I made
this one earlier.
It's not terribly
exciting, is it?
- Could use a boost.
- Yeah, I think so.
Okay.
(gentle piano music)
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- So what you're saying is
that contrasting things
can come together
to create something
that is beautiful.
- Exactly.
- Kinda like you and Constance.
- You. You caught
me in my own lesson.
- Maybe you have
something to learn too.
- I think it's
too late for that.
But you know what, I am
gonna go make us some lunch,
you're gonna practice
contrasting arrangements,
and then I'm gonna see what
you have when I get back.
- Okay.
(gentle music)
- Hey.
- Oh, hi.
- Are you in the floral zone
or can I say a quick hello?
- I think I would
have to be skilled
to be in the zone,
so come on in.
- So I have to ask,
which one of these
flowers is your favorite?
(Derrick sniffs)
- Uh, a favorite flower,
that's like picking
a favorite child.
I mean, I guess I would
have to say the hydrangea.
- Oh.
- Or maybe on second thought,
carnations or,
nope, maybe roses?
I don't know. It's too,
too difficult to do.
- I love seeing how
passionate you are about them.
(gentle piano music)
Well, flower protege, I'll
leave you to your craft.
But I do have one very
important question.
(Derrick clears throat)
Will you accept this rose?
(Amanda laughs)
- Um, well, after
careful consideration-
- [Derrick] Mm-hmm?
- I will gladly
accept this rose.
- You have my heart
pounding for a second there.
(Amanda laughs)
I have another question for you.
(gentle music)
(gentle music continues)
Hi.
- Is this because
of you, Pastor?
- Ask your daughter.
(gentle music)
All right, everyone, right
this way. Don't be shy.
- Thank you.
(birds chirping)
So what's up?
- Well, like I said Sunday,
I'm starting a new venture.
It's a new mountain
retreats program.
We're doing week-long
spiritual retreats
for young men up in
the Shenandoah Valley.
It's a great experience
for our retreatants
to be in nature and pray.
- [Derrick] Hmm.
- I've actively been looking
for a spiritual
leader to guide them.
But then it hit me, you're
the perfect guy for the job.
God, the mountains,
it has Derrick Matthews
written all over it.
(Derrick sighs)
- I mean, Sammy,
you know I would do
just about anything for you.
I mean, I wouldn't be here
right now if it wasn't for you.
It's just-
- I know relocation
is inconvenient,
given you just moved here,
but this is a
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Come on, don't you
miss the mountains?
- More than anything.
But, uh, I don't
rock climb anymore.
- That's not the only
thing this is about.
Your story is powerful.
The agony, the tears.
I wanna be able
to use your story
to draw others closer to God.
(Samuel sighs)
Please really think on it.
Our first retreat starts
shortly after Easter, so...
- So you need an answer soon.
(Derrick sighs)
(finger tapping)
- A new concoction? Why not?
I wanna see what your creative
side's been brewing up.
Vanilla. Solid.
Ooh, cardamom, um-
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, I know that you,
Amanda, are still kind
of a coffee novice,
but, um, I just...
Let me let you in on a
little industry secret.
You never combine
vanilla with cardamom.
They're totally different,
opposite, flavor profiles.
They don't work together.
Uh, yeah.
- Okay.
Don't think, just
experience it. (sniffs)
- Yes, it's just that the
sweetness of the vanilla...
(Effie chuckles)
Contrasts perfectly
with the spice
and complexity of the cardamom.
You're a genius. What?
- No, just a good student.
- We have to put this on the
regular menu, like, right now.
What do you wanna call it?
- Maybe, how about
Ladybug Latte?
(bell jingles)
- Ooh, two pumps, extra
handsome incoming.
Ooh, Mr. Lavender Latte.
- Mm-hmm.
(Effie clears throat)
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Good morning, Amanda, Effie.
- I'll do my usual,
please and thank you.
- Oh, you know what, actually,
you should try
Amanda's new creation,
the Ladybug Latte,
Mr. Lav, mm, Pastor.
(Effie clears throat)
- Right. Sure, Ladybug Latte.
That sounds very unique.
(Amanda chuckles)
It's Amanda's
creation, I'll try it.
(Derrick slurps)
Mm. Mm, that is, that is divine.
Well, thank you. It's delicious.
- Oh, um, Amanda,
great shift today.
Uh, you should go home.
- Uh, but don't I-
- No, no, no, no.
Actually, um, we're out
of your mom's cookies,
so I'm gonna need you to
make another batch of those.
- Uh, yes!
Ah, cookies, mm-hmm.
- Mm-hmm.
And it would be so much easier,
um, if there were two pairs
of hands helping you do that.
I have to stay here,
though, so I just...
I wonder if there's anyone
else who could help you.
- [Amanda] Mm-hmm, hmm.
- Oh, um, yeah, I
mean, the whole reason
I came in today was
to get a little break
from my Sunday preparations.
I'd be happy to lend
a stirring hand.
Of course, if you don't mind.
- No, she doesn't.
- I don't mind.
(dial whirring and clicking)
(stand mixer whirring)
- Have you done this before?
- What?
- Oh, um.
(dial whirring)
- Have you done this before?
- Is it that easy
to tell? (laughs)
- Just a little.
- My mom normally takes
charge in the kitchen.
I just kinda follow her lead.
- Yeah, I never
would've guessed that.
(Amanda chuckles)
- So, um, how did you get
into the business of God?
- Ah, I see you changing
the subject now, huh?
- Oh, just, you know,
redirecting away
from this floury fiasco.
(Derrick chuckles)
I was just kinda curious.
- You know, to tell you
the truth, I never thought
I'd be a preacher or a pastor.
I went to business
school, of all places.
Quickly found out the
corporate world was not for me,
so I decided to
follow my passion
for the great outdoors
and teach rock climbing.
I loved it, for
years, but, um...
And one event, uh,
changed my life.
I fell, 60 feet.
Yeah, cracked my vertebrae
in multiple places,
had five surgeries.
Doctor said I'd
never walk again.
- Derrick, I'm so
sorry to hear that.
- Yeah.
Yeah, that time in the
hospital, it was like my desert.
I didn't have much to turn to.
But then I met Samuel Stevens.
He was my occupational
therapist.
He not only taught
me how to walk again,
but he taught me about God.
He saved my life.
I'd do just about
anything for him.
He gave me his
granddaddy's Bible.
I started reading it,
haven't put it down since.
That book, it gave me hope.
Hope turned into healing and,
before I knew it, I
was walking again.
- Wow. I mean, that's
an amazing story.
- Yeah.
- But do you ever wonder
how you would feel
if you were never healed?
- Of course I did.
But I'm a firm
believer in faith.
You see, things
happen for a reason,
even if you can't
see it in the moment.
- Faith.
Yeah, (chuckles)
that's a hard one.
- Yeah, it is.
Especially when things
aren't going your way.
- Kinda like now.
- Yeah.
Care to share?
I mean, it's just me
and a big pile of dough.
(both chuckling)
- So I've been struggling
a lot with that
because, every year,
my dad would pray
for a bountiful Easter harvest,
and, every year, it seemed
that his prayers were answered.
So why did he, of all
people, have a heart attack?
When he died, I came home
to help my mom on the farm.
And after his funeral, I
just, I stopped praying,
stopped going to church.
And then, this year,
of all years when we needed
our biggest Easter bloom yet,
we've had the worst
winter in decades.
So am I supposed to trust
that's just a coincidence
or is that a punishment?
- I don't think God's waiting
for us to get outta line
just so He can reprimand us.
It's not a punishment.
Look, I like to
believe that God,
He loves us just as much
in good times as bad.
Maybe during hard times,
He just wanting us to get
a little closer to Him.
Comfort, support, love.
God loves us, always.
- I mean, you're a pastor, so
you have to say that, right?
- Technically.
(both laughing)
I am, but I still make mistakes.
Also, supposed to
take care of people
and, uh, right now,
getting this flour.
- Ugh.
- There.
(oven bell dings)
- So these are winners
from previous years,
and then there's mine.
- Well, there's still
time till Easter.
(cellphone ringing and buzzing)
- Oh. Good timing.
Lori.
- Good morning, Ladybug.
- Hey, please tell me that
you have another lesson ready
because I still don't
feel like I'm getting it.
- Patience makes perfect.
It's time for your third
principle: purpose.
Now, we've been working
on floral arrangements,
but it's important that
every design says something
on a more deeper,
personal level.
You have to find inspiration
outside the flowers
to put into the flowers.
- Okay, I'm following.
- So here's what
I want you to do.
The church is hosting
an Easter basket raffle
tomorrow evening at Parish Hall
to raise money for
the local food bank.
Church members and non-church
members are creating
and donating
individualized baskets.
Now, the items in these baskets,
they all mean something very
personal to their curators.
- So you want me to
arrange an Easter basket,
but how is that
supposed to make me
a better floral arranger?
Lori?
- Sorry, dear, um,
not every lesson reveals
itself right away.
- Okay. I will do my best.
- You always do. I'll
see you tomorrow.
(Amanda sighs)
- Any ideas on where
I'd get some inspiration
for an Easter basket?
- I just might.
(page rustles)
(Grace chuckles)
Oh, here's a good one.
- [Amanda] I used to love
it when Dad would push me
around in that wheelbarrow.
- And you always came
in needing a bath.
(both chuckling)
(page rustles)
(Grace chuckles)
You remember that Christmas?
- That was probably the
best Christmas ever.
You know, I still use
those pruning sheers?
- Hmm!
Feeling inspired?
- I think I've got an idea.
(people chattering)
- Oh, thanks so much for coming.
Don't forget your
raffle tickets.
(Lori chuckles)
So what do you have?
- I did a My First
Garden basket.
- Oh.
- I got something like this,
Christmases many,
many moons ago,
and it really meant a lot to me.
It gave me a sense of
independence and purpose,
so, hopefully, it'll do
the same for someone else.
- You, Ladybug, have
aced the assignment.
When you have a special
connection to your arrangements,
it's gonna show in
the final product.
Um, Grace, can I have
your help, please?
- Sure.
(Amanda sighs)
- Where's the mulch?
- Ah, didn't go
with the aesthetic.
- Ah.
- Where's yours?
- Uh, it's a faith-based basket,
complete with mustard seeds.
- Very own brand.
- [Derrick] Mm-hmm.
- But why didn't you do
something that's, you know,
like a rock climbing basket
with some ropes, carabiners-
- I know, I know.
I can't control everything,
but one thing I can
control is how people
in the church see me.
- Maybe there's
something important
about sharing all
sides of yourself.
- It's a little more
complicated than that.
- But of course. I'm here
to meet you where you're at.
- I'm sorry, are you
coming for my job?
- Mm, I'll stick to
farming, for now.
- All right. Well, for now,
I should go MC the event.
(Amanda chuckles)
(Amanda sighs)
(gentle music)
All right, and now for all the
green thumbs in the church,
we have a basket donated by
the wonderful Amanda Raymond.
A beautiful starter set
for the next great
gardener out there.
Would you look at
all those tickets?
All right.
- Please be my ticket.
Please be my ticket.
- See what we've got.
And the lucky winner is 2842.
2842.
28-
- That's me.
- Well, there we go.
Constance Hughes.
Constance Hughes, everyone.
Thank you, Constance. You enjoy.
Okay, everyone, I think that
wraps up our event for today.
Thank you all for coming out.
(audience applauding)
(gentle music)
Hey.
Look over there.
- [Constance] This is for you.
- Really?
- Yeah, I think it's...
Oh.
(gentle music)
You're welcome.
- Will you look a that?
- Uh-huh.
That right there? That's
the power of God's love.
- I do have to get
home and practice,
but, uh, I was wondering
if I could show you
something first?
- Yeah. Yeah, of course.
(gentle music)
- And voila.
- Wow.
(Amanda chuckles)
You've got good secrets.
(both sighing)
Look at those stars.
God's freckles.
That's what my mom used to say.
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure. Anything.
- I haven't been to church in
a year, and you're a pastor,
what do you see in me?
- So much. (chuckles)
I don't look at someone
and wonder how often
they're going to church
or if they're praying every day.
The size of someone's
faith, well,
that can change as life changes.
But the size of someone's
heart, that's what I see.
I see that in you.
The way you love your family,
your farm, those flowers.
- And I might be
losing all that soon.
- I know the stress of
all this must be a lot,
but have faith.
I see that in you too.
- You do?
- I do.
I'm praying for you.
Be patient with yourself.
That's my sermon for tomorrow.
The fruit of patience.
- Now that's a tough one.
- Yeah?
It is, but it's worth it.
(gentle piano music)
Um, you probably have
some flowers that
need to be arranged.
- Yes.
- We should probably get going.
- Yeah.
- Uh, thank you
for bringing me here.
(Derrick chuckles)
- Yeah.
Okay.
Patience.
- [Lori] All right.
Everything's set.
Yep.
Ah, Amanda!
- Hi, Lori.
(Lori laughs)
I remember doing these
egg races back in the day.
- This is your fourth
principle: balance.
- Oh.
- Mm.
- All right, kids...
Oh, and Amanda. Welcome.
The first race is a
practice race, okay?
Time to perfect your strategy.
If you drop your egg, don't
worry, it's a hard-boiled egg.
Just pick it back
up and keep going.
All right, come to
the starting line.
On your marks.
Get set.
Go!
(whistle shrills)
Go, go, go, go!
Careful, careful. You got it.
Go, go, go.
(egg bouncing)
- Oh!
- Oh, no!
That's it. That's it, Timmy!
Go, go, go! Yes!
Oh.
- Oh.
- Great effort.
Great practice round.
Okay, the real race
starts in a few minutes.
Do your stretches.
- How did I used to be
so good at this as a kid?
- Think of it like this,
look at your floral design,
and you have an imaginary axis
going right the middle of it
and you can distribute
flowers on both sides.
Well, think of it the
same way with the race.
Center the egg on the
spoon on that same axis.
- Center on the axis
to create some balance.
- Yes.
- So, feeling confident?
- Uh, about as confident as
I can be after one attempt.
- Well, good 'cause
I'm racing too.
- Oh.
- Care to make a friendly wager?
- I'm listening.
- Well, if you win,
I'll make you lunch.
If I win, you have to
listen to my Sunday sermon.
- You know what,
fine, you're on.
- All right. Line up
on the starting line.
First one to the finish wins.
And get ready 'cause
this one's gonna be
a lot faster than the last one.
- Okay.
- Are you ready?
(Amanda sighs)
On your mark.
Get set.
Go.
(crowd cheering)
Oh gosh. Don't drop it.
Oh gosh.
- You cheat.
- I'm not a cheat.
- Okay, wait, wait.
- I'm a pastor. I'd never cheat.
Oh, no!
(egg thuds)
- [Amanda] Oh, no!
- No, no!
Oh, good job, guys.
You did great.
(Amanda laughs)
Good work! Wow!
You really got me.
(both laughing)
- I don't think I've
ever seen somebody look
so happy to lose a bet.
- Well, losing means I
get to take you to lunch.
(Amanda chuckles)
- Well, Ladybug, those
are the four principles
that I can teach you.
Harmony, contrast,
purpose, and balance.
- But there's still one left.
Master four and earn the fifth.
(hand patting)
- That one's in here, my dear.
You have to discover it.
And in the meantime, you
need to do the three Ps
of an expert floral arranger.
- The three Ps?
- Mm-hmm.
Practice, practice, practice.
(Amanda sighs)
(gentle music)
(door clacks)
- All right.
Almost there.
(door thuds)
(Amanda sighs)
- It's incredible.
- Come on.
(Amanda chuckles)
So, this is what I
wanted to show you.
- [Amanda] They're snowdrops.
- [Derrick] I had no idea
what they were called.
I just thought they were pretty.
- They're perfect.
Snowdrops can grow in adverse
conditions like frost,
but they also tend to be
the first flowers
to bloom in spring.
- Mm. They, uh, kinda
remind me of you.
- Thank you for taking me here.
- Oh, we're not done yet. Nope.
We are just getting started.
- So, the other
day at the raffle,
you were talking about
how it was complicated,
your image and how
the church saw you?
What did you mean by that?
- Yeah, um, when I told you
about my accident the other day,
I wasn't able to tell
you the whole story.
You see, when I fell,
I lost my footing,
and one of my students,
he was tethered to me.
He fell even further than I did,
and, uh, he wasn't as lucky.
- He didn't make it?
- No, he did. Thank God he did.
Just, uh, he's in
a wheelchair now.
Not a day goes by that I don't
think about that poor kid.
I blame myself.
I can't even bring myself
to rock climb again.
- I'm sorry.
- You know, in many ways, I
feel like moving out here was
just my attempt to get away
from the memory of it all.
I feel like such a
hypocrite sometimes.
Now, I'm asking people to
find joy in their sorrow,
and here I am, I'm
running for my own.
- We all have
chapters of our lives
that we wish we could rewrite.
My dad would say,
"Without tests,
there could be no testimony."
Being open and vulnerable
shows your humanity.
It gives people hope.
- I really like that.
Thank you.
(gentle music)
(door clacks)
(door thuds)
(gentle music)
(flowers rustling)
- [Samuel] Have you decided?
Your great word will reach
so many young people.
- I know.
I wanna help, and you
more than anyone know
about my adventurous side.
- [Samuel] What
better way, then?
- There's no way around
this relocation thing?
- Unfortunately
not, given the need
to be near the mountains.
But think of all the upside.
- It's just too good
of an opportunity to
pass up, isn't it?
(door clacks)
Well, it's a pleasure,
Samuel, as always.
- It's good to see you.
- Take care, friend.
- You too.
(gentle music)
(gentle music continues)
(door clacks)
- Amanda?
(engine rumbling)
Amanda.
- So...
(Amanda sighs)
You got this. Just focus.
(cellphone chimes)
(Amanda sighs)
- [Lori] Good morning, Amanda.
I'm afraid I had a bit of a fall
carrying groceries this morning.
At the hospital now,
getting some X-rays.
Don't worry, I'll be
fine. Keep practicing.
I believe in you, Ladybug.
- Right.
Really? Is this part
of your master plan?
- Here's the good news,
you are the creator
of your own garden.
Yeah, there might be
a weed here or there,
those you just pull out.
They weren't supposed to be
there in the first place,
but with what's left, why
not water that with love?
Let the light shine down on that
and it'll grow into a
life that is beautiful.
(birds chirping)
- You're right. Thanks, Dad.
I needed that.
- Yeah.
(machine beeping)
- Hi.
- Oh, Amanda.
You and Derrick, you just
missed crossing paths. Oh my.
(Lori gasps)
You did these?
- Um, this morning.
- Well, Ladybug, I
think you are ready
to go win a competition.
- Well, there's still
one missing piece,
but I think I know what
that final lesson is.
- You do?
- True beauty comes
from the heart,
so the key to a winning
arrangement has to be love.
(Lori clapping)
- Bravo.
The final principle of love,
a winning floral
arrangement is filled with
the love that you
put into making it.
(Lori sighs)
Amanda, I very likely
won't be on my feet
in time for the competition,
but, I promise you,
I am gonna be there in spirit.
- Thank you.
That really means a lot.
- So, uh, what's going
on with you and Derrick?
You know, when someone
shows you who they are,
just believe them,
not just the bad traits,
but the good ones too.
Forgive him.
- It sounds like
we could all use
a little more
harmony in our lives.
- Yeah, you're so right.
Could you do me a favor?
- Sure.
(door knocking)
(door clacks)
- Oh. Hello.
- I'm Amanda Raymond.
We've never really
talked, but I work-
- Honey, I don't
mean to be rude,
but there's a very important
floral competition this weekend
that I need to focus on,
so now's not a good time.
- Yeah, I hear you.
Um, I just need five
minutes of your time.
- Come in.
(door thuds)
This way. Please.
- [Amanda] Wow, that's gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- I'm here, actually, as
a delivery person today.
Lori Matthews wanted
me to give this to you.
(paper rustling)
- Oh, Loretta, how
far apart we've grown.
- I don't actually
think the two of you are
as far apart as you each think.
Anyway, good luck at the
competition tomorrow,
I mean, not that
you're gonna need it.
- Thank you for stopping by.
- You're welcome.
(door clacks)
(door thuds)
Hey, God. It's me, Amanda.
I know we haven't talked
in a while, but I'm here.
We really need you.
- Thank you.
- Ladybug Latte for
luck. (chuckles)
- You're the best.
(Effie chuckles)
(Amanda sighs)
So, win the competition,
save the farm.
No pressure, right?
- Well, if it doesn't work out,
maybe you can come on as
a partner at the cafe?
But who am I kidding?
You're gonna win this thing.
(Effie chuckles)
Okay, bye. (chuckles)
Hi.
- Welcome, talented florists.
You will all have three
hours to create your designs
with a short break
at the halfway point.
As instructed in
the contest details,
you are all allowed to bring in
and incorporate one
item meaningful to you.
We look forward to seeing
your creations, and good luck.
(group applauding)
(timer dings)
* Been looking for
what's underneath *
* Holding on and keeping focus
* Oh, we're catching the
fireflies in the bottle *
* Don't wait until tomorrow
* We're living in the moment
* Not in control of
our final destination *
* We light up all
the places we go *
* We're catching fireflies
* Oh
(timer dings)
- Stop arranging.
We will have a five-minute
break before we continue.
- Ladybug.
(Lori laughs)
(Effie gasps)
- [Amanda] Lori.
You made it.
- I got cleared just in
time. How are you doing?
- Not great.
It's not coming together
like I want it to
and the clock is
ticking down and-
- It's okay.
Just close your
eyes, just breathe,
and I want you to think
about the five principles.
Harmony, contrast,
purpose, balance, love.
(gentle music)
- Okay. I'm gonna be okay.
- The halfway break is over.
The competition is back on.
- Okay. I, um, gotta
get back to work.
I will make you proud.
- You will.
* Oh
* There's hope for
a better tomorrow *
joy over sorrow *
* 'Cause God's still good
* And He's still got
it all in control, oh *
* There's hope for a
world that can change *
* There's hope for
love over hate *
* 'Cause God's still good
* And He's still got
it all in control *
* Oh
- [Group] Five, four,
three, two, one.
(group applauding)
* Oh, yeah
* Come on and keep on hoping
when the days get dark *
* Keep on singing, don't
you ever lose heart *
* Lift your eyes
- And third place goes
to Lacey Williams.
(group applauding)
We are down to our
top two finalists.
The judges would like
to recognize the work
of Constance Hughes
and Amanda Raymond.
(group cheering and applauding)
* Lift your eyes, you're
gonna be all right *
- The judges have collectively
decided that this has been
the closest margin
that we've ever seen.
But the winner of this year's
Easter competition is...
* Keep on hoping
(gentle music)
- The winner is
Constance Hughes-
(group cheering and applauding)
Which makes newcomer, Amanda
Raymond, our runner-up.
(group cheering and applauding)
Congratulations to
all our participants,
and happy Easter weekend.
(gentle music)
(Lori chuckles)
- I tried.
Sorry.
- You're apologizing?
Can you imagine the look
on your father's face
if he saw what you
accomplished today?
He'd be over the moon.
- Now that's the truth.
Oh, he left. Big day tomorrow.
- Lori, I just wanted
to say thank you
for teaching me the
five principles.
I realized that
they're all things
that I've been missing
in my own life.
You've given me a renewed
sense of purpose on Easter.
- That's the most
important lesson of all.
(gentle music)
- Congratulations.
It's really beautiful.
- Thank you.
- We're having an Easter
brunch at the farm tomorrow.
Um, wanted to invite you.
It's sort of a final sendoff.
- I'm not sure that I can,
but I really appreciate
the invitation.
- It would mean so much to
me if you could make it.
- We'll see.
Thank you for the sunflower.
- You're welcome.
- Happy Easter to both of you.
- Happy Easter.
(gentle music)
(gentle music continues)
Warm weather on
an Easter Sunday.
Doesn't get much
better than that.
- It's just wonderful to see
the best version of
my daughter back.
Joyful and hopeful.
(Amanda chuckles)
- You're my mom, you
have to say that.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
(people chattering)
(gentle music)
Dad did so many of
these for other people,
and we never did one for him.
Thank you for organizing this.
- Oh, it wasn't just me.
- It wasn't?
- No.
Pastor Derrick called me
and asked if it was okay.
(gentle piano music)
(Grace sighs)
I'm gonna go get our seats.
- Amanda.
- [Amanda] Pastor.
(Derrick sighs)
- On this Easter Sunday,
there is just one more fruit
of the Holy Spirit left
to talk about, love,
'cause today is
about a resurrection.
And in that
resurrection, love wins.
You see, God loves all of us.
After all, we are
made in his image.
(gentle music)
And yet, I realized
I haven't been
completely open
about my own journey.
God places people in
our lives for a reason,
and someone very special
in my own life taught me
the importance of being
who God created me to be.
(Derrick sighs)
Before God's path led me here,
I was involved in a terrible
rock climate accident.
It was a moment that irrevocably
changed several lives,
mine included, and
though I was lucky enough
to have forgiveness
from those around me,
I was unable to
find it in my heart
to forgive myself,
but, today, in the spirit
of the resurrection,
I forgive myself.
And I'm committed to embracing
who He created me to be,
including my love for rock
climbing, a gift from God.
You see, our relationship
with God is rooted
in love and forgiveness.
And just as God forgives
us, we, too, must learn
to forgive each
other and ourselves.
After all, forgiveness is the
purest expression of love.
So, on this Easter Sunday,
let us walk this path
of love together!
Amen!
(congregation applauding)
- Amen.
- Thank you.
Amen!
* Ooh
(door knocking)
- I'll get it.
- Making up for a late bloom.
Chicken looks delicious.
(door clacks)
- Hi.
- Hey.
(Amanda chuckles)
Happy Easter.
- Happy Easter.
(Derrick chuckles)
- Listen, I just
want to let you know
how much it meant to me.
You know, seeing your face
at church this morning,
it really warmed my heart.
And, uh, congratulations,
by the way, on yesterday.
- Thank you.
I, um, couldn't save the
farm, but, um, I did my best.
- I'm proud of you.
- And I'm proud
of you for showing
the church your authentic self.
Took a lot.
I'm gonna miss you.
- Miss me?
- Yeah. Aren't you
taking the job?
- Turned it down.
- Why?
- Because there's
something here,
something special, with you,
with us, and I feel
like it's just begun,
and I can't wait to
see where it goes.
Or grows or blooms or...
Okay, I'll stop.
That is, of course,
if you're open to it.
- Constance.
- Constance. (clears throat)
- You made it.
- I did.
- Come inside. I
can give you a tour.
(Derrick clears throat)
Come in.
- Thank you.
(door thuds)
- I have to do it.
- Yes.
- Thank you, Loretta.
And I just have to
say, I am so sorry.
Please forgive me.
- We both played an
equal part, Constance,
so I ask of you the same thing.
(group chattering)
(glass clinking)
(Constance clears throat)
- I have an announcement.
(Constance sighs)
(Constance chuckles)
This is such a beautiful farm
run by a beautiful family.
And, Amanda, you are the
most talented young farmer,
well, now, farmer and
florist, that I've ever seen.
And I might have won first
place in the eyes of the judges,
but you won first
place in my eyes.
And I would love nothing more
than to pass the
prize money to you.
(group applauding)
- Woo.
- Oh my gosh.
- I don't know what to say.
- You don't have to say
anything. You deserved it.
(Constance chuckles)
I just ask that you name
the sunflower section
on the farm after me and Lori.
(group laughing)
- It would be an honor.
(Lori chuckles)
Thank you.
- Oh, you're welcome.
- Thank you so, so much.
- [Constance] Oh.
- What incredible timing.
- So this $20,000,
it would be enough
to tide us over until
the bloom comes in,
and I was thinking
that in order for us
not to be in this
position again,
how would you feel about
the Raymond Family Farm
transitioning into a
one-stop wedding venue?
- I love that idea, Amanda.
I have always wanted
to bake wedding cakes.
(group laughing)
- Weddings are beautiful.
- I volunteer to officiate.
- Oh, and I can help
with the arrangements,
as long as my assistant
here is available.
- Oh, assistant.
(group laughing)
Oh, you haven't changed one bit.
(group chuckling)
- Oh.
(group applauding)
- Okay!
Okay!
- [Derrick] All right.
- Well, dig in, everyone.
- All right.
(group chattering)
(birds chirping)
- Happy Easter, Dad.
(gentle music)
- Are the flowers part of
the whole wedding setup?
- It's funny you ask
because I was thinking
that couples could
stand right about here
for their, um, first
kiss as newlyweds.
- Really?
Right here? You sure?
'Cause there's a lot of really
beautiful parts of the earth.
(gentle music)
(gentle music continues)
It's perfect.
- Decided, then?
- It's decided.
(gentle music)
No, you're right. Right here.
DOWNLOADED FROM WWW.AWAFIM.TV
For latest movies and series with subtitles
Visit    WWW.AWAFIM.TV    Today