Downloaded from
YTS.MX
(siren wailing)
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
(soft guitar music)
♪ White lips, pale face ♪
♪ Breathing in the snowflakes ♪
♪ Burnt lungs, sour taste ♪
♪ Light's gone, days end ♪
♪ Struggling to pay rent ♪
♪ Long nights, strange men ♪
♪ And they say ♪
♪ She's in the Class A Team ♪
♪ Stuck in her daydream ♪
♪ Been this way since 18 ♪
♪ But lately, her face seems ♪
♪ Slowly sinking, wasting ♪
♪ Crumbling like pastries ♪
♪ And they scream ♪
♪ The worst things in
life come free to us ♪
♪ 'Cause we're just under the upper hand ♪
♪ And goes mad for a couple grams ♪
♪ And she don't wanna go outside tonight ♪
♪ And in a pipe she
flies to the motherland ♪
♪ Or sells love to another man ♪
♪ It's too cold outside ♪
♪ For angels to fly ♪
♪ Ripped gloves, raincoat ♪
♪ Tried to swim, stay afloat ♪
♪ Dry house, wet clothes ♪
♪ Loose change, bank notes ♪
♪ Weary-eyed, dry throat ♪
♪ Call girl, no phone ♪
♪ And they say ♪
♪ She's in the Class A Team ♪
♪ Stuck in her daydream ♪
♪ Been this way since 18 ♪
♪ But lately, her face seems ♪
♪ Slowly sinking, wasting ♪
♪ Crumbling like pastries ♪
♪ And they scream ♪
♪ The worst things in
life come free to us ♪
♪ 'Cause we're just under the upper hand ♪
♪ And goes mad for a couple grams ♪
♪ But she don't wanna go outside tonight ♪
♪ And in a pipe she
flies to the motherland ♪
♪ Sells love to another man ♪
♪ It's too cold outside ♪
♪ For angels to fly ♪
♪ An angel will die ♪
♪ Covered in white ♪
♪ Closed eyes and hopin'
for a better life ♪
♪ This time, we'll fade out tonight ♪
♪ Straight down the line ♪
♪ And they say ♪
♪ She's in the Class A Team ♪
♪ Stuck in her daydream ♪
♪ Been this way since 18 ♪
♪ But lately, her face seems ♪
♪ Slowly sinking, wasting ♪
♪ Crumbling like pastries ♪
♪ They scream ♪
♪ The worst things in
life come free to us ♪
♪ And we're all under the upper hand ♪
♪ And go mad for a couple grams ♪
♪ And we don't wanna go outside tonight ♪
♪ 'Cause in the pipe,
fly to the motherland ♪
♪ Or sell love to another man ♪
♪ It's too cold outside ♪
♪ For angels to fly ♪
♪ Fly, fly ♪
♪ For angels to fly, to fly, to fly ♪
♪ For angels to die ♪
♪ When your legs don't work
like they used to before ♪
♪ And I can't sweep you off of your feet ♪
♪ Will your mouth still
remember the taste of my love ♪
♪ Will your eyes still
smile from your cheeks ♪
♪ And darling I will be
loving you 'til we're 70 ♪
♪ And baby my heart could
still fall as hard at 23 ♪
♪ And I'm thinking 'bout how people fall ♪
♪ In love in mysterious ways ♪
♪ Maybe just the touch of a hand ♪
♪ Me I fall in love with
you every single day ♪
♪ And I just wanna tell you I am ♪
♪ So honey now ♪
♪ Take me into your loving arms ♪
♪ Kiss me under the light
of a thousand stars ♪
♪ Place your head on
my beating heart now ♪
♪ I'm thinking out loud ♪
♪ Maybe we found love right where we are ♪
♪ When my hair's all but
gone and my memory fades ♪
♪ And the crowds won't remember my name ♪
♪ When my hands don't play
the strings the same way, mm ♪
♪ I know you will still love me the same ♪
♪ 'Cause honey your soul can
never grow old, it's ever green ♪
♪ Baby your smile's forever
in my mind and memory ♪
♪ I'm thinking 'bout how
people fall in love ♪
♪ In mysterious ways ♪
♪ Maybe it's all part of a plan ♪
♪ I'll just keep on
making the same mistakes ♪
♪ Hoping that you'll understand ♪
♪ But baby now ♪
♪ Take me into your loving arms ♪
♪ Kiss me under the light
of a thousand stars ♪
♪ Place your head on
my beating heart now ♪
♪ I'm thinking out loud ♪
♪ Maybe we found love
right where we are, oh ♪
♪ So baby now ♪
♪ Take me into your loving arms ♪
♪ Kiss me under the light
of a thousand stars ♪
♪ Oh my darling, place your
head on my beating heart ♪
♪ I'm thinking out loud ♪
♪ Maybe we found love right where we are ♪
♪ Oh baby, we found love
right where we are ♪
♪ And we found love right where we are ♪
♪ Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I ♪
♪ The club isn't the best
place to find a lover ♪
♪ So the bar is where I go ♪
♪ Me and my friends at
the table doing shots ♪
♪ Drinking fast and then we talk slow ♪
♪ And you come over and start
up a conversation with just me ♪
♪ And trust me I'll give it a chance now ♪
♪ Take my hand, stop, put
Van the Man on the jukebox ♪
♪ And then we start to dance,
and now I'm singing like ♪
♪ Girl, you know I want your love ♪
♪ Your love was handmade
for somebody like me ♪
♪ Come on now, follow my lead ♪
♪ I may be crazy, don't mind me ♪
♪ Say, boy, let's not talk too much ♪
♪ Grab on my waist and
put that body on me ♪
♪ Come on now, follow my lead ♪
♪ Come, come on now, follow my lead ♪
♪ I'm in love with the shape of you ♪
♪ We push and pull like a magnet do ♪
♪ Although my heart is falling too ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body now ♪
♪ And last night you were in my room ♪
♪ And now my bedsheets smell like you ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with the shape of you ♪
♪ One week in we let the story begin ♪
♪ We're going out on our first date ♪
♪ You and me are thrifty,
so go all you can eat ♪
♪ Fill up your bag and I fill up a plate ♪
♪ We talk for hours and hours
about the sweet and the sour ♪
♪ And how your family is doing okay ♪
♪ Leave and get in a taxi,
then kiss in the backseat ♪
♪ Tell the driver make the radio
play, and I'm singing like ♪
♪ Girl, you know I want your love ♪
♪ Your love was handmade
for somebody like me ♪
♪ Come on now, follow my lead ♪
♪ I may be crazy, don't mind me ♪
♪ Say, boy, let's not talk too much ♪
♪ Grab on my waist and
put that body on me ♪
♪ Come on now, follow my lead ♪
♪ Come, come on now, follow my lead ♪
♪ I'm in love with the shape of you ♪
♪ We push and pull like a magnet do ♪
♪ Although my heart is falling too ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ And last night you were in my room ♪
♪ And now my bedsheets smell like you ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with the shape of you ♪
♪ Come on, be my baby, come on ♪
♪ We push and pull like a magnet do ♪
♪ Although my heart is falling too ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ Last night you were in my room ♪
♪ And now my bedsheets smell like you ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ Come on, be my baby, come on ♪
♪ Come on, I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ Come on, be my baby, come on ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with the shape of you ♪
- I think the end process for every album
is always the toughest.
Finding the last possible
drop of songs to go into it.
I usually would play it to
sort of hundreds of people
before the album came out,
but probably six people
were in the process
of whittling down this album.
I think this is the best
record I've ever made
and I can't wait to play
in front of an audience.
(audience cheering)
Hello everyone, how's everyone doing?
So thank you very much for coming to this
Equals Live Experience for Amazon.
I'm gonna play some songs
that hope that you know,
and I'll start off with this one.
(soft guitar music)
♪ I took an arrow to the heart ♪
♪ I never kissed a mouth
that tastes like yours ♪
♪ Strawberries and somethin' more ♪
♪ Ooh yeah, I want it all ♪
♪ Lipstick on my guitar ooh ♪
♪ Fill up the engine,
we can drive real far ♪
♪ Go dancin' underneath the stars ♪
♪ Ooh yeah, I want it all ♪
♪ Mm, you got me feelin' like ♪
♪ I wanna be that guy,
I wanna kiss your eyes ♪
♪ I wanna drink that smile,
I wanna feel like I'm ♪
♪ Like my soul's on fire ♪
♪ I wanna stay up all day and all night ♪
♪ Yeah, you got me singin' like ♪
♪ Ooh, I love it when
you do it like that ♪
♪ And when you're close
up, give me the shivers ♪
♪ Oh baby, you wanna dance
'til the sunlight cracks ♪
♪ And when they say the party's over ♪
♪ Then we'll bring it right back ♪
♪ And we'll say, ooh, I love
it when you do it like that ♪
♪ And when you're close
up, give me the shivers ♪
♪ Oh baby, you wanna dance
'til the sunlight cracks ♪
♪ And when they say the party's over ♪
♪ Then we'll bring it right back ♪
♪ Into the car ♪
♪ On the backseat in the moonlit dark ♪
♪ Wrap me up between your legs and arms ♪
♪ Ooh, I can't get enough ♪
♪ You know you could tear me apart ooh ♪
♪ Put me back together and take my heart ♪
♪ I never thought that
I could love this hard ♪
♪ Ooh, I can't get enough ♪
♪ Mm, you got me feeling like ♪
♪ I wanna be that guy,
I wanna kiss your eyes ♪
♪ I wanna drink that smile,
I wanna feel like I'm ♪
♪ Like my soul's on fire ♪
♪ I wanna stay up all day and all night ♪
♪ Yeah, you got me singin' like ♪
♪ Ooh, I love it when
you do it like that ♪
♪ And when you're close
up, give me the shivers ♪
♪ Oh baby, you wanna dance
'til the sunlight cracks ♪
♪ And when they say the party's over ♪
♪ Then we'll bring it right back ♪
♪ And we'll say, ooh, I love
it when you do it like that ♪
♪ And when you're close
up, give me the shivers ♪
♪ Oh baby, you wanna dance
'til the sunlight cracks ♪
♪ And when they say the party's over ♪
♪ Then we'll bring it right back ♪
♪ Baby, you burn so hot ♪
♪ You make me shiver
with the fire you got ♪
♪ This thing we started,
I don't want it to stop ♪
♪ You know you make me shiver-er-er ♪
♪ Baby, you burn so hot ♪
♪ You make me shiver
with the fire you got ♪
♪ This thing we started,
I don't want it to stop ♪
♪ You know you make me shiver ♪
♪ Yeah, you got me singin' like ♪
♪ Ooh, I love it when
you do it like that ♪
♪ And when you're close
up, give me the shivers ♪
♪ Oh baby, you wanna dance
'til the sunlight cracks ♪
♪ And when they say the party's over ♪
♪ Then we'll bring it right back ♪
♪ And we'll say, ooh, I love
it when you do it like that ♪
♪ And when you're close
up, give me the shivers ♪
♪ Oh baby, you wanna dance
'til the sunlight cracks ♪
♪ And when they say the party's over ♪
♪ Then we'll bring it right back, yeah ♪
(audience applauds)
Thank you very much, thanks.
So thank you very much for coming,
this was meant to be the
week of the album release,
but obviously I got COVID
so I couldn't do it.
So I'm very, very happy
that we're able to do this
and it looks absolutely beautiful.
So basically in this show,
at the beginning of the show,
I played three songs
from old albums up there,
that are kind of prerecorded.
And then it kinda segues into this,
which is all the songs from the new album.
And a lot of these songs,
I haven't really played live before.
I'm playing "Two-step" later,
which actually I rehearsed
for the first time,
for the first time, about an hour ago.
So we'll see how that goes.
And if I mess up, then,
we'll just do it again and edit it.
So this album I basically made
over the course of four years
and it was a long process,
but I really feel like the
first song that was completed
for the album was this next song,
which I wrote in Nashville.
While I was making, it was kind of,
I didn't really intend
on making number six
collaborations project.
It kind of just happened by
accident whilst making Equals.
'Cause I was just sort of
making songs for Equals
and then every now and then making,
something that sounded
like beautiful people
or antisocial or whatever.
And I was like, well,
this doesn't really fit.
It sort of turned into number six.
But so this is a song that
I wrote around that time,
that I feel like has become
a fan favorite on the album.
And it's called "First
Times", so I hope you like it.
♪ I thought it'd feel
different playing Wembley ♪
♪ 80,000 singing with me ♪
♪ It's what I've been chasing
'cause this is the dream ♪
♪ When it was all over,
I cleared out the room ♪
♪ Grabbed a couple
beers, just me and you ♪
♪ Then we start talking
the way that we do ♪
♪ Ain't it funny how the simplest things ♪
♪ In life can make a man ♪
♪ Little moments that pass us by ♪
♪ Oh, but I remember ♪
♪ The first kiss, the first night ♪
♪ The first song that made you cry ♪
♪ The first drink, red wine,
on a step in Brooklyn ♪
♪ I still feel the first fight ♪
♪ But we both made it out alive ♪
♪ And I can't wait to make
a million more first times ♪
♪ The greatest thing
that I have achieved ♪
♪ Is four little words down on one knee ♪
♪ You said, darling, are you joking ♪
♪ And I just said, please ♪
♪ Ain't it funny how the simplest things ♪
♪ In life can make a man ♪
♪ Little moments that pass us by ♪
♪ Oh, but I remember ♪
♪ The first kiss, the first night ♪
♪ The first song that made you cry ♪
♪ The first look in your eyes
when I said, I love you ♪
♪ I can still feel the butterflies ♪
♪ From when we stumbled home that night ♪
♪ I can't wait to make a
million more first times ♪
♪ Ain't it funny how the simplest things ♪
♪ In life can make a man ♪
♪ Little moments that pass us by ♪
♪ Oh, but I remember ♪
♪ The first kiss, first night,
first song that made you cry ♪
♪ First dance in moonlight
in your parents' garden ♪
♪ I can't wait to see
everything that's yet to be ♪
♪ Our first child, and then
a million more first times ♪
(crowd applauds)
I always find like I overly
complicate things for myself
while writing songs sometimes,
'cause "First Times" and "Perfect",
no choruses are the same,
they're different words every single time.
So when I was singing,
"First Times" there,
I was going (beep).
(audience laughs)
Just trying to get all the
lyrics in the right place.
'Cause you know, when
you were kind of playing
in front of people that do know the songs
and they're like...
(audience laughing)
This is great.
I've missed gigs so much.
I've missed being able
to play people so much.
(crowd cheering)
So thank you.
So this album is a kind of
quote, unquote, a lockdown album.
'Cause it was pretty much
finished in lockdown.
The main guy that I've worked
with pretty much all my career
is a guy called Johnny McDaid,
who, I've done songs like, "Shape of You",
or "Photograph", or like
half this record, basically,
"Bad Habits".
And when lockdown hit,
we didn't really know what was going on.
So we were still keeping in
touch, and then he was like,
"Why don't I move next door to you?
And like for quarantine for a while.
And then once I've quarantine,
I can just move in and then
we can just create music."
And I was like, cool,
sounds like a good idea.
So he moved in and then we'd
sort of wave at each other
and whatnot.
And then when his
quarantine, had finished,
we started creating
music and this next song,
it was pretty much the first
song we wrote that week.
This was like May 2020.
So may last year it started off originally
like a power ballad and
it was a bit more slow
and it sped up now and
I kind of like both,
kind of like both,
but I'm gonna play it sort
of like halfway between both.
(audience laughing)
♪ This is a dark parade ♪
♪ Another rough patch
to rain on, to rain on ♪
♪ I know your friends may say ♪
♪ This is a cause for celebration,
hip-hip-hooray, love ♪
♪ Photographs in sepia tones ♪
♪ It's so still, the fire's
barely fighting the cold, alone ♪
♪ There are times when
I can feel your ghost ♪
♪ Just when I'm almost letting you go ♪
♪ The cards were stacked against us both ♪
♪ I will always love you
for what it's worth ♪
♪ We'll never fade like
graffiti on the overpass ♪
♪ And I know time may change
the way you think of us ♪
♪ But I'll remember the way we were ♪
♪ You were the first full stop ♪
♪ Love that will never leave ♪
♪ Baby, you will never be lost on me ♪
♪ This is a goddamn shame ♪
♪ I never wanted to break
it, or leave us tainted ♪
♪ Know I should walk away ♪
♪ But I just can't replace
us, or even erase us ♪
♪ The car was stuck, the engine stalled ♪
♪ And both of us got caught
out in the snow, alone ♪
♪ There were times when
I forget the lows ♪
♪ And think the highs were
all that we'd ever known ♪
♪ The cards were stacked against us both ♪
♪ I will always love you
for what it's worth ♪
♪ We'll never fade like
graffiti on the overpass ♪
♪ I know time may change
the way you think of us ♪
♪ But I'll remember the way we were ♪
♪ You were the first full stop ♪
♪ Love that will never leave ♪
♪ Baby, you will never be lost on me ♪
♪ I will always love you
for what it's worth ♪
♪ We'll never fade like
graffiti on the overpass ♪
♪ And I know time may change
the way you think of us ♪
♪ But I'll remember the way we were ♪
♪ You were the first full stop ♪
♪ Love that will never leave ♪
♪ Baby, you will never be lost on me ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Lost on me ♪
♪ Ooh, graffiti on the overpass ♪
(crowd applauds)
Thank you.
I'm gonna call Ashton Miranda on stage,
he's a very good friend
of mine and piano player.
Me and Ashton I've been playing together
for seven years now.
And I sometimes when I play certain songs,
feel very alone on stage
'cause we play them together so much.
So it's so nice to have him here for this.
Thank you for coming.
Ashton, I'm gonna throw a
curve ball in after this,
Ashton loves to rehearse
and we're gonna play
a song that we haven't rehearsed.
(crowd laughs)
After this one, though.
It's gonna be fun. It's gonna be fun.
I'm gonna leave you guessing
which one it is though.
So this next song we're gonna
play, is "Leave Your Life",
by the way.
This next song I'm gonna play,
I feel like the story around
it, is personal to me,
but I feel like now the song has come out.
I feel like the song
belongs to so many people
in so many other people's stories.
Instead of telling you
the story around the song,
I want to explain what the
song means to me now it's out.
And, I wrote this song in,
I'd never really experienced grief before,
I had my grandparents die and
I feel like your grandparents,
when you were at school,
everyone's grandparents died
and it's just a normal thing
that people get old and they pass away.
And although it's very, very sad.
That is just part of life.
But I had a friend pass away last year
and it was the first time I'd
ever had anyone close to me
just like that gone.
I had conversations with
him every other day.
And then those conversations just stopped.
So the song I wrote it,
trying to process it,
which I feel it helped.
I feel it definitely helped.
And I feel like the grief
is such a solitary thing
that I was very much solitary.
I don't wanna speak to anyone.
I'm gonna write, write,
write, write, write,
and then I don't wanna
talk to anyone about it.
'Cause if I talked to anyone
about it, I'll just cry.
And then when the song came out,
suddenly like the solitary nature of grief
became very public and it felt very bare.
And I felt weird about it,
before the song came out,
I rung up his family and made sure
that they were okay with it.
And we went through the
artwork and the mixes
and all of that stuff.
And then when the song came out,
I suddenly realized that
there was a whole world
of people feeling exactly the same way
and the song allowed
itself to be this thing
that basically gave a
voice to solitary grief.
And I've met so many people
since the song have come out
and people who,
I met a boy the other day
whose mother had passed away
and he was like, "This is
the way that I communicated
with my father as I send him the song.
And he knows exactly what
I mean without me having
to say anything.
And I can send that song."
And I found that going
on, the YouTube comments
for this song made it all make sense
because when you write a song like this,
it's very personal.
You go, ooh, I don't
want anyone to hear this.
And then when it comes out,
you realize that music
is a universal language
and it helps people communicate.
I find it, sometimes I send
songs to my wife and be like,
oh, this made me think of
you or this is our song.
Or this is that.
And I find that out of
a really sad situation,
something positive has
happened with this song.
And I'm really, really grateful
that people have connected
to it in the way that they have.
This is "Visiting Hours".
(crowd clapping)
♪ I wish that Heaven had visiting hours ♪
♪ So I could just show
up then bring the news ♪
♪ That she's gettin' older and
I wish that you'd met her ♪
♪ The things that she'll learn from me ♪
♪ I got them all from you ♪
♪ Can I just stay a while ♪
♪ And we'll put all the world to rights ♪
♪ The little ones will grow ♪
♪ And I'll still drink
your favorite wine ♪
♪ And soon they're goin' to close ♪
♪ But I'll see you another day ♪
♪ So much has changed
since you've been away ♪
♪ I wish that Heaven had visiting hours ♪
♪ So I could just swing
by and ask your advice ♪
♪ What would you do in my situation ♪
♪ I haven't a clue how
I'd even raise them ♪
♪ What would you do ♪
♪ 'Cause you always do what's right ♪
♪ Can we just talk a while
until my worries disappear ♪
♪ I'd tell you that I'm scared
of turning out a failure ♪
♪ You'd say, remember that the answer's ♪
♪ In the love that we create ♪
♪ So much has changed
since you've been away ♪
♪ I wish that Heaven had visiting hours ♪
♪ And I would ask them if
I could take you home ♪
♪ But I know what they'd
say, that it's for the best ♪
♪ So I will live life
the way you taught me ♪
♪ And make it on my own ♪
♪ I will close the door, and
I will open up my heart ♪
♪ And everyone I love will
know exactly who you are ♪
♪ 'Cause this is not goodbye,
it is just 'til we meet again ♪
♪ So much has changed
since you've been away ♪
(crowd applauds)
Thank you.
So, as I said, I was gonna throw
a curve ball, Ashton's way.
We've actually played this
song before for just once.
And this song was actually meant
to be in the setlist today.
And the reason I feel weird
about not putting this one
in this set is 'cause it
kind of goes hand in hand
with "Visiting Hours".
The story behind the song is I got sent,
we were finishing the album
and someone came up with
this bright idea of like,
"Hey, because you made most
of your last record in Sweden,
we should send you to
Sweden to finish the album."
And I was like, cool.
And they were like, "But this
is the idea, you fly to Sweden
without your baby and you land.
And then you write about
how miserable you are."
(crowd laughs)
I was like, ah, that's a bit cruel.
I basically said in my head,
I was like, do you know what?
I can write a song about missing my child
without actually leaving
the same room as them.
And I'll show you basically.
So I had this idea that I was
gonna do this song anyway.
And then my friend Michael
passed away and I flew
to Australia with my child
and we were in quarantine
for two weeks.
And basically I just
had this melody running
around my head every time I took a shower,
melody's come into showers by the way,
'cause shower sound great to sing in.
So I'm there going.
(Ed Sheeran humming)
So I had this melody
for "Leave Your Life",
but I didn't really know
what I was gonna write about.
Like, do I write about
just leaving my child
and flying somewhere?
If it felt a bit like not genuine.
And then Michael's funeral
happened and I was in quarantine
for the funeral and we
watched it over Zoom.
And I spoke to a member
of his family afterwards,
who said that basically
after every conversation,
he would end it with, I love you.
And no matter what, no matter
what every single conversation
ended with, I love you.
So the last thing he said
to everyone that he knew
was I love you.
And I thought that that
was such an amazing thing
to kind of take in to life.
And so I started doing it
with people in my family,
but I can't do it with my daughter
'cause she's 15 months now
and she was six months then.
And I felt like, even
though if I went tomorrow
and was not here on this planet,
even though she would
know that I did love her,
'cause people would tell her,
she would never actually know
it from the horses mouth,
if that makes sense.
So I wrote this song basically as that,
if anything happened and it's
called "Leave Your Life".
♪ If I forget to say goodbye ♪
♪ Before I catch the plane ♪
♪ Would you know the way that I ♪
♪ Feel when I'm away ♪
♪ We'll see the same sky tonight ♪
♪ But the stars are out of place ♪
♪ You'll never know the
weight of my heart ♪
♪ Every time I leave you, babe ♪
♪ It's hard to break the landing ♪
♪ But I'll see you again ♪
♪ I'm never gonna leave your life ♪
♪ Even at the times I'm miles away ♪
♪ You are always on my mind ♪
♪ Forever and now, I
will be by your side ♪
♪ I know it can change from day to day ♪
♪ But this love will keep alive ♪
♪ I'm never gonna leave your life ♪
♪ I-I-I, I'm never gonna leave your life ♪
♪ I could never tell you a lie ♪
♪ Or put in words your finest traits ♪
♪ The darkest green and hazel eyes ♪
♪ And yet I can't describe the shade ♪
♪ You are all this heart of mine ♪
♪ And there you will remain ♪
♪ You'll never know the
weight of my decisions ♪
♪ When I leave your smiling face ♪
♪ It's hard to understand it ♪
♪ But I'll see you again ♪
♪ Oh, I ♪
♪ I'm never gonna leave your life ♪
♪ Even at the times I'm miles away ♪
♪ You are always on my mind ♪
♪ Forever and now, I
will be by your side ♪
♪ I know it can change from day to day ♪
♪ But this love will keep alive ♪
♪ I'm never gonna leave your life ♪
♪ I-I-I, I'm never gonna leave your life ♪
♪ It's hard to break the landing ♪
♪ But I'll see you again ♪
♪ I'm never gonna leave your life ♪
♪ Even at the times I'm miles away ♪
♪ You are always on my mind ♪
♪ Forever and now, I
will be by your side ♪
♪ I know it can change from day to day ♪
♪ But this love will keep alive ♪
♪ I'm never gonna leave your life ♪
♪ I-I-I, I'm never gonna leave your life ♪
♪ If I forget to say goodbye ♪
♪ Before I catch the plane ♪
♪ Would you know the way that I ♪
♪ Feel when I'm away ♪
(crowd applauds)
Round of applause for Ashton, everyone.
I was just telling them to
give you a round of applause.
'Cause you know (indistinct).
So those songs kind of go hand-in-hand.
Weirdly, this next song goes
hand-in-hand with "Bad Habits"
and they could not be further apart.
They were written on the same
day and this one kind of came
as a sort of knee jerk reactions about,
you make a song like
"Bad Habits" and it's...
(Ed Sheeran humming)
And you go, all right, let's
try something quiet and slow.
And this song was written in
such a short period of time.
That for a long time, I
thought it was (beep),
'cause, it was written in
such a short period of time.
And I kept listening to me like,
oh, that's not any good.
And then my brother did a
string arrangement for it,
that basically brought out of its shell.
And it's turned it into this
big cinematic orchestral thing
that I love, that I love.
And yeah, I hope it lives on forever
and we're gonna play it now.
It's called "Joker And The Queen".
One, two, three.
♪ How was I to know ♪
♪ It's a crazy thing ♪
♪ I showed you my hand ♪
♪ And you still let me win ♪
♪ Who was I to say ♪
♪ That this was meant to be ♪
♪ The road that was broken ♪
♪ Brought us together ♪
♪ And I know you could
fall for a thousand kings ♪
♪ And hearts that could
give you a diamond ring ♪
♪ When I fold, you see the best in me ♪
♪ The joker and the queen ♪
♪ I was upside down ♪
♪ From the outside in ♪
♪ You came to the table ♪
♪ And you went all in ♪
♪ With a single word ♪
♪ And a gentle touch ♪
♪ You turned a moment ♪
♪ Into forever ♪
♪ And I know you could
fall for a thousand kings ♪
♪ And hearts that could
give you a diamond ring ♪
♪ When I fold, you see the best in me ♪
♪ The joker and the queen ♪
♪ And I know you could
fall for a thousand kings ♪
♪ And hearts that could
give you a diamond ring ♪
♪ When I folded, you saw the best in me ♪
♪ The joker and the queen ♪
(crowd applauds)
Everyone give it up for Ashton.
Well, now we're entering
into the interesting part
of the gig, 'cause this is the
song that I wasn't intending
on playing today
'cause I hadn't rehearsed
it once ever, ever.
And it's a loop pedal song,
and it's quite intricate.
And if it's not on time,
it will sound (beep),
but I've rehearsed it for a little bit.
And the beauty of this is
if it doesn't sound good,
it just won't make the show.
So your part of this tonight,
this is the first time I've ever,
ever, ever, ever played it.
(crowd applauds)
I hope it goes well. I hope it goes well.
This was the final song that
I finished for the record.
And this came, in a stage when
the album's being finished,
this is how "Shape of You" came about,
is basically like the album's done.
And then everyone goes, right it's done.
And then there's just this
little prodding finger
from everywhere.
My manager, Stuart is the most
genius person in the world
because he knows that
there's something good in
when you feel like a record's
finished and you just go in
and create whatever you want.
And that's where "Don't" in "Sing" came
and it's where a "Shape
of You" and what came in?
"Shape of You"" and "Eraser" came
and it's where "Bad
Habits" and "2step" came.
And this song basically came at my last,
I was on my last legs with
writing for this album.
And I was like, it's totally done.
I'd actually gone to Los
Angeles to promote the album.
I was doing all the voice
stuff and stuff like that.
And I went in for a sort of
like site session of this guy
who I'd been friends with
for a very long time.
And we hadn't really worked together
because we'd been friends.
And I just was like,
let's just go in and see what we create.
This song came out.
It's still my favorite song on the album.
And I hope I don't butcher
it today because of that.
I've just shot a music video
for it in Kiev, which is cool.
We did it in Kiev 'cause we
could shut down an entire part
of the city.
And we had like 250 dancers
and it looks pretty stunning,
but it was minus three.
All right, here we go.
If I mess this up, I'm gonna
have to do it a few more times,
but I'll probably get it first time.
Here we go.
(soft guitar music)
(crowd laughs)
♪ I had a bad week ♪
♪ Spent the evening pretending
it wasn't that deep ♪
♪ You could see in my eyes
that it was taking over ♪
♪ I guess I was just blind
and caught up in the moment ♪
♪ You know you take all
of my stress right down ♪
♪ Help me get it off my chest and out ♪
♪ Into the ether with
the rest of this mess ♪
♪ That just keeps us depressed ♪
♪ We forget that we're here right now ♪
♪ 'Cause we're living
life at a different pace ♪
♪ Stuck in a constant race ♪
♪ Keep the pressure on,
you're bound to break ♪
♪ Something's got to change ♪
♪ We should just be
canceling all our plans ♪
♪ And not give a damn ♪
♪ If we're missing out on what
the people think is right ♪
♪ Seeing through a picture
behind the screen ♪
♪ And forget to be ♪
♪ Lose the conversation for the message ♪
♪ That you'll never read ♪
♪ I think maybe you and me ♪
♪ Oh, we should head out to the
place where the music plays ♪
♪ And then we'll go all night ♪
♪ Two-stepping with the woman I love ♪
♪ All my troubles turn to
nothing when I'm in your eyes ♪
♪ Electrified, we'll keep
turning up and go all night ♪
♪ Oh, we had dips and falls in our time ♪
♪ But we know what it feels
to be low then up, alone ♪
♪ And loved ♪
♪ And all we need is us to go all ♪
♪ Night, night ♪
♪ Two-stepping with the woman I love ♪
♪ Night, yeah ♪
♪ All we need is us ♪
♪ What do you reckon, is it just me ♪
♪ Words are weapons and
occasionally they cut deep ♪
♪ Crisis of confidence ♪
♪ It tends to come when I feel the dark ♪
♪ And I open my heart ♪
♪ If you don't see it,
you should trust me ♪
♪ I feel like I've got
nothing left right now ♪
♪ Except this beauty
in a dress right now ♪
♪ She got me feeling like the best ♪
♪ And the rest are just less ♪
♪ Than she needs, so we press
play and step to the beat ♪
♪ 'Cause we're living
life at a different pace ♪
♪ Stuck in a constant race ♪
♪ Keep the pressure on,
you're bound to break ♪
♪ Something's got to change ♪
♪ We should just be
canceling all our plans ♪
♪ And not give a damn ♪
♪ Head out to the place where it plays ♪
♪ And we'll go all night ♪
♪ Two-stepping with the woman I love ♪
♪ All my troubles turn to
nothing when I'm in your eyes ♪
♪ Electrified, we'll keep
turning up and go all night ♪
♪ Oh, we had dips and falls in our time ♪
♪ But we know what it
feels to be low then up ♪
♪ Alone and loved ♪
♪ And all we need is us to go all ♪
♪ Night, night ♪
♪ Two-stepping with the woman I love ♪
♪ Night, yeah ♪
♪ All we need is us to go all night ♪
♪ Night, night ♪
♪ Two-stepping with the woman I love ♪
♪ Night, yeah ♪
♪ All we need is us to go all night ♪
(crowd applauds)
Thank you.
As a first time, I don't
think it went too badly.
(crowd cheering)
There was room for improvement.
There's room for improvement.
Now, something else that
I've never played before.
(crowd applauds)
I wrote a Christmas song,
which my manager always said that he quit
if ever I did a Christmas song.
This basically came about.
So Elton John is someone that
has been an integral part
of my career from the
very, very beginning.
When I first signed to my now manager,
he was on Rocket management.
And so Elton was essentially a
mentor and he used to call me
maybe like once every few
months just being like,
how's it going?
And what can we improve on?
You're not getting played on US radio.
Let me sort that out. I
could do a few phone calls.
You've been nominated for Grammy,
but you can't play the Grammy's.
Why don't I play it with you?
He'd basically just be this mentor
that would just always help me out.
And then as my career progressed and got,
I had more and more success,
I sort of started hanging
out with him more and more
and more and he became
from a mentor to a friend,
and then he just started ringing me a lot.
He has an iPad. I have an iPad.
So we're both not phone
people, which is quite good.
I feel like he might be
the only person on my iPad
that I call.
And I might be the only
person on his iPad that he...
'Cause we literally
speak every single day.
But this happened right
after I became a father.
He just started ringing me all the time,
just to check how I was doing.
He loved seeing my little
daughter on FaceTime
would chat to his kids.
He loves football. I love football.
His kids like Pokemon. I like Pokemon.
There's a lot of stuff that goes in there.
And he wrote me on Christmas
day, last year to say,
"Merry Christmas, you having a good day?
We should do a Christmas song."
(crowd applauds)
And so two things went
through my head at that point.
One is, God I've gotta do
a song with Elton John.
That's gonna be cool.
And then the second thing was
like, Stuart's gonna say no.
So I kind of like
tempered it a little bit.
And was just like,
I don't know if I wanna
do a Christmas song.
But if we do do one,
maybe 2022, maybe 2023,
like something like that.
And then the thing in March happened
where my friend passed away.
And instantly from that point,
I was just like, why am
I waiting to do anything?
Life is about doing everything now.
It's about grabbing life by the balls
and just having fun with
things and not worrying about
whether it's cool or not
to do a Christmas song.
'Cause I think doing a song
with Elton John in general
is pretty cool.
And he was sort of ringing me
throughout that whole process.
And so I was like, when I get back,
I'll come up to Windsor,
we'll eat some food and we
write some Christmas songs.
And so I went up to Windsor
and we finished three songs,
one of which, well we were
gonna release all three,
this Christmas, but we thought,
like let's stagger it a bit.
So there's one coming out next Christmas,
called, "Pull My Christmas Cracker,
You'll Get More Than A Bang".
And it's innuendo heavy, but
we've finished this song.
This is song the
basically after he rung me
on Christmas day, I was like,
well, I don't know what a Christmas song
of mine sounds like.
Let me think if I can think
of a chorus because you know,
it is Christmas.
So now is the time to feel Christmasy.
So I came up with a...
♪ Just kiss me under the mistletoe ♪
♪ Open the wine ♪
And I put it on a voice note and I just,
actually it says, Merry Xmas (beep).
I sent it to Elton.
And so we just had this
thing and then we finished it
and, "You not gonna put
that in them," I said, no.
(crowd laughs)
So basically I wrote
the chorus Christmas day
after Elton rung me and then
we finished it in Windsor.
And then we shot a music video recently,
which parodies all the
great British music videos,
such as East 17, Shakin' Stevens, Wizard.
I'm gonna get to playing this song.
And Ashton is back, the man.
So this is called, "Merry Christmas".
And I hope you like it.
By the way, and this is a 100%
true because I've said this
to loads of people and they'd be like,
"No, that's not true".
There's no other song called
Merry Christmas. There's none.
It's Happy X, Miss Mary X, Miss,
I'm telling you, look it up.
It feels like a glitch in the matrix.
So anyway, Merry Christmas.
(crowd applauds)
Here we go.
♪ Build a fire and
gather around the tree ♪
♪ Fill a glass and maybe
come and sit with me ♪
♪ So, kiss me under the mistletoe ♪
♪ Pour out the wine, let's toast
and pray for December snow ♪
♪ Yeah, there's been pain this year ♪
♪ But it's time to let it go ♪
♪ Next year, you never know ♪
♪ But for now, Merry Christmas ♪
♪ We'll dance in the
kitchen while embers glow ♪
♪ We both know love, this love
we got is the best of all ♪
♪ I wish you could see it through
my eyes and you would know ♪
♪ My God you look beautiful ♪
♪ Right now Merry Christmas ♪
♪ And the fire is raging on ♪
♪ And we'll all sing along to the song ♪
♪ Just having so much fun ♪
♪ While we're here can
we all spare a thought ♪
♪ For the ones who are gone
Merry Christmas everyone ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ So just keep kissing
me under the mistletoe ♪
♪ Pour out the wine, let's toast
and pray for December snow ♪
♪ Yeah, there's been pain this year ♪
♪ But it's time to let it go ♪
♪ Next year, you never know ♪
♪ But for now, Merry Christmas ♪
♪ We'll dance in the
kitchen while embers glow ♪
♪ We both know love, for this
love we got is the best of all ♪
♪ I wish you could see it through
my eyes and you would know ♪
♪ My God you look beautiful ♪
♪ Right now Merry Christmas ♪
♪ And I feel it when it come ♪
♪ Every year helping us carry on ♪
♪ Fill up with so much love ♪
♪ All the family and
friends are together ♪
♪ Where we all belong ♪
♪ Merry Christmas everyone ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ It's Christmas time, for you
and I we'll have a goodnight ♪
♪ And a Merry Christmas ♪
♪ It's Christmas time, for you
and I we'll have a goodnight ♪
♪ And a Merry Christmas ♪
♪ It's Christmas time, for you
and I we'll have a goodnight ♪
♪ And a Merry Christmas ♪
♪ It's Christmas time, for you
and I we'll have a goodnight ♪
♪ And a Merry Christmas time ♪
(crowd applauds)
Ashton Miranda, everyone.
What's everyone think?
(crowd applauds)
I feel like with Christmas songs,
you either go full in or you don't.
So the video we chuck
the kitchen sinken it,
that, I mean, that's one sleigh bell.
The actual recording of it
has a lot more sleigh bells on it.
Some ding-dong bells and yeah.
Thank you so much for being here today.
This has been really fun.
Has everyone had fun?
(crowd applauding)
I just wanna say thank you to everyone
that put on this event.
It looks phenomenal and I
had nothing to do with this.
Thank you very much everyone
who put on this event.
Thank you for Amazon
for making this happen.
Thank you for you guys to
going through all the protocols
to come here and be safe and
stand together and enjoy a gig.
And I hope you have an amazing Christmas,
and happy holidays, if
Christmas ain't your thing.
Thank you so much for letting
me play some of this album
for you and have an
amazing rest of your day.
This is my last song. Thank you.
(crowd applauding)
♪ Every time you come around,
you know I can't say no ♪
♪ Every time the sun goes
down, I let you take control ♪
♪ I can feel the paradise
before my world implodes ♪
♪ Tonight had something wonderful ♪
♪ My bad habits lead to
late nights, endin' alone ♪
♪ Conversations with a
stranger I barely know ♪
♪ Swearin' this will be the
last, but it probably won't ♪
♪ I got nothin' left to
lose, or use, or do ♪
♪ My bad habits lead to
wide eyes stare into space ♪
♪ And I know I'll lose control
of the things that I say ♪
♪ Yeah, I was lookin' for a
way out, now I can't escape ♪
♪ Nothin' happens after
two, it's true, it's true ♪
♪ My bad habits lead to you ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Every pure intention ends
when the good times start ♪
♪ Fallin' over everything to
reach the first time's spark ♪
♪ It started under neon lights
and then it all got dark ♪
♪ I only know how to go too far ♪
♪ My bad habits lead to
late nights, endin' alone ♪
♪ Conversations with a
stranger I barely know ♪
♪ Swearin' this will be the
last, but it probably won't ♪
♪ I got nothin' left to
lose, or use, or do ♪
♪ My bad habits lead to
wide eyes stare into space ♪
♪ And I know I'll lose control
of the things that I say ♪
♪ was lookin' for a way
out, now I can't escape ♪
♪ Nothin' happens after
two, it's true, it's true ♪
♪ My bad habits lead to you ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ We took the long way 'round ♪
♪ Burned 'til the fun ran out, now ♪
♪ My bad habits lead to
late nights, endin' alone ♪
♪ Conversations with a
stranger I barely know ♪
♪ Swearin' this will be the
last, but it probably won't ♪
♪ I got nothin' left to
lose, or use, or do ♪
♪ My bad habits lead to
wide eyes stare into space ♪
♪ And I know I'll lose control
of the things that I say ♪
♪ I was lookin' for a way
out, now I can't escape ♪
♪ Nothin' happens after
two, it's true, it's true ♪
♪ My bad habits lead to you ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
(crowd applauds)
Have a wonderful rest of your day.
Thank you so much.
(crowd cheering)
(crowd clapping)
(gentle music)