Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Once there was the
most beautiful place, EggTown.
A place where rabbits and chickens
lived together in perfect harmony.
Aah, but all was not perfect.
Beyond the lovely meadows in Meroly Brooke
were swamps and badlands,
where creatures lurked
and watched and waited.
And when everyone in EggTown was sleeping,
one little fellow in
particular tried his very best
to watch over his friends,
his name was Good Gracious Grasshopper.
- Good gracious.
Why can't I find a
butterscotch jelly bean.
Gracious.
Who could that be?
Sneaking about in the middle
of the night, good gracious.
Oh, that's Tiny Tessie's house.
Oh no, good gracious.
Aah, wake up Tessie, look out.
Good gracious, good gracious.
I must warn Boss Bunny Baker.
Boss Bunny Baker, Boss Bunny Baker!
Good gracious, good
gracious, wake up please!
Good gracious, get up,
you're being robbed.
- Good Gracious Grasshopper,
what are you doing here?
- Oh, good gracious, Mrs.
Baker, you're being robbed.
There's someone in your shop.
- We're being robbed?
Oh dear, wake up Bossy, quick, quick.
- Oh, he won't wake up, good
gracious, good gracious.
- I know how to wake him.
Bossy, oh Bossy, wake up!
- What? What's that?
- Good gracious, good gracious,
someone's robbing the bake shop.
- I'll call Sergeant O'Hare.
- I don't need Sergeant O'Hare,
no one robs my shop.
- Bossy come back.
Let Sergeant O'Hare handle it.
Oh, please be careful.
Good gracious.
Be careful.
- You're dead.
Who do you think you are?
- Yeah, who do you think you are?
Good gracious.
- Now, you're in for it.
- Yeah, now you're in for it.
Good gracious, good gracious.
You're in trouble now,
sergeant O'Hare is on his way.
This is outrageous, good
gracious, good gracious.
Good gracious!
Oh, no!
Oh, good gracious.
- Now I got you, you
miserable thieving thief
- I'm sorry mama.
- Hey losers, look whose back with dinner.
- All right.
- What took you so long Timothy?
We're starving here and
that Slack Cookie food
tastes like garbage.
- Here Steel, would you
like some chicken wings?
- Oh yeah, thanks Cookie.
- Anyone else care for some wings?
Now let's see how many
presents Timothy brought us
from those sweet little
bunnies and chicks.
Did you bring me any cute chicks?
- Yeah, all the chicks want
you, fried, extra crispy.
- Cough it up Timothy,
lets see what you got from
those EggTown Easter freaks.
You call this a haul?
A little crumby if you ask me.
We give you one simple job
and you'll follow it up.
- I'd have my pockets full
if it wasn't for that
sneaky little grasshopper.
He must've followed me.
- He what?
He followed you back here?
You let yourself be tailed?
You idiot.
- He didn't follow me here,
he followed me into town,
to the bakers but I gave them the slip
when I ducked into the woods.
- He's lying, he's got
fluff cream all over him.
I bet he ate most of the haul.
- Yeah, egg day is almost here.
There had to be more cupcakes and pies.
He's hiding it in the forest for himself.
Let's croak him.
- No, first we make him tell us
where he stashed the
goodies then we croak him.
- I say, if he's keeping our share,
we croak him and eat him.
- I could turn him into a
nice meat pie or a casserole.
- Just try it you vultures.
Shut up, I can't think with
all you dumb cluck shouting.
I swear you don't have
a brain between you.
Okay Steel, get the map, I have an idea.
Those little hair balls are gonna pay.
We're going to make them pay.
Make them pay.
- I can't believe I slept
all night in my chair.
I don't even remember sitting down.
Wake up Tilly, we can't
sleep the day away.
It's Monday morning and
tomorrow is Egg day.
I'm going to go to try to do my shopping.
I won't be gone too long
and I'll bring you back a nice surprise.
Can't go out without my pink chicken lips.
A little feathers spray and
I'm ready to face the day.
Bye Tilly.
What a beautiful day, a
perfectly lovely day to shop.
- Hey guys wait up, wait up you guys.
- Oh, I wish I could run that fast,
Oh, these flowers are beautiful Flora,
almost as pretty as you.
- Ms. Tessie, it's so nice to see you.
I'm glad you like them.
I saved a lovely basket of
violets out back for you.
- Oh Flora, violets are my favorite.
- I know that Ms. Tessie,
I knew you'd love them.
- That's perfect, what do I owe you?
- You don't have to
pay me now, Ms. Tessie.
Would you like me to send you a bill?
- I would love you to
send me a Bill or a Bob
or a Charlie and could you
make sure he's handsome.
Oh my.
Fresh plum cakes, they look luscious.
They were always Timothy's favorites.
- You there with the shawl,
you broke into my shop
last night and robbed me.
I'm calling the police
Would you run and get
sergeant O'Hare for me
and tell him I've captured the thief.
- Tiny Tessie robbed the bakery.
- Boss Baker just said so.
- Look, look at this, here's the evidence.
What's going on here, Boss?
- This is the thief who
robbed me last night.
The dried fluff cream from the pie I threw
is still all over her shawl.
- Ms. Tessie, is this your shawl?
- She admitted it, she nodded yes.
- See, she admits its her
shawl, she nodded yes.
- Ms. Tessie, why won't you speak?
- She's too embarrassed
to speak, she should be.
- Is that why you're nodding
yes and not speaking?
Ms. Tessie, are you ashamed
you robbed the shop last night?
- She admits it, she
confessed to the whole thing.
The fluff bream
is all over her shawl,
that's proof.
- I'm afraid I have no choice
but to arrest you, Ms. Tessie.
You'll have to come with me.
Back up everyone, back to work now.
Let's go folks, move it along.
If you won't come along on
your own accord Ms. Tessie,
we'll just have to carry you off to jail.
- Help me!
Help me!
Help!
- You will notice class
that the only way to weaken
the dangerous wolf vine violet
is to pluck out all the flowers.
That's it, no more
talking, no more laughing,
no more misbehaving, nothing.
Or you'll all be back here tomorrow,
I don't care if it is a holiday.
Who wants to be responsible
for ruining Egg Day?
Go ahead, speak up.
Now, I want it absolutely quiet in here
until the bell rings, no more nonsense.
Good afternoon
teachers and students,
this is your headmaster,
Benedict Bunny speaking.
School will be closed
tomorrow for Egg Day.
- Now, form a single line.
No talking in line, no pushing.
Stop laughing, no humming.
We can stand here all day you know.
I wish.
- That terrible Harriet, I
hope I don't get her next year.
- I had her last year.
- She's so mean, she hates everyone.
- She doesn't hate big
boring Benedict Bunny.
- Be quite she'll hear you.
- Hi.
- High is the opposite of low
young man, good afternoon.
- Tiny Tessie robbed the
bake shop last night.
- She totally destroyed the bake shop.
- The bakers were up all
night cleaning the place.
- I can't believe anyone
could be so stupid.
That's the most ridiculous
thing I've ever heard.
Ms. Tessie could never...
- She's already in jail.
It was a tail plucking.
- Excuse me, but have
you all lost your minds?
Do you really believe Ms. Tessie
robbed Boss Baker shop last night?
- Yes we believe it,
Boss Baker saw her do it.
- He recognized her shawl,
there was fluff cream all over it.
- That proves it.
- That only proves that Boss
Baker isn't any smarter now
than he was when I had
him in the sixth grade.
- Hi, I mean, good afternoon, Ms. Harriet.
- It is not a good afternoon, Mr. Baker.
I understand you have told half
the town and Sergeant O'Hare
that Ms. Tessie robbed
your store last night?
- She did.
- She did not and she
would not, Mr. Baker,
because, well first, she just would not
and second, she could not, Mr. Baker,
because Ms. Tessie does
not venture out at night
because she cannot see well at night
and because she is scared
half to death of Take-Its.
Remember Take-Its Mr. Baker?
Those lazy and thieving old
birds that live in the swamp.
They don't work, they
take whatever they need.
Think about it, Mr. Baker.
- I saw her shawl, she was...
It was her shawl.
- Could her shawl have been
worn by someone else, Mr. Baker?
- We asked her if she robbed the shop
and she shook her head yes like this.
- Mr. Baker, when poor,
Tiny Tessie gets scared
in the least, she forgets how to speak
and her head bobs up and down.
It is called shaking, Mr. Baker,
shaking from being so
frightened of Take-Its
and other idiots who accuse her of crimes
she could not possibly commit.
Do you think Tiny Tessie can
run faster than you, Mr. Baker?
Do you think Tiny Tessie could throw a pie
hard enough to knock you over, Mr. Baker?
Do you think Tiny Tessie could knock over
a great big pastry cabinet, Mr. Baker?
Do you think you should
run over to the jail house
immediately and tell Sergeant O'Hare
you made a mistake, Mr. Baker?
No more nodding Mr. Baker,
just be on your way.
- Get him, get him back.
- No, stay away from my ferret,
she doesn't bother anyone
and stop trampling through my flower beds.
- Hello Miss Harriet, I
just wanted to make sure
you were still planning to
picnic with me tomorrow.
- I always look forward to
our little once a year outing.
- As do I Ms. Harriet.
Big boring Benedict Bunny
is trying to kiss horrible Harriet Hare.
Do you think
he could reach her lips?
- Shall I pick you up at 11 o'clock then?
- 11 o'clock is perfect.
Miss Harriet, I was wondering
if you could come to my...
- I really need to go.
- Are you all right?
Those children were awful.
I've never been so
embarrassed in my entire life.
Headmaster Benedict heard the whole thing.
They were singing that horrible,
horrible Harriet Hare song
the entire time he was speaking to me.
Don't they know I have feelings too?
Well, headmaster Benedict
Bunny is never going to like
or fall in love with anyone who is called
horrible Harriet Hare.
Sometimes I think he only goes out with me
because he feels sorry for me.
I wish he could get to
know me, the real me.
or just what you see
- Hello, oh, hi mother.
No, I will not be bringing
Miss Harriet to dinner tonight.
I did not chicken out
mother, she was busy.
She was very busy.
I know I've said that before.
No one's getting any younger mother,
that would be impossible.
Yes, I will ask her another time.
I agree, I think if she got
to know me she might like me
but I don't think she's sitting home
just waiting for me to ask her to dinner.
Look, I am not perfect at all her mother
and I know there are those who call me
big, boring Benedict Bunny
when they think I can't hear.
No mother, I am not cute.
I am an adult and I am
big and I am boring.
I do not want you to invite her for me.
I will invite her myself
when the time is right.
Maybe on our picnic tomorrow.
Yes I know it's the ninth year in a row.
I love you too, mother.
Well, I can spend another
night practicing my piano.
I just wish Miss Harriet Hare and I
could get to know each other better.
But why would any creature as
lovely as Miss Harriet Hare
fall in love with big
boring Benedict Bunny?
Maybe if Miss Harriet just got to know me.
picnic, I feel so alive
or just what you need
just what you need today
- 11, 12, that's a dozen.
Okay everybody, listen up.
Chocolate tears upstairs,
losers can't be choosers, fourth floor.
We have some changes this year,
Jelly Beans with the greens,
Marshmallows with yellow,
Whites get it right.
Reds use your hands.
If you're working the straw,
stop flapping your jaw.
We want hackers not
slackers, players not layers.
Rappers snap to it.
If you work in this
room you lower the boom.
they're calling me magic
like I know you would
will be good if you can
with candy and money
I gotta have a boss
doughs, I'm the coast
shells in the truck, holdup
your son acting all funny
- Oh, it's no use, I can't
do anything with my ear.
Either one of them, and
on this of all days.
I'm having a bad ear day.
Hmm, too serious, I look
like I'm going to a funeral.
No, this doesn't fit right.
Okay, fluff up my tail,
now what do you think?
Well, do you like it?
Too puffy.
Oh, why didn't you say so?
Thank you very much, I
appreciate your honesty.
Why don't you just say it?
I look horrible.
Well, of course I look
horrible, I'm horrible Harriet.
I don't even wanna go.
Anyone as wonderful and
intelligent is headmaster Benedict
is never gonna fall in love
with horrible Harriet Hare.
Good morning, headmaster Benedict.
- I'm not late, am I?
- Heavens no, you're right
on time, I admire promptness.
I was just reading the
newspaper, let me get my things.
Well, headmaster Benedict,
I thought your proposal
for more napkin holders
on cafeteria tables
was simply inspiring.
- That's very kind of you
Ms. Harriet, thank you.
I didn't think anyone noticed.
Honestly, I can't take all the credit,
it was really my mother's suggestion.
We were having dinner one evening
and I made a bit of a mess.
I had gravy drizzling down
my shirt and globs on the...
Well, I try to institute
new programs now and then
to keep things exciting.
- Oh, I love this song.
- Wow, what a coincidence,
that's my favorite song.
- Oh, you're just saying that.
- No, it's my very favorite song.
I even sing it sometimes
when I'm by myself.
- Okay, if it's your favorite song,
sing me your favorite part.
I won't last without you
So what's your favorite part of the song?
won't last without you
Care to dance?
I might step on your feet.
- I'll take my chances.
- If you don't mind me
saying so, Miss Harriet,
you sure look lovely today.
- Well, thank you, sir.
And that's a nice vest you're wearing.
You do fill it nicely.
- Miss Harriet.
- Please call me Harriet.
- Okay, I will.
Very well, Miss, I mean Harriet.
I've been thinking, that is
thinking of you, I mean of us.
What I mean is...
with me, I can't go on
hang around just waiting
- What was that?
Gross, I can't believe this.
I can't believe this is happening.
- Is the thought kissing
me that disgusting?
No.
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to, I thought you, we...
No.
- I really need to go.
- Miss Harriet, no.
Please, don't go, you don't understand.
- I understand, I really do.
I have a million things to do.
Let me...
- Papers to correct.
- Harriet, no, please.
That's okay birdie, it's not your fault.
No one's ever gonna fall
in love with anyone named
big boring Benedict Bunny.
- Okay, listen up.
I'm tired of small jobs and small rewards,
we're gonna rob hatch house,
and we're gonna clean it up for good.
We'll have enough goodies
to last us a year.
Cookie, you pack the supply,
Steel, tune up that truck,
make sure it doesn't backfire.
We don't want any busy buddies here.
You get all the tools and knives together.
Pinch, find as many buckets,
bags, barrels as you can.
We're not leaving one stinking egg behind.
Now rest of you, empty your pockets,
make sure you have room
to really stuff them.
Then go outside and roll
around in the swamp.
What?
- To camouflage, get it?
Yeah, that's it!
- You moron, you said you
fixed this junk truck.
- Oh, my beak.
I did fix it, it's the way you drive.
Every time I fix it, you
manage to rip off the oil pan
or blow the carburetor.
- All right, shut up the both of you.
Steel, this thing backfires
again and it's your tail.
We wait here till they're
gone then we have some fun.
- Colorers, great job today.
Not too messy I'm happy to say.
Dippers, you worked hard, no one fell in,
not like last year.
Rappers, you can rap for me anytime,
though I'm not your fine shorty.
- Uh huh.
- I have an announcement.
I'd like to read the output for the day,
the grand total is.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
- And the total is
7,825,403 eggs processed.
That's about 600 more than last year.
Thank you again everyone,
you did a great job.
Be careful going home.
That was one impressive day.
I love this job.
- Hello.
Don't be ridiculous, of course
I wouldn't hang up on you
just because you're Benedict's mother.
Of course I can keep a promise.
I promise I won't tell
Benedict you called.
Why does he feel terrible?
A Bird did what?
Why didn't he tell me?
I thought...
Oh, I'm so embarrassed.
Really?
He likes me, Benedict likes me!
Of course, it'll be our little secret.
Absolutely, any time.
I would love to come to dinner
but Benedict will have to invite me.
Oh, thank you for telling me,
it was so wonderful of you.
Good night, Mrs. Bunny.
Big boring Benedict Bunny
likes horrible Harriet Hare.
Oh, what a beautiful
evening, it's perfect!
Nothing could spoil
such a wonderful night.
- Ooh, she is one great looking chick.
Oh, look at
that drumstick, I got...
- You don't remember her?
She's the old bird that
pecked off your tail
first time you tried to catch Hellen Hen.
- Oh yeah, she's a tough one.
- Good, well, she's gone
now so lets get moving.
Okay, let's go.
- Grab, get the gates.
Cookie, don't turn off the truck,
you know it can backfire when it starts.
We're taking everything, now!
What the?
What is it?
- Tiny Tessie detail, Ms.
Tiny Tessie was arrested
for the robbery of Boss Baker's bake shop.
Some old birdie took
their back for you Timothy.
- That's my mother, you oven stuffer.
Your mother!
- Sergeant O'Hare gave a statement earlier
that feather prints found at
the scene were a perfect match
to Ms. Tessie's son,
Terrible Timothy Takeit.
- You got your name in the paper, Timmy.
- According to a reliable source,
Bakers have offered a reward
for the capture of
terrible Timothy Takeit.
I need to write my mother a note.
We can drop it off on the way
back, everyone in the truck!
Come on, chap chap.
Can I have a snack?
No, you can't have a snack.
- I'm worn out, taking
takes a lot out of you.
- You can take that to the bank.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh, gotta go, gotta go.
If I don't go now, I'll
never make it to the swamp
and I'm not going there in the dark
with the rats running around.
- Take-Its, they robbed hatch house!
- I told you not to turn the
engine off you dumb twat!
There's a reward out for me,
you wanna wake up the whole town?
- Good gracious, everybody,
its an emergency.
- Oh my, it's the town bell,
I hope there isn't a fire.
It's from Timmy.
I just found out
what they did to you, I am so sorry.
I'm afraid I hurt you again
tonight, we robbed Hatch House.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm a terrible chicken,
I'm sorry I am a terrible son.
The others don't know it
yet but I'm leaving soon
to start a new life in
another place far away,
where I can never hurt you again.
I
know you will never forget
how bad I had been.
I hope you will never
forget how much I love you.
Maybe someday things will be different.
I love you Mommy, Timmy.
- Grasshopper, you can
stop ringing that bell.
What's going on?
- It's all gone, it's all gone.
What's all gone?
- Good gracious.
- What's all gone?
- Everything.
- What do you mean everything?
What are you talking about?
- I mean, everything including
Easter has been taken.
Good gracious, good gracious.
Hatch house is empty, I checked it myself.
The Take-Its took every last basket!
- Check it out, deputy Hopper.
Okay folks, everybody remain calm.
I'm sure our pal Good Gracious
here had a one too many
butterscotch jelly beans tonight
and probably had a nightmare.
- I'm completely out of butterscotch
and this is a nightmare
but I not dreaming.
The Take-Its truck
backfired under my porch
and it woke me up, I saw the
eggs myself with my binoculars.
- Hatch house is empty Sergeant,
he's telling the truth, sir.
- Good gracious, of course
I'm telling the truth.
- Take-Its?
Save me, I don't wanna
get chickennapped again.
- Oh, they're not here.
I followed the Take-Its,
they were headed to old
Takeit Town with our eggs.
- They stole my Hokey
pokey records last time.
- Keep quite!
Y'all sound like a bunch of old hens.
We are a bunch of old hens.
- Take-Its believe they
can come to our town
and just take whatever they want.
Well, I say, we're not
gonna take it any longer.
Everyone's Easter was stolen tonight.
We need to go to the swamp,
get our eggs back and kick their tails.
- I have an idea that could work.
If we disguise ourselves like Take-Its,
we can sneak through the swamp
and into old Takeit Town.
While the Take-Its are sleeping,
we'll tie them up and take back our eggs.
Anyway, Ms. Claire-line is right,
I'm going to get the eggs
back, who's going with us?
- I'm going with you Headmaster Benedict
and Ms. Claire-line.
I want the eggs back.
- I'm going too, I'm
small, they won't see me.
Good gracious, I can spy on the Take-Its
and find out what they did with the eggs.
- Last fall I was
chickennapped by Take-Its
and dragged through the
swamp to old Takeit Town.
I know the whole route
to that nasty old place
and I'm ready to lead the way.
- I'll go of course, to protect you all.
- Thank you Sergeant, but
you need to stay in EggTown
to protect our citizens,
just in case the Take-Its
come back and we don't.
- You're right and you are
the boss Headmaster Benedict.
- No, I'm the boss.
Listen, they robbed me, I'm going too.
- Bossy, you're not going without me.
- I don't go anywhere without you,
with your permission, Benedict.
- Of course, Boss and thank
you and you too Bernadette.
To the swamp, to
the swamp, to the swamp,
to the swamp, to the swamp!
Well, the
brave little group went home
to put on the darkest and
shabbiest clothes they could find,
so no one would spot them
traveling to old Takeit Town.
- I hear someone coming.
Whose that?
I don't know who that is.
- I'm going with you.
- Ms. Tessie, you can't come,
you've been through enough.
- That's exactly why I'm going.
My son is the reason you're all here,
someone in my family has
to make things right.
Please, let me come, I
won't be any trouble.
- I think Ms. Tessie has as
much right to come as any of us.
- Okay Tessie, let's go.
- Good gracious, good gracious.
Do you think the Take-Its
are watching us right now?
- That bird looks like he's following us.
- I hope he isn't a spy for the Take-Its.
- I think it's your imagination.
- What is that awful smell?
- It's disgusting.
- Dead bodies, has to be.
- Nope, that's the
stink of polluted water.
- We're going the right way,
we need to cross this stream.
- I can't put my toes in that.
- Would you rather swim across?
- Do you hear that?
- Hear what?
I don't hear anything.
- Exactly, even the crickets
have stopped singing.
- Oh my, what a beautiful flower.
I've never seen a red violet.
Oh, that smell, it's so unusual.
- That's odd, I don't ever
recall seeing red violets before.
Wait a minute, Ms. Tessie.
No, they're wolf vine violets.
- Oh my God, hold on Ms. Tessie.
- It's choking me.
Benedict, use your knife.
- Cut all the flowers, make it bleed.
It's the only way to weaken it.
Help me!
Help me, help me!
- I have her, quick, run.
- I need to get her bandaged,
she's covered in blood.
- She's bleeding but I
can't find the wounds.
- Benedict, that isn't Miss
Tessie's blood, it's yours.
- No!
- Oh Benedict, you are so brave.
- Ms. Tessie, your shawl, it's gone.
- Oh, there it is.
- I'm sorry, Miss Tessie.
- That shawl brought me nothing
but trouble, good riddance.
- Howling is louder.
- Those wolves are closer.
- That bird is still following us.
I hope he's not leading the wolves to us.
- That sign, it was here
before, I remember it.
Good,
that means we're all going
the right way and we're all gonna die.
- I'd like to be home right now.
- Oh, I don't wanna go in.
- We don't have a choice,
I don't know any other way.
- I hate to say this.
- What, what is it?
- I've read about cemetery swamp
pools, how they're haunted.
- Haunted by what?
- There's a legend about
a spirit called Muck.
They say it'll eat you
but first it sucks out your
vital juices through your...
I don't wanna hear the rest?
- Harriet, do you believe
in that weird stuff?
- I didn't say I believe in it.
- Oh, it's no use, we're
stuck in
- Stop screaming, calm down or
we'll never get out of this.
- Oh Harriet, you were
right, why didn't we listen?
Trespassers.
- Quiet, did you hear that?
Trespassers must die.
You must pay a toll.
- How dare you threaten us?
We've done nothing to you, let us go.
- Boss, keep quite.
- I've waited for you, wretched Take-Its.
- Take-Its, we're not Take-Its.
- Explain!
- Please, please, don't hurt us.
We're from EggTown disguised as Take-Its.
The Take-Its stole our Easter eggs.
Sir please, my name is Benedict
Bunny, what may I call you?
- It is of no consequence but
I am the one they call Muck.
You must be their leader,
the one they call Terrible Timothy.
- I told you, I'm Benedict Bunny.
Well, actually they call me,
big boring Benedict Bunny
but I'm not a Takeit.
- Take-Its or not, you are trespassers
and trespassers must die,
did you not see the sign?
- We did but the Take-Its stole our eggs
and we've come risking
everything to get those eggs back
or else no children anywhere
will ever get their Easter baskets.
- I will only eat one of you.
Now, choose the one among you to be eaten.
- We can't choose on
of our own to be eaten.
- Choose or you will all die.
Each of you will whisper to me one name,
the one whose name is spoke the most times
shall be my victim.
- I can't believe this is happening.
I know it's me, isn't it?
I'm so boring, I would be the one everyone
would miss the least.
We had a deal Muck, set them free.
You said only one of us has to die.
- Oh no.
- It's you, Muck?
- Yes, Benedict, my thanks to all of you.
This is how I used to be clean
and free before selfishness,
cruelty and waste conspired to
cast this evil spell upon me.
I asked you for a victim
expecting you to betray each other
but instead you each
unselfishly chose to whisper
your own name to me.
It was the purity in your hearts
that released me from my bondage.
- What happens to you now, Muck?
- Look for me in the fallen rain,
the snowy hill and the morning dew.
Farewell my friends and good
luck on your journey as well.
- If we ever get out of this
place, I'm changing my life.
- What would you change?
- Every day I teach
someone else's children.
Maybe someday, I'd like to teach my own.
- That would be nice.
- This doesn't look familiar.
- Helen, please tell me we're not lost.
- Sorry, I can't remember
if we go left or right.
It was a year ago, my mind was on escaping
not finding my way back here.
- Gracious, oh Benedict,
you need to do something.
- You're right, we have to
split up to confuse the wolves,
they won't know which way to go.
Boss, you take Bernadette,
Harriet, Clair-line
Hellen and Tessie, Good
Gracious, you come with me.
- I'm going with you, Benedict.
- No, you're not Harriet,
it's too dangerous,
I want you to go with Boss.
- Benedict, in case something happens
and we don't make it out of this mess,
I just want you to know how much
I loved seeing you everyday.
- Everybody, run, now!
- They're following us,
the others should be safe.
- I hope so.
- Good gracious, good gracious.
It's none of my business,
but I think Ms. Harriet's
in love with you.
- I wish.
Why did you say you think Ms.
Harriet's in love with me?
- Oh, good gracious, good gracious.
It's obvious to everyone
but you, Benedict.
What do you think she was
trying to tell you back there?
I can't believe you didn't at least say,
"Be careful, Harriet" or "I
love seeing you every day too."
- I wanted to, I was going
to but I didn't want her
to get hurt and the wolves distracted me.
- Well, what distracted you
for the past nine years?
- Look, Good Gracious, I've
never been able to master
the nerve to tell her how much I love her.
I mean, what did you expect?
They call me big boring Benedict Bunny.
- I hope you get another chance, Benedict.
I hope the wolves didn't...
if you'd ever told me
night trying to find her
time I won't fail
in a prison I've loathed
ended, my ways I've amended
find love in my life
move mountains if I want
back from the world
and I'll never forget
I don't have regrets
in life is for certain
feeling like, wow, wow
Harriet! Harriet!
- That's Benedict, follow me.
Benedict, where are you?
Good Gracious, over here.
- That's the bird that's
been following us.
I thought he was spying for the Take-Its,
he's showing us the way.
Good gracious,
where are you going?
- Oh, I don't believe it,
it's you from the picnic.
Thank you my brave friend.
That must be the opening to the tunnel
that leads to the Takeit's layer.
- Good gracious, good
gracious, not so fast.
This is a job for a grasshopper.
I'll go in first and make sure
the Take-Its are still asleep.
I'm so small they won't notice
me even if they wake up.
- Only you can make sure
we don't walk into a nasty situation.
Absolutely.
- Good gracious.
How many cigars can they possibly smoke?
That was a close call.
- Well, look what I found.
Look Cookie, you're always complaining
you never get any fresh ingredients.
- Oh, you're twisting it.
- Well what could be fresher than this?
- No, toast him with the stolen eggs.
- No, stuff him in muck
spice and marsh him in gravy.
- You idiots, we got a
gazillion Easter baskets
chock full of fresh goodies.
This one's too scrawny and sour to eat.
- I know, I know, Grasshopper sandwiches.
- Enough, you my scrumptious little friend
are going to be delicious grasshopper pie.
Now back off, all of you,
I got me some baking to do.
I like that too.
- Not much to you, aye Grasshopper?
- I think we should let him go.
Poor little guy, he seems like a nice guy.
- Yeah, I agree, we
really should let him go.
We are so sorry, my little friend,
we didn't mean to scare you.
We feel terrible.
- You look so thin, we've
decided to let you go.
What kind of host would we be
if we let you leave
weary and tired and thin?
How about an egg to fatten
you, I mean, to fill you up?
Strengthen your legs for
the long journey home.
- Oh good gracious, good gracious.
Oh, you are all so very kind.
I love eggs but I really must be going.
I don't wanna wear out
my welcome, you now.
- Don't worry about that,
wouldn't you like a little snack?
- Oh, I'm not hungry.
- That's too bad.
- I'm not hungry, I'm starving!
Oh, good gracious, good gracious.
My stomach isn't grumbling,
it's sending out a formal protest.
You guys take the cake, I
mean that in a good way.
You didn't even know I was
coming and here you are
inviting me for breakfast.
I'd love some egg right
now to strengthen my legs.
Good gracious, good gracious.
These eggs are delicious,
thank you so much.
They're just...
The pain, everything is going dark.
I can't, feel a thing, help me.
Take-Its, I'm dying.
The eggs are poisoned.
Oh, no, poisoned eggs?
- It's rat poison and now I'm nothing
but poisoned grasshopper meat.
- Oh, no.
They tricked us, that
could have been one of us.
They let us steal these poisoned eggs.
They were trying to croak us.
- Have they no shame?
- They're evil.
- You can't trust anyone today.
- Wait a minute, not so fast.
That grasshopper and his friends
came here to steal those eggs back.
They put a lot of time and effort
into decorating and packing and...
- You know what that means?
- They don't know the
eggs are poisoned either.
Rat poison must have accidentally
spilled into the sugar.
We're outta here, let's hide in the swamp.
We'll let them steal
back their poisoned eggs.
After they all croak
like their little friend
EggTown will be wide open.
- We'll live at the bake shop.
- We'll eat anything we
want anytime we want.
- Yes.
- I'll never have to cook again.
All right, way to go.
Let's go.
I gotta stop smoking.
Hurry up.
Hey, come on.
- Good Gracious said he'd
be back in 10 minutes.
- Something went terribly wrong,
Good Gracious is always punctual.
- Our little friend would
be here if he could be here.
They've captured him or worse.
- He went in first to make
sure it was safe for all of us,
we owe it to Good Gracious to rescue him.
- I agree.
- Let's go.
- What?
- That's it then, I'll lead the way.
Harriet, you follow me, Ms.
Tessie, you get behind Helen.
Helen, make sure you stay with Ms. Tessie.
Clair-line, you cover their backs.
- Good.
- Boss, you and Bernadette stay in back
just in case they sneak in behind us.
Everyone take your
positions, we are going in.
- Lead the way Benedict.
- Okay, they could be hiding
so don't wander off too far
while you look for Good Gracious.
Why would they abandon this place
and leave the door wide open?
- Oh no, Good Gracious, no.
He was so young.
- He was so brave.
- Even dead he's the
loveliest shade of green.
- Good gracious, good gracious, I'm alive.
I'm just faking it but
those are the nicest things
anybody has ever said about me.
What?
- You're the best
friends anybody ever had,
you risked your lives for me.
I'll never forget this moment,
but we're not out of the woods yet.
The Take-Its are hiding outside,
they could return any minute.
- But we thought you were dead.
- I played possum, I outsmarted them
and I don't wanna be
here when they find out.
- Oh, no.
- Quick, grab the create
of eggs on the floor,
I'll explain it on the way home.
Let's take our eggs and beat it.
The Take-Its haven't unpacked the baskets
from the truck yet.
It's parked behind this tunnel mountain,
we can drive it back to EggTown.
Oh, good gracious, that was
close, no one's following us.
We'll make it if this hunk
of junk doesn't fall apart.
Did everyone make it?
Yeah, I think so.
Where's Timothy.
He's not here, he
must be outside with the wolves.
Should we help him?
- You wanna go out there?
Forget him.
- Okay, I'm hungry, make
us something to eat.
I got a bad feeling we ain't
going anywhere for a while.
- You idiots, we're out of
food, we didn't stock up
because we were going
to move into EggTown.
- They're out of food, what now Dagger?
- We wait.
- Are you all right?
- Definitely, I'm better than all right.
I have the bravest friends in the world.
We have our eggs back.
I'm feeling like wow,
anything is possible.
- Wow, yay!
- We're out of forest edge.
Look, everyone is gathered on the commons,
they're all waiting for
us, but how could that be?
- Bossy, beep the horn.
Yes, yes, by all means beep.
- Hey, that's my mother.
Hey mom, over here.
How did you know were coming?
- A little birdie told me.
Tonight, we EggTown are celebrating
the return of our heroes,
our eggs and our confidence.
So in appreciation, we
are presenting our heroes
with fitting tributes.
First, the unsung hero
award goes to, Hellen Hen.
The leadership award goes
to, Miss Claire-line Clack.
The teamwork award goes to,
Boss and Bernadette Baker.
And I have to award for
performing above and beyond
the call of duty goes to
well, Miss Tiny Tessie.
The next award is really
two awards in one,
for uncommon courage in
the face of certain death
and for outsmarting the
enemy with strategy,
the showstopper grasshopper award goes to,
Good Gracious Grasshopper.
And now a very special award
for selfless service in the line of duty,
the bravery award goes
to, Ms. Harriet Hare.
- She's our teacher.
- She's so smart.
- And finally I'm proud to present
EggTown's action hero award
for boldness, determination
and for keeping cool in
the face of great peril,
I am so proud to present this award
to our music teacher and
headmaster, Benedict Bunny.
We have refreshments on the
common so enjoy yourselves.
Let the record show that
from this day forward,
today shall be known as
Easter Egg Escapade Day.
- I can't believe we
made it back to EggTown.
- I know, it's almost as
if it was all a bad dream.
- Well, it wasn't all bad.
Thank you for being concerned about me.
- Oh, you're welcome and thank you for,
well, thank you for everything.
I guess now that this escapade is over
everything can get back to normal.
- Benedict, everything
can't go back to normal.
When I was lost in the swamp
I realized I might never get out alive.
I thought about all
the things I'm missing.
I'm not coming back to school, Benedict.
What?
- You know what Benedict?
I was lost, but I've finally found myself.
I'm not ready to lose that
tomorrow, so, goodbye Benedict.
Oh, no.
- What do I do? What do I do?
Don't leave Harriet.
- She can't hear you Benedict.
- Excuse me, ladies and gentlemen,
I'm sorry to bother you.
There's just one more
announcement I need to make.
I can't live without you
I won't last without you
I won't lose you again.
- I love you.
- Good gracious!
Good gracious, having an
adventure certainly is tiring.
I think I'll pass up the free refreshments
and just go straight home.
Home, home, sweet home.
I haven't had a jelly bean
in, I don't know how long.
A butterscotch would
certainly hit the spot.
the grasshoppers roam
What's this?
It's from terrible Timothy Takeit.
- Hey, little grasshopper,
I saw you breathing.
- Take good care of my mother.
take a chance in the sea
I'll love you too till I die
- You look strong enough
but it's backbreaking work.
You have to be willing to work hard.
- Sir, I wanna work hard.
Well, Timothy worked hard
and the farmer never regretted
his decision to hire him.
What happened to all of our other friends?
Well, their lives soon returned to normal.
Oh, and by the way,
if you should ever be
passing through EggTown,
look for the tiniest house
on a top of the tallest tree
and I'm pretty sure you'll
see Good Gracious Grasshopper
munching jelly beans on his porch.
And the Take-Its, well
now, that's another story.
comes along, comes along
someone sings your song
loves me when I'm wrong
said our love will not end