Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[♪]
[sighs]
Sorry, I'm just
a little nervous.
It's my first time.
Online dating, I mean.
It's a little awkward, honestly.
She said I didn't listen.
I mean, what does that
even mean?
Well, communication
can be complicated--
She said I didn't hear her.
"Hear her."
I mean, if it didn't
always register,
it's just because
I've heard it all before.
Ho, ho, ho!
Merry Christmas!
You know, your picture
did not do you justice.
Oh, well, thank you.
And a doctor, no less.
An eye doctor, an optometrist.
As smart as you are pretty.
[chuckles]
But I've got to ask,
why the dating app?
Honestly,
my girlfriend set it up for me,
and it's my first time,
and probably the last.
[laughing]
What about you?
I...
You know, I'm just,
I'm so busy at the restaurant,
and it's hard, you know,
to meet people.
You know, I saw your show.
Oh boy.
What was I making?
Some kind of
Continental Sizzler.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah.
-It looked really good.
-It is, it is,
and you know what,
the best thing,
it's so simple to make.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
I think that I am going to lead
with my strong suit
and cook for you sometime.
In case I wasn't clear,
that was me
asking for another date.
-No, I... I got that.
-You did?
-[laughs] Yeah.
-And?
Yeah.
-Okay.
-That sounds good.
Good.
[♪]
[beeps car alarm on]
Good morning, Keisha.
Morning, Sarah.
How was your weekend?
Spill all the beans,
don't spare any details.
Okay, do not get too excited,
all right?
I don't know
if I'm ready to date yet,
but after a lot of coffee,
and a lot of disappointments,
I may have met someone.
A guy from the dating app?
Maybe.
Okay, yeah, you were right.
Am I hearing this correctly,
Sarah Levin on a dating app?
Yeah,
what's the big surprise?
It's just... so not you.
Well, maybe you don't know me
as well as you think
you know me.
Maybe I don't either.
Are you being profound
or you're just confused?
I think I'm just
profoundly confused.
-Me too.
-Yeah.
Okay, I want to hear
about this date.
Come on.
Uh, okay, well,
there were a lot
of "never-gonna-happens" there,
and then the last one...
might actually be a keeper.
Ooh...
does the keeper have a name?
He does, actually.
His name is Nigel Templeton.
Apparently,
he's this well-known chef.
Yeah, I've seen him on TV.
I love that guy.
Well, before you
and the top chef
run off together,
you wanna come take a look
behind the plastic curtain?
Hmm?
Tell me what you think?
Well, that sounds exciting.
Come on.
Well, as you can see,
everything is going--
[tools whirring]
[shouting] As you can see,
everything is going according--
Hey, Jimmy!
-Jimmy!
-[turns off tool]
You want to give it a rest?
Oops.
[laughs awkwardly]
Hey.
Didn't mean
to blow the moment.
You didn't blow anything.
This is really incredible,
you guys.
Everything should be done
by the last night of Hanukkah.
Wow.
You always pull through,
you know that?
Of course.
[chuckles]
Okay, the moment is over,
back to work.
[Sarah] Okay.
Um, thanks, you guys.
[tools resume whirring]
Yeah, here.
I'll help you.
Two in the morning,
and then two at night, okay?
Thank you for coming in.
Adam Lesser is coming in.
You're kidding.
He lost his glasses.
Says he needs another pair.
Again?
Mm-hmm.
I think he's got a thing
for his eye doctor.
A little Christmas,
a little Hanukkah.
Looks really nice.
I'm all about the Christmas.
And I'm all about Hanukkah--
[together] So we compromised.
Ah! Jinx.
Pow!
Well, I'm both,
so it works for me.
How can I help you, Adam?
I know this is getting old...
Mm-hmm?
but I can't find my glasses.
Have you checked your face?
Uh, these?
These are my spares.
Uh-huh.
You seem to have
a lot of spares.
You're not buying this,
are you?
No, but
it's very entertaining.
[chuckles]
Well, it might be easier
if I just ask you out.
Or I could, you know,
just keep buying glasses
until you run out of lenses.
No, no, um...
how about we start with coffee,
and, uh,
see where that goes?
[laughs in shock]
Yeah, okay.
Coffee.
Coffee would be great.
Okay, great.
Okay. Coffee.
Coffee.
[laughing] Okay.
Uh, hey,
see you at the meeting tomorrow.
Yes, you will.
9:00 a.m. sharp,
or I should say 8:55, for you.
-[message alert chimes]
-8:55, sharp.
-Don't be late.
-I won't be late.
Got a lot to cover.
[gasps]
It's Nigel.
Ah.
Does Nigel know about, uh,
our friend, Adam?
No, because I didn't even
know about Adam.
It's a complete surprise.
I feel like I'm putting off
this weird newly-single vibe.
It's not so "newly," Levin.
It's been four months.
Right, but, you know,
Paul and I were together
for a long time.
Four months feels like
a couple days.
He didn't deserve you,
and if you forget,
I'll be right here
to remind you.
You might
have to remind me a lot.
I'm beginning to think
I'm never gonna find
my soulmate.
Here.
Something to lift your spirits.
This right here
is from circa junior high.
-[laughs]
-Okay?
I found it in a box I have
full of Hanukkahs past.
I made it for Bubbe Rose.
You made this?
Yeah.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
Bye.
[singing]
♪ Dreidel, dreidel, dreidel... ♪
Hmm.
[sighs]
Hey, Bubs.
You know, things are looking up.
I actually met someone.
[chuckles]
Well, a couple of someones.
They seem a little more
accidental than bashert,
but you met Grandpa
on a trolley,
so who knows, right?
[sighs] What I wouldn't give
for another hug.
[woman] Hi, Sarah!
Oh, hey!
How are you?
So the Ball
is right around the corner,
and we still have a lot to do.
Are we really going to call
our annual fundraiser
"The Mazel Ball?
What's wrong with "Mazel"?
It means "luck".
[chuckles]
Well, good luck with that.
The invitations
have been sent out,
the banners have been ordered.
It's a lock, Myra.
Let it go.
I like the name.
Okay, so...
as the manager of the hotel--
I was able to get us
free parking--
Whoo!
[clears throat]
And the band will be free.
So--
I know that Jacob
is your brother,
but a band of CPAs?
Seriously?
The Bean Counters are not
just a garage band, Myra.
They also performed
at the Weinbergs' bar mitzvah--
And the Newmans'
anniversary party.
Thank you, Tom.
Who are now divorcing.
I don't think it was the band.
[laughs]
[dryly] Ha, ha, ha.
You're always Team Sarah,
Daniel.
Yes, I am.
[emphatically] Yes, I am.
I'm on that team, too.
Okay.
Let's talk about the menu.
Whatever.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, totally.
It's just, you know...
it's the first time
Paul has come
to one of these meetings
since we broke up,
and I was gonna marry that guy,
Now he's just
someone I run into sometimes.
I think this is my cue
to remind you
he didn't deserve you.
Oh, boy.
Hold that thought?
Sarah?
Uh...
Can you give us a moment?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
I don't want things
to be weird between us.
Then let's not
make it weird, okay?
I moved on
and so should you.
I just hope
we can still be friends.
We will be.
Okay.
Eventually.
And they're coming
around the final corner,
into the home stretch!
Oh! Zoey!
The undefeated champion!
Hey, Zo, do forks go
on the left or the right,
I can never remember.
Forks go on the left,
with the salad fork beside it,
and knives and spoons
go on the right.
Ah, got it.
She has a Ph.D. in cutlery.
I know.
I love you more than
all the stars in the sky.
That is a lot of love.
I'm starving.
I don't think
the kugel is done.
It smells great.
Looks good to me.
No, I think it needs
ten more minutes in the oven.
Yes, Your Honor.
See, this is what happens
when your mom is a judge.
You get used to being overruled.
Would you care to render
an opinion on the brisket?
Mm, looks good enough to eat.
[Sarah] They met in a courtroom.
Dad was a public defender
at the time.
I lost the case,
but I got the girl.
You certainly did.
That's sweet.
[Sarah] They still act
like it's their first date,
and it's been two kids
and 37 years later.
It's gross.
[laughter]
Aunt Sarah?
Yeah?
When are we
going to light the Menorah?
As soon as the sun goes down.
Can I light the candles?
How about
we light them together?
[singing together]
♪ Barukh atah Adonai ♪
♪ Eloheinu melekh ha'olam ♪
♪ Asher kid'shanu b'mitzvotav ♪
♪ V'tzivanu ♪
♪ L'hadlik ner ♪
♪ Shel Hanukkah ♪
Okay, so "Menorah" means...
"To shine."
And Hanukkah is...
The Festival of Lights.
In honor of the miracle
when just one day's
supply of oil...
Lasted for eight days.
Right!
[laughs]
You're a great teacher, Zoey.
I'm thinking
of becoming a Rabbi.
Yeah?
Or a doctor,
or an astronaut.
Those are three
excellent choices.
-Dad?
-Mm-hmm?
Can I go open
my Hanukkah presents?
Hmm, okay.
-Go for it.
-Yes!
Welcome to Zoey's squad
of pinch-hit moms.
Ah.
Thank you.
Anytime.
Everybody needs
a little babka.
Aw...
isn't that you
and your grandmother?
Yeah.
That's Bubbe Rose.
She was a survivor, you know?
Yeah.
And I love
how you use her glasses
for the optical shop's logo.
Well, she's the reason
I became an eye doctor.
Yeah?
Great face.
Great heart.
The best heart I ever knew.
Rugelach is in the oven.
Oh, I know,
I've been clocking it.
[laughing]
Daniel sure acts like
part of the family.
Yeah, well, he is.
He grew up
in the house next door.
His parents split
when he was young,
and his mom worked all the time,
so he would just come over
and hang out with Jacob,
and suddenly when I was seven,
I had another brother.
[chuckles]
So you guys never...
No.
We're just really good friends.
[♪]
[imitating sports commentator]
It's the start
of the Hanukkah Season,
and time for...
[together] Dreidel!
Dreidel, dreidel...
[all imitating echoes]
A hush falls over the crowd--
Hush!
--as Keisha
picks up the dreidel.
The prized newcomer,
no doubt feeling the pressure
of her arrival
in the Big Leagues.
Still, I think she's ready
to give it all she's got.
Here we go, here we go,
the initial spin!
[all shouting] Oh!
All she's got
is just too much.
That was very hard to watch.
I tried.
Next up is the reigning champ,
MVP,
and future Hall-of-Famer--
[all together]
Zoey... Levin!
Whoo!
[everyone cheering]
Levin has the best wrist
in the league,
and she's about
to show it off now
with her signature 360 spiral!
You got this, you got this.
I don't see spins like that
very often, Bob.
I believe she's using
the Manischewitz Maneuver.
Spinning, spinning.
The crowd waiting
in anticipation!
[all cheering]
Witnessing yet another show
of history-in-the-making.
That is a giant jackpot.
-Look at that golden gal.
-She's doing a great dance.
Get it, get it!
Oh, the crowd
loves to see that.
The future Rabbi--
Or astronaut!
--or astronaut
generously sharing
her coveted prize
with her Aunt Sarah,
who could never get
enough chocolate.
The same shtick every year.
You guys need new material.
-Hey, hey, hey!
-Hey!
Leave me and Uncle Daniel alone.
Zoey loves our shtick.
Don't you, Zoey?
Sure, Dad.
[laughter]
You know,
you should have one of your own.
Yeah, I'm thinking about it.
I said I'm thinking.
-Okay.
-What's with the look?
-I don't know.
-You have a look.
-What look?
-I see a look.
Hey, everyone,
it was so nice to meet you all.
Thank you for having me.
My first Hanukkah
did not disappoint.
Well, I hope
it's not your last.
Absolutely not.
Same time next year.
-Bye, baby.
-Bye.
Thanks again. Bye.
Dad, you're not going
to sleep tonight.
Sarah?
Sarah!
What?
Somebody left you a present.
Who's it from?
What's it say?
"For Sarah,
Night One,
Roses almost as lovely as you."
That's it?
Yeah.
Looks like you have
a secret admirer.
I guess I do.
[♪]
Whoever he is,
he has great taste.
And a man of few words.
[Esther]
I'm struck by the anonymity.
What's that?
-He didn't sign his name.
-Oh.
Well, maybe he isn't sure
how Sarah feels about him yet.
I can think of a few suspects.
There's no crime here,
Your Honor.
[chuckling]
Ooh, what about
that chef you met?
Or what about Adam?
I think it might be
closer to home.
What about Tom?
Ooh, or Paul!
Maybe he wants you back.
What about that cardiologist
you dated in med school?
No, he's married with two kids.
I do his taxes.
Okay, everyone needs
to just shh!
Roses mean a lot to me.
Okay?
Remember Bubbe Rose's garden?
It was her pride and joy.
I used to think
that's why we called her
Bubbe Rose.
[laughter]
And the white ones
were her favorite.
Well, whoever sent
those flowers
hit a home-run.
And I guess
there are seven
more innings to go.
But aren't there
nine innings in baseball?
Ah, yes,
but Hanukkah has eight.
Innings.
-Got it.
-[laughter]
Yeah.
Well...
game on.
So you know
I've been up all night
trying to figure out
who this guy is.
All right, we need
to narrow down the list.
Okay.
Well, I'm seeing Adam
for coffee.
I'm seeing Tom
at the hotel later.
That might help, I don't know.
What about Daniel?
No, it's not Daniel.
We know each other too well,
we go back too far.
I mean, there was this, like,
minute-and-a-half
in high school, but...
What happened?
Nothing.
Absolutely nothing,
which is exactly the point.
I mean, I just got it
into my teenage head
that maybe he would
ask me to the prom,
but he didn't.
He asked out what's-her-face...
Sandy Lembeck.
What about Sandy Lembeck?
What?
What are you talking about?
I thought I heard you
say her name.
[laughing]
Why would I say her name?
[laughing nervously]
How did you even get in here?
You gave me a key, remember?
Of course, I remember.
[scoffs]
I gave him a key?
-Apparently.
-I gave him a key...
You were saying?
I'm just saying,
the flowers are not
from Daniel.
We are just friends.
It's just as well.
What does that mean?
It means his relationships
never last.
No one's ever
good enough for him,
and besides,
he doesn't see me that way.
Good friends are hard to find,
so there's that.
Your mom called,
Tom said he would meet you
in the ballroom at the hotel,
and Adam is on his way.
Okay, great, thank you.
I was curious,
so I googled him.
Turns out
he's this genius
software developer.
Wow.
That would explain why
he's always so distracted, huh?
And he just sold his company.
We're talking tech-money,
which tends to be huge.
Expensive gifts
like two dozen roses
would make sense.
Hmm.
He's also very shy,
which would explain
why he wouldn't sign the card.
Hey, I'm grabbing some lunch.
You guys want anything?
Corned beef on rye,
extra mustard?
[laughs] Thanks,
but, actually, I have a date.
-You have a date?
-Yeah.
With who?
Uh... him.
You're here.
Yeah, I work here. [laughs]
Kind of a safe bet.
At the risk of blowing
any chance I have
of being mistaken for cool,
I've never been more excited
for a cup of coffee.
[laughs]
Okay, well, um...
Okay. [laughs]
Let's, uh...
Let's get some coffee.
Get some coffee...
Okay.
Bye.
Make good choices.
That's the guy who keeps
losing his glasses?
He's got a lot on his mind.
Like what?
Complicated tech-stuff...
and apparently, Sarah.
So if coffee goes well,
maybe we could
work our way up to lunch,
or maybe even dinner?
Yeah.
Yeah, I can see that happening.
Uh, there's this great place
in San Francisco
that I'd love to take you to.
[laughs]
San Francisco?
Wow, that's a long way to go
for a meal.
Well, when I sold
my start-up company,
part of the deal
was that I got to use
the corporate jet.
[sighs]
I'm trying to impress you,
and...
Is it working?
[laughs]
Uh, well,
asking that question is.
Honesty goes
a long way with me, so...
Here's some more.
I... I spent my life
talking to a computers,
so my social skills
are a little lacking,
hence all the spare glasses.
Well,
they got you a dinner
in San Francisco.
Really?
When?
Let's just keep it local
till after the holidays.
Right, right, okay.
You know,
in honor of Hanukkah,
I've been leaning into
my Jewish side a little more.
It is my favorite time of year,
you know.
And now it's mine.
Too much?
[laughs]
You're doing fine.
[♪]
I can't believe
how long it's been
since I've been here.
Yeah, I know.
Wow.
Is it finished?
I can't see this
getting any better than this.
It's pretty close.
You've come a long way
since building those forts
in my backyard.
I mean, you know,
cardboard boxes
are an underrated medium.
[laughs]
Except when they wilt
in the rain.
Well, they were fun
while they lasted.
Yeah. Come on.
[♪]
I think the Hanukkah Hunt
will be great here.
Wow.
For sure.
There's, like,
a million places outside
that we can hide the Gelt.
Yeah.
I mean, I can't wait
for all the kids to be here,
you know, running around,
jacked up on sugar.
I don't think
you should sell this place.
I think you should keep it.
You know, that way, one day,
you can have
your own little kids
running around
all hyped up on sugar.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think I'd like that.
Mm-hmm.
And I'm glad you like it.
The house.
I'm glad you like the house.
Yeah.
It's so you, I love it.
Thanks.
So your list
of anonymous suitors,
who's on it?
It's a work in progress.
What about your list?
Can we talk about your list?
My list?
I don't have a list.
Oh, please.
No one's leaving roses
on my porch.
Trust me.
Okay, it's not the roses.
It's the fact
that someone out there
actually cares.
Well, whoever he is,
he'd be lucky to have you.
True story.
Amen, sister.
You want a cup of tea? Yeah?
Yeah, I'd love some tea.
Okay, so good, yeah.
I think it will work
even better than the park.
I think so, too.
Yeah.
Do you have time
for a game?
Oh, ho, ho!
Bring it.
Well, last time I brought it,
you lost.
Uh, pretty sure I fell asleep
waiting for you to make a move.
And that move was check-mate.
[sighs]
You're going down.
This is just like Chess Club
in high school,
only you've gotten slower.
Mm-mm, you've confused
speed with ability.
Oh, you want to talk
about ability?
Do you know
that out of the 236 games
that we've played,
I won 141?
I cannot believe
you're keeping a tally.
you are not making a move.
You're so cautious.
It's very complicated
from my perspective.
Is that so?
Excuse me.
Rook to Bishop 4.
So I should just
ignore your knight?
Wait, is this a new queen?
Yeah.
When in doubt, I whittle.
What are you in doubt about?
My next move.
Well, sometimes, Daniel,
you just have to make one.
See, that was very bold of you.
You wanted me to make a move.
[laughs]
Right, I gotta...
I gotta get going.
Too bad.
I don't want the game to end.
Yeah, I, uh...
I promised my mom
I'd help her with dinner, so...
don't be late.
To be continued.
Is that enough chicken?
It should last me
until tomorrow night.
[chuckles]
To me, you're still
a growing boy.
Yeah, but I'm growing wider,
not taller.
[laughs]
And I packed extra latkes.
You can have those
for breakfast.
Ooh, Your Honor, I will oblige.
Mm-hmm.
You taking off, bro?
Yeah, bro.
You haven't called me bro
since high school.
Ah, it's getting the band
back together.
I'm reliving my youth.
[imitating drums]
My god, now there's
a scary thought right there.
[trilling playfully]
Okay, I gotta go.
I gotta go, thank you so much.
It was so good.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
I will see you tomorrow
at your
soon-to-be-renovated office.
Yes, you will. Bro.
Yeah!
[laughs]
-Bro!
Bye.
[sighing]
You guys are special.
Mm-hmm.
Mm!
Oh, these are for Zoey.
-Oh... right.
-Yeah.
-For Zoey.
-[chuckling]
I should probably get her home.
She's half asleep already.
Too much fun,
and too much Gelt,
and too many presents.
-Oh, come on.
-Never!
You know,
I can't resist myself.
Nougie, nougie, nougie!
Okay!
[laughs]
You know it takes
a lot of work
to look like this.
Yeah, no, I know,
a lot of work.
-Bye.
-Bye, sweetie.
Great dinner.
Shall we?
Yes, we shall.
I'll walk you and Zoey out.
[sighs fondly]
What a father Jacob's become.
I know.
When he lost Ava,
I wasn't sure he'd be okay.
Oh, he's fine.
He's got Zoey, and his band.
He's like the Ringo Starr
of CPAs.
[laughs]
So any idea
who your secret admirer is?
Mm-mm, no,
but I'm having a great time
trying to figure it out.
You always loved
puzzles and mysteries.
This is right up your alley.
Mm, I'm like
the Jewish Nancy Drew.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Maybe he'll give us
another clue.
Maybe I'll get us
another slice of kugel.
[laughs]
That's an idea.
[♪]
Whoa.
That's a lot of chocolate.
[telephone rings]
Did you get another gift?
What did the card say?
"Night Two.
Sarah, sweeter than chocolate."
That's not a lot to go on.
I know.
It's someone that knows
how much I love chocolate
and roses.
Well, whoever it is,
he hit another home run.
Yeah, well, there's
enough chocolate in here
to last me till next Hanukkah.
I feel like I'm always
trying to make things last
probably longer
than they should.
Still trying to find
a love that lasts.
Oh, sweetheart.
If it's the real thing,
it doesn't end.
It only grows.
[chuckles fondly]
Love you, Mom.
Good night.
Love you.
[Sarah] So, I get home,
and there it was,
this beautiful basket,
with the most amazing chocolate
I've ever had in my life.
And still no idea
who this guy is?
[imitating Forest Gump]
Life is like
a basket of chocolates.
You never know--
[together]
--what you're gonna get.
Or who they're from.
[laughing]
-What?
-Sorry.
"Forrest Gump" was, like,
my favorite movie as a kid.
She would sit in the dark,
chocolate all over her face,
crying her eyes out.
Not because of the story,
because she'd run out
of Raisinets.
Excuse me,
you love that movie
just as much as I do.
Yes, I do.
All right, I have to
get back to work.
Uh, Mr. Wilson should be
in Exam Room 2.
His eyes should be
dilated by now.
Also, did you get this email
from SwapOrBid
about those antique glasses?
[Sarah] Let me see that.
Oh, I hope
they haven't sold yet.
[cell phone rings]
Um, will you see
what you can find?
Yeah, sure.
I'm on it.
Hey, Nigel.
Lovely hearing from you.
That guy's very persistent.
Maybe he's the one
sending the gifts.
Well, I would love
to have lunch
at your restaurant,
but, um, I kind of have
a busy week.
Okay, well, how about
I bring the restaurant to you?
[chuckles]
What does that mean?
Well, think of it
like a picnic of sorts,
but one prepared
by a Michelin-starred chef.
Well, how can I resist
an offer like that?
[chuckles]
Well, you can't.
What was the offer?
Oh, nothing.
Just a gourmet meal
prepared by one
of Seattle's top chefs.
No big deal.
[♪]
Hey.
Welcome!
I'm Keisha,
Sarah's assistant,
and friend.
Good to know.
Is she here?
[chuckles]
Right. Sarah.
She'll be out in a second.
Hi.
-Hey.
I hope you're hungry.
Wow, what a lovely basket.
Do you always deliver lunch
in baskets?
It's a picnic basket,
but I do save it
for special occasions,
like this one.
Oh, um, Nigel,
this is my friend, Daniel.
Hey.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, you too.
We can have lunch
in my office.
Lead the way.
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
See ya.
I really hope
Nigel is the guy.
Really?
Yeah, I mean, he's nice,
and he's famous,
and he's really cute.
They've been in there
a long time.
Must be going well.
She met him on a dating app,
he could be anyone.
I'm sure he is
who he says he is.
I mean, he has his own TV show.
Right.
But it's sweet
how protective you are.
Well, that was
the best office picnic
I've ever had.
Also the only one...
-[chuckles]
-but still.
Well, perhaps
we can do it again.
I would really like that.
Well, in that case,
I hope it's very soon.
Me too.
I can't wait.
Not many guys can pull off
kissing a woman's hand.
Personally,
I thought it was a little much.
Well, I thought it was swell.
Swell?
Yeah.
Well, it was.
She did just say "swell"?
She did.
Swell...
[sighs]
Hey, I couldn't find
those knobs that you wanted,
but I got something close.
Okay.
I can finish up those shelves.
But only if you pay me
1,000 bucks an hour.
You're good,
but you're not that good.
[chuckles]
What is going on with you?
I got an offer
from a developer
to build seven custom homes
in Aspen.
And that's a bad thing
because...?
It means moving there,
probably for a few years.
And that's a bad thing
because...?
My life!
My friends,
the closest thing I have
to a family is here.
Okay,
so what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
I haven't decided.
Hey, am I invited
if you take this gig?
Not for 1,000 bucks an hour.
I'll give you a discount.
You'd give me a discount?
Oh, I appreciate that.
That's so nice of you, man.
Thank you.
Only for you.
So, in addition
to the Mazel Ball,
we're also overseeing
the Hanukkah Hunt this year.
For those of you
who don't know,
that's like an Easter Egg hunt,
but with Gelt...
And that is why
we need more toys.
We really want all the kids
to feel like they won.
We have a problem.
We're in the middle
of a meeting, Myra.
The caterer for the Mazel Ball
was double-booked.
That's why he wasn't
returning my calls,
and when I confronted him,
he quit.
The hotel restaurant
doesn't do private events.
We will never get
a decent caterer
on such short notice.
Okay, I may know someone
who might be able to help.
Nigel Templeton
is a friend of mine.
This is your solution?
He's a very
well-known chef, Myra.
Yeah, I know who he is--
Mr. Continental Fusion.
What does he know
about the traditions
of Hanukkah?
Do we really want our dinner
to be all chefy and fancy?
Fancy.
So the Mazel Ball
will have a fusion twist.
-[sighs]
-Mushy peas and Scottish eggs?
That is, if he's even
willing to do it.
I mean, honestly,
I cannot imagine him
catering a Hanukkah fundraiser.
Yeah, he's so busy,
he's not available probably.
Mm-mm.
Let's just see about that.
Yeah.
All right, moving on.
[message alert buzzes]
Sarah?
Yeah?
Can I talk to you a minute?
Uh, sorry,
this might be Nigel.
Is it him?
No, it's...
I've been trying to get
these vintage glasses online.
They look just like the ones
Bubbe Rose used to have.
Yeah.
Sorry.
What's up?
Well, a lot's happened
over the last few months.
I made partner.
Wow.
That's fantastic.
Congratulations.
I know how much
that meant to you.
You mean a lot to me, too.
I've been thinking a lot
about our life together.
I miss you, Sarah.
Um...
I'm not really sure
what to say.
[Sarah humming]
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
How many of these
did we put in it?
Three.
No, four!
[laughs]
I lost count.
Is that bad?
[laughing]
It's not like
it's our first time
making latkes.
I know, but this is
the first time
I've ever hosted
a Hanukkah dinner.
Aw...
are you nervous?
No!
Yes, I'm freaking out.
[laughs]
I want to make sure
I follow Bubbe Rose's recipe
to the letter,
or should I say, to the latke.
That's her recipe right there?
Yeah, she gave it to me.
Jealous?
Here.
She knew how much
I loved them...
and her.
Aw...
Ooh, brisket!
How's it looking in there?
Looks like Hanukkah.
[chuckles]
So, um, have you spoken
to your dad recently?
Uh, yeah,
he called to wish me
a Happy Hanukkah.
How did that go?
It was polite,
distant.
He and his wife seem to like
living in Florida.
You know your dad
was more of a father to me.
He's the one I want to be
when I grow up.
When do you think
that will be?
It could happen any day now.
[laughs]
My Peter Pan.
Well, Peter,
you have built a beautiful fort
all on your own,
you're making
this incredible meal
for your chosen family,
and you have yet
to burn that meal, so--
It's not burnt.
--I'd say
you did pretty good.
[♪]
L'Chaim.
[clinking glasses]
-Well, it is delicious
-Absolutely!
-Who did the bean salad?
-I did not make that.
Oh, I brought the bean salad.
It's store-bought.
-Oh!
-[laughter]
"For Sarah, Night Three."
"I picture you and I smile."
Well, whoever you are,
you certainly have my attention.
[Esther]
This guy is three-for-three.
[laughs]
Mom, I just spent an hour
going through about
a million photos of our family
trying to find the right one
to go in that frame, and...
[sighs]
I realized
the picture I'm looking for
hasn't even been taken yet.
I want a picture of my family.
You know, my husband.
My kids.
I didn't realize
how much I wanted that
until now.
That's turning out to be
quite some gift.
It sure is.
[sighs]
[♪]
There we go.
We'll put up the rest
of the decorations tomorrow.
I should go get cleaned up.
Where are you going?
I'm having dinner
with Sarah and her family.
You guys are really tight, huh?
Since I was a kid.
And you and Sarah
are just friends?
[sighs]
I don't know.
I don't know what we are.
That's what I thought.
You'd better make your move
before she falls
for this other guy.
What other guy?
The guy who's giving her
all the gifts!
I'm not worried about him.
Maybe you should be.
Believe me, if I lose her,
it will not be to him.
And how do you know that?
'Cause I'm the guy!
Oh!
Wow!
Yeah, I know.
So what happens now?
I have five more nights
and five more gifts
to see if we're bashert.
To see if you're what now?
Meant to be.
"Bashert."
[doorbell rings]
Hey.
I like Hanukkah already.
[Sarah laughs]
Come on in.
Great, thanks.
Uh, for you.
Oh, thanks.
No worries.
So, um, we can go over
the menus right in here.
Oh, wow.
They're so beautiful,
-Oh.
-And so many.
Yeah. [laughs]
It's a lot, I know.
My grandma collected them.
Some of them are very old.
Huh.
So much history.
Mm-hmm.
So many memories.
Well, hopefully,
tonight you'll make some more.
Yeah.
I hope so.
I was thinking
that I'd bake the falafel,
rather than deep fry it.
Oh, I don't know about that.
It's Hanukkah,
you're gonna deep fry it
in deep oil.
Mm-hmm, yup.
You're the boss.
[laughs]
Hey, thank you so much
for catering this event.
Honestly, you're saving
our tuches.
Well, it's my pleasure.
Yeah, it gives me an opportunity
to broaden my horizons
as a chef...
That's true.
...and to see more of you.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Yes, Mom, we're in here.
Oh, sorry we're late.
Dad's parking the car.
I got held up in court.
Yeah, Mom's a judge, so...
Well, that makes sense.
You're Nigel Templeton,
the chef.
Guilty as charged.
I've heard so much about you.
Oh, Mom.
Shush.
Well, thank you so much
for, you know,
sharing some of your Hanukkah
celebrations with me.
Well, a lot of the action
takes place in the kitchen.
Cooking and holidays
go hand in hand.
You can't have one
without the other.
Right?
[chuckles warmly]
So I'm sitting there,
waiting for Zoey to finish up
at the climbing gym,
and I bumped into
an old girlfriend of yours.
Okay?
Susan Kramer.
-Susan Kramer!
-Mm-hmm.
Susan Kramer.
She says to say hello.
Okay.
-What?
-What are you getting at.
I always liked her.
Whatever happened with that?
I always liked her, too,
she just wasn't the one.
Where have I heard
that before?
-What is with this voice?
-What voice?
We're about to have
Hanukkah dinner,
just cut me some slack.
I'm just saying, man.
Look, if I'm going
to marry someone,
if I'm going
to have kids with someone,
it's gotta be the right one.
I get that.
Come on.
Hey, where is the Zoesh?
She's having dinner
with Ava's parents.
By the way,
we've got company tonight.
Oh, who?
[with British accent]
Sarah's good friend, Nigel.
Swell.
Here you go.
I make my kugel with raisins.
Lovely.
I, if there's no objection,
might add some currants
plumped in port
for the Mazel Ball.
Ooh, objection overruled.
Hey!
Oh, busted.
Hi!
-Oh, hey!
-Hey.
-We brought wine.
-Good.
Nigel,
you remember
my friend, Daniel...
Of course.
Great to see you again.
Yeah, you too.
...and that's my brother, Jake.
Nice to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
-Easy there.
-Right.
Well, now that we're all here,
why don't we light the Menorah?
Gentlemen?
Let's do it.
This is from, uh,
from both of us.
Oh, nice.
That's actually one of
my favorite traditions.
What do you like most
about Hanukkah?
Probably the fact
that every night,
a little more light
comes into our lives, you know?
Yeah.
Well, I've got to say,
I am liking this night
quite a bit.
Me too.
Well, cheers.
Cheers.
This is so good.
It's so good.
It's a shame Nigel
couldn't stay for dessert.
Yeah.
He had to get to back
to the restaurant,
but you'll see him
at the Mazel Ball,
don't you worry.
I can't wait to see
what a Michelin-star chef does
with a Hanukkah menu.
-Mm-hmm.
-I know.
Nigel really is a charmer.
[Sarah] Isn't he?
Pass me--
Pass me the rugelach?
-How many do you want?
-Just... all of it.
You're gonna eat all of them?
[laughing]
You okay, Daniel?
You've been kinda quiet tonight.
Just thinking about stuff.
What stuff?
Like moving to Aspen.
-What?
What, he didn't tell you?
I didn't tell anyone.
Well, you told Jacob.
Well, I was there
when he got the offer.
What offer?
The developer wants Daniel
to build seven houses in Aspen.
Wow.
Why didn't you say anything?
My home is in Seattle.
Moving away
would be really hard on me.
When do you have to
make a decision?
I have to tell them next week.
I'd really miss you.
Yeah.
I'd miss you, too.
But I--
I want what's best for you.
Thanks.
Yeah.
[laughing]
Okay, yeah, I will.
Have a good night.
[Daniel] You owe me ten bucks.
[Sarah] We start
with deep-fried falafel--
[Esther] It's gonna be good
[Sarah]
--and then the Israeli salad.
-Ooh, I like that.
-Mm-hmm.
I'm going to use
my own latke recipe.
Yeah, that's not happening...
Look what I found
on the porch.
Sarah, your secret admirer
strikes again.
"For Sarah, Night Four.
When I'm with you,
time stands still."
[chuckling warmly]
[gasping]
Oh, Sarah, that's gorgeous.
-Wow.
-And so you.
Well, I am never
taking this off.
Hey, do you think
it's from Nigel?
The card is so romantic.
It could be anybody.
But how many anybodies
are there?
Well, there's Adam,
Tom,
Nigel,
Paul...
[Jacob] Paul?
Yeah, he's been making
subtle advances.
Maybe not so subtle.
Okay, you.
You have seen me
with all these guys.
Who do you think it is?
The possibilities are endless.
Well, the nice thing is,
I have about, um,
four more nights
to figure that out.
[laughing]
I think you're falling
for this guy.
Yup.
He had me at the roses.
[sighs]
[insistent knocking on door]
Hey.
Mind if I come in?
Uh... sure.
[panting]
Are you okay?
There's something
I need to tell you.
Okay.
Am I supposed to guess
what it is?
[stammers]
[laughing nervously]
You need to know...
Yeah?
I'm so sorry I didn't
tell you about Aspen.
Oh.
Yeah.
I don't know what
I'm going to do yet--
You don't need to apologize--
--and I didn't want to say
anything prematurely--
I'm not mad at you, I just--
I'm just going to miss you,
that's all.
Me too.
Well, I'm really glad
you're here.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I, uh, I actually have
a confession to make.
You do?
[sighs heavily]
Pretty sure I'm going
to embarrass myself--
No, no...
I-I don't think so.
Oh, I'm sure of it.
Okay, um...
Okay, do you remember
dance class in sixth grade?
Kinda.
You remember me
not being able to dance?
You were terrible.
It was hard to watch.
Terrible.
Hard to watch. Still is.
Scary bad.
-Mm-hmm, still is.
-Even for a kid.
What am I gonna do
at the Ball?
Stand around, lookin' fine!
I'm not kidding!
What?
I'm the co-chair,
and I hired my brother's band.
I mean, people
are going to be looking.
Come on, you have to help me.
All right, okay.
All right, relax, okay?
-Okay.
-Relax.
Can you move this?
It's heavy.
Okay. [straining]
Okay.
[exhaling]
-You're gonna be fine, okay?
-Fine.
-Just follow my lead.
-Okay.
-Okay, relax.
-I'll follow your lead.
[shivering]
All right,
you wanna try a box-step?
What?
I don't know what that is.
I'm gonna show you.
Okay.
[♪]
-Okay?
-Okay.
Back, together,
side, together,
forward, together.
[chant together] Here we go.
Back, together,
side, together,
forward, together, side--
-That's my foot. Ow.
-Ah! Sorry.
It's okay, I have another one.
[laughing]
That's good.
Okay, you know what?
I think
that I should just, um,
stick to swaying.
You should just stick
to swaying.
-Right?
-Yeah, look at you.
-You're a natural.
-You think?
Yeah, you know what,
stick to swaying,
and nothing else...
[laughing]
You're gonna be great.
♪ I worry
I won't see your face ♪
♪ Light up again ♪
♪ Even the best fall down
sometimes ♪
♪ Even the wrong words
seem to rhyme... ♪
[♪]
Mm!
Daniel, these latkes
are amazing.
I may have to move in.
Are you okay?
Did something happen
last night?
Sarah was talking about
all the guys
who might be giving her
the gifts,
including her ex.
It didn't even occur to her
that it might be me.
Well, here's a radical notion--
why don't you just tell her?
I almost did. Okay?
I got all the way home,
and then I went back there.
I just...
I just couldn't do it.
Why not?
It's complicated.
Yeah, I'm getting that.
Sarah was always
Jacob's little sister to me.
One day, I looked up,
the pigtails were gone,
and she was a woman,
one I really liked.
But you didn't tell her.
By the time I realized
how I felt,
she was with Paul.
The not-so-ex-boyfriend.
And when they broke up,
I thought that was my chance.
Here's what I don't get,
why do you have to do it
anonymously?
I don't know.
I didn't know
where to start with her,
after being friends for so long.
I felt like I had to do
something special.
I mean, Sarah's not just
someone you date.
You know?
She's the one you end up with.
Forever can be scary.
What I didn't see coming
was all these other guys
getting in the way.
Now it's becoming a test.
I want her
to figure out it's me.
Well, we're only
halfway through Hanukkah.
Give her a chance.
It's beautiful.
The mystery man is no fool.
Every time
you look at that watch,
you're going to think of him.
And I don't even know
who it is yet.
Adam.
You think it's Adam?
I know it's him.
Hey.
-Hey.
-You're here.
Uh, yeah, I was just
in the neighborhood
and wondered if you'd like
to go for lunch.
Lunch.
Uh... you know what,
I don't know
if I'm ready for lunch,
It's only 11:45.
That's a nice watch.
You think? Huh.
I just got it.
It was a Hanukkah gift.
So, what do you think?
About the watch?
About lunch.
Lunch.
Okay, I actually can't
right now.
I'm a little swamped.
We're setting up
this fundraiser for kids,
and I still have
a lot of toys to find, so...
Well, I can get you
any toy you need.
Yeah, I developed a software
for talking teddy bears
and all kinds of automated toys.
Let me know when and where.
Okay.
The Hanukkah Hunt
is tomorrow.
Not a problem.
So, Adam and I are going
to come by your place
tomorrow morning--
[playfully] Kssh!
--and he is bringing
all these incredible toys.
It's so adorable.
He's so into it.
That's so nice of him.
It is!
It's so nice.
He's got this real,
just generous nature to him,
you know?
Mm-hmm.
-Hey.
Tom Sherman
is coming by later
to pick up his new glasses.
Tom, the likable, dependable
co-chair of the committee?
Yeah, that one.
Yeah, he is all those things,
and he's a patient.
Are you okay?
Sorry. I'm okay.
I don't know why I said that.
He's a good guy.
He is a good guy.
He thinks he may need
a new prescription.
Okay.
Um, who's in Exam Room 1?
Hmm.
Maybe you should get
an eye exam.
But I don't wear glasses.
Maybe you should start.
Okay.
Get comfy.
Yeah, super comfy.
[laughs]
Are you nervous?
Am I nervous?
I don't think so.
Okay, just, um,
place your chin right there.
Here?
Mm-hmm.
Try not to move.
I'm not moving.
Okay.
All right, now, look up...
[laughs]
This feels weird.
What does?
-[giggling]
-What?
Doing this with you.
Oh.
-Ah-ah! No moving.
-Sorry.
Okay.
Now look to the left...
...and the right...
..and straight at me.
You okay?
What?
What do you see?
I see you.
Okay.
Well, your eyes look fine.
Have you experienced any, um,
difference in your eyesight
recently?
It's hard to explain.
I feel like I wasn't
seeing things clearly.
What do you mean?
What kind of things?
The people around me,
the road ahead...
When you're so close
to something,
sometimes, you don't
really see it.
Well, that's very subjective.
Yeah, I don't know,
maybe it's all in my head,
right?
Well, I don't have
a diagnosis for that.
So my eyes seem okay?
I'll live.
[laughs]
Yeah. [clears throat]
Yeah, you're gonna make it.
Good to know.
[groaning with effort]
Okay...
Wow.
"For Sarah, Night Five.
The Tree of Life
will light my way to you."
This guy is almost
as wonderful as your father.
[sighs]
Tell me about it.
And the mystery continues.
[sighs]
Hi, Bubbe.
I think I'm in love.
[sighs]
[groans]
-Oh, wow.
-Yeah?
-This looks incredible.
-It looks good, huh? Yeah.
Wow. Well done, Jimmy.
You understand
that this used to be us.
I mean, we were the kids
running around,
looking for
shiny gold coins everywhere.
So many Hanukkah Hunts.
So many skinned knees
looking for Gelt.
[laughs]
The good old days.
You do realize I let you win.
Mm-hmm.
-You did not.
-Mm-hmm.
You really think
that jar of Gelt
just happened to be lying around
in plain sight?
They were under a tree.
That had no leaves.
The leaves were on the ground,
covering the coins.
That I let you find.
[growls in frustration]
[car horn honks outside]
Ah, that must be Adam.
Adam?
Yeah.
Wow.
That is incredible.
I'm gonna go thank him.
Do I look okay?
You look...
you look great.
[voices murmuring in distance]
This is incredible.
Yeah, I got
every color of bear...
Which one is he again?
That's Adam.
The generous tech-genius.
And you think
she thinks he's the guy?
I think he's in the running.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, sure.
-Hey.
Looks like Adam
has some competition.
Never mind Adam,
what about me?
I didn't think you'd be here.
Why wouldn't I be?
You're a very busy man.
Sarah...
can we talk for a second?
Um, can it wait?
We're in the middle
of setting up.
Yeah.
[clears throat awkwardly]
Here, you can help.
He's the one
you've got to worry about.
Jimmy, look at my face.
Huh?
What do you see?
I think that you've got
"worried" covered.
[♪]
[Sarah] I wish there wasn't
an age limit on the hunt.
Look at this, it's so adorable!
[Adam] And so smart...
Ah, a bear after my own heart.
[both laughing]
[♪]
Come on, come on.
Huddle up, huddle up!
All right,
Happy Hanukkah, everyone!
Happy Hanukkah!
[children cheering]
All right, listen, up.
You are all going to have
15 minutes
to find all the Gelt
that you can.
[cheering excitedly]
That's right,
when you hear this bell...
[rings bell]
...and she does that dance,
that means it's time
to come inside
for some hot chocolate,
some sweet treats,
and I don't know,
maybe even some presents.
You guys don't like presents...
[all cheering]
Okay.
Ready...
Set...
Gelt!
Let the Hanukkah Hunt begin!
[laughing]
Wow.
This really is
the best Hanukkah ever.
You say that every year.
Well, this year, it really is.
Oh, yeah? How come?
Look at them,
look at their faces.
They're so happy.
[chuckling fondly]
And, you know,
the secret admirer thing
isn't hurting.
I don't know how he does it.
He just tops himself
every night.
And you really have
no idea who it is?
No, I keep changing my mind.
Well, maybe
he's giving you the clues
because he wants you
to figure it out
before the eight nights are up.
You think?
I mean,
that's how I would feel.
Hmm.
Maybe.
"For Sarah, Night Six.
You're the music in my heart."
[music box playing
"Ma'oz Tzur"]
[♪]
What a thoughtful gift.
It's the song, Dad.
I just well up
every time I hear "Ma'oz Tzur".
It just brings back
so many memories
of everything that Bubbe Rose
went through,
all the people that I love.
I wonder
if your secret admirer
understood that.
-I hope so.
-I hope so, too.
Because that would mean
he might deserve you.
I love you, Pops.
I love you, too, sweetheart.
[♪]
I should have known
you'd be here.
Can you believe
it's been two years?
I really miss her.
I know.
Me too.
[sighs]
Classic Bubbe Rose.
Still bringing people together.
Yeah.
What day is the Ball again?
Tomorrow night,
and I still have to find
some kind of glass slipper
to go with my amazing dress.
What color is the dress?
Oh, it's this mix
of royal blue
and navy,
and I guess you'd call it
Hanukkah blue.
It's rich, and deep,
and velvety.
It sounds really pretty.
Oh, it is,
and way out of my budget.
[laughing]
But it's gonna be worth it.
I know he's going to love it,
I know it,
whoever it ends up being.
What if he doesn't
show up to the Ball?
What do you mean?
He has to show up.
I know it. I feel it.
You know,
last night's gift was...
[sighs]
Not just the music box,
the song, "Ma'oz Tzur".
This guy, he really gets you.
[cell phone rings]
Oh.
Maybe it's a sign.
Who is it?
Paul.
Hi, Paul.
Hi. I was wondering
if we could grab a bite later.
Um...
I don't know, I just,
I have a lot on my plate
right now.
Can we meet up?
We really need to talk.
How about tonight?
I can't,
I'm going to watch
the menorah-lighting
with my family
at the community center.
Can you hang on a minute?
I'm getting another call.
Hey.
Hey, when are you coming back?
Um, I shouldn't be long now.
I wanted you to see
the new fixtures
before we install them.
Okay.
Give me one minute.
Wait--
Paul?
This is Daniel.
Sorry, one sec.
Paul.
Why don't we meet tonight
at the Menorah lighting?
It'll be good to see
your family.
Yeah, okay--
Great.
'Kay.
Daniel.
Oh, you remembered.
That's nice.
Don't worry,
I'm sure I'll love
whatever you choose.
I'll see you soon.
[sighs]
Shoes.
[♪]
["Ma'oz Tzur" sung
by Leslie Odom Jr. plays]
[♪]
♪ Ma'oz tsur yeshu'ati ♪
♪ Lecha na'eh leshabeakh ♪
♪ Tikon beit tefilati ♪
♪ Vesham todah nezaveakh ♪
♪ Le'et tachin matbeakh ♪
♪ Mitsar hamnabeakh ♪
♪ 'Az 'egmor beshir mizmor ♪
♪ Khanukat hamizbeakh ♪
[sighs deeply]
"For Sarah. Night Seven.
I see your face,
and I need nothing more."
Wow.
[♪]
Best Hanukkah ever.
[laughs]
Thank you for meeting with me.
Thank you, I'm good.
Oat milk, no sugar.
No thanks.
I can't stay long.
Look, I'm really not sure
what there is to say.
Then let me do the talking.
Now, maybe it's the holidays,
but I've been
taking stock of my life,
and I realized
what I've been missing.
You, Sarah.
And I realize
I chose a lawyer
just like my father,
but you two are very different.
Okay, my mom always came first,
and with you,
I felt like I was coming third,
or fourth,
or fifth--
I was trying to make partner.
I know it's no excuse--
I've spent the last four months
trying to get over you,
and I'm finally getting there,
so whatever this is,
please don't--
It's me trying
to win you back.
Is there, um...
Is there something that
you'd like to say to me, Paul?
[cell phone rings]
Can I call you back?
I'll have the brief
on your desk
this afternoon...
Yes, sir,
have a good day.
I shouldn't have
taken that call.
It's fine, it's no big deal,
I've gotta go anyways.
When we first met,
you told me
I had the makings of a good man.
I think about that a lot
these days.
I'm trying to prove you right.
I gotta go.
These are the glasses.
Remember?
Mm-hmm.
The ones
I've been trying to get?
I lost track of the auction
and someone outbid me.
Okay, this
has to narrow the field.
I know,
I keep trying to think
who I told about the glasses.
Let's go over the list.
Well, Tom knew about it,
but I don't think
Tom's the guy.
What about Adam?
Adam is prone
to dramatic gestures,
but this is too personal.
I don't think he's the one.
And Nigel,
well, he's super romantic.
I can totally see him
writing all those cards...
but then there's Paul.
Here's the more important
question...
Yeah?
Which one do you hope it is?
I don't know.
I mean, Paul keeps saying
he's changed...
I'm going to go pick up
those window shades.
Do you need anything
while I'm out?
[Sarah] Maybe he's trying
to prove himself
with all these gifts.
Can you get some hinges
for the cabinets?
[Sarah] Maybe he's the one.
Those look good on you.
You should keep 'em.
Uh, wow.
Happy Hanukkah.
Thank you.
You should take a look.
We're almost done.
Oh, yeah? Okay.
Happy Hanukkah.
Oh, wow.
This is even better
than I imagined.
We should be done by tomorrow.
[sighs]
Man, I'm really gonna miss
having you around.
You okay?
I'm fine.
You know what,
you should come check out
these glasses I just got.
Every time I look at them,
I smile--
Do you really think that Paul
gave you those glasses?
Um...
maybe.
You really think
he knows you that well,
cares that much,
or remembers
that you lost your watch,
or knows how much
you love white roses?
Or that one of your ears
is slightly smaller
than the other,
and that
you're a terrible dancer,
and somehow, you smell so good
all the time,
even when you sweat?
It's you?
You thought it was Paul,
you never even thought of me.
Daniel, I, um...
I didn't...
You know how much
I love you, I just...
I mean, you're my...
You're my best...
I didn't think that
you'd see me that way.
You're right.
We are friends,
and I guess that's all
we were ever meant to be.
Daniel.
[music box playing]
[♪]
[playing melancholy tune]
[insistent knock on door]
Mind if I come in?
What are you doing here?
How can you ask me that?
I think it's a pretty
reasonable question.
I have, like, a million
reasonable questions for you.
Like...
Like why?
Why now?
Or...
Or why didn't you tell me?
Or a better one, when?
When did you find out
that you felt this way about me?
I don't know.
I don't know,
there isn't one day
or one year
that I can point to.
Somewhere between second grade
and right now.
I realized that
the best moments of my life
were the ones spent with you,
but it doesn't matter because--
It matters,
because guess what,
I'm pretty sure
I have always loved you, too,
but I just
didn't know what it was.
I mean, you're my best friend,
you're also the boy next door,
I didn't think...
I just...
I don't want to lose you.
1 guess that's...
that's all I came here to say.
You could have
started with that--
Well, I didn't know that
until I said it.
There's a lot I didn't realize
until those gifts started
showing up at my doorstep, okay?
Look, I, um...
I'm the co-chair
of this committee,
I can't be late
to the Ball, so...
I gotta go.
I still don't have a date,
by the way.
[♪]
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Whoo... ♪
[♪]
♪ Every day I make a plan ♪
♪ To be the best of who I am ♪
♪ Work those numbers
on the page ♪
♪ Makin' sure I earn my wage ♪
♪ If the columns aren't tight ♪
♪ I can make
the balance right... ♪
[whispering]
♪ Just make sure
when we begin ♪
♪ To let me know
where to fit you in... ♪
Sarah!
♪ And this is my calling... ♪
Hey.
Did you talk to Daniel?
I did, I did.
Where is he?
I haven't seen him.
Yeah, he's not here yet.
Ah.
You look beautiful, Mom.
Oh, thank you.
You look gorgeous, too.
Aw, thank you.
You're not too bad yourself,
you handsome devil.
All right,
well, committee members
are supposed to--
[whistles] --mingle, so...
I'll be back.
Have fun.
-All right.
-[chuckling warmly]
Well, how about a dance?
The merry band of CPAs
are sounding pretty good.
Sounds great.
All right.
Whoo!
[♪]
That looks amazing.
Everyone
is complimenting the food.
They should be complimenting
that dress.
[chuckles] Oh...
thank you.
And, again, thank you so much
for everything.
Oh.
You're such a good friend,
and so handsome,
and that accent, I mean, whew!
[chuckles]
But there's someone else.
Is it someone
that you just met?
No.
No, someone I've known
my whole life,
and that apparently knows me
better than I know myself.
So...
[chuckles]
Then he must know
how fortunate he is.
Thank you.
Now go, enjoy your party.
Happy Hanukkah.
Happy Hanukkah!
[sighs]
[♪]
I've never seen you
look prettier.
Paul, there's something
you should know.
Or happier--
I'm in love with someone else.
Whew.
Ah.
It's Daniel.
I'm not surprised.
You're not?
I've seen the way
he looks at you.
I wish you both the best.
♪ And this is my calling... ♪
I wish you the same.
♪ Oh, I'm feeling alive ♪
♪ I've got everything
I need to survive ♪
♪ And I'm ready for it all ♪
♪ Oh, I feel alive ♪
[♪]
♪ Whoo-ooh... ♪
♪ Whoo... ♪
♪ Oh, I feel alive ♪
Happy Hanukkah, everyone!
-[everyone cheers]
-Whoo-hoo!
[cheering and clapping]
My dad is really good.
He's the best.
Go get him.
[♪]
[playing "Collide"
by Howie Day]
[♪]
May I have this dance?
Well, they are playing
our song.
I think someone requested it.
Interesting.
-Yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
So how about that dance?
♪ I'm open, you're closed ♪
♪ Where I follow
you'll go... ♪
You are nailing
this swaying thing, okay?
-Oh, this old thing?
-Oh, yeah.
You know,
it is my signature move.
Oh, you've mastered it.
[laughs]
Well, wait till you see this.
What is this?
A little bit of this guy?
-Oh, that's good.
-A little bit of that guy.
Oh, someone's
been taking lessons.
-Huh? What about that?
-Yeah.
I learned from the best.
Can't argue with that.
[laughs]
♪ Out of the doubt
that fills my mind... ♪
"For Sarah.
Night Eight."
♪ I somehow find, you and I... ♪
"It's the last night
of Hanukkah..."
♪ Collide ♪
"...and the first night
of the rest of our lives."
That's Bubbe Rose's
promise ring.
Yeah. She gave it to me,
hoping that one day
I would give it to you.
♪ You make
a first impression ♪
♪ I've found
I'm scared to know ♪
♪ I'm always on your mind ♪
We were always meant to be.
♪ Even the best
fall down sometimes ♪
♪ Even the stars
refuse to shine ♪
♪ Out of the back
you fall in time... ♪
[♪]