Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Shit.
Perfect.
Auntie Opal's here!
Late as hell, per usual.
Where's my birthday girl?
Party was at 4:00.
You have to stop doing this to her.
I'm late for work.
I'll see you in the morning.
Auntie Opal's special recipe,
mac and cheese.
So good, it'll bring you to your knees!
Well, how about a one-of-a-kind
collector's edition book?
Happy birthday, baby.
Leave that in, right?
You get the picture.
Take it all out, roll it out, then…
Ow! Auntie!
Lucky it's me!
Your dad used to do mine.
Had me looking like
that snake lady we read about.
-Medusa.
Couldn't look at myself in the mirror,
or I'd turn to stone.
Why didn't your mom do it?
She wasn't around.
Why do moms leave?
Doesn't matter why. They just do.
Look, whatever happened, happened.
You can't change it.
Just take care of yourself
because no one else will do it, okay?
You know what?
Why don't you read that beautiful new book
while I finish this hair?
"A guilty heart the auntie had.
Missed Nina's birthday, bad, bad, bad."
Nina, girl, I'm getting to my limit.
I got you a nice book!
I said, "Happy Birthday!" Let it go!
It's in the book!
The book has a story about
a girl named Nina and her auntie?
Yes!
Let me see this book.
"Erax smell your fear and doubt."
"They've been stuck in
and now they're out."
"If you fail, you'll one become.
You have until the sand has run."
I guess that's an Erax.
Mm-hm.
"It's your story, take the pen,
though growth may be beyond your ken."
"Rise up now and earn your wage,
or freeze forever on the page."
Is this the trippiest thing
you've ever seen or what?
Wasn't there…
Huh?
Auntie!
Mac and cheese is so good.
They took the book!
What? No, No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
-Are you serious?
-Auntie?
Get that book.
Oh my God!
Get off my auntie!
Where'd it go?
Hm?
How are you eating
popcorn right now?
Uh, when did you get so sassy?
Chill out. We're safe now.
That popcorn's older than me.
I don't want to be disrespectful,
but we have to make a plan.
Yeah, the plan is to hide up here
until somebody comes.
Where is it?
-Chubs!
-Huh?
Wow! Look at this!
Sounds like
they're tearing up the house.
That Erax is back in here.
That's what the poem means!
We have to get the Erax back in the book
before the hourglass runs out,
or we become one of them.
"Freeze forever on the page."
Look, I'm sorry, but that's insane,
and that can't happen.
Everything that's happening now
is insane and can't happen.
The sand is almost out.
Get the book.
Watch out for the bad step!
I know about the bad step!
Auntie! Dang!
What?
Oh, fuck.
Time to go!
I understand that time is running out.
Running, running, running, running!
Time's gonna run out!
Get on the bed. Now!
Auntie.
Nina, girl…
-It's getting through!
-Nina, Nina, Nina, listen to me.
I'm sorry, Nina.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I missed your birthday.
I'm sorry for every time
I didn't own up to my mistakes.
And I was wrong about that "looking out
for yourself and no one else" crap.
Baby, I got you.
I got you.
You want to get fictional?
Let's get fictional!
Auntie!
That was some
straight superhero thumping, girl!
You kind of stole my moment, but…
Want to read another one?
No.
We're on the set of Erax.
Here I'm gonna bite her leg.
-Oh my God!
-Me tasty!
Um…no, no.
Okay!
That was a good one.
Get off my auntie!
Hot damn!
Oh geez!
Sorry, Berserker. Showbiz.
Oh!