Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
♪ ♪
("Everything" by Becky Hill
playing)
♪ Ha ♪
♪ You're in a daydream ♪
♪ 'Cause you can see me
through the crowd ♪
♪ You're an amazement ♪
♪ You're trying to
figure me out ♪
♪ I don't even notice ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm lost
in my own world ♪
-(alarm clock): ♪ Olé, olé ♪
-♪ So don't worry about me ♪
-♪ Olé, o... ♪
-♪ There's nobody like me ♪
♪ You see that I-I-I ♪
♪ A-A-Am no-o cli-i-iché-é-é ♪
♪ It-it's mo-o-ore
tha-a-an you-ou think ♪
♪ You can't define me,
I'm everything ♪
♪ Everything... ♪
♪ Give me the crown
'cause I'm queen and king ♪
♪ You can't define me,
I'm everything ♪
♪ Everything... ♪
♪ Labels and names
can never box me in ♪
♪ So if you're asking,
I'm everything... ♪
-Morning.
-Hello, petal.
♪ Making no fuss ♪
♪ I'm having fun just being me ♪
-♪ Ain't that enough? ♪
-(thunder rumbling)
♪ What you get is what you see ♪
♪ I'm one in a million ♪
♪ So unique amongst the world ♪
♪ But we're in this together ♪
-♪ For worse or for better ♪
-(dog barking)
♪ You see that I-I-I ♪
♪ A-A-Am no-o cli-i-iché-é-é ♪
♪ It-it's mo-o-ore
tha-a-an you-ou think ♪
♪ Well, I'm everything ♪
-♪ Everything... ♪
-♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Give me the crown
'cause I'm queen and king ♪
♪ You can't define me,
I'm everything ♪
-♪ Everything... ♪
-♪ I'm everything... ♪
-(whimpers)
-Hi, Mum.
Happy birthday, Jamie!
-JAMIE: Yeah!
-(whoops)
JAMIE:
See you later.
♪ You can't define me,
I'm everything ♪
♪ Everything... ♪
♪ Give me the crown
'cause I'm queen and king ♪
♪ You can't define me,
I'm everything ♪
♪ Everything... ♪
♪ Labels and names
can never box me in ♪
♪ So if you're asking,
I'm everything ♪
♪ Oh, I'm making my own way ♪
♪ All the possibilities ♪
-♪ Today is a new day ♪
-(muttering)
♪ It's not the way
it used to be ♪
-Aw.
-♪ 'Cause we're taking over ♪
♪ We got the rainbow
at our feet ♪
♪ 'Cause we're made
of stardust ♪
♪ There's nobody like us ♪
♪ You can't define me,
I'm everything ♪
-♪ Everything... ♪
-♪ I'm everything ♪
♪ Oh-oh, labels and names
can never box me in ♪
♪ So if you're asking,
I'm everything ♪
HEDGE:
Take those off when you go in.
-Those socks are not regulation.
-MASOOD: Oh, morning, Jamie.
-Happy birthday.
-Thanks, Mr. Masood.
Okay, you're welcome.
Morning, everyone.
Come on, smile.
It's not that bad. Morning.
-(students chattering)
-HEDGE: As this is
your last ever careers lesson...
Year 11!
-Year 11, what did I just say?
-BECCA: I don't know, miss.
I couldn't hear.
It's really noisy in here.
Oi, Vicki, we still on
for Friday or what?
-Becca. -VICKI: I need
my brother, though,
-or we can't get ciggies.
-Vicki!
-You having a party? Can I come?
-GIRLS: No.
-LEVI: Can I come? Boom!
-GIRLS: Yeah.
HEDGE: What?
Cy, Bex, Becca, Vicki, Levi,
-all of you, quiet!
-(chatter stops)
STUDENTS:
Ooh!
-(sighs)
-Miss, a-are you stressed?
BEX: What have you got to be
stressed about, miss?
Yeah, miss. What have you got
to be stressed about?
-Are you getting stressed now?
-Is this stressing you now?
-Are we stressing you?
-Girls, don't push me.
I literally know where you live,
and I will hunt you down.
-(laughter)
-Now, shush.
As I was saying, this is
your final careers lesson.
-(student whoops)
-(laughter)
Mickey, sit down.
Pritti, you've been
paying attention.
I want you to explain
to the rest of the class
what I've been saying.
Miss is saying that
you can't all be, like,
pop singers and movie stars
and that there's other jobs--
like, just normal stuff
and that--
and they're kind of good, too.
HEDGE:
So having realistic expectations
about your future
career potential
is what is gonna help you
get a real job.
Right, so... so what
do you want to be, Pritti?
A doctor, miss.
-(mocking): "A doctor, miss."
-(students murmuring)
HEDGE:
Settle down. Yes, Bex.
Miss, why does she get
to be a doctor
and I have to work
in a slaughterhouse?
What?
This careers brochure
you gave me--
-"Your Future in Meat."
-(laughter)
I couldn't work
in a slaughterhouse, miss.
I'm a vag-etarian.
-(laughter)
-HEDGE: You're a... what?
You're a vag-etar...
Nice. That's real nice.
(laughs)
Right, Denzel, Tyson,
what about you?
-BOTH: YouTubers.
-Right.
And if that doesn't work out?
-BOTH: Jedis.
-(laughter)
Right. Okay, does anyone
in the entire class
have a realistic career plan,
apart from Pritti?
Anyone.
Jamie.
-Jamie.
-Oh, uh, me?
Sorry, miss.
Away with the fairies.
-(high-pitched): Ooh!
-GIRL: Shut up.
Yeah, yeah, gay kid. Ha-ha.
HEDGE:
I was saying-- careers,
realism, your future.
Discuss.
What job do you want?
I don't know, miss.
The future's just alive
with enticing opportunities.
-(scoffs)
-HEDGE: Good. See?
That is a good attitude.
It's incredibly vague,
but it's good.
I love those shoes.
What?
I said nice shoes, miss.
Oh. Thank you. They're, um...
they're Jimmy Choos.
-(students murmur, laugh)
-What? Come on. Class.
We have the results of your
psychometric careers test here.
♪ There's a clock on the wall,
and it's moving too slow ♪
♪ It's got hours to kill
and a lifetime to go ♪
♪ And I'm holding my breath
till I hear the last bell ♪
♪ Then I'm coming out hard
and I'm giving 'em hell ♪
♪ I'm a superstar,
and you don't even know it ♪
♪ In a WonderBra,
♪ You're so blah blah,
and you don't even know it ♪
♪ I'm like, "Au revoir,"
-♪ There's a path I've planned ♪
-♪ And you don't even know it ♪
-♪ To the promised land ♪
-♪ You won't understand ♪
-♪ And you don't even know it ♪
♪ 'Cause you're
my backing band ♪
-♪ And you don't even know it ♪
-♪ And it's the Jamie show ♪
-♪ 'Cause you're meh, so-so ♪
-♪ And you don't even know it ♪
-♪ And, uh, sorta slow ♪
♪ And you don't even know it ♪
♪ And I'm go, go, go ♪
♪ I got the dreams ♪
♪ I got the style ♪
♪ I got the moves
to make you smile ♪
♪ So kiss my ass goodbye ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm gonna be the one ♪
♪ You're in my lane,
you're in my light ♪
♪ Get out my way,
I'm taking flight ♪
♪ And I ain't coming back ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm gonna
kiss the sun ♪
♪ And if ever you find
life is getting you down ♪
♪ There's a party to start
in a new part of town ♪
♪ Where there's
a guest list of one ♪
♪ And the name's Jamie New ♪
♪ And if you ask me real nice,
I might sign you in, too ♪
♪ 'Cause, baby, I'm a hit ♪
♪ And you don't even know it ♪
-♪ Legit ♪
-♪ And you don't even know it ♪
-♪ Better give me room ♪
-♪ For my va-va-voom ♪
-♪ And you don't even know it ♪
-♪ And I'm coming up ♪
-♪ In a double-D cup ♪
-♪ And you don't even know it ♪
♪ 'Cause when a boy's
this stacked ♪
-♪ And you don't even know it ♪
-♪ He's the headline act ♪
♪ And you don't even know it ♪
♪ ♪
(cheering)
CROWD (chanting):
Go, Jamie! Go, Jamie!
It's your birthday!
Go, Jamie! Go, Jamie! Go!
♪ I got the dreams,
I got the style ♪
♪ I got the moves
to make you smile ♪
♪ So kiss my ass goodbye ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm gonna be the one ♪
♪ And when you're old, like 32 ♪
♪ You'll all remember
Jamie New ♪
♪ The kid who learned to fly ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm gonna
kiss the sun ♪
-♪ Oh, baby, I'm the shit ♪
-♪ We don't even know it ♪
-♪ So admit ♪
-♪ I'm a hit ♪
-♪ She don't even know it ♪
-♪ Just a bit ♪
-♪ He don't even know it ♪
-♪ And I'm smoking hot ♪
-♪ We don't even know it ♪
-♪ 'Cause I got the lot ♪
-♪ She don't even know it ♪
-♪ And yeah, what I got ♪
♪ Yeah, you have not ♪
♪ We don't even know it ♪
-♪ You don't even know it ♪
-♪ We don't even know it ♪
♪ You don't even know it ♪
-♪ She don't even know it ♪
-♪ He don't even know it ♪
-♪ We don't even know it ♪
-♪ You don't even know it ♪
-♪ She don't even know it ♪
♪ We don't even know it ♪
♪ And you don't even know it. ♪
What was that, Jamie?
Uh, nothing, miss.
Just daydreaming.
DEAN: He's away with
them fairies again, miss.
Bumming 'em over a toadstool.
HEDGE:
Dean.
I'm gonna pretend
I didn't hear that.
So, Jamie, you never answered
the question.
What do you want to be, love?
Uh...
-a performer.
-(Hedge scoffs)
For a minute there,
I had such high hopes for you.
Well, you can just
join the queue
with all the movie stars
and the footballers
and Sheffield's Next Top Model.
I keep telling you all
over and over,
you got to keep it real.
I wish I could tell you
that you're all gonna
achieve your dreams,
but I'd be lying,
and that would be wrong.
That'd be cruel.
-Ta-ra, Gill.
-Ta-ra, love.
Hi, Ray.
Oh, hiya.
(Margaret sighs)
You were busy today.
Oh, I know.
Them senior citizens
are like locusts.
Here.
-The cake for Jamie's party.
-Oh.
Balloons are in me new car.
Which one's your new...
Oh, yeah, got it.
-Those are nice wheels.
-Mm.
I had a fling with Sexy Stan,
the secondhand car man.
-(alarm chirps)
-Did me a dirty discount.
-(chuckles)
-You lucky pup.
It's got heated seats.
They don't work,
but it's got 'em.
Hey, Jamie texted Wayne.
Said he's coming.
-Oh, Ray, not today.
-(sighs)
I said nothing.
I love Jamie's dad.
Ooh. (grunts)
Careful.
(balloons squeaking)
(straining)
-(balloon pops)
-(gasps)
(kids chattering playfully)
PRITTI:
I hope it goes well tonight.
How do you mean?
Oh, with your dad coming round.
When was the last time
you saw him?
Oh, not that long ago.
Uh, you can come, too,
if you want.
There's cake.
The icing's pink,
so it's probably halal.
-I've got to babysit, or
I would. -(knocking on window)
-Anyways...
-Hiya.
(chuckles) Good luck.
He's me dad.
We have met before.
I know. Shut up.
Happy birthday.
Hey, 16-- you're getting old.
-What's that?
-You're getting old!
-(laughs)
-PRITTI: Hey, Dad.
Hey, Pritti.
Have a good day at school?
(conversation continues
indistinctly)
♪ ♪
RAY:
So...
how was your singles night?
Oh, that.
Couldn't make it.
Oh, Margaret.
Get yourself out there.
You don't know
what you're missing.
Trust me, I do.
Besides, it's been
double shifts all week
paying for his birthday.
Plus that prom coming up.
He'll need a tux,
and knowing our Jamie,
it won't just be any tux.
(cell phone ringing)
(sighs)
Who's that?
"Can't make it. Sorry."
Is that it?
Chuffing useless father.
Oh, Mags, where you going?
♪ ♪
Ray!
Action stations!
(noisemakers blaring)
BOTH:
Surprise!
OMG. Is this all for me?
-(pops)
-Oh! (chuckles)
-(chuckling): Oh, look at it.
-Yeah.
It's all glittery plastic.
Oh, my God, I love it.
Happy birthday, love.
Thanks, Mum.
Hiya, Ray.
And another kiss from me, petal.
Mwah.
So, how was school?
Mortifying.
-I'm gonna be a shelf stacker.
-Oh.
Where's Dad?
Didn't you get his text?
He had to go out of town.
Work emergency.
Oh. Well, never mind.
He's not forgotten you.
He popped into work,
left you this.
Oh, ace. Thanks.
"Have a full-throttle birthday.
Love, Dad."
Oh, and a picture
of a racing car.
He knows me so well.
50 quid, though.
Thanks, Dad. You're a star.
(chuckles):
Oh. Anyway...
It must run in the family.
'Cause you'll be my star
wearing these.
♪ ♪
Happy birthday, love.
You didn't.
Oh, you didn't.
You did.
-These are the ones.
-MARGARET: I know.
-The ones I've been
saving up for. -I know.
They're 120 quid-- 120.
Where'd you get money like that?
I got it. Don't you worry.
Let's just say she went without.
JAMIE: Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Oh, me first ever heels.
Oh, they're amazing.
MARGARET:
Woman in the shop said to me,
"Ooh, your daughter's
got big feet."
I said,
"They're not for me daughter.
-They're for me son."
-(Jamie chuckles)
Should've seen the look
on her face.
(all chuckling)
-(all exclaim, gasp)
-It's all right.
-She's down, but she's not out.
-(Margaret chuckles)
Mm... ay, Chihuahua.
♪ ♪
MARGARET:
Do you remember the first time
you tried my shoes on, Jamie?
He fell downstairs in them,
nearly broke his nose.
I told his dad he got hit
in the face with a rugby ball.
He was so proud.
(sighs)
Jamie?
It's just...
Well, it's a shame
Dad ain't here.
Well, why don't you have
a little walk in 'em?
Take 'em for a spin.
Yeah, you do that
while we light cake.
Shit. Bollocks.
You didn't hear me say that.
♪ ♪
♪ It was something he said ♪
♪ Something he said ♪
♪ His words built a wall ♪
♪ A wall inside my head ♪
♪ Just one little thing ♪
♪ Didn't mean that much to him ♪
♪ But it keeps building
and building ♪
♪ And building this wall
in my head ♪
♪ This wall in my head ♪
(kids shouting playfully)
♪ Just one tiny thought,
it started out so small ♪
♪ The thought made a brick ♪
-♪ The bricks made a wall ♪
-(cheering)
♪ And the wall keeps me down ♪
♪ And the wall trips me up ♪
♪ And it keeps building
and building and building ♪
♪ This wall in my head ♪
(jovial chatter)
♪ And here I stand ♪
♪ With my feet
stuck to the floor ♪
♪ As I shout ♪
♪ Down the street
screaming for more ♪
♪ Over the wall, over the wall ♪
♪ I see my future
standing tall ♪
♪ Over the wall, over the wall ♪
♪ I can believe
I'd have it all ♪
♪ So I keep climbing
and climbing and climbing ♪
♪ This wall in my head,
head, head ♪
♪ This wall in my head ♪
♪ It was something he said,
just one little thing ♪
♪ The thought left a scar ♪
♪ The words left a sting ♪
♪ Those words are the walls
that still hold me in ♪
♪ And they keep building
and building ♪
♪ And building
and building and ♪
♪ Don't fall ♪
♪ I'm finding my feet ♪
♪ There's shoes to be filled ♪
♪ But this wall ♪
♪ It's harder to beat ♪
♪ When it's one
you helped build ♪
♪ Over the wall, over the wall ♪
♪ I see my future
standing tall ♪
♪ Over the wall, over the wall ♪
♪ I can believe
I'd have it all ♪
♪ So I keep climbing
and climbing and climbing ♪
♪ This wall in my head,
head, head ♪
♪ I'll keep on climbing
and climbing and climbing ♪
♪ This wall in my head,
head, head ♪
♪ Oh, I'll keep climbing
and climbing and climbing ♪
♪ And climbing and climbing
and climbing ♪
♪ And climbing and climbing ♪
♪ And hand over hand over hand
over brick over hand ♪
♪ Over brick over hand
over brick over ♪
♪ Climbing, climbing ♪
♪ Climbing and climbing
this wall in my head ♪
♪ This wall in my head ♪
♪ This wall in my head. ♪
Here. Blow 'em out quick.
Wax is burning me thumbs
to buggery.
Make a wish, son.
-Laters.
-GIRLS: Bye.
(students laughing)
(excited overlapping chatter)
(overlapping chatter continues
in distance)
Come in quick
and shut the door.
I've got summat to show you.
Show me what?
Shut the door.
But what if other people
want to revise?
No, good point.
Okay, first of all
you've got to swear
not to tell anyone.
-Tell anyone what?
-Swear first,
then I'll tell you.
All right, I swear.
I'm gonna need more than that.
I swear on maths.
Right.
Done, sit down.
(quietly):
Okay, okay, okay.
Close your eyes.
Is it gross?
I don't want to see it
if it's got willies.
And...
open them.
Oh, my days.
Oh, they're so glamorous.
Who are they for?
Me.
You?
Do you mean to wear?
Yeah.
On your feet?
Uh, no, Pritti, I'm gonna
pierce me nipples
and swing 'em round me tits.
Yeah, on me feet.
Jamie, are you saying, you...
All right, what are you saying?
You remember, right,
when we were little,
and we used to play dress-up
and I'd always be
pre-breakdown Britney?
Well...
for me...
that's a game I don't want
to stop playing.
Dressing up as a woman?
Yeah.
Do you want to be a woman?
Uh, no. I want to be a boy.
Who sometimes
wants to be a girl.
Is it... sexual?
No. It's fun.
It's wonderful.
I want to be a drag queen.
You can do that, you know.
Get instafamous,
make some money.
Just not on Parsons Cross.
Why can't you do it
on Parsons Cross?
Oh, 'cause this is Sheffield,
not San Francisco.
I'm Jamie New
not Bianca Del Rio.
So...
What do you think?
I think...
You think I'm a freak.
No, it's not...
Not a freak. I just...
I do think it's weird. Yeah.
-Chips with that?
-Uh, no, thanks.
I'm watching me waist.
But I guess that's
the point, in't it?
Everyone thinks I'm weird, too.
I'm a Muslim girl
with a Hindu first name.
I mean, thanks, Mum.
The looks they used
to gimme at mosque.
Yeah, Pritti.
Me, being a drag queen,
in Sheffield,
is exactly like that.
I'm just saying,
that's us, in't it,
weirdos together?
I don't fit in
'cause I want to be a doctor.
You don't fit in
'cause you want to dress up.
High achiever.
High heels.
-(laughs softly)
-So we're still friends, yeah?
Bezzy friends, #4eva.
Oh, thank God.
I mean, Allah, or whatever.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Tweedle Dum
and Tweedle Bummer.
-I got a joke for you, Jamie.
-(sighs)
-What's gay and says ow?
-I don't know.
Ow! Get lost, Dean.
I've got better things to do.
Oh. And what about you?
You got better things to do,
you fat sweaty, swotty, spotty,
speccy, piggy virgin?
Don't you dare call her that.
Why? It's what she is.
Just like you're
a gay, gay, gay, gay,
gay, gay, gay, gay...
...gay boy.
Yeah, Dean, I'm gay.
I am gay.
So if I call me gay,
then being called gay
in't an insult, is it?
'Cause I am bent,
and I am queer,
and I am a faggot batty bum boy,
you tragic meathead,
micro-dick scrounger,
povvo, waste of space
wanker.
-I ain't got a small dick.
-(boys laughing)
That's not what Becca says.
Stuff you, Jamie New.
Oh, my days, look at you.
-(sighs)
-You're amazing.
You're fearless.
You're Emmeline Pankhurst.
Who's she?
Oh, she were like Beyoncé
back in't day.
-Shut up.
-(bell rings)
Oh, double maths.
-Kill me now.
-Jamie, wait a minute.
-Why?
-Just wait.
Wear these to prom.
What?
If you want to be a drag queen,
be a drag queen.
Why not come out
as a drag queen at prom?
-I can't.
-Jamie,
stop waiting for permission
to be you.
♪ 'Cause the party's
just starting ♪
♪ And you don't want
to miss it ♪
♪ The party's just starting ♪
♪ Almost so close
you can kiss it ♪
♪ Don't wait for tomorrow ♪
♪ Be happy today ♪
♪ And all of
those stupid people ♪
♪ Who cares what they say? ♪
♪ I know it's not easy ♪
♪ But I know you're strong ♪
♪ And I know that somewhere ♪
♪ They're playing your song ♪
♪ Out of the darkness ♪
♪ Into the spotlight ♪
♪ Everyone's waiting ♪
♪ Jamie ♪
♪ In a place where you belong ♪
♪ 'Cause somewhere's a party ♪
♪ That can't start without you ♪
♪ Somewhere the DJ ♪
-♪ Is playing your song ♪
-♪ When the curtain's going up ♪
♪ All eyes on you ♪
♪ When the lights
are going down ♪
♪ All eyes on you ♪
♪ When the crowds
are showing up ♪
♪ All eyes on you ♪
♪ 'Cause tonight's
a-going down ♪
♪ All eyes on you ♪
♪ Hey, can you hear them? ♪
♪ That's your audience waiting ♪
♪ There'll be queues
round the theatre ♪
-♪ All eyes on you ♪
-♪ For all the shows ♪
-♪ You're creating ♪ -♪ 'Cause
tonight's a-going down ♪
-♪ All eyes on you ♪
-♪ And maybe there'll be ♪
♪ Curtains ♪
-♪ All eyes on you ♪
-♪ Hung in velvet maroon? ♪
-♪ All eyes on you ♪ -♪ And
maybe there'll be ice cream ♪
♪ In a tiny tub,
with a built-in spoon ♪
♪ Out of the darkness ♪
♪ Into the spotlight ♪
♪ All eyes on you ♪
♪ Everyone's waiting, Jamie ♪
♪ 'Cause that's where
you belong ♪
♪ And somewhere's a party ♪
♪ That can't start without you ♪
♪ All eyes on you ♪
♪ Somewhere the DJ ♪
♪ Is playing your song ♪
♪ When the curtain's going up ♪
♪ When the lights
are going down ♪
♪ Playing your song ♪
♪ When the crowds
are showing up ♪
♪ 'Cause the party's
just starting. ♪
-(music fades)
-Jamie, you're unstoppable.
I am.
And I'm coming out
as a drag queen at prom.
-♪ ♪
-'Cause sometimes, Pritti Pasha,
you've gotta grab life
by the balls.
You take those balls,
you tuck 'em between your legs
and you put your best
chuffing frock on.
♪ Out of the darkness ♪
♪ Into the spotlight ♪
♪ A teenage sensation ♪
♪ Is coming ♪
♪ The new star of the show ♪
♪ Give me the encore ♪
♪ The standing ovation ♪
♪ Then watch me ♪
♪ Go... ♪
(music stops)
Jamie New:
The boy so nice,
he came out twice.
-(laughs)
-(song ends)
(engine stops)
WOMAN:
What is she doing here?
I need a word.
(man sighs)
I'll be inside.
You know, sometimes...
...I think I might just be
the stupidest woman alive.
You see...
I allow meself to believe
these ridiculous things,
like that maybe,
this time,
on his 16th birthday,
you might actually show up.
And not even a text to him
to say you're sorry.
I'm sick of covering for you.
So don't do it.
What, and tell him the truth,
that his own dad
doesn't want to see him?
Happy birthday, Jamie. Surprise.
It's not as if we've got
anything in common.
He's...
He's... (sighs)
Well, you know what he's like.
I do.
And I love him for it.
Oh, don't you just.
It was always the two of you,
wasn't it?
Your little jokes,
your little club.
And me as shit daddy
on the sidelines.
Yeah, well, you are a shit dad.
That's 'cause that's
the part you gave me.
Oh.
He don't wanna do
any of the things I wanna do.
What is so wrong with a boy
wanting to do boy's things, eh?
(sighs)
It's not fair.
We tried and tried
for that baby for so long...
and you were the only one
who got the kid you wanted.
WOMAN:
Are you coming in or what?
He'll not be a minute, Cheryl.
We're just reminiscing
about our love life.
What'd you have to say that for?
I'll not hear
the last of it now.
Well, I've gotta hand it to her.
I could never whip you
into shape like that.
She's even driving you around
in your brand-new car.
You're literally
in the passenger seat.
You think you know it all,
don't you?
Well, I'll tell you something
you don't know:
Cheryl's pregnant.
We're having a boy.
Jamie's 16.
I've done my duty.
He don't need me anymore.
Tell him the truth
and then, for Christ's sake,
move on.
(scoffs)
♪ ♪
Here.
It's a different brand of tea.
Tell me if it tastes funny
only it were 20p off.
(slurps)
No, it-it's lovely.
Are you revising?
Sort of.
I'm trying to find a dress
-to go with me shoes.
-Oh, ey? Let me see.
No. I haven't found
the right one yet.
Oh, all right, then,
I'll leave you in peace.
-M-Mum?
-Mm-hmm?
I've not heard from Dad
since he missed me birthday.
♪ ♪
Oh, don't blame him, love.
It's that Cheryl.
She runs him ragged.
(laughs softly)
♪ ♪
Ta-da.
Wow.
This is it. Good luck, Jamie.
You're not coming in with me?
Some doors, Jamie,
you have to walk through
on your own.
(door chime playing)
(mouths)
Come in if you're coming in.
Don't just linger
like an old nun's fart.
Welcome to my world of wonder,
drag couturier to the stars.
Is this the Hose of Loco?
House of Loco.
House.
Oh, don't tell me.
That ruddy "U"
has dropped off again.
I'll have a rummage
in my cupboard,
and see if I can rustle up
an upside down "N."
Originally I was going
to call it "The Tuck Shop."
Think about it.
And what's your name?
Jamie.
Can I try one of these on?
Knock tha' self out, lad.
Tha tears it, tha wears it.
So, what's it for?
Fancy dress party?
Let me guess-- Rocky Horror?
No.
It's for me to wear.
It's not a costume.
I want to be a drag queen.
Hmm?
How old are you, Jamie?
16. Just.
Sixteen?
Oh, they're getting younger
and younger.
Whilst I just curl up here
in an ossifying ball
growing ever more fabulous.
So, does she have a name?
Does who have a name?
Does your drag queen
have a name?
Well, I've thought,
a bit, you know,
-brainstormed and that, but...
-Out with it.
Come on.
You'll never know
if you don't say.
What is it?
Sandra Banana.
-(weakly): "Sandra Banana."
-Oh, I know.
-Sandra Banana?
-I know.
You'll have to do better
than Sandra Banana.
Your name's your brand.
Take it seriously.
I mean, who's ever heard
of Archibald Leach?
Who's Archibald Leach?
That's only Cary Grant's
real name.
(chuckles)
Who's Cary Grant?
Oh, bloody hell.
Come here, come here, come here.
Now listen, listen.
You need to create a persona.
Look at her.
Look at everything she is.
A goddess made flesh.
"The Warrior Queen
in the Blood Red Dress.
Miss Loco Chanelle."
Warrior?
You can't just be a boy
in a dress, Jamie.
A boy in a dress
is something to be laughed at.
A drag queen is something
to be feared.
Oh, you won't believe
the power it gives you,
putting on that wig,
slipping on them heels.
You'll hold the audience
in the palm of your hand.
Folks love a drag queen,
but folks are terrified of 'em.
But I don't want to make
people scared of me.
Shoot first, or they'll shoot
you down. First rule of drag.
So why...
why do you want
to be a drag queen?
I dunno, I just do.
You just do.
Oh, that's some inspiring
stuff there.
Put that on a fridge magnet,
why don't you?
Bloody hell.
Because I can't really ever
imagine doing anything else.
Because it's all I dream of.
It's all I live for
and when I close me eyes,
it's all I can see.
I don't want to be a drag queen.
I have to be one.
Bingo, poppet!
Which is why
I'm going to me school prom
in drag.
Chuffing hellfire.
You don't ask much of yourself,
do you, kiddo?
What if the other lads
turn on you?
-Have you thought of that?
-So...
...you don't think
I should go?
Oh, no, you have to go,
in honor of all your
fallen comrades
what have come before you.
How far away's your prom?
-Six weeks.
-Six weeks?
All right, well, that's tough
but not impossible.
Oh, kids today.
Well, luckily, Jamie,
you just found yourself
a mentor.
Wait.
Are you a drag queen?
I was, once, Miss Loco Chanelle.
-No way. No.
-Oh, yes, yes, yes.
In daylight hours,
I was the ever so humble
Hugo Battersby,
but at night...
and at the right price...
Look at you.
Look at how you move.
It must've been amazing.
♪ Let me tell you
how it used to go ♪
♪ Freddie playing
on the radio ♪
♪ The Iron Lady
couldn't stop the show ♪
♪ We felt like we could fly ♪
♪ Poison patter
and a barbed remark ♪
♪ Bette Davis doing
Joan of Arc ♪ (kisses)
♪ Dirty glamour dancing
in the dark ♪
♪ On days that wouldn't die ♪
♪ When we felt
like we could fly ♪
Don't be like that.
I love you...
HUGO:
♪ It was real love ♪
♪ Look around and feel love ♪
♪ Tearing up the floor ♪
♪ Something we loved more ♪
♪ More than life ♪
♪ This was me ♪
♪ We were children
in the night ♪
♪ Every star burned
twice as bright ♪
♪ We were tough
and we could fight ♪
♪ We held the line ♪
♪ This was me ♪
♪ Every sorrow had a song ♪
♪ Every lost boy could belong ♪
♪ We were young
and never wrong ♪
♪ And I was divine ♪
♪ This was me ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Every Friday
we'd emerge reborn ♪
♪ Keep on dancing
till we saw the dawn ♪
♪ Making history
and breaking laws ♪
♪ Oh, God, how good that feels ♪
♪ We were heroes
in our heels ♪
-(cheering)
-♪ This was me ♪
♪ We were children
in the night ♪
♪ Every star burned
twice as bright ♪
♪ We were tough
and we could fight ♪
♪ We held the line ♪
♪ This was me ♪
♪ So adored and born again ♪
♪ She's a smoking ten for ten ♪
♪ I was beautiful back then ♪
♪ I was divine ♪
♪ Let me take you round
the bars I knew ♪
♪ The stars I knew ♪
♪ The battle scars I knew ♪
♪ The cobbled alleyways,
the ways I knew ♪
♪ The maze I knew ♪
♪ The waifs and strays I knew ♪
♪ The siren singing
to the way back when ♪
♪ And wishing I could
live it all again ♪
♪ But now I pass it on to you ♪
♪ We were dreamers,
only just begun ♪
♪ We were sinners
playing in the sun ♪
♪ Kept on partying till '91 ♪
♪ Until that fateful day ♪
We were peacocks
in exotic herds
Wouldn't listen
to the warning words
That's the problem
with such pretty birds
They always fly away
♪ Even Freddie
couldn't stay... ♪
The rock star, Freddie Mercury,
died last night,
the day after he announced
that he had AIDS.
HUGO:
♪ This was me ♪
♪ Were we foolish to believe ♪
♪ That a painted face
can't grieve? ♪
♪ We were hopelessly naive ♪
♪ Just out of time ♪
♪ This was me ♪
♪ Every heart is made to break ♪
♪ Sometimes love's
a big mistake ♪
♪ Every weekend was a wake ♪
♪ But weren't we divine? ♪
Someone help.
Ta-da!
Bitch is back
and she's brought some flowers.
♪ ♪
Hello, beautiful.
Just come here.
Come here, babe.
♪ This was me ♪
I love you.
(laughs softly)
♪ This was me ♪
(music ends)
♪ This was me. ♪
Me friend, she's...
I'm sorry.
-(door opens)
-(door chime playing)
(door closes)
The drag queens
in the olden days,
they weren't just queens.
They were warrior queens.
I thought I'd got it hard.
They had the whole world
against them,
and they still
never backed down,
and me... (scoffs)
I just wanna dance round and
show off and be a bit famous.
Drag, it's not just
a TV show, Pritti.
It's a revolution.
So go... join the revolution.
I'm not even halfway
brave enough for that.
You know, some of them died.
Like literally, they died.
And the rest of 'em
still kept on fighting.
♪ ♪
PRITTI: And what do you think
they were fighting for, Jamie?
For the future.
And that's you.
This is how you honor them.
By picking up their torch,
and passing it on.
-(door chime playing)
-Hugo?
(calling):
Hugo!
All right.
Let's do it.
Yes!
I mean, I'll try
and squeeze you into
my oh-so-busy schedule.
Oh, hello, love.
Hiya. I'm Pritti.
Yes, you are.
This is Loco Chanelle's
bloodred dress.
It don't fit me anymore,
but it'd fit you.
And, uh, it's for sale.
And for only 250.
-Pounds?
-I've only got 80.
Well, kiddo, nobody said being
a goddess was gonna be easy.
Have you heard of Legs Eleven?
The drag night
at Social Club? Course.
Drag exists on a stage.
If you want to take it out
into the real world,
you've got to carry
that stage with you.
That prom is a show.
-(snaps fingers)
-Your show.
The Jamie Show.
So you'd better be show ready.
Now, I taught them girls
everything they know.
If I ask, they'll put you on
-as opening act.
-(snaps fingers)
Yeah. Yeah, yes, please.
Oh, my days. I mean, wow.
So, go and create her.
Remember, practice,
practice, practice,
until your act, your dress
and your face are flawless.
-(laughs)
-Oh, and don't forget,
you need a name.
And, uh, take my advice.
Keep this show under wraps.
Only tell your nearest
and dearest.
JAMIE:
I promise, Hugo.
I will not let you down.
(dog barking in distance)
MARGARET: So, why is
your car in for repairs?
RAY: The suspension went
at the car wash.
How did your suspension go
in the car wash?
No, not in the car wash.
At the car wash.
-I met a new man.
-Oh.
-Ray!
-(chuckling)
You're a terror. (gasps)
Soapy Dan, the car wash man.
He was ever so attentive
to my bodywork.
MARGARET:
Hmm.
Hello, old friend.
Hey.
What's he done this time?
Cheryl's pregnant.
A boy.
Where does that leave Jamie?
He wants nothing more
to do with him.
He means it this time.
Well, what the hell do I do?
There's only one thing for it.
Time to tell Jamie the truth.
Oh, I know, I know, but, um...
(cell phone ringing)
(sighs)
Speak of the devil.
-JAMIE: Mum! Mum!
-Hello, love.
Get home now, quick!
-Don't talk. Just run.
-(Ray chuckles)
Jamie?
-JAMIE: Mom! Ray!
-(running footsteps)
Guess what, guess what,
guess what!
You've done your hair different?
Ha-ha. No.
I've got news.
By the way, what do you think?
Very nice.
Brings out your... eyes.
-What's your news?
-Mum, Ray...
I've booked me first drag show.
-Bloody hell, how'd you do that?
-Eh?
Well, I googled this drag shop
for me prom dress.
-Your prom dress?
-Me prom dress, yeah.
'Cause the drag show,
well, it's gonna
be like a warmup for the prom.
-For the prom?
-The prom.
Yeah, Mum. Keep up.
It's all about making her her,
building her,
road-testing her
for the prom itself.
Well, say something.
(chuckles)
I don't know what to say.
Oh, tell me I'm stupid.
Tell me not to bother.
No, I'm not gonna say that.
I'm gonna say do it.
Just do it, just go for it,
and just ruddy do it.
I've never been prouder
of you, Jamie. I mean it.
-Never.
-Oh, I'm doing it.
I'm really doing it.
Oh, I just need to buy
this epic dress.
You asking for a handout?
Of course not.
I'm gonna earn it.
-Mum.
-Hmm?
Do you think you could get us
some shifts at the shop?
RAY: You can come and work
for me as well.
Butter me bread cakes.
What would you say
if I invited Dad to me show?
I'll ask him.
Can't hurt, can it?
JAMIE: Could you imagine
if he were there...
seeing me?
He might actually be proud.
♪ ♪
Right, uh,
I'm gonna call Pritti.
Laters.
Margaret.
I'm sorry, Ray.
I just couldn't break his heart.
Not today.
♪ ♪
♪ I'm a diva in training ♪
♪ But I'm doing my thing ♪
♪ When these hips
start swinging ♪
♪ They know I'm about to slay ♪
♪ I think my haters
must love me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm always
on their mind ♪
♪ And if you don't
see me shining, then, girl ♪
-♪ You must be blind ♪
-♪ Work, girl ♪
-♪ Honey ♪
♪ So whip your weave, baby boy ♪
♪ Just believe, it's time
to grab your pumps... ♪
JAMIE:
Hiya!
(sighs heavily)
♪ Work, girl... ♪
Kay Cera.
Kay Ce-what? Too confusing.
What about Lady Upsydaisy?
(scoffs) Too random.
Beverly... Hills.
Too geographical.
♪ Girl, get your moola, get your
coins and pounds and things ♪
♪ Pull up like booyah with
your wigs and gowns and rings ♪
♪ Pay me, do my thing,
then I'm clocking out ♪
-Thank you!
-♪ Jamie, that's who ♪
♪ Everybody talking 'bout ♪
♪ Money don't grow on trees ♪
-(squeals) -♪ You better
roll up your sleeves ♪
♪ It's time to grab your pumps
and work for the money ♪
-♪ Whoo ♪
-♪ Pump-pumps ♪
-♪ And work for the money ♪
-♪ Work, girl ♪
♪ Work, girl,
work, girl, work, girl ♪
♪ Pumps and work
for the money... ♪
Sashay away.
♪ Work, girl, work, girl ♪
♪ Pumps and work
for the money. ♪
(indistinct chatter)
"Promfabulous."
Like that's even a word.
HEDGE:
Bex, Becca, eye shadow.
BECCA:
But, miss...
-Dean.
-Bloody hell.
-What have I done now?
-You've done nothing.
I just wanted to say good luck
with your maths exam.
-Well, I'm not doing it.
-Dean.
Ugh. Look, I know exams are
a massive pain in the arse,
but imagine how much harder
your life is gonna be
if you don't pass maths.
Miss, you're wasting your time.
I'm thick.
(scoffs)
Okay.
-What's that for?
-Shake on it.
I think, if you try,
you can pass maths, so...
so go on.
Just try.
All right,
I'll try and pass maths.
Good.
I believe in you.
Pritti. Pritti!
Jamie?
In here, quick.
-Jamie, what are you doing?
-Look.
Just look at me eyebrows.
It's like me forehead's been
raped by epileptic caterpillars.
Did you do that yourself?
No, Pritti, I'm the victim
of a drive-by clowning.
Yes, of course I did it meself!
-Jamie, I've got...
-The show's tonight.
Help me, please.
Jamie, I've got
me maths exam tomorrow.
Pritti, me eyebrows.
Jamie, I've got to pass
me maths exam
so I can go to Cambridge
so I can become a doctor.
Yeah, but this is important.
(Jamie sighs)
(school bell ringing)
Pritti, please.
(sighs) Give it here.
Look at me.
-What's going on in there?
-JAMIE: It's Miss Hedge.
She can't see me like this.
Hide me!
-There isn't anywhere.
-Find somewhere!
What am I supposed to do,
flush you?
-I'm coming in.
-JAMIE: The window.
-Give me a leggie.
-(key turning)
Who does that backside
belong to?
JAMIE:
Me, miss.
HEDGE (sighs):
Jamie New.
Surprise, surprise.
Pritti Pasha,
I'm disappointed in you,
getting caught up in...
What is it you're doing in here?
-JAMIE: Parkour, miss.
-HEDGE: What?
JAMIE:
Free running. It went wrong.
Just get down.
Turn around, Jamie.
No, you're all right, miss.
Turn around and face me now!
It's for my art exam, miss.
I'm exploring gender identity.
I wanted to use a face
as a canvas to make a statement.
And why aren't you doing this
in the art department?
Jamie's shy.
-Oh, I am.
-Mm-hmm.
Jamie, if you want to throw
your future away, then...
(sighs)
But I'm not letting you
distract her.
-Get back to your revision.
-Okay.
-You know, she actually has a
shot. She's got a... -(scoffs)
Uh, I'm sorry,
have you got something to say?
Yeah.
At least I've got a future.
♪ ♪
Art exam. (sighs)
Right, well, I think you should
go to the art department
and finish your piece off.
I'll just wash
my face off, then.
What are you talking about,
Jamie?
You're Pritti's work of art.
You can't wash a work of art
down the drain, Jamie.
That would be
an act of vandalism.
Go as you are.
♪ ♪
Please, miss.
Don't.
But the corridor is
your catwalk, Jamie.
Your public awaits.
♪ You belong in the spotlight ♪
♪ On the wall of the Tate ♪
♪ In a ten-megawatt light ♪
♪ 'Cause your brushwork's
so great ♪
♪ You're the next phase
in feminine ♪
♪ You're a Lichtenstein dot ♪
♪ You're a bed
with Tracey Emin in ♪
♪ You're Grayson Perry's
next pot ♪
♪ Work of art, work of art ♪
♪ You're a perfect work of art ♪
♪ Like Picasso,
so kick-ass, oh ♪
♪ I just don't know
where to start ♪
♪ Work of art ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You're Yoko Ono on vinyl ♪
♪ Oh, you just raised the bar ♪
♪ You're a canvas that's blank ♪
♪ Watch your value increase ♪
♪ You're a Duchamp urinal ♪
♪ See how precious you are ♪
♪ You're half a dead cow
in a tank ♪
♪ Work of art ♪
HEDGE: Miss Haylock,
I hope you don't mind me leaving
this work of art
in your capable hands.
(laughter)
What is that?
GIRL:
How embarrassing.
-(scoffs)
-DEAN: What's next, Jamie?
You gonna turn up in a dress?
Miss Haylock.
Everyone's a work of art,
Jamie New,
but you are a masterpiece.
("masterpiece" echoing)
A boy in a dress, hmm.
Something to be
laughed at, yeah?
Well, come along
to my show tonight
at Legs Eleven, and you'll see--
a drag queen is
something to be feared.
-And I am a drag queen.
-("masterpiece" echoing)
♪ Yes, you are, yes, you are,
yes, you are, oh ♪
♪ You're the biz, you're
the biz, you're the biz, yeah ♪
♪ Superstar, superstar,
superstar, oh ♪
♪ You're the shiz, you're
the shiz, the shiz, yeah ♪
♪ You're so neat, you're
so neat, you're so neat, yo ♪
♪ Off the chart, off the chart,
the chart, yeah ♪
♪ Super sweet, super sweet,
super sweet, oh ♪
♪ Work of art, work of art,
work of art, yeah ♪
♪ Work of art,
work of art, work of art, yeah ♪
♪ Work of art, work of art ♪
♪ Yes, I am a work of art ♪
♪ You won't shame me,
you should frame me ♪
♪ I'm a Jamie work of art ♪
♪ Work of art, work of art ♪
♪ Gonna blow your world apart ♪
♪ I'm offending,
I'm a trending ♪
♪ Gender-bending,
gender-blending ♪
♪ Gender-pending, gender-ending
and transcending ♪
♪ Work of art. ♪
(birds chirping)
JAMIE:
Please, Pritti.
I need you.
PRITTI (over phone):
I'm sorry.
I've asked. I've begged.
But he says no.
You're a distraction
from me revision,
and I've got to stay in me room.
So climb out the window.
Yeah, I think that's
the kind of distraction
he's talking about.
I've got to go. Good luck.
Oh, my God, it's Dean Paxton.
Shit.
All right, freak show.
What did you say?
I said you are a freak.
No, I'm not.
You put on a dress and a wig
and makeup.
You look like a freak.
Like a dirty, ugly freak.
So, uh...
break a leg.
Ta-ra.
(laughter)
TRAY SOPHISTICAY: And how's
the talentless one today?
SON OF A TUTU:
Talentless? Talentless?
They call me
the Great Wall of China
because my talent
goes on and on.
They call you
the Great Wall of China
'cause they can see you
from space.
-(gasps)
-(light laughter)
Oh, Harry H. Christ
on a biscuit,
I'm so out of shape.
No, darling, never.
Round is a shape.
-Assholes.
-(gasps)
Shape, shape, shapes.
Uh-oh.
And where in the name of Cher
do you think you're going?
Hugo?
Who the bloody hell's Hugo?
I'm Loco Chanelle.
Now, get in here!
Now!
(sighs)
LOCO CHANELLE:
Good evening, goddesses.
-Oh!
-Oh, there she is.
May I present...
...to you the future.
The futura.
This is...
What's your drag name?
I still don't have one.
Hey, please, can I have a word
in private, Hugo?
Don't mind us.
We're not listening.
I screwed it.
I swear I meant to keep
the show a secret,
but I blurted it out, and now
they're all here from school.
Dean Paxton with
a bunch of his mates.
I can't go on.
A drag queen doesn't know
the meaning of the word "can't."
Just ask my seven ex-husbands.
No, I'm stupid.
I'm wasting your time.
I've got no name.
I've got no tits,
and I've got no eyebrows.
For God sakes,
I'll do your eyebrows,
I'll make you look beautiful,
and you can borrow some tits
from the tit box.
You're not listening to me.
It's Dean Paxton.
I can't go on.
Girls, a moment, please.
Oh, pretty please.
One, two, three four,
get to walking.
Trot on.
(gasps)
I don't give a pixie's shit
about Dean Paxton.
Tonight's your night.
♪ ♪
♪ When the dogs of war
are dancing ♪
♪ And the arrows
hit their mark ♪
♪ When your days
are getting darker ♪
♪ And there's daggers
in the dark ♪
♪ You will always find
your spotlight ♪
♪ You will always
find your feet ♪
♪ Scream until
your lungs expire ♪
♪ Ready, steady, aim and fire ♪
Can you give these to Jamie New?
Who's Jamie New?
He's skinny, blond.
It's his first show.
Leave them there, love.
(laughs)
♪ Did you think
it would be easy? ♪
♪ You're one footstep
from defeat ♪
♪ But a soldier
shan't surrender ♪
♪ And a hero can't retreat ♪
♪ Though your enemies
surround you ♪
♪ And they've got you
in their sights ♪
♪ Sound the bugles ♪
♪ All set, Sarge ♪
♪ Ready, steady,
aim and charge ♪
♪ Over the top ♪
♪ My friend ♪
♪ Unto the breach ♪
♪ Rend the unending night ♪
♪ Let's get your armor on ♪
♪ Let's get
your war paint done ♪
♪ Now it's time to fight ♪
(quiet chatter, laughter)
Crikey, Ray.
They're going to eat him alive.
He's his mother's son.
Have a bit of faith.
Look, his friends are here
to support him.
-Hi.
Hi.
-(gasps)
-(others murmuring)
Jamie? Jamie New?
Flowers.
No way. That's mental.
It's from me dad.
"Sorry I can't be there,
but I know you'll do me proud."
This is for you, Dad.
♪ When your sisters
are behind you ♪
♪ Ah-ooh ♪
♪ They're your brothers
marching, too ♪
♪ Left turn ♪
♪ And the warrior inside you ♪
♪ Ah-ooh ♪
♪ Comes to run
the dragon through ♪
♪ Right turn ♪
♪ Though your darkest demon
comes the day that you doubt ♪
♪ You'll become a he-man
every demon you rout ♪
-♪ Time to face your fear ♪
-♪ Your fear ♪
♪ Ready, steady,
aim and cheer. ♪
This is it, Jamie.
Name her now.
Who is she? Who is she?
-I don't know.
-You have to know.
-I don't know!
-Come on.
-What's all this been about?
-I don't...
-You do.
-I can't.
Say it. Say it.
It's about me.
That's it, kiddo!
Yes!
♪ ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
would you give a warm
Legs Eleven welcome
for her premiere appearance,
her virgin unveiling,
her maiden voyage,
the soon to be legendary...
Miss Mimi Me!
(gasps)
(applause)
(audience murmuring)
Oh, my God.
("Kiss the Sun"
by Beverley Knight playing)
-♪ I got the dreams ♪
-(lip-synching)
♪ I got the style ♪
♪ I got the moves ♪
♪ To make you smile ♪
♪ And I am gonna ♪
♪ Yes, I'm gonna be ♪
♪ The... ♪
-DEAN: Freak show!
-♪ One ♪
-Freak! Freak show!
-(mock retching)
-MAN: Oh, shut up.
-MAN 2: Hey.
DEAN:
Freak!
-♪ You're in my lane ♪
-♪ You ♪
-♪ You're in my light ♪
-♪ You're in my ♪
-♪ Get out my way ♪
-♪ Out my way ♪
-♪ I'm taking flight ♪
-♪ Hey, hey ♪
-♪ Yes I'm gonna ♪
-♪ I'm gonna ♪
♪ I'm gonna be the one ♪
-♪ Gonna be, yeah ♪
-♪ Yes, I'm gonna ♪
-♪ Gonna ♪
-♪ I'm gonna kiss the sun ♪
-♪ Yes, I'm gonna ♪
-DEAN: Freak!
♪ Gonna be the one ♪
♪ Yes, I'm gonna ♪
♪ Gonna kiss the sun ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm gonna ♪
♪ Gonna be the one ♪
♪ Yes, I'm gonna ♪
♪ Gonna, gonna, gonna... ♪
♪ Over the top, my friend ♪
♪ Quick step, forward march,
left turn, right turn ♪
♪ Unto the breach, my friend ♪
♪ Clean shoes, fresh starch,
old dog, new look ♪
(cheering)
♪ Rend the unending night ♪
♪ We shall fight them
on the beaches ♪
♪ You've got your armor on ♪
♪ You've had
your war paint done ♪
♪ Now you're a man, my son ♪
(cheering)
-All right, Jamie!
-MARGARET: I love you, Jamie!
♪ So get out there and fight. ♪
That's how a legend is born.
Mwah! Mwah!
(giggling)
Yes!
(over alarm clock):
♪ Olé, olé, olé, olé ♪
♪ Olé, olé, olé, olé... ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You should've seen it,
you should've been there ♪
♪ You won't believe the shit
we saw that went down in there ♪
-♪ The men were women ♪
-♪ The girls were fellas ♪
♪ He did a rain dance
wearing nothing but umbrellas ♪
-♪ Pass it on ♪
-♪ There was a lady ♪
♪ She had a sister ♪
♪ But it was kinda weird
the way the lady kissed her ♪
♪ There was a woman
whose name was Norman ♪
♪ And the frilly knickers ♪
-♪ That was just the doorman ♪
-♪ Pass it on ♪
♪ There was a doorman
whose name was Norman ♪
♪ And then the doorman
kissed his sister ♪
♪ She's a Mormon ♪
♪ I heard there's dungeons
inside the cellars ♪
♪ Where they rain down pain
and spank you with umbrellas ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's
talking 'bout J-J-Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's talking 'bout
the boy in the dress ♪
♪ Who was born to impress ♪
♪ Everybody's talking 'bout
the things that he wore ♪
♪ Everybody's listening
'cause we need to know more ♪
♪ Everybody's talking 'bout
the boy in the wig ♪
♪ 'Cause he's gonna be big ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Ja-a-a-a-a-amie ♪
(indistinct chatter)
-♪ And there was music ♪
-♪ And there was dancing ♪
♪ And all the drag queens
have to lip-synch ♪
-♪ 'Cause they can't sing ♪
-♪ Pass it on ♪
-♪ And there was smoking ♪
-♪ And there was boozing ♪
♪ And there were boys
that looked like girls ♪
-♪ Which was confusing ♪
-♪ Pass it on ♪
♪ So what's a lip-synch?
Is that like kissing? ♪
♪ Yeah, he kissed a girl whose
girlie parts were missing ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's
talking 'bout J-J-Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout the boy on the stage ♪
♪ Who broke out of his cage ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Ja-a-a-a-amie ♪
(excited chatter)
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's
talking 'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Jamie... ♪
Jamie?
What are you doing?
Jamie!
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's
talking 'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's talking 'bout
the boy in the dress ♪
♪ Who was born to express ♪
♪ Everybody's talking,
and we're talking about ♪
♪ The eyes and the thighs
and the p-p-p-pout ♪
♪ Everybody's talking,
and there ain't no doubt ♪
♪ Who we're dying to see ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Ja-a-a... ♪
-♪ Ja-a-a... Ja-a-a... ♪
-♪ Ja-amie! ♪
Right. Settle down, Year 11.
I want to run through
the last few exams with you.
Hiya. Is everybody
talking about me?
(students gasping, chuckling)
Well, I'm sorry I'm late, miss.
Must have overslept.
Late night.
No, I'm sorry, Jamie.
I'm sorry you suddenly
feel the need
to be the center of attention.
I don't know what
you're talking about, miss.
(students laughing, murmuring)
Miss.
You know that makeup like that
is completely
against school uniform rules.
JAMIE: The school uniform rules
for the girls, miss, yeah,
but if you check the code
for the boys-- and I did--
it don't say nothing
about makeup at all.
Hiya, Dean.
Having a nice day so far?
Jamie, what are you doing?
Who's Jamie?
I'm Mimi Me.
HEDGE:
Take them off.
No.
(students murmuring)
What did you just say to me?
I said, "No."
I won't take them off.
Can I remind you that I am
a teacher at this school?
You don't need
to remind me that, miss.
I just get a whiff
of desperation, and then, oh,
-look, there you are.
-(students laughing, murmuring)
You're in real trouble now. Out!
(students laughing, chattering)
Sit down and stay there.
(sighs)
Hiya, gorgeous.
Freak show.
Freak show, freak show,
freak show.
Like that word will ever
bring me down.
'Cause I'm fabulous, Dean.
And you might be fit,
and you might be handsome,
but you're so ugly.
I'll see you at prom, Dean.
I'm picking out a dress
just for you.
(grunting)
HEDGE:
Break it up!
Break... break it up!
-Stop it! That's it!
-The pair of you!
Get him away from me.
-Where are you going?
-Home.
You've got your exam, Dean.
Screw my exams, screw you,
and screw that
disgusting thing there.
'Cause if you're going
in a dress,
you won't find me
nowhere near that stupid prom.
-(sighs)
-What's got into you, Jamie?
Eh? You know you can't
behave like that.
A drag queen don't know
the meaning of the word "can't."
Just ask me seven ex-husbands.
You, take those off.
(door closes)
MASOOD:
Jamie's behavior has been
utterly unacceptable, Mrs. New.
And I don't use
such strong words lightly.
It's just a bit of makeup.
Oh, Ray, please.
I work shifts. I didn't see him
leave like that, but...
it's hardly
the end of the world.
Well, it's the end of prom
for Dean Paxton.
MARGARET:
Who's Dean Paxton?
Dean from the drag club, eh?
The boy who had 'em all jeering.
-Oh.
-He's a knob head.
Well, that's not
very helpful language.
Well, he is.
Uh, I-I'd like to downplay
this dialogue and say to Jamie,
I want to encourage you to
uncover your individual, yeah?
I want you to interface
with the true you.
But is it right you want
to go to prom in a dress?
(whispers):
Go on.
Yeah.
RAY:
Is that a problem?
No, no, 'cause in this school,
we are, you know, promoters
of, um, freedom of expression,
and, uh...
Yeah, I think what Mr. Masood
is trying to say
is that there is a fine line
between individuality
and disruption,
and that you need to think
about how your actions
are going to affect
other people.
Because not everyone is
as lucky as you, Jamie.
For some of these kids,
prom is...
I mean, it's their last chance
to have one amazing night,
and I'm not gonna let you
take that from them.
How is Jamie taking anything
away from anyone?
Because some of the kids
have said they're not gonna
go to prom
if Jamie wears a dress.
She means Dean Paxton.
You heard what he called me.
What? What?
What did Dean Paxton call him?
Well, I don't want
to repeat the word.
MARGARET:
Well, I do. I want to hear.
I want to know what my son's
being called at school.
He called him disgusting.
And-and we will deal with that.
But, Jamie, this is
gonna keep happening.
Mimi Me is not a student
at this school.
Jamie New is.
And if Jamie wants to come
to prom, he comes as Jamie.
In a tie and-and a shirt
and trousers,
like all the other boys.
I'm sorry, but your
behavior today-- that's...
that's just the way
it has to be.
We've heard enough.
-(door opens)
-Jamie!
-(sighs)
-JAMIE: Disgusting.
How could he call
Mimi Me disgusting?
You know, Mimi is gorgeous,
and glamorous.
Look at Miss Hedge
in her knockoff Jimmy Choos.
-You know she's just jealous.
-Jamie.
Calm down.
Me mum and dad'll hear you.
I'm not supposed to have boys
in me room.
Oh, I'm sorry,
please hold me back
whilst I try not to ravish you.
Jamie. House rules.
Come on.
(sighs heavily)
Your room's so tidy.
I don't know how you do it.
I don't have as many dresses
as you do.
I like your lamp.
Thanks.
Jamie, do you think...
Miss Hedge maybe has a point?
If Mimi goes to prom,
it'll only be about her.
Everyone else'll
be overshadowed.
No, everyone loves Mimi.
They love her on a stage...
but in real life...
she can say things
that upset people.
Why does Mimi have to be
part of the equation?
I'm gonna be a doctor,
but it doesn't mean
I have to go everywhere
swinging my stethoscope.
'Cause without Mimi, I'm...
I'm just ugly.
Jamie...
you are stunning.
You know there's a name
like Jamie in Arabic.
Jamil.
So if you were, like,
Pakistani or Middle Eastern
or whatever,
we'd call you Jamil New.
And do you know
what Jamil means?
It means "beautiful."
♪ ♪
♪ It means something
that's only yours to give ♪
♪ It means choosing
the way you want to live ♪
♪ It means wonderful ♪
♪ And it means powerful ♪
♪ And it means true ♪
♪ It means something
as perfect as it's pure ♪
♪ It means waiting
until you know you're sure ♪
♪ It means beautiful ♪
♪ And it's beautiful ♪
♪ Like you ♪
♪ Beautiful ♪
♪ Beautiful... ♪
♪ A little bit of glitter
in the gray ♪
♪ Beautiful ♪
♪ Beautiful... ♪
♪ Is something precious
you don't simply give away ♪
♪ It means something
that's always yours to keep ♪
♪ It's the face you don't
take off to go to sleep ♪
♪ It means simple ♪
♪ And it means magical ♪
♪ Like a kiss ♪
♪ It's a path that you choose
to walk upon ♪
♪ Not some fleeting thing
you find one day is gone ♪
♪ It means innocence ♪
♪ And it means confidence ♪
♪ Like this ♪
♪ Beautiful ♪
♪ Beautiful... ♪
What are you doing?
♪ A little bit of glitter ♪
-♪ In the gray ♪
-Take it off.
-♪ Beautiful ♪
-This is...
-♪ Beautiful... ♪
-disgusting.
♪ Is something precious
you don't rush to give away ♪
♪ Beautiful. ♪
(song ends)
Jamie.
Talk to me.
Me dad...
...he caught me once,
dressing up.
The look on his face,
and what he said,
has made me feel ugly
my entire life.
People can change.
I mean, he sent you flowers
for your show.
But he's not replying
to me texts.
Well, you know,
in the olden days,
people used to go
and actually talk to each other.
I can't go round.
I'm scared.
You were scared to walk
into that drag shop,
you were scared
to step onto that stage.
What would have happened
if you'd turned back then?
Everything you've achieved
these past few weeks, Jamie,
has brought you here.
You can't let being scared
stop you now.
♪ ♪
If I don't say it enough,
you're the best friend a boy
who sometimes wants to be a girl
could ever wish for.
-(door opens)
-See ya.
Bye.
(door closes)
♪ It's a secret ♪
♪ You never get to tell ♪
♪ Something shy and special ♪
♪ Stuck inside its shell ♪
♪ It means brilliant ♪
♪ And resilient ♪
♪ But not free ♪
♪ Beautiful. ♪
Hiya, Dad.
Jamie.
I can't stop,
I'm off to the match.
Yeah, this'll just
take a minute.
I wanted to thank you
for the flowers.
What flowers?
A-At me show.
What show?
Me drag show at Social Club.
You sent me flowers to say...
What, you got on a stage
at Social?
-You sent me flowers.
-I sent you now't.
Why would I?
-Mum said she told you.
-Yeah, well, she didn't.
I suppose she didn't tell you
what I told her, neither?
I'm done with this. All of it.
I'm done with you.
No, you don't mean that.
I wanted a son so badly.
And I got you.
♪ ♪
(engine starting)
(car driving away)
♪ ♪
Who sent me the flowers, Mum?
What else was from you?
The birthday card?
The 50 quid?
(quietly):
How could you?
I just wanted you to be happy.
So you lied.
-No, don't. Don't.
-No, I don't want it anymore.
-I-I said...
-No, no, Jamie. No!
-get off!
-(material ripping)
(Jamie scoffs)
You ruin everything.
Stop living your life
through me.
Just 'cause you've never
been anyone.
(door opens)
(door slams shut)
♪ ♪
♪ The cold empty mornings ♪
♪ The coffee cup warnings ♪
♪ Remembering the spark ♪
♪ That lived in a love ♪
♪ That died in the dark ♪
♪ But life keeps you guessing ♪
♪ Along came a blessing ♪
♪ My world was awake ♪
♪ My precious surprise ♪
♪ My perfect mistake ♪
♪ And maybe ♪
♪ He'll break my heart ♪
♪ 'Cause he'll take my heart ♪
♪ When he goes ♪
♪ I'm dreading the day
when he just walks away ♪
♪ He's my boy ♪
♪ He drives me insane ♪
♪ My pleasure, my pain ♪
♪ He's my boy ♪
♪ Believe me,
he don't make it easy ♪
♪ He'll own me
until he's outgrown me ♪
♪ But still he's my boy ♪
♪ He's my boy ♪
♪ From the moment I saw him ♪
♪ No man came before him ♪
♪ He taught me to fight ♪
♪ To knock back the black ♪
♪ To let in the light ♪
♪ And maybe ♪
♪ He'll break my heart ♪
♪ 'Cause he'll take my heart ♪
♪ When he goes ♪
♪ It's cruel that he can ♪
♪ But that's just like a man ♪
♪ He's my boy ♪
♪ My blessing, my curse ♪
♪ For better, for worse ♪
♪ He's my boy ♪
♪ Believe me,
he don't make it easy ♪
♪ He needs me, fulfills me,
then bleeds me ♪
♪ But still he's my boy ♪
♪ He's my boy... ♪
♪ And don't tell me
I'm fooling myself ♪
♪ Falling again ♪
♪ 'Cause I know the pattern ♪
♪ I know the price,
and I know the men ♪
♪ And I know the bright lights ♪
♪ Are going to tempt him
to stray ♪
♪ But I'd trade my tomorrows ♪
♪ To have him today ♪
♪ Today... ♪
♪ Today, he's my ♪
♪ He's my, he's my ♪
♪ He's my boy ♪
♪ And boys always grow ♪
♪ And boys always go ♪
♪ He's my boy ♪
♪ He's blinded
and so bloody-minded ♪
♪ He's clueless and clever ♪
♪ Confusing but ever ♪
♪ My boy... ♪
(sighs)
Dad.
♪ He's my voice ♪
♪ He's my chance ♪
♪ He's my smile ♪
♪ He's my day ♪
♪ He's my life ♪
♪ He's my pain ♪
♪ He's my joy ♪
♪ He is my baby ♪
♪ He's my man ♪
♪ He's my boy. ♪
-(pounding on door)
-We're closed!
(pounding continues)
I said we're closed!
(pounding)
We're chuffing well
still closed.
-(hinges creaking)
-(door chime playing)
Oh, Jamie.
I'll be honest with you, flower.
It's not your best look.
-(water running, stops)
-HUGO: You must have known,
turning up dressed like that,
to the match,
what would happen.
So... why'd you do it?
'Cause I deserved it.
Oh.
My life's a mess, Hugo.
I'm nobody.
I'm nothing.
I'm disgusting
and vile and nothing.
Jamie,
never say such terrible things.
Do you hear me?
Well, that's what he thinks.
Who?
Me dad.
Oh, don't listen to him.
He's a silly, ignorant man,
that's all.
And he has no power
over you now.
No.
When I'm Mimi,
I can do anything.
But Jamie...
he's pathetic.
Jamie, you put grown men
to shame,
do you know that?
I look at you, and this world,
and how you live in it,
and how everything's
changing so fast,
and I think...
what do I know anymore?
(scoffs)
I'm so bloody old
and out-of-date,
and you, you're just...
new.
I don't know what that means.
I don't know who I am.
You're 16,
of course you don't.
You're still cooking.
Jamie, the final rule of drag
is that there's no such thing
as rules.
Do what you need to do.
Be who you need to be.
Because if anyone can do it...
it's you.
You.
Eh.
Now.
Drink it up.
Come on.
♪ ♪
(sets keys on table)
I'm sorry, Mum.
I'm all right.
It's just a stupid thing I did.
I won't be doing again.
Sit down.
I'm sorry I lied.
Why did you do it?
I didn't think it through,
did I?
(inhales sharply)
-Sorry.
-It's all right.
I deserve it.
No, Jamie.
You don't deserve any of this.
Your dad...
Oh, what was I thinking
loving a man like that, eh?
(Jamie laughs softly)
Who needs a dad anyway?
We got Ray.
She's twice the man
he'll ever be.
And with bigger balls.
Mum.
Do you ever wish
I were just normal?
No.
Never.
And what's normal anyway?
This is normal for you.
Oh, well, if I were normal,
I could go to prom.
If I was normal,
Dad would've stayed.
Your dad's an idiot.
You've done nothing wrong,
Jamie.
You never did.
But I am sorry.
I'm sorry for him,
because he's missing out
on so much.
I mean, look at you, eh.
And you can still go
to the prom, if you want.
I don't care if you go
in trousers or a dress,
or wearing nothing at all,
as long as you go as you.
Because whatever you do,
you are always beautiful.
♪ Beauty is the face I see ♪
♪ Smiling right in front of me ♪
♪ I've been so dumb ♪
♪ 'Cause you are beautiful,
my mum ♪
♪ Me birthday shoes
were meant to roam ♪
♪ But beauty's
in the coming home ♪
♪ And feeling free ♪
♪ You are more beautiful
than me ♪
♪ And I have seen a light
that's shining bright ♪
♪ And it's been brighter
than I knew ♪
♪ And it's a light
that passed me by ♪
♪ But it shines
right from you, my mum ♪
♪ I'm sorry for the stupid
things I've done ♪
♪ I'm sorry for the stranger
I've become ♪
♪ And I'd be nothing
if you'd not been there ♪
♪ To care ♪
-♪ And now ♪
-♪ I'd give my life to see you ♪
-♪ I'll get out there and show
the world ♪ -♪ Smile ♪
-♪ And how ♪
-♪ I thought I'd lost you ♪
-♪ For a while ♪ -♪ 'Cause you
and me aren't easy ♪
♪ To destroy ♪
♪ And I will always be
your biggest fan ♪
♪ My man ♪
♪ Your boy. ♪
Give us a love.
(song ends)
♪ Are you ready to go? ♪
♪ Don't miss this party ♪
♪ Got to let your light glow ♪
♪ While you're still young ♪
♪ While you're
still young ♪
♪ While you're still young... ♪
BOTH:
It's prom night tonight.
We'll see you there.
Aw, twinnies, so cute.
Oh, my God, that shade
looks so lush on you.
Well, I was gonna wear blue
but You're Gorgeous says "no."
(laughs)
Looks good.
Don't judge.
It's just one night.
♪ The whole world dance ♪
♪ Don't waste a moment more ♪
♪ Time to take the floor ♪
♪ Show what you feel inside ♪
♪ And you're gonna find
your tribe ♪
♪ Are you ready to go? ♪
♪ Don't miss this party ♪
♪ Tonight is yours ♪
♪ Better put on a show ♪
♪ The music's starting ♪
♪ Got to let your light glow ♪
♪ While you're still young... ♪
BECCA and BEX:
This is epic.
-Evening.
-What is she wearing?
BOTH: Hiya, Vicki.
We love what you're wearing.
Looking fine, ladies.
Boys in suits.
Check them.
Think they're all James Bond.
License To Drill, innit,
'cause I'm gonna drill me
some sweet, sweet...
-BOTH: Shut up, Levi.
-(laughter)
BOTH:
Chuffing hell.
-Pritti, you're wearing makeup.
-Yeah?
-Looks lush on you.
-Thanks.
DEAN:
Oh, my God.
Look at the makeup on it.
I thought there were only one
drag queen in this school.
-What, is it contagious?
-Dean,
why do you have to be
such a wanker?
Why does she have to be such
a waccy, spaccy virgin?
-Dean.
-It's all right.
It doesn't matter.
What did it say?
I said...
it doesn't matter.
And that's the truth, Dean.
What you say, what you think,
what you do...
it doesn't matter anymore.
No, I am not a "spac,"
as you so ignorantly call it.
What I am is clever.
But if you want to turn that
into an insult, then fine.
Knock yourself out.
Because tomorrow, we're done.
Exams over, school finished.
And I start getting on
with the rest of my life.
But you...
tomorrow...
you're nothing.
-(shocked laughter)
-This school is your world.
No more big fish,
no more small pond.
You've got...
five hours left
of being someone
that anybody cares about,
and that's it.
So call me spaccy,
if it makes you happy,
but enjoy it while you can,
because your time's almost up.
And, yeah, I am a virgin,
and I'm proud of that, too.
Whoa, man,
she totally nailed you.
(laughter)
Yeah, well, you haven't got
a date for prom.
What are you talking about?
I'm here with him.
(students gasping, murmuring)
Jamie, you look amazing.
He looks so good.
(excited chattering)
(laughs softly)
BOTH:
Jamie, you're iconic.
Oh, my God, if I didn't know,
I totally would.
-You made it.
-Course I did.
-You look beautiful.
-Thanks.
So do you.
You're enormous.
HEDGE:
Jamie.
I thought I told you you weren't
welcome dressed like that.
Uh, you told me not to come
as Mimi Me, miss.
And I haven't.
This is just Jamie, in a dress.
No, this is just Jamie
hijacking an event
that's meant for everyone.
I meant what I said:
Tonight is for all the students.
I'm not going to have you
ruin it for them.
But he's not ruining it.
He's making it
a night to remember.
-(students murmuring)
-No.
No, I've made my decision.
All right, miss.
(sighs)
I love me dress,
and me shoes.
I've got everything
I wanted, so...
I'm just gonna go home now.
(quietly): Laters, Pritti.
(kisses)
(students murmuring)
Are you fucking kidding me?!
(shocked gasps)
After all this?
Pritti, you dropped the f-bomb.
(laughter)
She won't let Jamie in
'cause he's wearing a dress.
No, because rules are rules
for a reason.
There is a dress code.
Dress code says "Promfabulous."
Promfabulous.
STEF: I mean, miss,
what's the problem?
I tweeted his picture
and got 12 likes.
That's more than me gecko.
(laughter)
Let Jamie in, miss.
Please.
(chuckles)
Ladies and gentlemen,
the doors to prom hall are open.
-Everybody, in.
-BEX: No.
Not without Jamie.
He don't go in, we don't go in.
-I said, everybody, in.
-PRITTI: No.
Everybody, out.
(chanting):
Jamie.
STUDENTS (chanting):
Jamie. Jamie.
(faster):
Jamie. Jamie. Jamie.
-Oh, you be quiet.
-Jamie! Jamie! Jamie!
-(chanting continues)
-Stop. Stop! Stop!
-Stop! Stop! Stop!
-(chanting stops)
-Honestly, you're all mad.
-(students chuckle)
And I can't tell you
what this means to me,
but this is
your special night, not mine.
♪ ♪
You told me to come
as the real me, miss,
and I have.
Prom-- it's a fairy tale.
But this--
me like this-- is real.
(sighs)
-(students murmur)
-Jamie.
Just go in.
-Yes! -Yes!
-(students exclaiming)
(students whooping,
chattering excitedly)
♪ ♪
Nice shoes, miss.
Nice shoes, Jamie.
Get you, leading the revolution.
(chuckles):
I know.
You're rubbing off.
You're like a superhero.
I'm not a superhero.
-I'm just a boy in a dress.
-(chuckles)
You will dance with me,
won't ya?
Pritti, you and me--
we'll be dancing forever.
(chuckles softly)
-See you inside.
-Okay.
You're not coming in, then?
Sod off.
So now you know what it's like.
-Being the odd one out.
-Screw you, Jamie New.
Oh, come on, Dean.
I mean it.
We're never gonna see each
other again, not after tonight,
so just... come in
and have a dance.
Why not do one nice thing
before it's all over?
-She's right, isn't she?
-Who?
Your little mate in there.
Big fish, small pond--
you think that's all I am?
Oh, it doesn't matter
what I think.
Yes, it does.
'Cause, Sod's Law, Jamie New,
we are gonna see
each other again.
And I'll be doing
some shit job, if I'm lucky,
and you'll walk right past me;
you won't even recognize me.
How could I not recognize you?
You're Dean Paxton.
Come on.
I'll even let you
have a dance with me.
Turns out I'm pretty popular
at the minute.
Might help
with your street cred.
♪ ♪
Go on, be a man.
Take my hand.
-I'm not gay.
-That's all right.
I'm not really a girl either.
Nobody's perfect.
So, Dean Paxton,
how about it?
One last dance.
For old times' sake.
♪ ♪
No, Dean, I'll lead.
("Out of the Darkness (A Place
Where We Belong)" playing)
I'm sorry for being a dick.
♪ Well, you've come pretty far ♪
♪ But you know
where you are... ♪
It's all right.
You're only a little one.
♪ And the friends
that you choose ♪
♪ Wanna walk in your shoes ♪
♪ You're home ♪
(phone dings)
♪ Any day you feel
your skies falling ♪
(sighs)
♪ Look above,
see a bright silver lining ♪
♪ Listen up,
there's a new freedom calling ♪
(both screaming excitedly)
♪ Calling you to a place
where you're shining ♪
(sighs)
♪ Out of the darkness,
into the spotlight ♪
♪ There is a new star
shining so bright ♪
♪ Out of the darkness,
into the spotlight ♪
♪ There is a new star ♪
-(students cheering)
-♪ Shining so bright ♪
♪ In this place
where we belong ♪
♪ In this place where
we belong ♪
♪ So get up when you're down ♪
♪ 'Cause this homecoming crown
has come home ♪
♪ I was lost, I was found,
took the long way around ♪
♪ But I'm home ♪
♪ You and me got a song
that we're singing ♪
♪ You and me got a drum
that we're drumming ♪
♪ Listen up to the changes
we're ringing ♪
♪ Nothing's going to stop us
from coming ♪
♪ Out of the darkness ♪
♪ Woo-hoo ♪
♪ Into the spotlight ♪
♪ There is a new star ♪
♪ Woo-hoo ♪
♪ Shining so bright ♪
-♪ Woo-hoo ♪
-♪ Every day's a chance ♪
♪ Every day's a choice ♪
♪ Even losers
sometimes end up winning ♪
♪ So go and find your dance ♪
♪ Go and find your voice ♪
♪ 'Cause the party's
only just beginning ♪
♪ There's a place
where we belong ♪
♪ There's a place where
we belong ♪
♪ And you'll hear us ♪
-♪ Sing our song ♪
-(cheering and applause)
♪ In this place
where we belong ♪
♪ Out of the darkness ♪
♪ Into the spotlight ♪
♪ There is a new star ♪
♪ Shining so bright ♪
♪ Out of the darkness ♪
♪ Into the spotlight ♪
♪ Find your freedom ♪
♪ It's gonna be all right ♪
♪ In this place
where we belong ♪
♪ In this place where
we belong ♪
♪ In this place
where we belong ♪
(chuckling):
Oh. Thank you.
♪ In this place
where we belong ♪
♪ In this place where
we belong ♪
♪ In this place
where we belong ♪
♪ In this place where
we belong ♪
(fading): ♪ In this place
where we belong... ♪
MARGARET:
Jamie?
Jamie!
JAMIE:
I know! I'm coming!
You've got to put it out
before the lorry comes!
I know! I'm doing it!
-Well, shake a leg.
-I am.
♪ ♪
I'm shaking it for all of us.
♪ In this place ♪
♪ Where we belong. ♪
("When the Time Comes"
by Chaka Khan playing)
♪ I'm ready
when the time comes ♪
♪ I'm ready when
the time comes ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ My opportunity
to shine comes ♪
♪ I'm ready
when the time comes ♪
♪ Look at me, I'm back again ♪
♪ Feeling the joy
that a new day can bring ♪
♪ There's new music,
there's new sounds ♪
♪ All the excitement
got me spinning round ♪
♪ So I'm gonna seize the,
seize the day ♪
♪ I ain't gonna
let it get away ♪
-♪ I ain't gonna let it
pass me by ♪ -♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I got the wings to fly ♪
♪ And I'm ready
when the time comes ♪
♪ I'm ready when
the time comes ♪
♪ I'm ready
when the time comes ♪
-♪ I'm ready ♪ -♪ My opportunity
to shine comes ♪
-♪ Ready ♪ -♪ I'm ready
when the time comes ♪
♪ We're on the edge
of opportunity ♪
♪ And we're gonna blaze a trail
for the world to see ♪
-♪ So when the time comes ♪
-♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ The time comes,
the time comes ♪
♪ I'm ready ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
MARGARET CAMPBELL:
He's me boy, and I love him.
♪ And when the time
comes for love ♪
♪ And the time comes for hope ♪
♪ When the time
comes for friends ♪
♪ And the ones
who helped me cope ♪
♪ When the time comes for them ♪
♪ Lifting me up ♪
♪ Time comes for joy ♪
♪ And the family I love, yeah ♪
♪ Ready when the time comes,
ready when the time comes ♪
♪ My opportunity
to shine comes ♪
♪ Ready when the time comes,
I'm ready ♪
♪ We're on the edge
of opportunity ♪
♪ And we're gonna blaze a trail
for the world to see ♪
-♪ So when the time comes ♪
-♪ I'm ready ♪
-♪ The time comes, time comes ♪
-♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ When the time comes ♪
♪ I'm ready
when the time comes ♪
-♪ I'm ready ♪ -♪ My opportunity
to shine comes ♪
-♪ I'm ready ♪ -♪ I'm ready
when the time comes ♪
-(vocalizing) -♪ We're on
the edge of possibility ♪
♪ And we're gonna blaze a trail
for the world to see ♪
-♪ I'm ready ♪
-♪ So when the time comes ♪
-♪ The time comes,
the time comes ♪ -♪ Oh ♪
♪ I'm ready, I'm ready ♪
♪ I'm ready ♪
♪ I'm ready, yeah, yeah. ♪
(song ends)
("Everybody's Talking About
Jamie" by The Feeling playing)
♪ You should've seen it,
you should've been there ♪
♪ You won't believe the shit
we saw that went down in there ♪
♪ The men were women,
the girls were fellas ♪
♪ They did a rain dance
wearing nothing but umbrellas ♪
-♪ Pass it on ♪
-♪ There was a lady ♪
♪ She had a sister ♪
♪ But it was kinda weird
that way the lady kissed her ♪
♪ There was a woman
whose name is Norman ♪
♪ And the frilly knickers,
that was just the doorman ♪
-♪ Pass it on ♪
-♪ There was a doorman ♪
♪ Whose name was Norman ♪
♪ And then the doorman
kissed his sister ♪
♪ She's a Mormon ♪
♪ I heard there's dungeons
inside the cellars ♪
♪ Where they rain down pain
and spank you with umbrellas ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's
talking 'bout J-J-Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's talking 'bout
the boy in the dress ♪
♪ Who was born to impress ♪
♪ Everybody's talking 'bout
the things that he wore ♪
♪ Everybody's listening
'cause we need to know more ♪
♪ Everybody's talking 'bout
the boy in the wig ♪
♪ 'Cause he's gonna be big ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Ja-a-a-amie ♪
♪ He had one go-go boy,
five go-go boys ♪
♪ Ten go-go boys in kilts ♪
♪ He had one dancing girl,
five dancing girls ♪
♪ Ten dancing girls on stilts ♪
♪ He had one backing singer,
five backing singers ♪
♪ Ten backing singers
plus choir ♪
♪ He did one somersault,
five somersaults ♪
♪ Ten somersaults on fire ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's
talking 'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's
talking 'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's
talking 'bout J-J-Jamie ♪
♪ Everybody's talking 'bout
the boy in the dress ♪
♪ Who was born to express ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
and we're talking about ♪
♪ The eyes and the thighs
and the p-p-p-pout ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
and there ain't no doubt ♪
♪ Who we're dying to see ♪
♪ Everybody's talking
'bout Ja-a-a-a-a-a-a-amie. ♪
(song ends)