Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
I found this necklace by the tree.
Okay.
OFFICER MILLER: You found the body, Mrs Clark.
Yes.
And you knew the dead girl, is that right Chloe?
Yes, that’s right. I spoke to her a few times.
OFFICER MILLER: Where?
Out here.
What was she doing?
She said she was communing.
She said the countryside was her church.
She was really nice.
Did she tell you her name?
Sarah!
MILLER: Just Sarah?
That’s all she said.
Is that all?
Yes, thank you.
SUTTON: Dave!
Mike!
What have we got?
Female, aged about 21.
Been dead for less than 24 hours.
People at the house found her this morning.
The land here used to be a small farm.
It's pretty wild now.
We found her necklace over by the tree.
Looks like the body was moved from there to here.
Any clues to the cause of death?
Only this.
What else?
More severe burning across the inner thighs and abdomen.
Pathology’s not goIng to find anything.
My thoughts exactly.
Same as the others.
You okay?
Come here. Come here.
Panic attack?
Okay, okay. You know what to do.
Breathe in quickly.
Out slowly.
Did you take your beta blocker?
Okay.
Do you want a Diazepam?
No, they make me drowsy in the morning.
Okay, okay, it’s all right.
That’s it.
Come on, lie down.
Feeling better?
Was it a bad dream?
No. Just woke, and there it was.
Like ants under my skin
and this growing sense like I’m gonna die.
Shhhh!
You’re okay.
You’re okay now.
Maybe you should go and see a doctor.
No point.
But you were so much better before…
...before Sarah died.
I know.
But that was a year ago and since then
you’ve been having these attacks again.
I know!
I just want you to be -
Normal?
Better.
I will be...
...if I can just know what happened to Sarah.
If the police had solved her murder…
But there’s nothing you can do about it now.
There is.
There might be.
Oh, you’re not talking about that spirit medium thing.
Leah recommended her.
It’s all bullshit.
You don’t know that.
Anyway...
...I’ll be late home after work.
REBECCA: Sarah?
Sarah?
There’s one here who loves you.
REBECCA: Your sister.
Your twin, Emma.
Come closer.
REBECCA: Closer.
Sarah’s here.
Speak to her.
Sarah!
Are you at peace?
She is.
But she wants you to be at peace too.
I try, Sarah, but...!
I miss you so much. I just want to know...
...what happened!
Sarah, I know you’re tired. Can’t you stay a little longer?
Sarah!
It was a good beginning.
Can't you bring her back?
It's too soon.
We can’t know the energy it takes
for those who have passed through the veil
to look back through it.
And it takes its toll me on me, too.
We’ll try again.
Tomorrow?
I can’t tomorrow. I have another reading.
I can only manage one a day.
Next week.
How much do I owe?
Nothing.
Hi Tess.
I was just wondering if Emma was home yet.
Er, no, she’s not back yet.
I tried calling her.
She’s probably driving.
Yes, I’m just wondering...
...have you heard how it went?
Leave him alone...
I’ve no idea.
...and wait till Emma calls.
Can you get her to ring me?
Okay.
Okay. Bye.
Hi mum. I was driving.
Oh, you’re not driving now, are you?
No mum. I just got here.
Well? How did it go?
Nothing much happened.
So something happened.
I’m a bit washed out. I'll call you.
Call me tomorrow -
Well, it would help if you cared.
Do you want a drink?
No, you’re all right.
Mum called.
Called me too.
She wanted to know - you know.
Yeah!
Well, don’t you want to know?
What I want is for you to move on.
You and your mum.
Well, that's all I want. That's why I'm -
Paying someone to tell you what you want to hear.
She wouldn't take my money.
She will.
I'm going to bed
Emma, I’m sorry.
You’ve got to let me do this.
I just worry that this is something
that’s going to give you false information,
you know, false hope.
If it’s false then all I’ve lost is one evening,
maybe two of my life.
If not...
...at last I’ll find out who killed Sarah.
I just wish the police had done their job.
Then let me do what I can.
I’m so sorry.
I just...
Sometimes I just feel like I don’t know what to do for you.
I know.
I know it’s not easy for you dealing with the anxiety
and the attacks.
Sometimes I feel guilty for letting you take all this on
when we got together.
No. I knew what I was doing.
Okay, I didn’t know anything about panic attacks
but you told me you had them
and I fancied you so much that...
that didn’t matter.
And then I fell for you and…
...here we are.
I hope you're in the mood.
Emma?
Sarah!
He was...he was killing her.
No, it was just a dream.
I saw her die.
No, you're just having a panic attack.
His hands around her neck...
...the detective.
Well that just proves it was just a dream.
I think she was trying to show me.
Okay, just breathe in quickly...
...out slowly.
It wasn't a panic attack. It was...
Okay, okay, just lie down. Just lie down. You're fine.
Okay...okay...
It's all right, It's fine,
SAM - Coffee?
Mmmm.
Look -
I know what you’re going to say so don't.
Okay, but can I say it anyway?
Why don’t we go away? Anywhere you fancy.
Oh!
I thought you were going to tell me not to see Rebecca again.
Well, we haven’t had a holiday in like over a year.
I don’t know if I can get the time off.
Ask.
What about you?
Won’t be a problem.
Okay.
So, how’d it go?
What?
With Rebecca.
Christ, Leah, let me get a coffee first.
You really need decaf.
What’s the point?
Caffeine’s bad for you.
You don’t drink decaf.
I’m insensitive.
So, what happened with Rebecca?
I don’t think I’m going to see her again.
What?
Sam thinks…
No, actually I think I need to move on.
So you’ll do what Sam says.
It’s causing problems.
Life is full of fucking problems.
Maybe he’s right.
He’s fucking wrong.
You want to know who murdered your sister,
and the police know fuck all.
I don’t know.
JESS: Morning.
Morning.
Mail!
You’ve just not been yourself lately.
I don’t know what myself is.
I’m talking about the panic attacks.
I had them before. I thought they’d stopped.
You never said.
Did you get treatment?
I saw a psychologist.
Did it help?
He taught me relaxation and gave me cognitive therapy.
Well, whatever that is, it clearly didn’t work.
Look at the state of you now.
Yeah, I know. I’m a basket case!
It stopped but…since Sarah, it’s come back.
You’re telling me.
Somedays when you come in it's like
you’ve fought a battle between the car park and here.
The first time I thought you were going to actually fucking die
and that gave me a panic attack.
That for you is just panic.
A real panic attack is…
You’re anxious and you’ve got this feeling of worry all the time.
Like when you take your driving test,
or you’re in the waiting room of the dentist
and your stomach feels scrambled,
and it’s like that.
And you feel worried, but you’re not actually
but you don’t know why you feel like that anyway.
And then when you're doing whatever you’re doing
whether it’s watching telly or walking,
you get this feeling
and it gets worse and it spreads all through your body,
and you heart is pounding
and your breath gets hard and you feel like…
...like you’re going to die.
So what do you do?
I find time to do relaxation every day.
It helps but…
...since Sarah...
...it never went away. I just managed it...but...
...now I can't.
Hey, come on.
Sometimes I feel like I’m the one that should have died.
Sarah and I were identical in every way.
Things that made us laugh,
the food we ate,
but not our clothes though,
or our hair.
She had something I didn’t have, and I had something she didn’t have.
What do you mean?
She had what my dad had -
the ability not to worry, to not let things get to him.
Sarah was the sea of calm.
Me? I took after my mum.
She’s anxious. She can get herself into such a state,
and that’s her gift to me, only with me it was worse -
has been since I was thirteen.
A few years ago I got treatment but…
...now it’s come back.
So you need closure.
Yes, I do.
See, that is where I think Rebecca can help.
Look, I know...when I first went I thought it was a load of shite,
but my friend made me go and I never regretted it.
My mum had just died and...
...I just needed to know she wasn’t...
...gone forever.
I mean, it took a couple of sessions, but...
...I got what I needed.
Do you think Rebecca’s the real deal?
If I didn’t believe in her, I wouldn’t have asked her to see you.
She doesn’t see just anyone.
She needs to...
She needs to believe in what you want.
And I guess she’s not interested in people being just curious.
So you must see her again.
Does she take any money?
No, she doesn’t do it for the money. She’s got a day job.
She does it because she can.
Hello, Human Resources, how can I…
Oh, hi!
Yep! Just a minute.
His master’s voice.
Who?
Sam!
Hi!
Oh, I meant to tell you, I’ve got an exhibition
in Liverpool, Tuesday next week,
SAM: so I need to stay overnight.
Oh!
I know you can’t be on your own but I bet Joanna will stay with you.
Yeah, Jo’s good like that.
Have a girls' night.
Yeah, I will.
Okay, see you later.
Yeah, love you.
Girls' night next Tuesday?
Tuesday?
Bollocks! I got the step-mum invading.
It’s so nice to get you out for lunch.
Are you okay?
Yeah!
You still taking those meds?
No, I don’t like the way they make me feel.
Seriously, Emma, how do you cope?
I kind of exchange one sensation for another.
Okay, let’s go.
So…this sensation!
Sex!
Oh! Okay! Yep!
That’ll do the trick.
It does.
Well, I can think of worse things to do.
So, is that something you like discovered
in the middle of a panic attack?
It’s before it gets to that.
It’s when I feel more anxious than usual
but it’s something that’s always worked for me.
Sex, I mean!
So you’re a nymphomaniac.
No!
Let's just say I have a pretty healthy libido.
You just like it a lot.
A lot!
Well, most days!
Lucky Sam!
I think it’s all a bit too much for him really.
But I can’t think of a more powerful sensation
so it helps when I feel more anxious than usual.
An orgasm a day! Yes, please!
Sshhh!
It’s not like that.
What then?
The cuddling.
It's when he strokes my head and kisses my face.
I find that more relaxing than just about anything.
And then there’s the intimacy. The closeness.
The feeling of his hand on my head and neck.
That makes me less anxious
and then usually it leads to….!
I can see why he doesn’t want you to get better then.
Sorry, insensitive!
It’s all right, I don't usually tell people this.
So, does Sam know, like, why he's getting sex every day?
Oh yeah, the funny thing is he’s happy just to hold me
and caress me. I’m the one who takes it further.
Okay, I think I underestimated Sam.
Sounds like a decent bloke.
He is.
He must also be really knackered!
SAM: Anything on telly?
No, nothing any good on.
Oh, do you want another?
No! Had enough. Too easy!
So…!
What?
The spirit medium thing.
I’m gonna give it another try.
Look…
I think if I'm gonna get better I need closure.
I know, and I understand how you feel.
No you don’t.
You don’t know what it’s like to lose a sister,
to know that she was murdered, and you don’t know who by.
And you miss her so much
you just wanna walk in a room and see her
and when she’s not there
it hits you like a punch in the stomach.
And you know you’re life will never be the same
because one of the most joyful things,
one of the most precious things in life has been taken,
and I need to know how
so don’t tell me not to do everything I can.
What, now?
I want to.
Is this what the weekend’s gonna be like?
Oh no!
It’s gonna be much filthier.
And how was the dirty weekend?
Dirty!
Details.
You could’t handle it.
Oh, I can!
I really can!
I need to know!
I've got to know!
Keeley’s not getting enough of her own.
i haven’t got the time. NHS would grind to a halt.
Supernurse.
Ta-da-da-daaaa!
Here to save the day with my big hypodermic!
Boasting again.
Thank God for nurses like you.
Let’s not forget about the little people…
...like Jo.
Excuse me! If it wasn’t for the little people like me,
the people like you would have to do all their own checkouts.
Oh, that would be terrible, having to scan your own shopping.
But I ike it when Jo does it for me instead of going to it
and it saying, 'Call for assistance.'
I mean, what’s the point if you have to have someone do it for you?
See!
Oh, do that again.
That look’s terrible.
High fever,
rapid pulse.
I prescribe lots of sex and another glass of wine.
The wine works for me.
Darling, you really have to lose your cherry some time.
Oi, who says I haven’t?
Well, you never say anything about getting any….
...wahay!
'Wahay'? Who says ‘Wahay'?
Just being polite.
You’re only polite when your gob’s shut.
Keeley, tell us one of your nursie stories.
Oh, I love those.
Oh, okay!
Oh, do you know what a tracheotomy is?
No.
Okay, well, when someone's airway is blocked
you make an incision in their trachea.
Their what-ier?
Their windpipe.
I knew that.
Yeah, right!
I did!
So, you make a hole in their windpipe so that the patient can breath.
Now the trouble is that sometimes it can get stuck
with lots of mucus and gunk...
Ewww!
and that needs suctioning out.
You make good sucking noises.
She gets a lot of practise.
Oi! Carry on Keeley.
So, to do this you take this long piece of tubing
with a suction pump at one end,
and at the other this piece of kit called a yankauer.
A what?
A yankauer!
So, I was on nightshift, and it was 3 AM in the morning.
It was nice and quiet and peaceful
when this man, who had just had a tracheostomy,
started gurgling and struggling to breathe.
So Jenny, the staff nurse, went right over to him
and said in a really loud voice,
‘Would like me to yanker you?’
The man’s eyes nearly popped out.
I bet that wasn’t the only thing.
I was eating a sandwich at the time
and laughing so much I nearly choked.
You needed yankering!
Nearly!
It must be weird with all those men in bed letching at you.
You think? Get this!
So, I was taking handover from day shift
from this very handsome male nurse named Dan.
And I’m talking hot!
And I mean hot!
He's really hot!
So, he was giving me details abut this 20-year-old female patient
who was laying in bed and she was gazing up adoringly.
And I was like, oh yeah,
she's having some amazing fantasies about hot Dad.
And then later on I go through some routine stuff with her,
and I say, 'How are you feeling?'
And she goes, ‘I am gagging for sex.’
And I was like, Oh, okay! Well, hey ho! I can’t help you there!
So I was like, 'Oh it must have been really difficult for you
having hot Dan looking after you,'
and she goes,
'I didn’t mean him. I’m gay. I meant you!'
And I was like, Oh my God!
You must have run a mile.
Not really. She was kind of cute.
Yeah, but you’re not gay.
Not gay, no, but...one time....
...like Katy Perry said,
and I kinda liked it.
God!
Honestly, Jo, you’re such a weeny sometimes.
I tell you, with some of the things I have to deal with,
kissing a girl is no big thing.
Blood! Shit!
Sick! Death!
Can I ask you something?
Sure?
You’ve seen people die.
Yeah, i've been right by their side when they went.
What happens? Do you see anything?
Feel anything?
No, but, you know they’re not there any more.
One thing I do, which is a personal thing -
I open a window.
Sort of let the spirit out.
So you think there is a spirit?
I’d like to think there is.
And I want to help it out on its way.
And if you didn’t open the window would the spirit remain,
like a ghost?
I have no idea,
but maybe that’s what a ghost is -
a spirit that hasn’t gone to where it needs to go.
Right! Let’s talk about what scares us the most.
Okay, you first.
Spiders!
Is that all?
Well, what scares you then?
Well, nothing really.
Nothing scares you! Makes you jump!
Oh, well, okay, well, I don’t like people making me jump.
I hate it.
When I was a kid I freaked out
when I was in my bedroom
and my brother jumped into the doorway and yelled ‘BOO!’
I kid you not, I took off, leaping into the air
and landing onto the bed in tears.
He thought he was hilarious, of course.
So come on Emma, what about you?
Er, I dunno!
Well, there must be something. What about when you were a kid?
All kids are scared of something.
Erm…!
My dressing gown!
What?
Your dressing gown?
Er…I’d be lying in bed
and it would be hanging on the bedroom door, and...
...in the dark and...
it looked like it changed shape,
and I’d hide under the covers until I fell asleep.
You’re just a couple of wussies.
I need to pee.
You know where it is.
That was quick.
Yeah, I -
I just remembered...
I needed...get home -
Yeah!
Sorry!
Will you be okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, just - just -
- short walk.
Bye!
That was all a bit sudden.
Yeah, maybe she left the gas on or something.
Funny girl!
You sure you don’t mind staying over?
Of course not.
Helps knowing someone’s here.
Cute PJs.
Thanks.
Night then.
Night!
Emma?
Sorry…erm -
Bad dreams.
Come here.
EMMA: I’m so sorry!
What can I do?
Sam strokes my head.
Oh, I am so sorry.
It’s okay.
I am so embarrassed.
It’s just -
JO: It’s okay, really.
I mean, if you want to get in, we can just -
No, I'm not sure either -
- if that would help.
Oh God! Erm -
I feel so much better. I’ll just go back to my room.
I’m sorry, Jo.
Oh, I helped myself.
I’ll be off as soon as I‘ve finished. I don’t want to be late.
Okay.
I can get you some coffee, if you’d like.
No, thanks.
I’m sorry about last night.
It’s okay.
When I get a panic attack, I just…I can’t…
It’s okay. That’s what I was here for.
Although I’d not seen you have one before.
Glad you were here, thanks.
When Sam’s away I find it hard to -
Any time. I have to rush. Call me if you need me.
Thanks Jo.
I can see her...but...
I can’t see her face.
All this medium stuff, it’s messing with your mind.
But...what if it's -
It’s all in your mind.
Then I need to find out.
I need your help.
Hi, come in.
I hope you don’t mind me bringing Leah with me.
I wouldn’t have found you otherwise.
Funny thing for a psychic to say.
Oh, I’m not a psychic, I think of myself more as a conduit.
Without a satnav, I keep telling her, she needs to get one.
Oh I didn’t mean it like that, I wasn’t meant to be funny.
It’s okay. Leah convinced me to come.
I’m grateful.
Just as long as you're aware,
I’m not like that woman from Polstergeist.
I don’t normally do home visits.
My gift is more about being able to let the spirits into my home.
But tell me what’s happened.
I feel a presence.
Okay. Can I have a look around?
Feel free.
Shall I make coffee or...
No, stay where you are. Let’s see what I can sense.
Sarah stayed in this room.
Yes sometimes.
She liked it here with you. It was fun.
Is she here?
Yes.
Can I see her?
She’s been trying to show…
Sarah!
She’ll stay over like she used to,
and you’ll see her every now and then.
Sarah’s here.
Emma, you look so different.
I feel different.
I’ve never felt so calm, no anxiety at all.
It’s Sarah making you feel like that.
Can she do that?
Sarah’s a spirit. The spirit’s much stronger than the physical.
I believe the spirit possesses a purity
that we can’t even begin to imagine until
we, too, are spirits.
And all the pain and anxiety of the physical body has gone.
I think Sarah shared some of her spirit with you.
SAM - What’s going on?
Something amazing has happened.
Yeah?
We’ll be going.
See you in the morning, yeah?
Sarah’s here.
She came to visit.
Emma -
She made me feel completely calm,
like I have so anxiety whatsoever.
Well, if you’re going to be well again…
I know I’m going to be much, much better.
Well, that’s all I want.
Okay?
Perfectly okay. Goodnight.
So it’s all good.
Yeah!
And what about -
What?
The sex!
Don’t feel the need.
So what happened to horny Emma?
I don’t know. I feel like I have something more.
So no more dirty weekends?
Who needs them?
I fuckin’ do.
EMMA: What’s this?
LEAH: The Empire. It shows films and live shows.
LEAH: Let’s go one evening.
EMMA: You and me?
LEAH: Yeah, girls' night out.
EMMA: Yeah, okay!
TESS: Richard, why are you so hesitant?
I'm not, I just -
Don’t believe.
I can’t believe in something I haven’t seen.
What about God? You can’t see Him.
I stopped being in God when he let our daughter die.
Mum!
I’ve not seen you look so happy before.
Dad!
So!
Come with me.
Dad?
You two go up.
Have you seen her?
No.
Sarah!
Mum’s here!
Can’t you feel her spirit here?
Maybe another time.
Sarah?
I don’t think she can hear the way we understand, so...
…just love her.
I do!
Richard...
...I saw her.
You can see here too. Just go up.
What’s the point?
She’s not coming home.
Give him time.
Sarah!
Sarah, can you show me you’re here?
Oh, Sarah!
It’s beyond wonderful to see you.
You’ve changed my life.
It’s been so hard since you left me,
but I feel so much better knowing your spirit lives on.
But Sarah,
there’s something that’s a hard question to ask and...
...I need an answer.
Can you tell me…
...can you find a way to tell me who killed you?
Wait!
No, come back.
Yeah yeah yeah - great, I’ll send that...I’ll sort it soon as -
Yeah!
Right, okay, great! Bye!
Pick up, Emma.
Answer your fuckin’ phone.
Emma!
Come on, wake up.
You all right?
What time is it?
Almost six.
It’s still early.
In the evening!
Morning, Sleepy!
Morning!
Come on, up you get coz I’m off to work.
Okay!
Yeah?
Mmm.
Okay!
I’ve brought you some tea, sir.
I have to go and see a young woman in the morning.
I want you to come with me.
Why don’t you have a regular partner, sir?
What do you see here?
Their throats are all burnt.
Conclusion?
Serial killer?
SUTTON: If it’s a serial killer
he’s been killing for over a hundred and sixty years.
What happened?
My back!
Let me see!
Uh…!
I always knew having a nurse for a friend would come in handy.
Well, it’s better dressing than what Emma did.
Well, that’s why you’re a nurse and I work in human resources!
We're going to see Emma West.
Her twin sister was murdered a year ago.
Her throat burned.
And other parts.
Take notes. Don’t speak.
KEELEY: You seem…
...different.
Yeah! I’m doing great.
Okay, well, I’ll see you later.
Bye.
See Ya.
Don’t be late for work.
Miss West? Do you remember me?
I know this sound weird but have you seen me...
...in a place where you wouldn’t expect to see me?
Yes.
Where?
In a dream.
In a dream!
I saw Sarah being killed…
...by you.
Do you know why you would dream that?
I thought maybe Sarah was trying to show me how she was killed,
but it was just an anxiety dream.
I’ve been much better since I saw Sarah.
In your dream?
No. She’s here. Her spirit! I see her.
I’ll come back.
You have your notes?
Yes, sir.
Tear them up. You’ll never need them.
MILLER: Shit!
That’s why I don’t have a regular partner!
Emma!
Yeah?
Wasn't sure if you were asleep.
Not sure of anything.
Just doing my relaxation.
I thought you were relaxed enough.
I am. I was.
Is there something you want to tell me?
The other night I saw Sarah, and she kissed me
and I asked her to tell me who murdered her
and I think she will.
I don't know, it's like you're worse, you're different.
It's like you've got some sort of insanity.
I don’t know what you expect.
How about some fucking honesty?
When have I not been open and honest with you?
All those looks between you and Keeley.
What? What looks?
The sort of looks that tell me you two know something I don’t.
Well, maybe you don’t need to know.
Well, call me paranoid but if Keeley was a guy
I might be fucking jealous.
You know what, Sam?
Whatever I did in the past really has nothing to do with you.
Yeah, well…
I never took you for a dyke.
First of all, I’m not gay.
And if I was, what the fuck has it got to do with you?
Except for the fact that I wouldn’t be fucking you in the first place.
But, yeah, Keeley and I played around when we were younger,
exploring how we felt. What’s the harm in that?
I mean you didn’t have to do, like...
...anything.
What we did or didn’t do has nothing to do with you.
Just like what you did in the past has nothing to do with me.
And who are to be judgemental, anyway?
You who used to smoke dope and peddle drugs
and rob old ladies to pay for your habit.
That’s not the same.
No! I wasn’t hurting anyone.
Look…
...you’ve done amazing to change your life around,
but you had something to change. I didn’t.
I’m still the same person.
It’s like I don’t know who you are.
Surely you’re not insecure.
You know what? I can’t be dealing within this.
I’m going to bed…in the spare room.
That’s Sarah’s room.
Yeah, well Sarah can move out, or I will.
I’ve brought someone.
Emma?
Could I have a drink?
Erm…tea?
Do you have any brandy? Scotch?
We have water.
Is it bottled?
No.
Well, thank you but no. I never drink water from the tap.
Neither would you you if you knew what went into it.
Excuse me, but who exactly are you?
My name’s Susan Brooke.
I’m a parapsychologist.
What’s this about?
Emma, this morning you told me you saw me,
or what looked like me, killing your sister.
This morning?
He came by the house.
What? You never said.
Argue later.
Emma, have you sought out your sister’s spirit in any way?
I went to see a medium.
And then you started seeing your sister here in your home.
What you’ve been seeing is not your sister.
I believe that there are dark forces
that can appear in many different forms.
Sometimes we see them as those who’ve died.
Ghosts!
But why?
To delude us. To cheat us.
To make us think that what is evil is really good.
I don’t accept that.
What I’m telling you now you must accept.
Why must I?
Because there is a dark force intent on destroying you.
What is this dark force?
It lurks in a kind of spiritual darkness.
It can’t exist in our world without a vessel,
so it attaches itself to someone.
It can infiltrate our thoughts…
our dreams…
but most importantly,
it can imitate the dead...
And the living.
It will take on a physical form
so that it can achieve its darkest desire
and will bring itself to a sense of depraved fulfilment
that it just can’t achieve in its own dark spirit world.
And this attacked Emma tonight?
It attacked you?
I thought it was Sam.
It made my neck sore.
Emma, you remember that your sister
was found with severe burning around her throat?
What we never made public was that
she was the fourth girl found dead with these burns.
SUSAN: It generates heats that intensifies
SUSAN: and it leaves its victims with terrible burns.
But leaves no forensic evidence. No DNA. No fluids.
The only thing I know for sure is that Cain appears as me.
Cain?
That’s the name I chose for it.
Why Cain?
Because Cain was the first murderer.
In the Bible.
It’s the name that came to mind when I saw it
standing over Sarah’s body,
and I knew what it was.
But why does it look like you, and how can we tell which is which?
I don’t know how to answer that except that I knew it,
and it knew me.
Like twins.
What’s important here, Emma, is that it found you during a seance.
And I brought it home.
And it won’t leave until -
I’m dead.
Which is why we’re getting out of here now.
Wherever you go, it will go with you.
You have to defeat it here.
How do we do that?
I think perhaps when it realises you know what it is
it might just leave you.
You think it might?
I know, it’s not an exact science,
but I do have one suggestion
that might help you defend yourself against it. Salt!
Salt?
I’ve read in some old texts that it’s a kind of barrier against evil,
perhaps because it has some come kind of pure quality to it.
You read in old texts?
You don’t have a shred of evidence for any of this, do you?
In the Bible it says, 'You are the salt of the earth.'
Even in the Bible there are indications.
'Regard them not that are familiar spirits.'
And what about you? You who can see this evil.
Perhaps by some kind of providence,
there are those among us who are here to help us...
...to warn us.
An angel?
I prefer to think that he’s someone with a special gift.
Or curse!
In my job you tend to prefer something stronger than tea.
Do you believe any of that?
Yeah!
Wait here.
We might need some more. I’m going to go and get some.
Don’t leave me here.
You’re right. Come with me.
He’s messing with our minds.
SAM: Where is this?
I mean, there’s no walls, there’s no roof.
We’re standing on something.
Emma!
Emma, Help me!
Help me!
Please! Emma!
Give it to me.
Hope that mad woman knows what she’s talking about.
I know who you are!
TESS: What on earth’s going on?
Mum!
We have to get inside the circle.
Circle?
Ow! Mum! Mum!
You’re hurting me.
What the fuck did you do that for?
It’s Keeley!
Come on.
We’ve got to stay inside the circle.
Yeah, it doesn’t like salt.
What doesn’t?
The demon…thing!
It killed Sarah.
And now it wants Emma.
Well, it’s not getting you.
What?
Keeley!
Love you, Emma.
It’s not real.
It’s an illusion.
I know you and you know me.
I was on fire.
And the room, it...it...wasn’t here.
An hallucination. Cain’s tricks.
Let’s get you all to a hospital.
What just happened? Why’d you come back?
Because I suddenly knew that Cain wanted to take you
to whatever hell he came from.
So what does that make you?
That’s a question that’s been worrying me.
You loved the countryside so much
and I know it’s where I can be with you Sarah, but…
it’s taken these past two years for me to be able to do this.
Mum still visits your grave.
Sam is doing well.
His scars are fading faster than his surgeon expected.
All of our scars are fading
and we’ve put what happened behind us
because there’s no other direction to go but forward.
I've changed my way of thinking and...
...I meditate.
And though it’s not been easy,
you’ve always said that I was stronger than most people you knew
because I had to be,
and which is why…
I’ve finally been able to come out here on my own, ta daaaaa!
But now I believe in angels.
But not the way mum does.
You’re my angel, Sarah,
and whatever Inspector Sutton is or how he knew what he knew,
it really was you, I do believe.
And I’ve come to understand that poem that you loved so much
and which I knew you wanted to be read at your funeral but....
...you know her!
Which is why I’m going to say it for you today.
Not because you’re gone.
Because you’re here.
Do not stand at my grave and weep.
I'm not there.
I did not sleep.
I’m a thousand winds that blow.
I’m diamond glints on snow.
I am the sunlight on rippened grain.
I’m the gentle autumn rain.
When you awaken in the morning's hush
I'm the swift uplifting rush
Of quiet birds in circled flight.
I am the soft silent stars that shine at night.
Do not stand at my grave and cry.
I’m not there.
I did not die.