Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Whenever the order
for table down the federal.
That's the special lunkhead
to go, ooh, la la.
We used to make it in culinary school,
but I did my own little twist.
All right, look alive, everyone.
We have a full house tonight.
Ari, you're overcooking it.
Start over. This is the Bowery,
not a burger joint.
I like burgers, is that the special?
It looks like beef stroganoff.
It's Blanka Duvel.
Try some. No thanks.
I'll leave the fancy cuisine to you.
Brett? Just nervous, Alice.
You know, we're expecting Janice Silver
any day now. Relax, babe.
The customers are going to love it.
We sold out of my bouillabaisse
last time, remember?
Bold words from a sushi chef.
Well, I'm not going to
be a sous chef forever. Hmm.
Welcome to the Bowery.
Do you have a reservation?
No, I don't. Well,
we can put you on the waiting list.
We're running about an hour.
Your name, Janet Silver.
Actually, I have something
ready for you right now.
Isn't that nice?
Right this way, Miss Silver.
There. She's here.
Janet Silver is here. Super.
OK. This is the moment
we've been waiting for.
Janet Silver is here.
We've made a top 10 list
for the last 10 years.
And this year will be no different.
Am I being clear? Yes, chef.
All right. What did you order?
Potato bisque, swordfish, filet mignon
and the special. The special.
All right, everyone.
Let's get to it.
Potato leek soup.
He grilled swordfish.
He filet mignon and a special.
Oh, I was surprised to see
that you have at DVO on the menu.
Usually you're so predictable.
Enjoy. So far, so good.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So are you all right?
Oh, boy, it is this one moment.
What's in the blockhead to vote, Bill?
Onions, garlic, carrot, egg,
clarified butter, shanté,
parsley, thyme, parsley, parsley,
cardamom. Whip, now
janissaries electric.
Parsley, every seven new knows that.
Not every chef. I'm sorry,
but how was I supposed to know
about the parsley?
Least she'll be all right. Right.
Stick to the menu from now on out.
It's going to pass us big time
and it still might.
We're definitely
not going to make our top two this time.
I'm sorry. There is nothing
actually wrong with the dish.
I'm sticking around here for a while,
so maybe you should take off.
I want you to miss your train.
Good night. Hey, hey, Christine.
We're so excited for your new concept.
You tell me what drew you to the space.
I love the open kitchen layout gives
the customer a true culinary experience.
No, I don't have an opening date yet.
I'm still looking for a chef,
but I got to runner.
So she, like Danielle, is waiting for you.
Good morning, Marta.
Christian, good morning,
Daniela. Good morning.
You want something to eat?
No thanks. Oh, 70
at 10:00 a.m., you have a conference call
about the design
of the new hotel in Charleston.
Then lunch with the governor at 12 30,
followed by a 4:00 p.m.
tour of the new wing of the Children's
Hospital and a 7:00 p.m.
dinner with the Association
of Female Business Owners.
Can we push dinner back?
I've been emailing with the director of
the hospital, and I want to stick around
after the tour to discuss
additional fundraising strategies, OK? OK.
Unless my charming
nephew would attend for me.
Heaven knows he could use an evening out
with some strong, intelligent women.
What you could at least act interested.
You know, it's one of the many skills
you'll find handy when you're in my shoes.
I'm interested. I promise.
Maybe you'll find the next topic
a little more captivating.
The annual fundraiser for the St.
Andrews Children's Hospital is coming up.
We attend a fundraiser
every other weekend, Moynat.
Yes, but we're hosting this one.
And it's a cooking competition.
The theme is Farm to Fork.
I like it. It's cute.
It was Marty's idea.
We still haven't
settled on the judges yet.
Maybe our resident Garamond
could make a suggestion.
We could get Duncan
Rames, that British Ebola. Absolutely not.
This is a charity event. It's
not one of his reality shows.
All the best chefs
have the most difficult personalities.
Why have we under season
a dish at the Academy?
Chef Baumgarten would feed it to his
master and make us watch this one time.
Alice Toxify? Yes. Alice Meyers.
Hmm. Well, in any case, Martta,
I will be selecting our judges.
OK, your conference call is in 20 minutes.
OK, I'm going to confirm every word
for you. Thank you, Marta.
Christian, what's wrong?
You've been distracted lately.
Sorry, I didn't mean to be here.
I know the prospect of taken over
the family business can be quite
overwhelming. I felt the same way
when I took over from my husband.
But now, short, 20 years later.
I can't think of any path more fulfilling.
Thanks, Daniel. How would you like to be
one of our judges?
I'm not qualified. Of course you are.
You may not work in the kitchen,
but you are a chef.
You've got the diploma to prove it.
That's very kind, but you want judges
with big personalities for the fundraiser.
That's why people watch those shows.
Is that why they watch them?
I never knew why.
Well, offer still stands.
Think about it, will you?
I will. What's got into you, Chef?
I just came from a meeting.
Guess who's catering
this year's Gotham gala?
The Gotham Gala is in the biggest party
in New York City.
That's the one red carpet celebrities.
And now the Bowery.
This came for you, Alice.
That isn't the Jay Leno week.
Their first choice canceled.
We're the runner ups.
But after the Jenna Silver incident,
we need this one.
Alice, are you listening?
I've just been invited to judge
a cooking competition.
What do you miss, Myers?
You are cordially invited
to serve on the judges panel for the St.
Andrews Children's
Hospital Charity Cookoff.
This event will bring together
esteemed chefs from around the world
for a weekend in Kansas City.
I look forward to you being my guest.
Please respond before October 1st.
Daniela Billups, the hotel
magnate and philanthropist, apparently.
Wow, it's in Kansas City and a week
and they are paying for everything.
I recognize your talent.
That's why I want you working
with me at the gala.
This will be great recognition
for both of us, for you.
Look, I don't want to argue with you.
You can stay here with me
and cook for the stars,
or you can watch
some old washed up chefs cook.
It's your choice.
Blackcurrant plum.
Give me a little, OK? Nice Tannin's.
What do you guys think?
Tastes like red wine? Very astute.
We're not here to talk about the wine.
We want to talk about you
and the cooking competition.
You have to go. I don't know.
Bret really wants me
to work with him at this gala.
It's a big deal for him.
But Brett's too busy thinking about bread
to think about what's best for you.
How long did it take him
to let you try out that special?
Then he turns around and pulls it off
the menu after one tiny accident.
Well, in his defense,
I did send a food critic to the hospital.
She's fine. That's not the point.
He's the head chef.
He should have seen the parsley
before the dish even went out.
He dropped the ball, not you.
Maybe it's OK to have your own dreams.
I don't get it. A
lot of people would kill for my job
and my boyfriend.
Why am I not happier?
It's a great restaurant, but
maybe it's not great for you.
Well, then. Here's
to Dreams, to dreams.
I think the prime. I'm feeding my.
So close that I can touch.
I'm thinking. I'm Alice Myers,
welcome to Kansas City.
If you. Everything of.
This is our power and light district.
Just a short walk
from your hotel. Hotel Phillips.
You sure this is where I'm staying?
Yes. I think that'll be fine.
Checking it. Yes. Welcome.
We're glad to have you stand with us.
Could I have your name, Alice Myers?
It might be. And I see
you're one of the judges for the cookoff.
Miss Phillips has made some
very special arrangements for your stay.
This might be a silly question,
but does Miss Phillips own this hotel?
Yes, she does. This hotel was the first
built by the Phillips Group in the 1930s,
and now they have luxury hotels
all over the world
San Francisco, Paris, Tokyo, Zurich.
Everything is taken care of.
You're on the fifth floor.
Elevators are to your left.
If things will be brought to your room.
And if there's anything I can do for you,
do in your state, please let me know.
And I will. Thank you.
This is amazing.
Do you mind? Not at all.
Thanks. If you want to see a great view,
you don't have to do.
I well, thank you.
Have a nice day with you, too.
Please join us for a meet and greet
this evening, 7:00 p.m..
Lisa Whiteley's. Yeah.
Some mean great losers,
nothing Switalski this weekend, huh?
Alice Christian.
You must be this Myres Alice.
Let me introduce you to Christian.
This is Daniel's nephew.
He'll be a judge this weekend.
We know each other
more than a small world. Really small.
I'll leave you two
to get reacquainted thingee.
Daniela's nephew,
Daniella Phillips. That's the one.
Why don't you tell me?
Yes, it never came up, never came up.
How long were we together back then?
And Danielle and I don't
particularly close friends,
but being part of the Phillips family,
it's not the sort of thing we talk about.
People look at you
differently, like, you know,
I'm sorry. I'm just surprised is all.
So that's why I'm here, because of you.
Believe me, I had nothing to do with this.
I mean, surprised as you.
So what are you doing now?
I'm Daniela's apprentice.
You're not a chef. Don't tell me.
After my parents
passed, Antonello took me under her wing.
She doesn't have any children
of her own, so Yaroun,
she runs the hotel business and spearheads
a million charity events. And I help
you live here, mostly based here,
but it involves a lot of traveling.
Sounds like a dream job.
What about you? You must be doing
very well for yourself.
One of the esteemed judges
of the competition.
I am a sous chef in New York.
A sous chef. Here we go.
Oh, I mean, that's great.
Go on. You can say.
I'm just surprised. That's all.
But I can't say anything.
I'm purely out of nepotism.
Well, I don't know about now.
But you were a great chef in school.
That's pretty nice.
There was a long time ago.
It won't be weird
us together as judges right
now with me. Me neither.
That is all ancient history.
I should mingle with the other guests.
That's certainly.
Yeah, definitely.
It seems like everyone
is enjoying the party.
Christian, you are.
Have you met Governor Dumont? Yes.
Nice to see you, Governor.
I believe we're still overdue
for a round of golf.
Your club or mine?
Let's set it up.
We will. Can I steal my hand for a moment?
I just need to have a quick word
in private. By all means.
What's so pressing,
you put a sous chef on the judges panel.
You must be referring to Alice
Myers. That's the one.
She's an up and coming
young chef, very talented.
She is a sushi. She's been working
at a top tier restaurant in New York
since she graduated from that
very prestigious Swiss culinary school.
You might have heard of it.
I can't believe you did this. Did what?
Wasn't she a friend of yours
who you still talk about?
And I didn't think you'd mind
seeing an old friend.
You don't have a problem
with that, do you?
I don't have a good because you too
will be working a lot together
then yellow fields,
businesswoman, philanthropist,
matchmaker, maybe. Oh, thank you.
Are you kidding me? I know, right?
It's just like reality TV.
Seriously. We're so proud of you, Ellen.
Well, I'm here because of you guys.
I'll bring you a souvenir. Oh,
how about one of those bathrobes?
So the other thing is,
I ran into an old friend
here. Oh, Christian.
Wait, wait. The guy from Switzerland.
What's he doing there?
How does he look?
Turns out he's Danniella Philip's nephew.
He is one of the judges, too.
Wait, wait a minute.
So he's like super wealthy.
You're dating a millionaire.
Well, he wasn't rich then.
He didn't act like it.
Just Googled him.
Yeah. Dude is loaded. OK,
so he's rich and good looking.
Now I'm really jealous.
I'm with Brett. Remember?
Oh, got to go. That's Brett,
speak of the devil, text us by five.
Hi, I wasn't sure I'd hear from you.
Yeah, it's kind of a madhouse here.
How are things with you?
I'm sorry. I can't be there to help.
I wish I could be two places at once.
Me, too. I'm sure they'll be fine.
You're just stressed.
You just see the menu I put together.
Nothing fancy, but I think the guests
are going to dig it.
That's great. We've had this organic
beef farm upstate.
You should see these cuts
being some of the best I've ever.
Hey, hey, watch that flame over there.
Where was I? Hey, I
have to go. Actually, I'm really tired.
Talk soon, though. Oh, OK. Later.
Good afternoon. I'm Daniela Phillips.
And I'd like to welcome you to the St.
Andrews Children's
Hospital Charity Cookoff.
Most importantly,
I want to thank all of you
for your very generous and kind donations.
Now to get things started.
Let's meet our judges.
Tony Mitchell, Tony has been a food writer
for over two decades.
She has written for Gourmet and Food
and wine magazines.
And her most recent book,
Toni Appetite, is on The New York Times
bestseller list.
Alice Myers is a sous chef at the Bowery,
one of Manhattan's finest restaurants.
She is also a graduate of the prestigious
McAdams EastWest Desert Culinary.
And last but not least of our judges
is my dear nephew Christian Graham,
a globe trotting gourmand
and also a graduate of the Academy.
And let me introduce to you our chefs,
Chef Leigh, Chef Martinez.
And Chef Rafaelle.
So, chefs, you have come
from all around the world.
Thank you for your first challenge.
I'd like for you to prepare an appetizer.
From your hometown.
And 60 Minutes. Ready, chefs ready.
All right. On your mark, get set, cook.
One having flashbacks.
Contract infusion.
Good cooking isn't a race,
but you have to move fast.
Five more minutes.
Time's up, chefs,
now our judges will go to work
to decide the winner. Chef Lee.
I'm from Taiwan,
and these are Xinjiang lamp's Uighurs
season would kuman chili flakes,
Sichuan peppercorn
and fennel. Spice is nice.
The great combination of flavors.
I agree it's bold
but not overpowering. Nice work.
And it finishes very nice. Good job.
I live in Los Angeles,
but originally I'm from El Salvador.
So this is my version of pupusa,
a traditional appetizer.
It is the national dish of El Salvador.
And we celebrate it every year, annually
on the second Sunday of November.
Please enjoy. 1813
voted for my native France, but Nepeta.
Judges have you reach a decision,
the authentic flavors really stood out.
The winner of today's competition.
The Shepley. Hey, congratulations, chef.
So winning this round, Chef Lee has earned
you 100 points. Well done.
The next round is worth 200 points.
And the final round
will be worth 300 chefs.
It's anybody's game. Our next challenge.
You have 24 hours
to create an entree of your choosing.
But there's one catch farm to fork.
You can only use ingredients from our
local farm. Are you ready?
The challenge begins.
Great meeting you.
If they put that together in an hour.
I can't wait to see
what they come up with tomorrow.
You just love to eat.
It doesn't matter what it is.
Okay, Mr. Pretentious,
how did we ever agree on the lamb skewers?
You know, so little
surprised myself. Are you ready?
What you're going
with the chefs to the farm in case
they have questions about the rules.
Is that really necessary?
Oh, come on, it'll be fun. Splendid.
You can ride on the bus with the chefs
if you want the bus
else you want to ride with
me. Hmm. Depends.
What are you driving these days?
I guess something fast, shiny and foreign.
I miss the fresh air.
It's not exactly New York.
He chefs, let's get a photo.
I love markets, everything's
just so fresh. Oh, my gosh.
I just smelled something so wonderful.
I'm going to go follow my nose
and I'll catch up with you both later.
Oh, I guess we don't have to stay
with the chef. Adobe fine.
Where are you going?
You'll see. Hi, Christine. Hey.
Well, looks good.
What just came out of the oven Christmas?
They smell amazing.
I want those who live for please.
Wait till you taste them.
They made with European butter
and a Wild East starter.
This kind of reminds me of our trip
to move on, the water was like glass.
It was beautiful. Yeah, but what was that
name of the little shop
we went to back then? Canini Dorce.
That's right. Here we go.
Thank you. Enjoy that.
Not yet, but some place on
shore, are you OK?
So you own a farm, too?
Well, mine. It's a family farm,
almost reminds me of Switzerland,
though I do believe
the Alps are just a tiny bit bigger.
Well, I mean, this
and spending time with you
and all it took was a free trip.
Well, can't all be jet setters.
You know, as you recall, I'm
from Long Island and not the ritzy part.
I worked my tail off since graduation.
Since since you got the job
as a prep cook, the Bernadine, I remember
you were jumping and screaming
all over the place when you found out.
And we all wanted
to lock you in the freezer.
Right. Sorry about that.
We were jealous. You deserved it.
And you made your own way.
I respect that. Really? You mean that?
I left a lot of things unsaid
when we were together.
And I'm sorry. And the way things ended.
I really do handle it that well.
It was a long time ago.
You don't have to say anything. I want to.
I was supposed to join you
in New York, but I didn't.
You were going through a lot
with your parents death.
I just wanted to be there for you.
I know you did. It was a dark time
and I shut you out.
You deserve better than that.
I understood. Really? It's OK.
Oh, I'm in a real mess of things.
But everything worked out for the best.
You're taking over for your aunt.
I'm number two at one of the
best restaurants in New York.
I couldn't be happier. It's.
I don't know what I was thinking,
letting you go. Whoa!
I guess we've worn out our welcome
back to the car.
Daniela, relax Sheff's
I'm not here in any official capacity
and just merely feeling a little peckish.
It would be an honor
to serve you something.
Oh, that's quite all right. Thank you.
Just pretend I'm not here.
Squint to read the refrigerator.
Oh. That's perfect.
Do you mind if I use this?
Do you mind terribly as Chef
Rafael Natatorium?
No, I quite enjoyed your dish today.
I have spent plenty of time in France,
and I must say your tartine
was delicious. Merci.
In my humble opinion, uniform chic.
I might stumbly disagree,
but I must admit I was quite
surprised by the level of competition
you brought together,
but not unpleasantly.
What do you mean?
I love surprises,
combining new ingredients,
improvising a mere Adobe
cooking my whole life.
But I am yet a student.
There's always something new to learn.
You're very insightful.
A side effect of spending most of my life
at my cutting board.
Plenty of time to think.
Speaking of which, may I?
Oh, by all means. Please do.
I'm frightful in the kitchen.
I disagree with Tissier.
I think there's a smooth.
After a few calls,
well, a few dozen.
I was able to book
you back to back meetings
while you're in San Francisco next week.
You're an angel, Marda.
That's your revised itinerary.
As much as I love a full schedule.
I am so looking forward to retirement.
No second thoughts.
I think Christian is about
as ready as I'll ever be
to take over the Phillipsburg, but
I do love my job,
but I am so ready to do
all the things that I just.
Yeah, I'm going to
sound like a foolish old woman,
but I'd really like to find love again
before it's too late.
You are not old,
you're not foolish. Not at all.
One more minute, chef.
Ten seconds left.
Shefali, this is Shway
show you or Szechwan boiled fish?
I've made it with a fresh catfish
from a local lake catfish.
Interesting choice.
Chef Martinez, this is my
take on off the Google,
a specialty of Lombards cuisine.
The volcano cut lamb shank
braised in a red wine vegetable sauce
on top of a Parmesan risotto. OK.
Not about osso buco. I agree.
The sauce is a bit thin.
It's supposed to be a hearty dish.
I'm sorry, but any Italian grandmother
can make it better.
Who's pretentious now?
And Chef Raphael.
This is Gasolina for volson.
Unfortunately, the rules did not permit me
to use to lose sausage,
but I discovered that many local options.
Daniela? So you. C. Bon appetit.
I vote Chifley as opposed
to respond so delicious.
Chef Rafael's dish was much more complex
and at least a solution.
You and I have to agree
with Alex Castellanos, one of the most
challenging dishes in all of French
cuisine. Superb.
It's four fights to.
Cheverly is hiding behind the spices
that was overcooked.
I'm standing up.
I have to agree.
OK. Well, looks like we have a winner.
The winner of today's
competition, Chef Raphael.
Congratulations to Chef Rafaelle,
who has captured the lead with 200 points,
but I have one more challenge to go.
Well, chefs, the final challenge
will be to complete
the meal that you've done so far.
My personal favorite dessert.
Now you can cook or bake
anything that you like.
The only requirement is that the recipe
must come from the heart.
All right. You've got 24 hours. Let's go.
Good luck, chefs.
Great job, thank you.
You're quite the food critic.
Oh, you're just mad, you're outnumbered.
I'm still not sure I agree with you,
but you did argue your point.
Well, you know, all this eating
is actually making me pretty hungry.
I know a place where we can go,
if you don't mind working for your food.
Sounds good to me.
This space is amazing.
Reminds me of what we used to talk about,
it looked to me.
I thought you'd like it.
Location's great, too.
You said a friend's opening this place.
Yeah. What kind of food?
He hasn't decided, really.
Once the opening?
I'm not sure yet.
Less questions. More cooking. OK, OK.
You're the pseudo.
Why believe when you mix little love
into Olive? You have.
Why? Because when you add it all.
Well, it all goes back.
Jackie Mason from Hilton.
What happens when
you take a leap of faith?
Guess we're bound to find out.
Something beautiful. Let's get down.
I forgot our funguses.
I know it's ready to happen.
There will be. Not.
Twenty. Oh, it's perfect.
Just just. Chef Rafael Re,
I thought you'd be in the kitchen working.
It may not seem like it,
but I'm actually hard at work right now.
Well, if that's hard work, then
I'd like to enroll in culinary school.
Will you join me? Sure.
I'm searching for
the perfect cheese for my dish.
Of course, in France,
we invented the cheese for the occasion.
I have been outside of my country.
I have not tried too many other kinds.
It seems pointless, but there are times
when I have been surprised.
These trees, for example, it's
not like anything we had at home.
Is. I say. Sebel.
Yeah, it's good, it's good.
Where we both have a passion
for what we do. We do.
Have you ever heard the same?
If you love what you do,
it will never work a day in life.
I just hope Christian finds that.
What do you mean?
Can you keep a secret?
I'm retired, but you are so young.
Well, I appreciate
your flattery, but I'm tired.
I'm not tired of my job,
I'm just I'm tired of only having my job.
I, too, am fanatical and it hasn't
been easy on my personal life,
but giving up my work
would be like giving up myself.
Who am I without my job?
But aren't you curious to find out?
I know who I am.
Do you? What did we make again?
So this is my take on Tyrolean food.
I fell in love with it
when we were in Austria.
You mean Innsbrook? I remember that trip.
We just met, you know,
growing up in Long Island.
I'd never seen a mountain before.
And suddenly there I was in the Alps
on skis falling all over the place.
You were delirious
and you kept making fun of me.
But you stayed on the bunny
slopes with me all day just to make sure
I got the hang of it.
I wasn't going to leave you alone.
Those were good times.
Yes, they were. Unbelievable.
This makes me feel like I'm right back in
that Özkan ski lodge.
Well, that's the idea.
I try to recreate
my experiences on the plates.
I use the flavors to convey my memories.
How do you not have
your own restaurant? I'm serious.
Running a restaurant has so little
to do with cooking.
It's all about having a mind for business
and a lot of luck.
I have a good job.
Be a huge risk going out on my own.
I know I feel there
you seem to have your future
pretty locked up.
I went to culinary school
the same as you, and I had a dream
of working in a kitchen to.
As fortunate as I am
to be in the situation.
It's not what I want.
I no idea, as I've got
a confession to make.
This is not my friend's
restaurant. It's mine.
I bought it about a year ago
from a retiring chef and.
I've just been fixing
it up, it's sort of a hobby
I've been wanting
to tell and Danniella, but
I don't want to let her down.
You know, she's she's been so good to me
and she has no one else
to take over the first group
when she retires.
Tell me about your restaurant.
Tell me tell me everything
you planned. Why?
It's not like I'm going
to open the place anyway.
It's a hypothetical question.
OK, I'll start my dream restaurant.
It's someplace where there are no food
critics or best of lists,
a place where I can cook
using only what's fresh and in season.
And there's only a few tables
in the dining room
so I can come out of the kitchen and talk
with the guests, maybe share some wine.
I live in a cozy apartment upstairs
because I never want to leave.
Now you go. OK. At my dream restaurant,
you're the chef because you cook
better than I do,
but I still want to cook
some and manage the place well ahead.
Sorry. Why am I the chef
at your restaurant?
You could have any chef in the world
in the history of Yoshihiro
Murata, Julia Child,
Edna Lewis, Thomas Keller.
And YouChoose Me. Yes.
Excuse my reach.
Delicious. Forgot how much I love cooking.
Don't you cook where you work?
I do. Not for fun.
We don't experiment with new.
Stick to standard fare. Price.
Hey, Bill, what about your restaurant?
Do you realize how perfect it is?
I wouldn't give it up.
I mean, even if you can't be the chef,
that you could hire
someone to run the daily and sneakin
whenever you feel like cooking.
That idea. Beyonce.
It's because of you that I'm here judging
the competition, it's
not some random coincidence
or my talent. Is it.
Some call it coincidence.
The point is, you're young enough
and coming chef who's very talented.
Thanks. You can't believe it's only.
I had a lovely day. To.
I thought I saw you come out here.
The bellman said
I should come check out The View.
It's beautiful. I come up here
when I need a little perspective.
From my apartment in New York
or someone else's window.
A smaller city does have its perks.
Like what? We're friending.
There's no fighting over
parking, low cost living. Less traffic.
Sounds like you're on the tourism board.
Well, we are in the
hotel business. But honestly,
I like it here. I can see why.
Do you ever see yourself living near or.
If there were. The reason?
A reason. Christian,
do would like a word with you. Excuse me.
Sit down, Christian.
Is there something wrong
we're supposed to be doing in the kitchen?
No, this will only take a minute. OK.
After the competition,
I am going to formally announce
my retirement from the Phillips Group.
Why now? Because you're ready
and because now more than ever, it's
become apparent to me that it.
I want more. Thanks so much.
This is a great honor and Daniela,
but we have a competition
to get to. Quite right.
That's not. Well,
let's go and Daniela.
Oh, Christian, don't look so nervous.
You are going to be
a great leader. I'm certain
your mom and dad would be so
proud of you. I know I am.
Was there anything else?
No, good, then, off we go.
Oh, one more thing.
I quite like your girlfriend.
Oh, she's not my girlfriend.
Hmm. Well, I like her.
She'll read as easily
daily fantasy and love.
Five more minutes.
One minute left.
I don't think about your husband.
I'm not sure your dream show is available.
I know a lot of people in New York
would love to work with you.
I'll introduce you.
I appreciate that.
All right, time's up, chefs.
Ready, judges? Shefali.
This is Steve who.
Or black sesame soup, a sweet soup
popular in southern China,
where my wife is from.
I parroted what Chinese
donuts were dipping.
Chef Martinez, this is
my take on three is cake.
It's a cake soaked in three kinds of milk,
evaporated, condensed and heavy cream.
You can find it all across Latin America,
and that is where
my heart will always be.
Well, I like the.
And Chef Rafaelle,
this is a souffle
I prepared from a surprising cheese
I found at the creamery
outside of Kansas City.
The day I tasted my first souffle,
that was the day I fell in love with
cooking. Perfect walks.
Are you. Saying that's a vast right wing.
OK, judges, have you reached a decision?
We have the winner of the dessert
challenge with one of the most
elegantly delicious executed
desserts. Chef Rafael.
This win erns chef Rafaelle,
an additional 300
points, making him
the winner of this charity cook off.
Thank you. This is truly an honor.
And of course, tomorrow night,
our judges will prepare dinner
and Chef Rafael's honor.
What was that? You got to read the letter
before you've been to being a judge.
Not the fine print, apparently
if you prepare just one of the dishes
you did last night.
Everyone will be eating
the best meal they have read.
MSG Myers, has Christian told
you the good news yet, but good news.
Go on. Tell her tomorrow night
I will be announcing my retirement.
But more importantly, I'll be announcing
that Christian is the new head
of the Phillips Group
who has such a bright future ahead of him
, don't you think, tomorrow?
Well, I must be off.
And you three have a dinner to prepare.
I catch up with you guys.
I was going to tell you myself. Congrats.
That's what you want.
Is it oh. Alice? Brett?
Whoo! Oh, well, what are you doing here?
I got on the first flight here
after the Gaylon.
I wanted to surprise you. You did?
How was it? Major success.
The Bowery is back on the map.
Have some really incredible news.
They may. Bret Porchetto,
Alice's boyfriend.
Christian Graham.
And I was just leaving.
I'll see two more.
Who's that? Old friend.
All right. There you are.
Just sign right here.
And it's official.
You'll be owner and CEO
of the Philips Group.
Now that you're in charge of everything,
I think you look a little more pleased.
I appreciate everything
you're doing for me, but. But
what is it, Alice?
You think it's a secret?
Don't be ridiculous, everyone knows.
So what if she has a boyfriend?
That's a pretty big
so what do you think? No, I don't.
Well, I've seen you two together
the past few days. And,
you know, if it's meant to be, then
no job or amount of money
to to change the fact
that she's living a life in New York,
a good life, a life without me.
Have you told her how you feel about her?
I'm pretty sure she knows.
Well, I'm no expert in love,
but in any business
deal, you always
state your intentions clearly
or you will never get what you want.
Oh, there you are, chef,
I've been looking all over for you.
What is it? I was just hoping you
might join me for a celebratory beverage.
You're aware that we employ
a small army of dishwashers here, chef.
I requested the dishwasher leave me be.
I don't trust anyone
with my cooking utensils.
Chef's job doesn't end
when the meal is served.
In fact, a chef's job never ends.
So is that a no on the drink?
May I join you when I finish
my task, please?
Because I have something
to celebrate as well, which is that
tomorrow night I will be announcing
my retirement from the Phillips Group.
I will finally have all the time to do
everything I've put off.
I'll travel the world.
I suppose I've already done that, but
maybe I'll find a hobby.
I've never had one of those.
Should I take up cooking?
May I speak my mind, please?
I can't understand
why you are leaving a career
that has made you suffer fulfilled.
You're good at what you do.
You have a bathroom of shows.
It material from time to time,
but what honest work does?
I want some things for my life that.
This job has just made impossible.
Love, for instance.
I took over my husband's business
after his death, and
this job has has driven away
every proper man I've met since then.
Perhaps some fault was with the man
and not the job. Excuse me.
I don't have to be familiar
with the details to know
that these were the right man for you.
They became involved
with the hardworking woman and what
hanaway, because you couldn't change.
Only a fool would have to admire
and respect your dedication
for your business, your philanthropy.
If you retire now,
you stand a chance of beating Wohlforth
when you deserve a man
who appreciates the power.
Remind me, why are we here again?
I'm making a deconstructed
apple strudel for dessert.
Don't they have grocery stores?
I want everything
as fresh as possible. Huh?
Why are you so worked on?
We're on vacation.
You're on vacation.
I'm cooking and I want this
dinner to be perfect.
Well, I have some good news
that will put you in a better mood.
The Times did a glowing review on this
after the Gailen.
The owners want to capitalize
on the publicity.
They're talking about
opening another location in Brooklyn.
That's great. They
want you to be the head chef.
You mean I'd have my own restaurant?
Mazing, I want. The idea
is that you'll serve everyone's favorites,
but with a pared down menu.
A pared down menu.
I'm still the executive chef
of the flagship restaurant,
so I have the final approval on
everything, but we'll work on it together.
Oh. You have to stick to the brand.
Steaks, potatoes and martinis.
Not any of the fancy European stuff.
It won't really be my own kitchen
if I can't make my own food.
I basically still be your sous chef.
This is a big opportunity for you.
I thought you'd be excited. I am.
I think I just have a lot on my mind,
the dinner tonight and.
And you're right.
It's a lot to digest.
I'll let you concentrate
on what you're doing
and I'll go look
at some animals or something.
Thanks. And thank
you for coming out to surprise me.
Really appreciate it.
Hey, small world.
Big world, small farm.
You've assigned quite the shopping list.
It'll all be worth it.
I've got everything under control.
Right. Hey, I'm sorry
I didn't tell you about Brett.
It just never came up.
You've got a boyfriend.
It's not a big deal. Yeah,
that's what I thought.
Why would it be no reason?
We're friends house.
Exactly. Just friends.
If you'll excuse me,
I've got some shopping to do.
I'll see you in the kitchen.
Hey, if you want to talk
about your restaurant,
I decided to sell it. Just like that.
Some dreams are just dreams.
You all let them go. Is it?
You're going to knock them
down and look good doing it.
You know, I haven't said yes, right?
I know, I know, but you will.
So what are you going to do today?
There's a museum nearby, or you could do
one of those walking tours.
Now I want to go back to the room
to answer emails, order room service.
But you're on vacation.
Yeah, you're right.
I want to watch TV.
Ha'apai, I bet. That's money.
I can't believe you still have
our school chef's coat.
I don't wear it all the time or anything.
Right. Head chef. Aren't you a.
Alice got a promotion.
Isn't that great?
Yeah. The Thari wants to open
a restaurant in Brooklyn
and its owners want me to run it. Really?
That's wonderful.
I'm really happy for you.
Yeah, of course, your own kitchen,
this is what you've been working for.
Congratulations.
Oh, that's so sweet.
Well, we got a four course meal to prep.
Let's go. Right.
All right, Tony.
You're on salad and order.
Irv's Christian.
You got the appetizer? I'll get main
and I might need a hand with dessert.
Sounds good, huh?
All right. Let's get to it.
OK, everyone likes Steak Totar.
They will love it.
What's for dessert?
Deconstructed apple strudel.
Can wait. Sounds delicious.
What do you think?
This might sound crazy,
but what about cardamom trimming?
Genius. Finished.
May I? Here, a magician.
It wasn't even my recipe.
I stole it from Chef Baumgarten.
You did not share filmgoer
would never make something like this.
He was strictly old school.
Well, it wasn't exactly his recipe,
but I used it as a jumping off point.
It's amazing. Whatever
it is, it wasn't just me.
They still make a great team.
Yes. Can I tell you something?
Guys, that's talking
more plaiting, come on,
our first course goes out in five.
What did you want to tell me?
You heard Tony all hands on deck.
Well, can I get a photo
blades of grass?
They're handling the circus
quite well, chef.
The apps I've learned a thing or two
from the ring master himself.
I used to make a huge announcement
after dessert. OK.
You don't think I should do.
Only you can do that.
And Daniela Christian,
what are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be in the kitchen?
Can I have a word?
Now, excuse me a moment.
So what's so urgent?
Being your apprentice
has been a true honor,
and I appreciate that
you think I can do what you can do.
It's your dream.
No. It's not my dream
is to own my own restaurant.
And I know that you've been preparing
for your retirement and you deserve that.
But I'm not the person
to take your place. Christian.
I don't want to say
this is a lot to take in right now.
This time, it's time to heal. Yes.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to this very special dinner
honoring Chef Rafael The Room.
Tonight's meal has been prepared
by our judges panel
Tony Mitchell, Alice Myers
and my nephew, Christian Graham.
And now I believe our first course
is about to be served.
But hello, everyone.
Tony Mitchell, many of our dishes
this evening come from France,
which, of course is Chepa Frails.
Oh, and your first course is a mushroom
tartlets made with fresh
local mushrooms. Bon appetit.
So. Our next course
is steak tartare.
For main course,
I've prepared my take on Blanket Duvel.
It's a personal favorite
and a classic of cuisine bourgeoisie.
Messy, so messy.
That please get the recipe.
This needs to be in my next cookbook.
And doing you'll get full credit.
Yes, of course. I'd be honored.
I don't know. To me,
this is a bit complicated. Excuse me.
Do you know the prep for this requires
some serious technique?
And in my opinion, it is flawless.
Unless the flavors, though,
they're complex and accessible.
Susan, look around the entire room.
Everyone's loving.
What do a bunch of rednecks
know about food? Right.
That is so rude.
And what do you know about
cooking, young man?
I am the executive chef at the Bowery
in New York City.
And I know a good man when I taste one.
Rockefeller, for instance, or
a filet mignon. Is that so?
And do you think filet
mignon is better than this?
I cannot agree with you.
And I am French.
I agree. This dish is sublime.
That was. Come on. Yes, OK. Sure.
But it meant this is a fireworks show
steak. And potatoes.
I think that's what everybody here wants.
Can I talk to you from.
Some people like steak and potatoes.
A lot of people really.
But I don't. And I am tired
of you trying to shove it down my throat.
And I don't care
if you think my food is too fancy
or complicated or European. It's my food.
And as much as I appreciate
the opportunity to run my own kitchen,
if I can't make what I love,
I don't want it.
You're making a big mistake,
Alison. I quit, Fred.
The Bowery and us.
He sure. Have it your way.
I'm sorry about that.
I didn't mean to ruin the meal.
Oh, not at all, dear.
I'm pretty certain that you made.
And if he's not going to eat his, I just.
Before we serve dessert,
I have an announcement.
Lately, I've been considering retirement
stepping down from the Phillips Group
after a long and very fulfilling career.
But after all the fun
I've had this weekend and the lessons
I've learned from Chef Rafael,
Chef Alice and Chef Christian,
I want you all to know
that Daniela Phillips is here to stay.
I love my job and I'm not going anywhere.
Why didn't you just tell me?
I wanted to make you happy.
I don't want to let you down.
Christian could never
let me down. I love you. You
changed your mind.
I came to my senses.
You know, chef, I'm going to be in Paris
for a few business meetings,
should I find myself
having a free evening,
would it be possible
to reserve a table at your restaurant?
You'll have the best seat in the house
next to the kitchen,
I hope. But, of course.
So you're not taking over the Phillips?
Just like that. Just like that.
Which means I guess
you can open up that restaurant now.
They're still going to have a chef.
Oh, that is a problem. It is.
I don't suppose you're interested.
I'll take that as a yes, that's a yes.
That might be some kind of.
Ladies. Stuff that.
Chef, now I'm going with the crab.
I believe I have a reservation
under the name at Danniella. You made it.
I'm so proud of you.
We saved you accountancy.
Good. My date will love it. Date
you've met. Actually, he just popped
into the cheese store across the way.
Those who could possibly
use your refrigerator
wait for you to how, where, when.
We'll talk about the details later.
But right now, we are famished.
All right. You think so?