Downloaded from
YTS.MX
(projector whirs)
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
- I should've never let you in here.
- You shouldn't have gotten
mixed in with those guys.
What are you afraid of?
(gun fires)
(Fay grunts)
(serene country music)
- Why'd you leave so early?
I wanted to make you breakfast.
Yeah, I know, I'll be able to
make you breakfast every day.
Yeah, no, me, I gotta go
pick up my assignment.
I'm not sure yet, but
I'm hoping it's not far.
You know, L.A. traffic
is already a nightmare.
Okay, babe, I'll see you tonight?
Love you too.
Bye.
(somber music)
(radio static buzzes)
- [Anchor] The country is in
a complete civil race war.
(police sirens wail)
(guns fire)
- Is someone shooting?
(gun fires)
(Fay screams)
God, move, move!
(tires screech)
(guns fire)
Not again.
(gun fires)
(Fay yelps)
(crashing)
(tense music)
(men grunt)
(police sirens wail)
Call me back, call me back, I need you!
(man shouts)
I'm downtown near 10th!
(grunts)
(suspenseful music)
(locks click)
Hey, hey.
I hear you, somebody in there?
Somebody?
(helicopter blades whir)
(foreboding music)
(knocking)
- [Man] Yo, bitch!
Yo, bitch, I know you in there!
I hear you!
I'm coming for your ass!
Yeah, we'll be back!
(newscaster chatters)
- What the fuck?
(people shout)
(guns fire)
- [Man] Let's go, cover your head!
- They finally did it.
- Who finally did what?
- This has been coming.
For anybody listening, watching.
This has been coming.
(helicopter blades whir)
(woman screams)
(gun fires)
- I have to see what's going on.
My car is out there.
- You know what's going on.
You were already out there.
Just getting worse.
(dial tone blares)
- [Fay] Do you have a phone I could use?
- Stopped working an hour ago.
- Well is there another way out of here?
What about that door?
- It's just storage.
This is the safest place
in the city right now.
- [Fay] What are you, some kind of artist?
- Bingo, what gave me away?
All my dirty paintbrushes?
Or my high fashion wardrobe?
- What's a white girl
doing living down here?
You slumming?
- Till my splashes of color
can actually make me money,
warehouse in the hood is
all a white girl can afford.
- We just heard a big explosion.
(guns fire)
Not more than a block
away from us.
And a gang of men, a gang of armed men
have been going back and
forth from each other.
There's been looting everywhere.
(people shout angrily)
This is Fabia Lopez, back
to you at the studio.
Let's get out of here.
(gun fires)
(static buzzes)
(foreboding music)
(car alarm blares)
- Might as well make
ourselves comfortable.
There's not much we can do.
Just ride it out.
- This is not just some
wave that will come and go.
- No, you're right.
Like all waves, there'll
be another one after this.
And another one after that.
- You don't look like a surfer.
- I'm not.
Just a student of history
and human behavior.
(ominous music)
Called some of my friends.
They should be here by now.
- Thought you said the
phone stopped working.
- It did.
I talked to him this morning.
They're coming in from out of town.
(men shout angrily)
(gun fires)
(gasps)
(melancholy music)
- We did it, Pops.
I got my badge today.
Yeah.
I know you always wanted a boy
to follow in the family legacy.
But I guess it was me, huh?
And I promise I'm gonna be
the best cop you ever saw.
(sobs)
- We should stay away
from the windows.
We don't want anyone to see us.
- No.
We can't just sit here and do nothing.
We have to do--
- What?
We have to what?
The world is on fire.
If we go out there, we'll burn with it.
- Well you might be okay with just sitting
and watching it burn, but I'm not.
- There's nothing we can do.
Who do you think you are,
some kind of wonder woman?
- No.
I'm a--
(phone rings)
Ric, where are you?
I'm okay, I'm...
I don't even know what happened.
I was leaving downtown from
work when everything happened.
Yes, yes, I'm safe right now, I'm...
I'm in a warehouse building near Central.
What's the address here?
- There's no address outside.
Just middle of the
block on 14th, red door.
- Middle of the block on 14th, red door.
I'll look out for you.
What's going on?
I can't see anything.
This is crazy.
I mean, they always said
something like this would happen,
but I never thought...
Just be safe and get
here as fast as you can.
Okay?
Okay, I love you.
(dial tone blares)
Fuck.
- I think there's somebody out there.
- What are you talking about?
- I think I see somebody,
but I'm not sure.
(police siren wails)
- It's a little girl.
- Is she alive?
- I don't know.
(helicopter blades whir)
I'm going out there.
Go to the window and look out for me.
If you see something,
you see anyone, yell out.
Can you open the door for me?
I'll be right back.
Hey.
You all right?
(booming)
(hisses) Are you hurt?
Fuck.
(gasps)
(man breathes heavily)
- I always wanted myself a black--
(gun fires)
(yelps)
(tense music)
- [Man] Now you're next.
Can't run from me!
I see, no, I'm not there!
Am I there?
I'm everywhere!
You can't hide from me, I see you!
(man screams)
You!
(tense music)
(metal clatters)
(thudding)
(man yelps)
(helicopter blades whir)
(emergency sirens wail)
- Nova, it's me!
It's me, let me in!
(knocking)
Nova!
Need you to let me in, please!
Now, now!
I know you're afraid, please.
Please.
Please, please.
- You all right, sister?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm all right.
- Good.
I saw that motherfucker
trying to go after you.
But we ain't having
that today, not no more.
We cleaning house today.
Getting rid of all those white devils.
You alone in here, sister?
- Yeah.
This is my studio.
You read a lot, that's good.
We need smart black women
to raise our children.
The white devils have been poisoning them
with lies about us.
(guns fire)
(emergency sirens wail)
- Yo, Adisa!
Yo, man.
Yo, dog, come on, man.
They coming, man, come on, bro.
They coming!
- Come with us, sister.
We ain't free yet, there's a
lot of fighting to be done.
- No.
I'm gonna stay here.
- Yo, man!
Come on!
- You can breathe now.
They're gone.
- I'm sorry.
I don't know what happened to me.
I froze.
- Forget it.
- What about the little girl?
- It wasn't real, it was a doll.
- A doll?
- Forget it.
We've got other things to worry about.
It's gonna get dark soon.
And things are probably
only gonna get a lot worse.
Come on.
(dramatic music)
(people shout)
(electricity buzzes)
Oh great.
Somebody must have cut the lines.
(phone rings)
(ominous music)
I thought you said...
- They must have fixed it.
- [Lestor] Nova. (chatters)
- Yes, but...
It's not a problem, she's...
Okay.
I'll do what you say.
Good news, friends are all right.
Just taking longer to get here.
- Pick up, pick up.
(dial tone blares)
Damn.
What do we do now?
(ominous music)
(serene country music)
- You're kidding.
- Oh my god.
- I don't feel like drinking.
- Oh, come on.
It's the end of everything
we know outside.
You and I should both be dead right now.
That's at least worth a drink.
- Okay, fine.
Give me it, you talked me into it.
- Cheers.
- [Nova] You got somewhere to be?
- Yes.
No, I...
I was going to visit my father.
He gave me this watch.
I was going to visit his
grave to tell him something.
- Your father's dead?
- Yeah.
Three years now.
When he gave me this watch, he said,
"There's always time
to do the right thing."
I try to remember that
when times get tough.
- What were you gonna tell your dad?
- What?
- You said that you were
on the way to the cemetery
to tell your father something.
What was it?
- You don't seem worried about all this.
I mean, it's like you said,
it is the end of the world.
Don't you care?
- I care.
There'll be something after all this.
- Is that what it says
in "The White Wave"?
- [Nova] What?
- The book on the table.
- It's just a book a friend gave me.
I know a lot of crazy people.
Lestor, he's got a lot of
crazy ideas about the world.
- This the same friend that's on the way?
- [Nova] Who, Lestor?
Yeah.
Him and some others.
- Some others with crazy ideas?
- You ask a lot of questions.
You a cop?
- [Fay] What's in the van?
- I don't know, cleaning supplies?
It belongs to Lestor.
That's why he's coming, to pick it up.
- Must be something pretty important
to drive through a war to pick up a van.
(heart thumps)
(tense music)
- You should've never came here.
- What's in the van, Nova?
You put something in my drink?
Why?
Why, why did you do this?
(foreboding music)
- What have we here?
She's still breathing.
Love.
Well, shit.
- Man, stay out of it--
- Come on, man, this is the time--
- Don't you fucking touch--
- Whoa, what is your problem, man?
Don't fucking touch me, don't touch me.
- You find some rope, I
want you to guys tie her up,
set her off to the side,
we'll figure out what
to do with her later.
Right now we gotta get our shit together,
cause we got somewhere to be, don't we?
- Go grab the rope, man.
He told you to get the rope, dumb.
(slow motion speech)
(ominous music)
(gasps)
(sighs)
- Baby?
What's wrong, couldn't sleep?
Must've been thinking about me, huh?
- (giggles) Shut up.
No, I...
I just had the craziest dream.
I can't even remember.
I was alone,
and I kept calling you,
but you weren't there.
- Well I'm here now.
What was it that you wanted?
- What?
- In your dream, you
said you were calling me.
All right, here I am.
What'd you want?
- I...
I can't remember.
- I got an idea.
- What?
- I was kinda planning
this for another time.
This kinda seems like the
right time, right place.
(Fay sighs)
Just a picture, I'm always
here when you need me.
In your dreams or when you're awake.
Fay, will you do me the
honor of being my wife?
(gentle music)
- Yes. (laughs)
- Yes?
- [Fay] Yes.
Yes.
- Yes?
- Yeah.
Yes.
- You gonna put it on,
or you just gonna look at it?
- I don't know. (laughs)
I don't even know.
Oh.
I love you.
- I love you.
(Fay giggles)
- Oh, god.
(gasps)
(whimpers)
(grunts) Fuck.
(groans)
(tense music)
Hello?
Okay.
Fuck, fuck.
(phone rings)
Ric, Ric?
Where are you?
I'm in trouble.
Please.
Ric.
I'm in trouble.
I'm with some bad people.
(dial tone blares)
(shouts)
(cries)
Okay.
Come on, girl.
Okay, no one can help you but you,
no one can help you but you.
Okay.
- Nova, I've been thinking
about you a lot lately,
living in that dark little cave of yours.
Having had everything taken from you,
passed off and given to
people who didn't deserve it,
who didn't earn it, who
haven't worked hard.
I've begun to think that
maybe God has a plan for you.
A good white woman with nothing.
It's my belief that God
wants us to fight back,
to fight for change.
To take it back.
- [Newscaster] All federal
buildings are on high alert,
but law enforcement resources
are spread very thin.
It's safe to say right now
that each man is for himself.
This is the known symbol of their militia.
If you see something, say something.
(foreboding music)
(dramatic music)
(metal clangs)
(chains clink)
(man moans)
- Who are you?
Are you hurt?
Okay.
All right.
(grunts)
Okay, oh my god, okay.
Okay, okay, okay, one second.
(man coughs)
(Fay grunts)
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh my god.
You're okay, you're okay, you're okay.
You're all right now, you're all right.
You're all right, you're all right.
Okay, okay, oh man.
- Where are they?
- There's no one here right
now, they're all gone.
- We can't stay here, we gotta go. (sobs)
- Okay, okay.
Can you stand?
I'll help you, help you.
Okay, on three, one, two.
(grunts) Three.
Okay, come on, okay.
(grunts)
Okay, okay.
- I can't walk!
- What happened?
- They jumped me, beat me up.
I thought they was gonna kill me.
- Who?
Who did this?
- I don't know who they are.
Skinheads, white boys.
Some guy they call Lestor.
- Lestor, what, fuck.
Okay, okay.
Stay with me, stay with me.
Hey, hey, hey, come on, stay with me.
Hey, hey.
- I don't wanna be here
when they get back.
- We can't go outside, it's not safe.
- We're not safe here.
Can we lock the door
or something?
- No, no.
No, they have a key.
That won't keep them out.
What is it, what is it?
What's in the van, what's in the van?
- Chemicals, dangerous stuff.
- My god.
- I was on my way to the plant
and dump when they jumped me.
- [Fay] Did they say what they
were gonna do with the stuff?
- No. (sobs)
But I'm pretty sure it's some crazy
let's kill a lot of black folk shit.
- Okay, okay, listen to me.
We have to stop them, okay?
- How you think we gonna do that?
I can't even walk.
- I'm a cop.
(Issac sobs)
- You a cop.
You don't even look like a cop.
- Well I just graduated from the academy,
and they still haven't
given me my assignment,
but yes, I'm a cop.
- Good for you.
Now what?
- Okay, okay, okay.
I have a gun.
It's in my car, come on.
I have to go and get it.
Hey.
Can you let me in if I come back?
Can you do that, I need yes, yes or no.
Yes, yes?
Okay, okay, good, good, good.
Lock the door, listen for me.
I'll be right back, I promise.
Okay.
(grunts)
(foreboding music)
(dog barks)
(tense music)
(gasps)
(gun fires)
(suspenseful music)
(men arguing)
(ominous music)
- [Lestor] All right.
- Now it's as if we--
- Guys, bro?
- I told you we should've
killed that black girl
before we left.
God, why did we bring this kid with us?
This ain't no time to get your nuts--
- The fuck is your problem?
- Stop, enough, all right,
both of you knock it off!
We've got bigger fish to fry.
I want you to get the driver
into the truck with the explosives,
and I want this rig ready
to go within the hour,
am I understood?
Now where the fuck fuck is my--
- Don't move!
Drop your weapons on the floor.
Do it now, or I'll shoot.
Now kick your weapons towards the walls.
- Now what?
You gonna shoot all of us?
- I'm gonna shoot you if
you don't shut the fuck up.
- Do it, you can't stop what's coming.
- Don't make me.
- Hm?
(gun fires)
(Max grunts in pain)
- Fuck.
- [Max] That bitch
almost shot my foot off!
- Yo man, she locked herself
in the van, you idiot!
- Fuck the van, what about my foot?
- All right, both of you shut up a second.
Now she's got the detonator,
and we can't arm the
explosives without it.
- Just shoot the lock off.
- Are you fucking stupid?
Do you remember what we
just loaded in there?
You blow the lock off, you
blow the whole building apart
and us with it.
- Told you this kid was a moron.
- Okay, we can't blow the lock off,
she ain't coming out on her own,
so how do we get that
black bitch out of there?
- Just get my tools.
Hey, uh, lady?
Can we talk about this a second?
- Ain't nothing to talk about.
I ain't opening that door.
- [Lestor] I think you got me
and my boys out here all wrong.
- Oh yeah, you're just a
bunch of boy scouts, right?
- (chuckles) Well, I mean, you know,
there's some materials in
there that are very dangerous,
and if you're not careful,
you're gonna get yourself hurt.
- We all might get hurt
if you don't back off.
- Okay, listen.
I'm gonna go ahead and introduce
myself proper-like now.
I am the big bad wolf,
and one way or another,
I am coming in there.
Now are you really gonna
make me huff and puff
before I blow your fucking house in!
(tense music)
(drill whirs)
Time's almost up, Miss!
We gonna do this the easy
way or the messy way?
Okay, messy way it is.
(gun fires)
Oh shit!
- It's gonna get a lot messier than that
if you come any closer.
- Are you trying to get yourself blown up,
you stupid bitch?
- If I go, we all go, you
dumb white motherfucker.
- [Nova] Leave her alone.
She's a nice person.
- Nova?
(somber music)
Is that you?
- Why did you come back?
You didn't have to.
Why did you come back?
- I can't explain it.
- You saved me.
I didn't wanna drug you.
But I had to, or they
would've killed you on sight.
- Then help me.
Do something.
- No.
She ain't gonna do shit.
She belongs to me.
- Nova.
Just tell them to back away
from the van, and I'll come out.
- Why?
What are you gonna do then?
- I'll give you what you want.
Just give me the van driver and I'll leave
if you just let me have him.
- You want a half dead driver?
You can have him, my gift to you.
I mean, he's probably not gonna
make it till morning anyway.
- We've got a deal.
Back away from the van, and I'll come out.
- Back up.
She said that she'll
come out if you back up.
(tense music)
- Nova.
You're not, you're not gonna shoot me.
You're a good person.
You may have gotten into
it with the wrong people,
but you're not like them.
No.
Put it down.
Yeah.
Okay.
- Nova.
What are you doing?
You know you can't trust them.
- Nova, don't listen to him.
- You remember what you told me?
What they did to you when
you were a little girl?
How they hurt you?
Never gonna let that
happen again, are you?
Never again.
(emergency sirens wail)
(Fay grunts)
- Okay, synced up.
- Put that in the truck.
Wrap this shit show up, people.
Wheels up in five minutes.
Dallas, gas up the truck,
I want it topped off.
- [Dallas] Got it.
- Yeah, we're good.
(timer beeps)
It's okay.
- Why are you doing this?
- I could tell you the story
about how when I was a little
kid, I got jumped every day
by a bunch of big black
kids in my neighborhood.
Or I could tell you the story
about how my dad lost his job
because the company had to
fill some bullshit quota.
No, I know the one you wanna hear.
You wanna hear the one
about how some drunk nigger
fucking ran his car into my
wife's at 80 miles an hour,
and what I had to say at her funeral.
- Is that true?
- Does it matter?
It could all be true, or none of it.
It still wouldn't change the fact
that you will never understand
this white man's burden.
Hour from now, things go boom.
- [Max] What do we do with her?
- Fuck it, throw her in the truck,
it's more body parts for the cleanup crew.
- In another life, you and
I would've had some fun
before I did this.
(Fay grunts)
(door opens)
- Whoa, whoa.
Hey, friend.
Oh, sorry, I thought you were another one
of them crazy monkeys with a gun.
- Nah, I heard the noise, man.
Needed to get out of the street.
It's crazy out there.
- Yeah.
About to get crazy here too.
Say I find myself in need of
another able-bodied individual.
I don't suppose you'd
be willing to join us?
- Looks like you're up to something big.
I like big stuff.
- Big stuff, I like that.
Well big stuff, we're
about to go get ourselves
a whole lot of money.
- What are you talking about?
- While the world is burning,
we're gonna go rob a bank.
The World Bank, in fact.
And they got enough money in there
that you can live whatever
kind of life you want.
- So you're robbing a bank
in the middle of a riot.
- Well, best time to steal shit's
when no one's looking, right? (chuckles)
We're just gonna drive down
there, blow a hole in the wall
and walk out with everything they got.
- [Max] Hey, why are you telling him?
- Because your stupid
ass went and got shot
and we need somebody else
who can drive the van.
So what do you say, big stuff?
Are you in?
Or are you out?
- I'm in.
(laughs)
- All right, let's get
this show on the road.
- This bitch is a cop.
- What?
- Fucking bitch.
He's with her.
- God damn it.
All right, I'll tell you what, big stuff.
(tense music)
I'm gonna blow your
girlfriend's pretty face off.
- Do it and you're dead.
- [Lestor] Drop your fucking gun.
- You first!
- I will shoot her!
You wanna see her brains
all over the fucking floor?
- I can't let you leave here.
- Put the fucking gun down,
you fucking nigger lover.
Put the gun down now!
(guns fire)
(Lestor grunts)
Ah, fuck.
(dramatic music)
- So much for the white wave, huh?
- I should've never let you in here.
- You shouldn't have got
mixed in with those guys.
- I still gotta sacrifice
for what I believe.
You see, it's not too
late for the revolution.
(dramatic music)
- What are you afraid of?
- If we let the monkeys out of the cage,
they'll remember how we treated them.
(gun fires)
(Fay grunts)
Okay, okay, okay.
(fan clatters)
(groans)
(timer beeps)
(tense music)
(Fay grunts)
(fan clatters)
- Hey, beautiful.
- What took you so long?
- Little bit of traffic, babe.
(Fay laughs)
Ah, fuck.
- Can you stand?
- I think so.
Help me up.
God. (groans)
(foreboding music)
(gasps)
(Fay grunts)
God.
(Ric groans)
I can't go any further.
- Okay, okay.
I'm staying with you.
(dramatic music)
I'm scared.
- I know.
Me too.
(thugs shout angrily)
(guns fire)
(Fay shouts)
(dramatic music)
(projector whirs)