# JOHANN STRAUSS II:
The Blue Danube #
(MUSIC CONTINUES, DIALOGUE MUTED)
(ROARING EXPLOSION)
(WIND WHISTLES, ENGINES WHINING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
# LESLEY GORE:
Sunshine, Lollipops and Rainbows #
(MAN HUMS ALONG WITH SONG)
(PHONE RINGS)
Huh?
(SCREAMS) Fuck!
Fuck.
Good morning, Mr Hunter.
Fuck off!
Have a nice day.
Fuck you!
WOMAN: Yeah, interesting.
MAN: Group B was really strong-
Nope!
Not today.
(INHALES AND EXHALES DEEPLY)
Come on.
(DOORS CLICK)
(DEVICE CHIRPS)
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON COMMS)
(PHONE BEEPS)
Uh...What is that?
Hey, Hunter, this just came through
ten minutes ago.
This happened ten minutes ago?
No, it came through ten minutes ago.
It seems to have happened
several hours ago.
I am so confused.
It must have been a covert op.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Uh...Agent Simmons.
OK. Am I talking to you or him?
Me.
OK, Agent Simmons, shut the fuck up.
Robinson,
what the fuck is happening?!
OK. We found this.
One of our assets in Bangkok.
(RADIO CHATTER ON VIDEO)
I don't understand.
If this happened hours ago,
why are we just getting it now?
It wasn't on our books,
or we would've been monitoring it.
(GUNSHOTS)
MAN 1: 'What the fuck is that?'
MAN 2: 'God, no!'
'We've been compromised.'
'It's the fucking Ghost!
Pull back! Pull back!'
(GUNSHOTS AND SCREAMING)
(UNDER BREATH) No.
Well, isn't that a bag of dicks?
Yeah, it's all very strange.
As I said, we've got nothing
on the books for this op,
or the Ghost they mention.
We're trying to pull-
You're joking, right?
(CHUCKLES) The Ghost?
THE Ghost?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON COMMS)
Christ. Move out of the way.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
The Ghost is a Blackhat terrorist.
He's crashed the GDP
of multiple countries,
bankrupted a dozen
Fortune 500 companies,
not to mention destroying
Yemen's oil reserves.
You remember that hack
we got hit with?
The one we don't talk about
in front of you-know-who?
Yeah, that too. And we don't
even have a reliable ID of him.
He's the bogeyman.
Completely off-grid.
Absolutely fucking impossible
to find.
This him?
What's that? What am I looking at?
The only person to leave
the warehouse alive.
See, I was able to backtrack-
No fucking way.
Get me a team
to that intersection right now.
Well, that's the thing, we-
What the fuck is it
with you today, Kyle?
Do you realise
how fucking important this is?
If I don't have this bird in hand
before Brunt hears about this,
we're all fucked!
Hello.
Brunt.
Uh... (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Hi. Um...
How... I mean, look, we-we...
The Ghost, we've got him.
I mean, we've found him-
What's "the thing"?
Sorry?
You said, "Well, that's the thing."
Well, I wanted to say
that we don't have any people
on the ground in Bangkok.
I mean, we have people,
but we don't have
those kinds of people.
What about the Bangkok team?
Uh...
You mean these guys?
'I have no visual.
I've lost comms!' (SCREAMING)
OK. Stop, stop.
'The fucking Ghost! Pull back!'
Turn it off.This is bullshit, man.
Turn it off!
Just fucking chill!
Hunter, what the hell is going on?
I promise you
I will answer that question,
but I just got here myself
and I'm as confused as you are.
Let me make something very clear.
This is not a safe fucking space.
The person in your job
doesn't get to make excuses.
He gets paid a shitload of money
to give me the answers I need
because the security of millions
of people is at stake.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Good.
All right, people,
activate the Singapore team now.
The Singapore team
is over an hour away.
That's our only option at this point.
Is it?
Uh...He's getting a taxi.
Can you track him?
If I can find the tag number,
then we can hack the car's GPS.
Do it. And you...
Yeah.
..pull up a map of his movements
since he left the warehouse.
The airport.
Shit.
Obviously.
What's the ETA on the Singapore team?
He will have slipped away
by the time they get in the country.
We need someone in Bangkok now.
We got techs, interrogators, bagmen,
but for something like this,
we have zero options.
Less than zero, actually.
(TENSE MUSIC SWELLS AND FADES)
(HORNS HONK DISTANTLY)
(INTRIGUING MUSIC)
(MAN SNORING)
Hey, motherfucker! (INHALES DEEPLY)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS) Morning, Mae.
What's shaking?
It's afternoon, you hobo.
I still need breakfast.
Coffee first.
(GRUNTS)
I'm Irish.
You're gonna die young, man.
If I die in your bar, you can
sell my organs to pay my tab.
I don't think they're worth
what they used to be.
(PHONE RINGS)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(RINGS)
BRUNT: 'Lucas, don't hang up.
I know I owe you an explanation,
but I have a developing
situation and I need your help.'
Come on, you know I wouldn't call
unless it was extremely urgent.
Are you seriously calling me
after two years
to ask for my help?
Two years, Katherine.
You know what? You're not worth it.
I am not your friend.
I am not a toy that you can
pick up and put down.
(SIGHS) 'Lucas...'
I am not your fucking patsy.
So you can take
those enormous balls of yours
and you can go fuck yourself.
'I-I understand. Hear me out.'
Fuck you and die!
Please, Lucas-(PHONE SLAMS ON BAR)
Shit! (SIGHS)
Wrong number.
(BAR PHONE RINGS)
Don't answer that!
Hello? How may I help you?
'Hi, Mae, is it?'
'Would you pass the phone to the...
roguishly handsome blonde
at the end of the bar, please?'
(MEN TALK NEARBY)
'Hello? Come on, Mae.
I know he's there.'
No.
No, no, no, no, no...
'no, no, no!'
This is the last place
I could drink in peace!
I can't...
I just can't fucking run anymore.
I'm done.
(MEN GRUNTING AND
GLASS SHATTERING OVER PHONE)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(CLAMOURING CONTINUES OVER PHONE)
Classified?
(PHONE LINE BEEPS)
Simmons?
Update.
Uh...
Ghost is about to arrive
at Bangkok International.
And the Singapore team?
Uh...About an hour out.
Fuck!
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
(EXHALES)
(PHONE RINGS)
'Oh, good, you're alive.'
I'm guessing
you'll make me regret that.
'Just name your price, then.'
I can fix this.
'Ohh! Now you can fix this?'
Yes, now I can fix this.
I can give you your life back.
'I can clear your name.
'I'm no longer bound
by the Agency's protocols.'
Then get to the point, Katherine!
I need you to get to the airport.
(LAUGHS)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
In case you forget
our not-so-recent history,
you put me
on a fucking no-fly list!
OK, OK, OK.
This is a good place to start.
You get in a taxi right now,
you head to the airport,
I will have a passport waiting
for you by the time you get there.
'Come on. Call my bluff.'
(GROANS) 'And if I did, then what?'
We're tracking a high-value target.
I need you to take them into custody
and accompany them back
to the United States alive.
As in unharmed, Lucas.
Do you understand?
Fuck!
(MOPED BUZZES PAST)
Two fucking years!
Two fucking years I've been hunted
and stuck in this fucking town!
'You snap your fingers
and just like that! Fuck!'
You have nothing to lose
and everything to gain.
You have to understand, if there was
anything I could have done-
Fuck you.
(SIGHS)
Taxi!
BKK International.
Wet wipes?
(SPEAKS IN THAI)
Are we good?
We need a cobbler working
on his passport right now.
It's already happening.
The only thing is...
his file's encrypted,
even for my clearance.
Who is this guy, Brunt?
Why is he on the no-fly list?
Well, Hunter,
if you'd been on top of things
like I hired you to be,
I wouldn't have to dumpster dive
through the fucking rejects.
Holy shit.
What?
(EXHALES)Someone on the dark web was
talking about the Ghost in Mandarin.
Luckily, I did a semester
in Shaanxi, a province in the-
Nobody gives a shit.
Get to the point.
He's going to San Francisco.
You sure?
I am.
Nice work. Get Reyes on that flight.
I'll update him now.
(JET ENGINES ROAR NEARBY)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(UNDER BREATH) This fucking guy.
(PHONE CHIMES)
(PHONE BEEPS)
Yeah, yeah.
Lucas Reyes.
Thank you.
(PHONE RINGS)
O ye of little faith.
We'll see if it gets me anywhere.
'It will.'
That text you just received is
your boarding pass
and your credentials.
'Yeah, none of which really matters
if I still have a fucking
red notice on my head, Katherine.'
I told you
everything was taken care of.
I just got you a clean passport
in less than 37 minutes.
What else do I have to do
to get you to trust me?
(SCOFFS)
Build a time machine.
Erase the past.
Your flight is about to board.
If you want what I'm offering you,
you need to be on it.
Right.
HUNTER: Is that blood?
Robinson, bring that up.
ROBINSON: I've noticed this
at several spots
along the Ghost's route.
Looks like our little friend
has been shot.
Must have got patched up somewhere.
Explains the gap in time
before heading to the airport.
Hit the street doctors.
SIMMONS: On it.
I see you.
(ANNOUNCEMENTS OVER PR IN THAI)
MAN: Passport.
Next please.
Thank you.
Passport.
(CHIMES)
(SPEAKS IN THAI)
(BEEPS)
(IN ENGLISH)
Have a safe flight, sir.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(PHONE RINGS OUT, CLICKS)
Believe me now?
What am I doing here, Katherine?
Deliver the mark to us alive,
you get your life back.
'It's that simple.'
And who is the mark?
Our latest intel
is that he's bleeding,
so he shouldn't be
too hard to find.
OK.
Any physical description?
Height, weight, anything?
My, my, you've become a needy,
little bitch during your exile.
'I swear to God, Katherine,
one more word,
I will walk right out
the fucking door.'
No, you won't. Because now you
know I can come through for you.
'And even though you have
tried to convince yourself
that you are fine drinking
yourself into an early grave,
your heart just isn't in it.'
Rest assured, as soon as we have
more intel, you will have it.
But in the meantime,
just do your best
to find the only gunshot victim
on the plane.
So you're saying
you don't have any information?
And, Lucas?
This time...
...make sure those uh...
ethics of yours...
don't intervene.
Find the target,
deliver the target.
Oh, Katherine, you are
stitching together a parachute
as we fall from the sky.
I don't know what else to say.
You don't have to forgive me,
but at some point
you're gonna have to move on.
Oh, thanks, Katie.
You always give the best advice.
WOMAN: (OVER PR) 'Mayko Airlines
flight MK7517 to San Francisco
is now ready for boarding.'
(TENSE MUSIC CRESCENDOS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hi, Marcel. Take your time.
We're all waiting for you.
Sixteen-hour flight time today,
guys.
Weather's looking pretty good,
apart from maybe the last stretch
over the North Pacific,
so just keep an eye out for that
when we get there.
Seventy percent capacity
in upstairs economy,
and 90 percent here
in downstairs economy. Yeah?
OK. Have a fantastic flight,
everybody.
And remember,
happy faces, look alive.
Yeah? Fantastic. Thank you.
(MOTOR WHIRRING)
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Here they come.
Remember, Royce.
Happy faces, look alive.
Got some new material today, then?
You know me.
(PHONE RINGS)
You guys ready up there?
Does the Pope love dresses?
(LAUGHS)
Send them up.
OK, copy that.
Happy faces, everybody.
Look alive.
Good evening, Mr O'Donnell.
Can I get a drink?Yep. Katie...
Let's get you to a seat first.
Mrs Nazareth, how are you?
Fine, thanks.
May I take your ticket?
I'll show you to your seat.Madam.
You'll be very pleased
to know you're seated
in Diamond Elite's
new Tranquillity class.
Thank you.
Your seat's just over there.
Seat 1A.
There's a bit more privacy for you.
Guys.
Guys!
This better be
some good fucking news.
Got a team tracing the Ghost's
blood trail through Bangkok.
It looks like he stopped
at a 24-hour vet clinic.
The team just got there.
OK.
Send them the ID photos
of everyone on that plane.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ROYCE: Boarding pass, sir.
Boarding pass, sir.
That's fine, sir. Thank you.
Right this way.
(LOW, RESONANT HUMMING)
(INHALES, CONTINUES HUMMING)
Nervous flier.
Champagne? Water?
Do you have anything stronger?
Orange juice?
No, thanks.
Actually, you know what?
I'll have that champagne.
(RESUMES HUMMING)
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
(UNDER BREATH) Fuck champagne.
PILOT: 'Cabin crew, prepare doors
for departure and cross check.'
Seat belts, please. Arigato.
Trays up. Danke.
Electronics off. Gracias.
'Good evening, ladies and gentlemen
and welcome aboard
this double decker A380.
This is your pilot speaking,
welcoming all passengers
in our first,
business and economy cabins
to flight MK7517 to San Francisco.
Cabin crew, prepare for take-off.'
(ENGINES ROAR DISTANTLY)
(EXHALES)
WOMAN: 'As I said,
my shift started this morning.'
BRUNT: She's lying. Her phone
hasn't left the office in 24 hours.
'But let's look
at last night's patients.'
Hunter. Brunt.
We have uncovered
some new intel and it's, uh...
..sensitive information.
My office.
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS) So, what have you got?
We were trying to understand
why anyone would be posting
this itinerary in the places
we were finding it.
The Ghost has a bounty
of up to ten million dollars.
If someone had that info,
why not keep it to themselves, right?
Yes. And?
We can't trace the source,
but we have traced where
it's gone since posting and...
it's bad.
(CLICKS KEY)
What am I looking at,
the fucking Matrix?
What is happening?
In the short time it went online,
even buried as deep as it was,
it went around the world 30 times.
There isn't a country
in the Western hemisphere
that doesn't have a bounty
on the Ghost's head.
Not to mention all the criminals
and oligarchs he's stolen from.
Are you telling me
that plane is full of killers?
Exactly.
You don't need me
to alert the FAA or...?
Mm.
Stay calm.
Stay focused.
Nobody on that plane
knows what the Ghost looks like.
We need to figure out his identity
before anybody else,
and get that intel to Reyes ASAP.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Excuse me, Agent.
MAN: (ON RADIO) 'Yes, ma'am.'
Start torturing the vet, please.
'Copy that, ma'am.'
Thank you.
'You're welcome, ma'am.'
(BEEPS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Rough night?
Something like that.
I feel you, brother.
I've been there.
You know what they say?
The darkness is always strongest
just before the stars are crushed
by the morning sun.
Huh?
I was born Cayetano Montoya.
But that was just a toxic label
others used to smother me.
But I broke free.
Now I'm Cayenne.
And Cayenne knows that
if you don't chase your dreams,
other people's dreams
will chase you.
Stay positive, my friend.
Don't worry.
And everything will become clear.
I gotta...
Yeah.
(SEATBELT CLICKS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(WOMAN CHUCKLES)
This? Come on, like...
Oh, my God, you don't know it.
(CHUCKLES)
OK, I gotta go.
Enjoy.
(CHUCKLES) Thank you.
Fuck champagne, yes?
I need your help with some
very serious business.
Serious business?
I just finished the choreography
of my new show,
but I just can't decide
the final move.
OK.
Hmm.
You mind if I show you?
Please do.
(SINGING IN SPANISH)
# Yo quiero que te sientas como yo #
Hm.
Mm-hm.
See?
I see.
Which one?
Can't you do both?
That's the positivity
I'm talking about.
Yeah.
UNDER BREATH:
# Yo quiero que te sientas... #
Yes! Let's drink.
(SCOFFS)
Whoo!
(EXHALES)
Yes, yes, it work.
Nice. Thank you. Thank you, man.
Uno no hay ninguno.
Fuck. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(LOUD THUD)
Ow.
(GLASS SHATTERS, PASSENGERS GASP)
Whoa, whoa. I got it.
It's OK, it's OK,
it's OK, it's OK.
Hey, my friend, you look a bit pale.
Let's sit you down. Here.
(GROANS)
Why are you not sleeping?
What the fuck
did you put in my drink?
I gave you enough xylazine
to put down a horse.
(LAUGHS)
I guess you can't pickle a pickle.
I guess that's your bad luck.
(GRUNTING, GROANS)
You think you're gonna take
my bounty? Cayenne's ten million?
What bounty?
Whoo!
(SCOFFS) You're funny.
You're a funny guy.
(GROANS)
"What bounty?"
The bounty
that is gonna make me a star.
(TENSE MUSIC BUILDS)
(GRUNTS, BREATHES RAGGEDLY)
Too bad you're not gonna
be around to see it.
(YELLS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(CERAMIC CLANK)
Argh!
(GRUNTS) Please...
stop...
hitting me!
(GROANS) Fuck...
(GRUNTS)
Goddamn it, fucker!
At first I thought
that you might be the Ghost.
(PANTS)
(GRUNTS) But look at you, man.
(GRUNTS)
OK.
Night-night.(GROANS)
(SPLUTTERS)
(SINGS 'ROCK-A-BYE BABY' IN SPANISH)
(CRIES OUT)
(CRASH, FLESHY SQUELCH)
(PANTS)
Oh, fuck...
(EXHALES)
(PANTING)
(PHONE CLICKING)
(PHONE CHIRPS)
HUNTER: What the fuck is this?
That's where we found Reyes
last night.
Where we found him?
Exactly who is this guy, Brunt?
We need to call his last handler.
Handler? He's disavowed,
it's a waste of time.
Is it? I'm not sitting in front
of a Congressional hearing
cos we forgot to vet some merc,
burnt-out contractor or whatever-
(CLEARS THROAT) Secret Service.
What?
He wasn't a merc,
he was Secret Service.
Seriously?
The guy who did that?
What the fuck landed him in
that shithole in the first place?
(PHONE CHIMES)
Believe it or not...
..a conscience.
(PHONE BEEPS)
Oh, shit.
(SIGHS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(GROANS)
(GROANS, PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
(RETCHES)
(JET ENGINES ROAR)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(DEVICE BEEPS SOFTLY)
(PHONE CHIMES)
(KNOCKS ON DOOR) Hello?
Sir?
(STRAINING) Shit.
Please open the door.
(MUFFLED GRUNT)
(MUFFLED CLATTER)
One second! (GRUNTS)
(GROANS WITH EFFORT)
Do you need medical assistance?
Come on. (GRUNTS)
Sir?
(GRUNTING)
As a matter of protocol,
I'm demanding you open the door.
(PHONE BEEPS)
Just a minute!
(FOOTSTEPS SQUELCH)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
I'm a sky marshal, open the door.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(SOFTLY) FFFFuck.
(PHONE CLICKS)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I've been airsick.
Sir, for the safety
of all passengers,
I'm going to need to ask you
a couple questions.
Are you currently on narcotics?
Is he really a sky marshal?
You can vouch for him?
Excuse me?
Oh, my God. Is that blood dripping
from the ceiling?
(GUN COCKS)
(GASPS)
(CRASHES ONTO FLOOR)
Inside, both of you.
(WHIMPERS)
Oh, God.
(GLASS CRACKS UNDERFOOT)
Oh, my God.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(INHALES SLOWLY)
(SOFT, GRIPPING MUSIC)
I don't wanna have to use these.
(BOTH WHIMPER)
What do you want?
Uh... (SUCKS AIR IN)
Your help.
With what?
He's gonna kill us.
He's actually gonna kill us.
He's a bloody maniac in pink.
Stay calm.
Relax, OK? Just...
try to relax, calm down, OK?
There's another sky marshal on board.
He'll come looking for us.
(GASPS)
What the fuck?!
Exactly. Listen,
what I'm about to tell you guys
is gonna sound absolutely crazy,
but you're gonna have
to trust me.OK?
Why should we?
I didn't kill him.
Well, him, I had to kill.
He made me. (INHALES)
He made you?
Mm.
Who are you?!
I'm FBI.
(MOUTHS) FBI?
I...Identification?
(SIGHS)
Department of Justice
to Attache to Thailand.
Agent Lucas Daniel Reyes.
Officer number 808.
Sorry, but do you have a badge?
I don't have time for this shit!
This is the situation that you,
me and everyone else on board
suddenly find ourselves in.
Wait.
What?
I-I don't understand.
You're looking for someone
that's on this plane?
Yep.
And other people are looking too?
Uh-uh. (SIGHS)
To kill him?
Right.
That's just lovely, isn't it?
We need to tell the pilots.
Yes! Do that.
And find the other sky marshal.
Get me the manifest, all right?
And maybe...
put a sign on the door?
Let's go. No, wait!
Can you find me something
to change into?
Hm.
Hmm.
(SIGHS)
All good?
Doesn't quite fit, but...
You're making it work.
Can you guys do something with this?
(BOTH GASP)What the fuck?!
For crying out loud!
I don't have a place to put it,
do I?
You cannot just walk round
this plane with a gun!
No shit. That's why I asked you
to do something with it.
What if...What if it goes off?
It won't, the safety's on.
The what?
That the manifest?
Yeah.
Oh, good. It's Ambien time.
Most people will be going to sleep.
We'll start with the
people that haven't.
Mm...
You guys speak to the pilots?
No, not yet.
Go do that.
We'll start with this cabin.
We'll circle anyone who looks...
dubious. Yeah?
(SCOFFS SOFTLY)
Let's go.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no...
What? What?
36D, they asked for
some peppermint tea 15 minutes ago.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I'm sorry,
but I'm trying to do a job as well.
Hey, hey, hey!
Stop being such a little pusswah.
You don't understand.
I have extreme OCD
with these kind of things.
You know what?
Would you rather I knocked you out
and zip-tied you to the sky marshal?
Could I get the tea first?
Fine.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Yes, rear galley. Lower deck.
Get here right now.
What's up?
I found these in the bin.
Where does this go?
Down to the cargo hold.
(PANTS) What happened?
I need to go down to the cargo hold.
My God, is this blood?
Is there another way down,
or do I have to slide?
There is a way, but I don't know
if I'm the best person to...
I'll take you.
Right.
Yeah, you guys go ahead,
and I'll just...
keep an eye on things here.
That's him. That's the sky marshal.
(SOFTLY) Fuck.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
I don't understand.
How is this possible?
Who is this guy
that you're looking for?
Are you hot?
What?
You're sweating.
That's a cold sweat.
It's your immune system fighting.
I used to do that too,
touch all the places I was wounded.
And I've been shot, stabbed,
burned, run over, you name it.
Gotta hand it to you. Flight
attendant's a pretty good cover.
Cover? This is my job.
Lift up your shirt.
Fuck you.
(LAUGHS) Goddamn it, man.
Everybody thinks
the Ghost is a middle-aged man.
And the Ghost is a what?
Like, what are you, 16?
The Ghost is a 16-year-old girl!
(LAUGHS)
You're crazy.
I-I can't even engage with this.
I've got a job to do.
Look out!
No!
(GUNSHOT)
What the hell are you thinking?
You could blow the fuselage
and get us all killed.
Only if you miss.
There you are.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
You're bleeding.
I had an appendectomy.
(LAUGHS) Yeah, with a bullet.
You do realise that there are
dozens of people on the plane
looking to kill you, right?
And I'm the only person
that needs you alive.
No-one else knows who I am.
Is that how you wanna play it?
It took me 15 minutes
to figure out who you are.
It's a pretty long fucking flight.
Who hired you?
You're clearly not FBI.
I mean, look at you.
You're not even sober.
Getting way closer
than I'd like to be.
Look, I don't need your help.
I can take care of myself.
You don't get it.
There is no scenario
in which I do not hand you in
at the end of this flight.
That's cute.
But you do know I can't just
disappear for ten hours, right?
People will come looking for me.
We have security protocols.
Did you not think
any of this through?
Goddamn it.
What?
This is gonna be
so fucking annoying.
You mean I'm gonna be annoying?
Yeah.
Well, you're right.
Listen...
Isha the Ghost, here's the plan.
You'll stick with me and keep
your head down while I protect you
and we figure out
who we're up against. You got it?
No.
You got a better idea?
Yeah, I do. I've got lots, actually.
And they all have
one thing in common.
They don't include you.
They don't include me. Mm-hm.
Yeah, unfortunately
none of those are gonna work
because you're in my custody now.
Like I said...
you need me out there
doing flight-attendant shit,
else I draw suspicion and risk
the hitters figuring out who I am
and getting myself killed.
Which apparently you can't have
because you need me alive.
Need. Why?
Doesn't matter.
Money?
Yeah, that's right.
No.
It's something more fundamental.
I smell desperation.
Oh...really?
Because I only smell condescension
and entitlement,
with a heavy waft of arrogance
that's gonna get us both killed.
Fine.
Well, I obviously don't trust you...
(SIGHS)
..but I guess this is
the best option.
For now.
Fine. Shall we go talk to
the pilots?
(COOL MUSIC)
And don't call me Isha the Ghost.
What do you want me to call you?
Casper?
And I'm 25, arsehole.
Of course you are.
What?
(SIGHS)
You're not gonna find
a chapter on this in there.
So what are we supposed to do?
You keep this door locked
until we land.
Don't open it for anyone but me.
What about the flight crew?
Only me.
And you don't know
which passenger they're looking for?
How long until we land?
Eight hours.
(SIGHS)
Right, call it in.
(BUTTONS CLICK, STATIC CRACKLES)
The channel's static.
Reboot it.
All right.
You know, this might not
be all bad for us.
Sully?
Ding-ding.
Guy lands a tiny plane
on the Hudson. Guy gets a book deal.
(SCOFFS) And a movie.
Hanks.
Yeah, Hanks.
(BUTTONS CLICKING)
Love Hanks.
He's all right.
What's shaking, Royce?
Royce?
Are you OK?
OK?
(LIQUID GLUGGING)
Yeah. Yeah, no, I'm absolutely fine.
Absolutely fine.
Aside from the fact that
we're 40,000 feet up in the air
with a plane full of hidden...
assassins.
A girl with a peanut allergy
asked me for an apple juice.
I thought she was gonna
claw my eyes out.
Hey. You've got this.
We're gonna be OK.
I've got your back.
This...is our safe space.
Safe space.
I'm gonna go upstairs
and check out first class.
(SOFTLY) It's our safe space.
It's our safe space.
It is. It's a safe space.
Uh...8J needs a coffee.
27D needs a blanket.
And 9G needs something.
He needs a... What was it?
I can't remember what it was.
Oh, my God. It was a...
I'll get the coffee for 8J.
Uh...You get the juice.
Right.
Yeah, I'll uh...
I'll get the juice.
Deep breaths.
Yeah, deep breaths.
We've got this.
Right.
What's the worst
that could happen, eh? (SIGHS)
Coffee for you, sir?
Mm-hm.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
SENIOR ATTENDANT: It's made from
lavender and seal blubber,
actually, which is a bit naughty.
It sounds a bit odd,
but it is lovely on the skin.
You just rub it
in a sort of clockwise motion.
(MOUTHS)
So just take your time.
That's for you to enjoy.
Can I get you anything else?
WOMAN: Hmm...
If there's anything else
that I can do for you,
please do let me know.
Maybe some champagne?
Thank you ever so much.
I need the manifest.
Isha's called,
I know exactly who you are,
but we both have a job to do, OK?
Now these people have paid a lot
of money for first-class service
and I cannot have them disturbed.
They're Diamond Elite.
Oh.
They're notorious
for giving bad reviews.
I don't need that.
Not now. Not ever.
Garrett?
Yes.
I'm only gonna ask you
this nicely once.
Could you please give me
the manifest?
(GRUNTING)
# ANNO SAKURA: Leather Boots #
Stop, lady!
(SCREAMS)
Just fucking stop, please!
Triads? Oh, shit.
(YELLS)
(SCREAMS)
(SQUEALS)
(GASPS)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
What the fu...
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(EXHALES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(GRUNTS)
(NECK CRACKS)
Ya!
(CHOKED CRY)
Fuck!
(GROWLING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(FLESHY SQUELCH)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING DROWNS OUT SPEECH)
(BONES CRACK)
(TRIAD MEMBER SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
Mm-mm.
# (WINDOWS START-UP MUSIC)
Ya!(GRUNTS)
(CRASHING)
(SOFT, OMINOUS MUSIC)
Excuse me, miss.
Would you happen to know
where one can find
$100 million
in stolen cryptocurrency?
Last seen in Djibouti.
I think I read an article
about that once.
Laundered money, right?
A couple of generals in Yemen
had a ROUGH morning at the ATM.
We certainly did.
Fortunately,
my associates in the Congo
were able to describe
the likeness of the attacker.
And I did not...expect...
(COUGHS)
(CHOKING)
Coffee not sitting right?
Sleep tight.
(WHOOSHING, GLASS SHATTERING)
(LUCAS GROANS)
(PANTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BONE CRACKS)
(SCREAMS)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING, CHOKING)
(SPINE CRACKS)
(GROANS)
(EXHALES, BREATHES HEAVILY)
What the fuck?
(DOOR WHIRRS)
Oh, my...
ROYCE: Oh, my God.
(GRUNTING)
Oh, my God.
Anybody hear anything back there?
I don't think so.
Thai Wan Deng?
They have something against you?
Maybe.
Then why the fuck
are they trying to kill me?
You?
I don't understand.
Really? No idea?
I mean, why are they after you?
Or I mean us?
The Ghost...
..may have blown up
an electronics factory
in their territory of Mae Sai.
(LAUGHS)
And why the fuck
would the Ghost do that?
They use child labour.
As in slaves.
Sure. Whatever you say.
The whole world is glued
to their screens all day
not realising that their cheap phones
are made from little kids pulling...
We have to figure out
just how fucked we are, hmm?
Go find Garrett
and scan this deck for threats,
just like you did downstairs.
And you, Rory,
help me with these dead bodies.
(WEAKLY) The bodies?
Yeah, come on.
Oh, God. (BREATHES HEAVILY)
HUNTER: Oh, my God.
Why?
He said...
that someone's put a hit on him.
(SIGHS)
Did we just put a paranoid psychopath
in the mix?
There are civilians
on that plane, too.
(SIGHS) He has no reason to lie.
I'm not saying he's lying.
I think he's just deranged.
God.
OK...
Brunt, no more bullshit.
Excuse me?
I'm sorry,
but this shit
officially just got out of hand,
and at some point...
we're gonna have
to set our stories straight.
So, I need to know exactly what
the fuck we're dealing with here.
Well?
When Reyes was in
the Secret Service,
he was in a detail overseas
in Bangkok.
He was detached
as part of a team to babysit...
a high-value...
..but...
deeply disturbed diplomat.
(MAN GRUNTS LOUDLY)
(WOMAN YELPS)
HUNTER: Deeply disturbed how?
(WOMAN SHRIEKS)
BRUNT: Let's just say that he, uh...
had a fetish for beating up
young prostitutes.
(MAN GRUNTS)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Lucas didn't get the memo and...
..he snapped...
in spectacularly brutal fashion.
(MUFFLED THUDS)
Shit, um...
Well, fuck that guy, right?
Son of a bitch deserved it.
Oh, a thousand percent.
Except his brother
is the deputy director of the CIA.
Fuck.
Mm.
He's been hunted ever since.
Then...
please tell me just...
..how you know so much about him.
We were dating
when all of this went down.
(SCOFFS) What?
It's tragic...
..but my career at the Agency
was on the line so I gave him up.
You sold out your own boyfriend?
I tipped him off.
(SCOFFS SOFTLY)
Gave him a head start.
He's still running.
And somehow still alive considering
all the hard motherfuckers
that have gone after him
and not returned.
It's like the years
have turned him into something...
...Inhuman?
Different.
Garrett, what did you do
to Mrs Nazareth?
I may have given her an Ambien.
Or four.
Four?!
She was very traumatised
by being in economy.
Being around these people
is very stressful for her.
We have a problem.
You think?
What's this? Another factory?
No. Another region altogether.
I gave him a sedative.
He's dead.
Yeah. I'm not a doctor. So?
The vet that patched me up
gave me a bunch of this shit.
I don't know what it is.
Morphine, antibiotics, adrenaline.
How can I protect you when your
enemies are trying to kill me
and you're out gallivanting,
killing other passengers?
I NEVER asked you to protect me!
What is going on? Who's killing who?
Hey, hey! Garrett!
Can you do us a favour
and go out to the galley,
check on all the passengers
that are still alive?
Let us know if you come across
anyone who looks...murderous. Hm?
Murderous? Sure. Murderous.
How am I supposed to trust you?!
To be honest,
I don't really give a shit!
Am I gonna have to restrain you?
I suppose you could try.
We have a big problem.
They have your photo.
Who does?
Everybody does.
(PHONES CHIMING)
(SOMBRE BRASS MUSIC)
(YELLS)
# GORAN BREGOVIC: Kalasnjikov #
(PASSENGERS SCREAMING)
(MUZAK PLAYS)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
What's going on?
(GRUNTING)
What the hell are you doing?
I was trying to help you!
If they figure out it's you
I'm protecting, it's gonna make
my job twice as hard!
Both of us are half as likely
to get out of here alive!
(FLESHY SQUELCHING, MAN GROANS)
(CLARINET PLAYS JAUNTY TUNE)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(METALLIC HISS)
(GRUNTS)
(FURIOUS MUSIC)
(GASPS)
(CRIES OUT)
(SCREAMS)
(CRACKING)
(GURGLES)
(DISTANT GRUNTING)
(STRAINING) Oh, God...
(GRUNTS AGGRESSIVELY)
(SCREAMS)
(HAND SLAPS)
(METALLIC CLANG)
(YELLS)
Ohhh!
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(STRAINS) God...
(GRUNTS)
(CHOKING GURGLES)
(YELLS WITH EFFORT)
(PANTS)
Ah!
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(DOOR WHIRRS)
(WHOOSHING)
(YELPS)
AHHH!
Stop! He's with me.
Stop it! He's with me. Stop. Stop.
(GRUNTS)
She's with me! You're both with me!
Stop. Stop.
(GROANING)
Who the fuck are they now?
A strip-mining company tried
to force them off their land
in the Wudang Mountains.
I bought it back.
They were grateful. And loyal.
Master Lian and her clan
have protected me ever since.
OK. Sure.
Why the fuck not?
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(WHIMPERS) Oh, God.
Hold tight.
Put this here. Here we go.
(GROANS)
You're gonna be OK.
No...I'm not.
No, you're not.
You're quite fucked, actually.
I just don't know what else to say.
That's more like it. (CHUCKLES)
We need to find him somewhere safe.
Where? Everyone on the plane
has his photo.
Follow me. (BREATHES HEAVILY)
(STRAINING) Oh, be careful.
So explain this to me again.
No.
You'll be fine.
No-one's trying to kill you.
Why is anybody killing anybody?
Oh, my God. Just keep an eye out
and call down
if things get fucked up.
Get fucked up?
How much more fucked up can it get
until it qualifies
as being fucked up?!
(GROANS)
How many ways in?
That hatch
and the one in the front galley.
Plus the service elevator.
Can you lock the elevator?
Yeah, I have the key.
OK.
Oh, thank you.
AGENT: 'Photo sent.
Coming your way now.'
HUNTER: (CHUCKLES) OK.
Here's our mark.
BRUNT: Well, well.
It would seem the Ghost is a lady.
I wanna see every byte of data
she's ever generated ASAP.
How much do you think
he got for that book deal, then?
What, net? Thirty percent, tops.
Is that it?
Comms are still down.
Autopilot's working, though.
Says we're right on course.
Weather?
Uh...Yeah, working.
Says there's clear skies ahead.
What's that, then?
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(DOOR WHIRRS)
(DEVICE THRUMS SOFTLY)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SIGHS)
Ooh...
..yeah.
So what the fuck is going on?
(SOFT MUSIC)
There are over 200 million
abandoned kids in the world.
I grew up as one of those kids.
I was sold to
a child-trafficking ring at seven,
and they passed me around.
No, no, no, not what you're thinking.
They soon discovered
that I had a different value.
The soldiers who kidnapped me
worked for warlords,
and those warlords
worked for corporations
mining the minerals
they needed for their products.
Video game consoles and phones.
They had all the guns they needed,
but they were completely
digitally exposed.
Turns out that I had skills
that were useful to them.
So, you're a hacker?
Hacker. Sure.
By the end,
I could bypass any firewall,
infiltrate any database.
(TEARFULLY)
Commandeer any drone in the sky.
The atrocities I was forced
to commit knew no bounds.
So, I escaped and went off the grid.
I spent the next decade of my life
trying to figure out how to make...
that a reality.
Hoping that it could undo
some of the damage.
So, it's a weapon?
The most powerful computer
in the world
would take about a thousand years
to break through
current top encryption methods.
That thing can do it
in 30 seconds.
Hmm. Sounds valuable.
The computing power
of that device is...
limitless.
You asked if it was a weapon.
In the wrong hands...absolutely.
Hm.
And I suppose you consider yourself
the right hands.
I know I can change things.
I just wanna stop what happened to me
happening to other kids.
(PHONES BEEPING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
You're not as smart as you think.
I'm sorry?
You were my first hire.
You know why?
Because you and I are the same.
Cut-throat.
We'd sell our own kids to get ahead.
But you are playing both sides.
(SCOFFS)
I can have forensics run
the last two weeks of your life,
or you can just come clean
and maybe we both get what we want.
(SIGHS) Walk with me.
A source close to the Ghost
contacted me a week ago.
Said she'd built a device that
could disrupt our entire industry.
We made a deal to do
an exchange at SFO, but then,
I traced his phone back to Bangkok
and I sent a team to intercept...
which went sideways. (SIGHS)
There is a plane filled
with dead bodies and murderers
about to land in San Francisco.
Now would be a really fucking good
time to get to the point.
(SCOFFS)
The source wanted a million dollars.
He's an amateur.
So then I thought, well,
if I took out the Ghost,
I could just get it for free.
You cheap-ass little bitch.
(LAUGHS)
You just murder her
so you don't have to pay, huh?
See, now you're catching on.
Then two days ago, I posted
the Ghost's itinerary
on the dark web,
just in case, as a backup.
Every killer trying to collect
the Ghost's bounty took the bait...
all of them with their eyes
on the wrong prize.
And Reyes?
Oh, yeah, wow!
Fucking hell, what a psycho, huh?
I really did try to handle
that one quietly,
but we just kept getting photos
of dead people, so...
I just went nuclear
and, uh, well...
I distributed his photo widely.
He's probably dead by now.
And now that they have
the Ghost's picture as well...
once that plane lands,
they're all dead
and we will have the device.
We?
Whoever owns that device
is a multi-billionaire overnight.
And you think that I should just...
trust you?
I think trust is irrelevant.
You and I are about to be
the only two people on Earth
who know about this.
So...
you could turn me in and...
figure out how to explain
this unholy pile of shit
you're currently presiding on, or...
you join me,
and have more money
than you could ever possibly imagine.
Like I said...
..cut-throat.
MAN: OK, deep breath, everyone.
Let's go.
GROUP: Om.
(HUNTER SCOFFS)
Must be hashtag
whatever-the-fuck day.
Very good, everybody.
What a bunch of fucking pussies.
Yeah.
ALL: Om.
I bet they pass out
participation trophies.
(STIRRING MUSIC)
(JET ENGINES ROAR)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Oh, God.
So now you know everything.
Why are YOU here?
I guess this is my last shot
at redemption.
Turning me in redeems you?
If I bring you in alive...
I'm free.
(SCOFFS SOFTLY)
Free.
Free to do what?
(GRUMBLES)
(PHONE RINGS)
GARRET: 'Isha, Isha...'
Yeah?
'..they've moved from the upper deck
and they're tearing
the lower deck apart.
They know you're down there.
They're looking for a way in.
And, Isha...' (BREATHES HEAVILY)
Listening.
'They have your photo.'
Lian, go secure the rear galley.
(MUFFLED BANGING)
Oh, fuck.
(HATCH RATTLING)
It holds for now.
(RATTLING CONTINUES)
We won't survive down here.
This is a death trap.
I have to go up and face them.
No, that's suicide.
If I don't go up,
we're dead already.
Lucas, they have
their real target now.
They're not after you anymore.
(BANGING CONTINUES)
Start going through the luggage.
There must be something
we can use as weapons.
This is my fight.
I'm not gonna let anyone else
die on my behalf.
Adrenaline, yes?
That's what the vet said.
(SIGHS)
(BANGING CONTINUES)
(EXHALES)
(BANGING INTENSIFIES)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(BREATHES SLOWLY AND HEAVILY)
Kill box!
The economy cabin is the box.
You come from the front,
I come from the back.
If we do it right,
we meet in the middle and we kill
every last motherfucker
who stands in our way.
Kill box!
(EXHALES)
Fff... Kill boxxx!
(EXHALES INTENSELY)
We'll take the elevator up.
Pull them away from the trapdoor.
And I go with you?
Wh... No!
You go nowhere. You stay right here.
No way.
Yes!
I'm not sitting down here
while you all die for me.
I need you alive.
Right.
We all need you alive.
Are you high?
I feel great.
Toad venom. Very powerful.
(EXHALES)
(TENSE MUSIC BUILDS)
Let's fucking do this.
(MUZAK PLAYS, ELEVATOR BELL RINGS)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
MAN 1: Open the fucking door!
MAN 2: Come on!
(SHOUTING AND BANGING)
(BANGING CONTINUES, NERVOUS CHATTER)
(REPETITIVE WHOOSHING)
(PASSENGERS SCREAM)
(EXHALES)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Ah!
(SCREAMING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(SOUND DISTORTS AND PULSATES)
(DISTANT ECHOING SCREAMS)
(BREATHING ECHOES)
(ECHOING SOBS)
(SOUND MUFFLED)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MARTIAL ARTS MUSIC)
Ya!
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(DISTORTED) Behold.
For you are in the presence
of an apex predator.
I am Pantera.
The cold shadow of death
cast upon you.
You seem a worthy adversary,
so I shall offer you
the mercy of choice. (ECHOES)
Deliver to me the Ghost,
and I shall-
(ELECTRONIC BOOM)
(TRIUMPHANT RING)
(CHEERFUL POP MUSIC)
(FRANTIC SCREAMING)
(CHEERFUL POP MUSIC RESUMES)
(MUSIC BECOMES DISTORTED)
(MAN YELLS)
# TCHAIKOVSKY:
Romeo and Juliet - Love Theme #
MAN: Hey. Hey!
(MUFFLED) Hey! Hey!
(GRUNTING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(SCREAMS)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(SPEAKS IN ITALIAN)
(ECHOING GUNSHOT)
(GROANS)
(AIR HISSES NEARBY)
(ECHOING CREAKING)
(ALARM BLARES)
We've lost cabin pressure!
Dive, dive, dive!
The checklist says that-
Eight thousand feet, you moron!
Just tell me when we're there!
(WIND WHISTLES)
(EXCLAIMING IN ITALIAN)
Cazzo!
(SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERING)
Oh, fuck!
(PANTING)
Twelve thousand. Ten thousand.
(ALARM BLARING)
Nine thousand.
(SCREAMS)
(ALARM STOPS)
(PANTING)
(OBJECTS CRASHING)
Huh?
Ah...
(GASPING)
I can't breathe.
Get a grip, man.
(GROANS)
What the fuck are you doing?
I need to get some air!
Get some air? What...?
Do not open that door!
(PASSENGERS SCREAMING)
Freeze!
(BLOOD-CURDLING GROAN)
(ALL SCREAM)
(CONTROLS BEEPING)
(BOTH SCREAM)
(GROANS)
(WIND WHISTLES)
(GRUNTS)
(MUFFLED SHOUTS AND BANGS)
(INTERCOM CHIMES)
ISHA: 'Attention all passengers.
On behalf of Mayko Airlines,
I'd like to thank
everyone on board
who hasn't tried to kill me.
And to the rest of you...
# ELVIS COSTELLO AND THE ATTRACTIONS:
Pump It Up #
(CHAINSAW REVS)
Oh, yeah!
(SCREAMS)
(YELLS WITH EFFORT)
(CHAINSAW REVS)
(FLESHY SQUELCH)
(MAN SCREAMS)
(CHAINSAW REVS)
(REVVING)
(SCREAMS)
(MUFFLED REVVING)
(PASSENGERS SCREAMING)
Move! Keep moving!
(YELPS)
(SLOW, ECHOING HEARTBEAT)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS OF PASSENGERS)
(ECHOING WHIMPERS)
(CHAINSAW REVS NEARBY)
(PASSENGERS GASP)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
ISHA: It's OK. It's OK.
He's with us.
(WOMAN SOBBING)
Oh. Hey.
(FLESHY SQUELCH)
Someone killed the pilots.
(ALL GASP)
(JET ENGINES ROAR DISTANTLY)
It's gonna be right there...
in five, four, three,
two, one...
(DEVICE BEEPS STEADILY)
Huh?
Um...
It's supposed to be right there.
I mean...
it disappeared,
but it was right here.
(SPLUTTERS) It's supposed to...
It's probably the fog.
Oh, God.
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
What the fuck?
(SIGHS) I'm gonna shoot Robinson.
(GUN COCKS)
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
(ALARMS RING SOFTLY)
(KEYS CLACK)
(EXHALES)
(GROANS)
(PHONE RINGS)
Goddamn it! (EXHALES)
OK.
(LAUGHS)
Ow.
(GASPS) Oh.
(PHONE BEEPS)
Hey, what's up?
'Lucas, what the hell is going on?
Where's the plane?'
I don't know.
We're in the sky.
We're flying. (CHUCKLES, PANTS)
Are you OK? You sound weird.
Yeah.
No.
No, I'm definitely not OK.
I haven't been for some time.
'I know.'
I know, and I am sorry. And
I promised that I would fix that,
but our deal was contingent
upon you bringing me the Ghost.
'Are you gonna hold up your end?'
Yeah...
No.
I'm not gonna be able to do that.
'No, huh?'
Well, I am still willing
to honour our agreement,
provided you can help me
tie up one loose end.
(LAUGHS)
Now this is really important,
so please try to remember.
Did you see a device?
Maybe it looked like a...
Oh, what, like a neural net?
That was maybe connected
to the plane's mainframe?
Yes. Yes, that is exactly it.
Maybe something that could expose
your whole supply chain,
maybe the fact that you use
child labour in your factories,
I'm sorry, slave labour,
to the whole world?
Something like that?
Do you have it or not?
No.
No, I haven't seen anything
like that. (CHUCKLES)
You dumb son of a bitch!
You just threw away
your fucking life!
'I have more reach and more power
than I ever did at the Agency!'
OK, bye now.
'And you will never-'(PHONE BEEPS)
Fucker. We have to find the manual,
figure out how to land this thing,
but I think I could do it.
I did take a flight class once.
The pilots weren't flying the plane.
Oh...
We're not landing
in San Francisco, are we?
Not even close.
(GROANS)
Oh, God.
Lucas?
Yeah?
Thank you.
You're a good man.
Goddamn it.
What?
You're gonna ruin this
by being sentimental.
(CHUCKLES)
OK, fine.
You were no help at all.
That's more like it.
Isha...
..you saved me, too.
(TOUCHING MUSIC)
(ECHOING) Lucas?
Lucas?
(BELL RINGS DISTANTLY)
(MUFFLED GUNFIRE)
(WEAKLY) What the fuck?
(SOFT, SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(MUFFLED GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(MUFFLED EXPLOSIONS, GUNFIRE)
(CAR ENGINES REVVING)
MAN: Everybody get down!
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINE)
ISHA: Get the kids out through
the east exit. I'll get Lucas.
Quick! Everyone out.
You're awake. Good.
What the fuck is going on?
Good news, you're not dead.
Bad news...
we're not done yet.
Oh, fuck!
# THE CLASH: Career Opportunities #
# They offered me the office,
Offered me the shop
# They said I'd better take
Anything they got
# Do you wanna make tea at the BBC?
# Do you wanna be,
Do you really wanna be a cop?
# Career opportunities,
The ones that never knock
# Every job they offer you's
To keep you out the dock
# Career opportunities,
The ones that never knock
# I hate the army and I hate the RAF
# I don't wanna go fighting
In the tropical heat
# I hate the civil service rules
# I won't open a letter bomb for you
# Career opportunities,
The ones that never knock
# Every job they offer you's
To keep you out the dock
# Career opportunities,
The ones that never knock
(ECHOES) # Oi!
# Bus driver
# Ambulance man
# A ticket inspector
I don't understand
# They're gonna have
To introduce conscription
To take away my prescription
# If they wanna get me making toys
# If they wanna get me,
Well, I got no choice
# Career opportunities,
The ones that never knock
# Every job they offer you's
To keep you out the dock
# Career opportunities,
The ones that never knock
# Career
# Career, and I'm never gonna knock #