[dynamic music]
[wind howling]
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[wind howling]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[clock ticking]
[air whooshing]
[mysterious music]
[letters clicking]
[energy humming]
[thrilling music]
♪ Money's the king,
money's the queen ♪
♪ Money's just a vice
everybody needs ♪
♪ Money's the king,
money's the queen ♪
♪ Money's just a vice
everybody needs ♪
- [Radio Announcer]
We're high in the sky.
It's a beautiful day
in Downtown L.A.,
where the G-20 World
Economic Summit
will meet later this week.
Let's hope the spate
of recent tremors
doesn't spoil their party.
Of course, maybe shaking
up some bureaucrats
isn'’t such a bad thing.
♪ I don't need a soul,
I don't need a face ♪
♪ Everything I need
money can replace ♪
♪ Weigh it down, let
it, weigh it down ♪
[helicopter propellers whipping]
- Gavin, my money's
going right here.
- [Gavin] Mr. Cole,
maybe move back a bit.
- The future Douglas Cole Plaza.
I'm not funding that
Tesla research anymore.
What a view.
[phone buzzing]
[siren wailing]
This is Cole.
No, I didn't sign up for that.
Then get another
solution, I'm out.
[Mr. Cole shouts]
- [Gavin] Mr. Cole, please!
Please.
[thrilling music]
[energy whooshing]
- Jump, jump, jump.
Now.
- Mr. Cole?
Mr. Cole.
- [Man] Jump.
[Mr. Cole groans]
Jump.
[device beeping]
[Mr. Cole groaning]
- [Gavin] Mr. Cole, please!
- [Man] Jump, jump.
Jump, jump!
[Mr. Cole groans]
Now!
[Mr. Cole screams]
- Mr. Cole!
[suspenseful music]
[objects rattling]
[siren wailing]
♪ Designed to bring
to you, ooh hoo ♪
[dog barks]
[Esther sighs]
[suspenseful music]
[ground rumbling]
[car door closing]
[helicopter propellers whipping]
- George.
Yeah, I just felt
another tremor downtown.
[sighs] I'll be back in an hour,
but I need you to check
the seismic charts
and find the fault line.
Listen, George, something
felt very unnatural
about this one, okay?
No, I know, I know, just
print the charts out.
- [Radio Announcer] President
Trump called the sonic weapon
attacks on American diplomats
in Cuba highly unusual
and felt that Cuba
was responsible.
This dovetails with
a story out of China,
where US government
employees were victimized by,
in their words, "Something
we've never seen before."
- Uh, Paul Dahlset.
- [Radio Announcer] Secretive
Chinese military expansion.
- And she said, "Dad, I'm not
coming down this weekend."
I get it.
She's got kids.
And you know, she don't,
she don't live close.
It's not Santa Monica.
It's, it's a
blessing in disguise.
I don't want her
seeing me in here.
I don't want anybody
I mean, you, that's,
you know what I mean?
You're just, you're new.
[heels clacking]
You got company.
- I see you made a new friend.
Hey, I, uh.
I bought you something.
[soft country music]
[Esther sighs]
Paul.
- Stop signing, I
can read your lips.
And I don't need any help.
- Everyone needs help sometimes.
[walls rumbling]
[suspenseful music]
[objects rattling]
[air whooshing]
[distant gunshots blasting]
[explosion blasting]
Paul.
Hey.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wait, man, look at me.
Come on, man, look
at me, look at me!
- Is he okay?
- Ma'am, I think
you oughta leave.
Come on, look at me.
Breathe!
Now!
Breathe.
Come on, look at me, breathe.
[Paul panting]
Come on, good.
- Excuse me.
For Paul, anonymous please,
I want him to use it.
- Ms. Dahlset.
[Esther exhales]
Ms. Dahlset, a word.
If I may, Esther,
he'll never say it,
but he appreciates you coming.
- I doubt that.
To him, his being
here is all my fault.
I got to go to college,
and he got to go to Syria.
- Honey, I've seen
soldiers trapped
by the voices in
their mind forever,
while others just
snap out of it.
If he's gonna win the battle,
he's gotta know someone
believes in him.
- I've tried.
I can't save him from himself.
- You can't.
Love can.
Mean the world to him,
if you just invite him
over for a few days.
Give him a break from all this.
[gentle music]
[heels clacking]
[dog barking]
[car door closing]
[Esther sighs]
[gentle music]
[seatbelt clicking]
[engine revving]
[gentle music]
- [TV Reporter] A
3.2 tumbler rocked
Downtown Los Angeles today.
Fortunately, no one was hurt.
Government officials vowed
there will not be a delay
in the G-20 downtown despite
these recent L.A. tremors.
In other news, the weather has
been changing quite rapidly,
as you've noticed, and we're
going to talk more about that.
- Hey, Siri, TV off.
- George, give me the graphs.
Come on.
- What's so very important, hmm?
- Something is wrong here.
Okay, do you see this curve?
It's supposed to shape this
way, but it's inverted.
Look, it's right above
the dormant fault line
that we found after
the quake in '94.
It goes straight
through Downtown.
Bring the map.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- What's the big deal, we
get 400 tremors each year.
- No, no, no, no, no.
This is a vertical fault
line, not a horizontal one.
All of Downtown, the
high rises were built
on rollers to withstand
horizontal shakes.
A vertical quake this size
could collapse half of Downtown.
I have to tell the professor.
- Aren't you supposed to
be in class right now?
Yeah, you better hurry.
- Now, through his
work on frequency,
Nikola Tesla used AC power
to illuminate the 1893
Chicago World's Fair,
with spectacular results.
Must have seemed truly
miraculous at the time.
And now some of you have
light bulbs in front of you.
Could you hold them in
your hand for the moment?
Just like that.
Imagine if you will
this coil is the Earth.
Tesla, by bouncing certain
frequencies off the ionosphere
and using the Earth
as a giant battery,
Tesla said that he could
provide unlimited free
and wireless power to
any place on the planet.
[electricity buzzing]
[students gasping]
Ooh, impressive, huh?
Now, unfortunately, the
financier JP Morgan,
as Tesla's primary investor,
wanted to monetize this
revolutionary source of power,
not just hand it out
for free like Tesla did.
So, Morgan withdrew his funding
and shutdown the project.
[remote clicking]
A century later, that
same power is used today
in our cell phones.
[footsteps pattering]
- Hey.
- But perhaps the most
significant unfinished work
of Tesla's was in the
area that we know today
as High-frequency Active
Auroral Research, or HAARP.
[door clicks]
See, Tesla believed that
everything, all of nature,
all things, all that we see,
everything that we know,
that's the weather,
that's earthquakes,
that's even the human mind.
All of it is governed
by frequency.
Tiny vibrations that
animate or destroy.
Case in point. When the
wind in Washington State
reached the resonance
frequency of the mighty
Tacoma Narrows Bridge, it
snapped like a toothpick.
[water splashing]
See, Tesla believed that if
you control the resonance
frequency of an object,
you control that object.
Whether it be a bridge,
weather, earthquake,
even a human thought.
Fun fact, if a little sinister.
When Tesla died, the
government invaded his offices
and seized all this research
in the name of
national security.
But Tesla was canny,
and he committed all his most
critical notes and research
to a particular notebook
that he hid away.
Imagine.
Just imagine if you
will what you could do
if you got hold of
those notes, hmm?
- Professor, didn't
he also say we should,
"Prevent the breeding of
the unfit by sterilization"?
- Someone's been doing
their reading, very good.
Yes, Tesla was interested
in birth control,
but unlike some of his
contemporary eugenicists,
he was more interested in
the betterment of mankind,
not just in creating
some kind of master race.
Think of it, if you will, as
a sort of benign evolution.
Ah, Ms. Dahlset, would you
care to edify Ms. Smith?
- I think Tesla knew
from natural selection
that only the
strong will survive.
- But aren't all
men created equal?
- Ah, well, let me take
that in Tesla's own words.
To quote Tesla, he said,
"Science is but a
perversion of itself,
"unless it has as
its ultimate goal
"the betterment of mankind."
Isn't that right, Mr. Harris?
Mr. Harris!
You see, I controlled
the resonant frequency
of Mr. Harris, and so
I control Mr. Harris.
- Is it true as a student
you put big speakers
in your dorm's basement to
find the resonance frequency,
and you almost brought it down?
- Ah...
At this time I can neither
deny nor confirm that report.
[bell ringing]
Right, midterms, Friday!
Those who fail to
evolve, fail to pass!
Thank you very much.
[footsteps pattering]
[students chattering]
There you go, get that down you.
Quintin's Chamomile Tea.
Just the remedy for a long day
of interminable lectures, hm?
Mm.
You know, I couldn't
help but notice
that you were a little
late this morning,
and your answer in class was
a little less than convincing.
- Why don't you just
use your wristwatch?
It works.
What is it with you
and that old thing?
- This old thing?
This, my dear, is
a special edition.
Do you know that Tesla
used to sell these things
from time to time to
put food on his table?
And this one has a, you see
it has a scratch on the T,
makes it very special.
But you are avoiding
the subject.
You went to see your brother
again this morning, didn't you?
- That's not what I'm
here to talk about.
- Be that as it may, if
you want to achieve success
in science, you have to put
distractions aside and focus.
You know, Esther, I
don't have a daughter,
but if I did, I'd want
her to be just like you,
with your special talents.
Wind is inspiration, Esther,
and windmills are
in short supply.
- He's my brother,
and he's hurting.
I can't just ignore him.
- I know, and you've done
a lot for him already,
but science needs
your special gift.
So, science can help society
and help your brother
along the way.
- [clears throat] I, um...
I brought you these to show you.
[suspenseful music]
- When was this?
- Today, downtown, right
near this fault line.
- Well, this is a...
This is a counterwave.
This is, this is serious.
- Have you ever seen a
pattern like this before?
[phone buzzing]
- Oh, excuse me.
[dramatic music]
- [Esther] Is everything okay?
- Uh.
Yeah, I just, I have to
take care of something.
It was just, something
just came up.
Would you...
Would you mind covering
my classes for me?
And I need to take these.
- Oh, actually, you know what?
I wanted to keep this
chart for my research.
Are you finished with
my notes on my thesis?
- Yes, they're at my house.
I'll...
I'll leave them in my mailbox.
- Okay.
[suspenseful music]
[car humming]
[footsteps pattering]
[suspenseful music]
[gate creaking]
[Esther panting]
[suspenseful music]
[heels clacking]
[door creaking]
Professor?
Professor, it's me, Esther.
[suspenseful music]
[heels clacking]
Professor?
[suspenseful music]
[papers rustling]
[dramatic music]
Professor?
[door creaking]
[suspenseful music]
[heels clacking]
[door creaking]
[suspenseful music]
[heels clacking]
[engine revving]
- [Dispatcher] 911,
what's your emergency?
- [Esther] I'm a grad
student at Cal U.
I think my professor's missing.
He wasn't at his house,
and it was a total mess.
- [Dispatcher] Do you have
any proof he's missing?
- [Esther] No, but.
- [Dispatcher] Ma'am, we can't
file a report for 48 hours.
If he doesn't show up
after that, give us a call.
- [Esther] That's
the best you can do?
- [Dispatcher] I can connect
you with the local police.
- [Esther] No, no, thank you.
[engine humming]
[heels clacking]
[water splashing]
[door creaking]
[dramatic music]
- What are you doing in here?
- I work with the professor.
- That's not what I asked.
I asked you what you were doing.
- Looking for the
professor, obviously.
What happened here?
- Well, you didn't
touch anything, did you?
- I'm not stupid.
- Okay, Einstein,
I'm just making sure.
Cops should be here in a few.
- Police aren't coming.
Colin Ward, FBI.
- Esther Dahlset.
Why is the FBI involved
in a campus break-in?
- And why aren't
the police coming?
- 'Cause this is my case.
- The professor did
a lot of work for us.
- We don't need a
G Man to tell us
that some students tried
to steal test answers.
- Wait, do you know where
Professor Conrad is?
- He told me earlier
he was leaving town
and seemed to be in a hurry.
- What is this all about?
- Let's just say there are
a lot enemies of the State
interested in his research.
- Uh.
- Is there any security
footage of this office?
- Yeah, if it gets you
to leave campus, yeah.
I'll show you.
You, too.
Okay.
[video game music]
[controller buttons clicking]
- Yeah!
Your death is sweet
to me, Shao Khan!
- G Man, Einstein, meet
Rocky, our IT specialist.
- They're not players.
- No, this is reality.
Can you pull footage
from the break-in?
- Nothing's there, you sure
you want to see it again?
- Humor me, we have guests.
- Humor.
Okay.
Analog.
- Double mocha latteccino!
No foam.
- Thanks.
Nice hat.
- Oh.
- Ngh-ngh, ngh-ngh.
[static buzzing]
- What is this, a joke?
It's all static.
I got all I need.
[footsteps pattering]
- What a moron, what's the deal?
- Professor Conrad is
missing, I'm really worried.
- Is that really the only copy?
- Of course not.
You want me to use
my superpowers?
Oh!
- Can you pull an
image from that?
- Duh, takes like
one to two days.
- Okay, yes, use
your superpowers.
[tape rattling]
- Okay.
[video game music]
Yeah!
[water splashing]
[birds chirping]
[computer beeping]
[footsteps pattering]
- Ms. Dahlset?
I apologize for the intrusion.
Dr. Conrad has spoken
so highly of you.
- And you are?
- Oh, forgive my manners.
I'm Dr. Cyrus Stanton, FIT.
Stuart was helping me on
some very sensitive research.
- The professor had
mentioned FIT before,
but he never told
me what it was.
- Future Invested Technologies.
We're what one might consider
an advanced think tank.
We at FIT are committed
not only to thinking
about the problems
but to solving them.
- That sounds like Dr. Conrad,
always trying to
better humanity.
- Hmm, unfortunately not
everyone shares our value set.
There are many governments
with most likely nefarious
intentions out there who'd love
to get their hands
on our research.
Dr. Conrad was about to
submit his final frequency
data research on earthquakes,
now we can't reach him.
- Do you think he was taken?
- It's quite possible.
One of our colleagues,
a Douglas Cole,
had mysteriously died yesterday.
- I'm sorry.
I wish that there was
something more that I could do.
- Dr. Conrad had acquired a
little leather bound notebook
from an antiquities dealer that
was critical to our research.
Perhaps you may
have come across it?
- No.
- Well, if you do come
across this notebook
or hear from Dr. Conrad,
please contact me
as soon as possible.
- It's connected to
the recent tremors.
- Yes, I believe
it is connected.
So, please find Dr.
Conrad and his data
before it's too late.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Excellent.
Gentlemen, thank you.
[water splashing]
[footsteps pattering]
[suspenseful music]
[computer beeping]
- [Esther] Professor,
it'’s me Esther, again.
Please call me back.
[suspenseful music]
[computer dinging]
[computer keys pounding]
[computer beeping rapidly]
[computer keys clicking]
- [Reporter] You thought
you'd never see science
shooting weapons at viruses
and deadly diseases.
Imagine shaking them to death,
or more precisely,
drowning them in vibration.
It just may be possible
to use high frequencies
to wipe out HIV, AIDS, even the.
[computer key clicking]
[suspenseful music]
[device buzzing]
[soft buzzing]
- Uh.
If you're viewing this,
it means that something
terrible has already happened.
My research has
been hijacked and
they killed my
financier, Douglas Cole,
and I'm afraid I maybe next.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean for you to be
dragged into any of this.
I...
Whatever you do, don't
go to the police.
I think they may have
been compromised.
There's an old brown
battered notebook
in my office at work. You
have to find it, take it,
and keep it hidden at all costs.
The G-20 leaders meeting
downtown, they're in danger.
In fact, the whole of
downtown could be in danger.
Take down these numbers, and
keep an eye out for things
that look like strange
sonic listening devices.
They're not, they're weapons.
They were used against
those diplomats in Cuba.
[suspenseful music]
[Esther sighs]
- [Reporter] The Cuban
attack is shrouded in mystery
with both countries
remaining tight-lipped.
Even the scope of the
attack is unusual.
At least 21 people in Havana
have suffered a variety
of strange illnesses,
including hearing loss,
dizziness and headaches.
The State Department has
ordered all US Embassy staff
to leave the island.
- [Professor] The whole of
downtown could be in danger.
Take down these numbers, and
keep an eye out for things
that look like strange
sonic listening devices.
They're not, they're weapons.
They were used against
those diplomats in Cuba.
- What do you think?
- I think you must
be pretty desperate
if you're coming to me.
- You're the only
one I can trust.
- You need to steer
clear of these people.
They don't mess around.
- My professor is missing,
thousands could die.
You want me to just steer clear?
- You gonna stop them, Esther?
You'll end up getting
yourself killed.
- What's your plan?
Just hide out here, give
up, that's your solution?
- Works for me.
- Maybe if you got
your ears blown out
you'd be a little
more cautious too.
And you should be,
you're being followed.
- What, I am not being followed.
How would you know?
- I just know.
- I have to do this.
I'll do it with or without you.
[somber music]
[car humming]
- You should have seen him.
She came in, he stopped, he
stopped listening, stopped.
You want some of this?
- No, I'm good.
[Jeremiah laughs]
- [Man] Kill.
[device whirring]
Kill.
- Jeremiah?
Are you all right?
- Kill.
- Oh, okay, enough of that.
- [Man] Kill him now.
- What, what, hold up.
Back off, back off.
Jeremiah, Jeremiah.
[men muttering]
Get off!
[tires screeching]
[body thudding]
[thrilling music]
Jeremiah.
Buddy.
Help!
Help, we got a man
down over here!
[suspenseful music]
- [Professor] There's an
old, brown battered notebook
in my office somewhere.
You have to find it, take it,
and keep it hidden at all costs.
The G-20 leaders meeting
downtown, they're in danger.
In fact, the whole of
downtown could be in danger.
Take down these numbers, and
keep an eye out for things
that look like strange
sonic listening devices.
They're not, they're weapons.
[device whirring]
They were used against
those diplomats in Cuba.
And don't trust anyone.
[suspenseful music]
[device humming]
[device beeping]
[device sputtering]
[suspenseful music]
- You're gonna get me fired.
- I was just grabbing a book.
- From behind the bookcase?
- You should see where he
hid the midterm answers.
- I don't want to know.
What's it for?
- I just need it to
teach class tomorrow.
- George is teaching tomorrow.
- [sighs] You're
quite the detective.
- Well, I was once.
Till I blew the whistle on
some higher-ups at the LAPD.
- Wait, you're not kidding?
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to
be rude earlier.
I was just, I...
Wait, why are you doing
campus security then?
- Like it's beneath me?
I get free tuition for
my law school classes.
- Oh.
- I guess you can't judge
a book by its cover, huh?
- So, are you gonna arrest me?
[Frank laughs]
- Is that book gonna help
you find the professor?
[somber music]
Go on, get out of here.
The truth is, after
this whole break-in,
they're probably
gonna fire me anyway.
Just return it.
[suspenseful music]
[elevator beeping]
[elevator door rattling]
[suspenseful music]
[heels clacking]
[tires rumbling]
[engine revving]
[dramatic music]
[tires screeching]
Oh!
- Oh my gosh!
[tires screeching]
- You forgot your phone.
Look, Esther, seriously,
what is going on?
- I'm not sure.
- Look, if you want me to
help you find the professor,
you gotta let me in.
- Honestly, Frank, I am in
way over my head right now.
Everything is happening so fast.
I. [sighs]
I just need time to process.
[phone buttons clicking]
I'm ready when you are.
- Wait, do you mind
walking me to my car?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
[heels clacking]
[suspenseful music]
[Professor whimpers]
- [whimpers] No, no, no,
no, please, no, no, no.
- [Man] Where is the book?
[suspenseful music]
[camera lens clicking]
[lid clicking]
[suspenseful music]
[cars humming]
[wave humming]
Bring the book.
Bring me the book.
[device beeping rapidly]
[suspenseful music]
[device beeping]
[device buzzing]
[fist pounding]
[suspenseful music]
- Who is it?
[fist pounding]
- What are you,
deaf or something?
- What are you doing here?
- Come here.
Let me see your eyes.
What's the last
thing you remember?
- Uh.
I, I don't know, I
can't remember anything.
- There was a guy
outside your window
in a car pointing some
kind of weird gun at you.
He's gone.
The car's gone.
I told you not to mess
with these people.
- Who are they?
I don't know,
Russian, Chinese, NSA.
Doesn't matter,
they're gone now.
[Esther sighs]
- This stupid notebook.
- Where is it?
- How did, how did you
know they were out there?
- Look, I've been coming by.
- I have to find the professor.
- Hey, look, we're gonna
get you out of this, okay?
- Would you sleep on
the couch tonight?
[footsteps pattering]
[suspenseful music]
[crickets chirping]
[dramatic music]
[objects rattling]
[walls rumbling]
- [Jeremiah] Look
at me, look at me.
- Something is wrong here.
I think the professor's missing.
[dramatic pounding]
- My research has been hijacked.
They killed my
financier, Douglas Cole.
I'’m afraid I may be next.
[energy buzzing]
- I told you not to
mess with these people.
[tires rumbling]
I don't know,
Russian, Chinese, NSA.
- Let's just say there
are a lot of things
at stake with your
professor's research.
- Dr. Conrad had acquired
a leather-bound notebook
that is critical
to our research.
Perhaps you may
have come across it.
- [Announcer] President
Trump called the sonic weapon
attacks in Cuba highly unusual.
[dramatic pounding]
- That look like strange
sonic listening devices.
They're not, they're weapons.
[dramatic pounding]
- [Paul] What are you gonna
do, stop them, Esther?
You'll end up getting
yourself killed.
[dramatic music]
♪ Holding out for a secret
♪ A way to make you smile
♪ I was not expecting anything
♪ Holding out for a secret,
a way to make you smile ♪
[birds chirping]
[heels clacking]
- Sorry, Paul, I
have to do this.
[door creaking]
[door closing]
[people chattering]
- Dude, gimme, gimme, gimme.
No foam, right?
- Of course, are
we not civilized?
- Mm.
[computer keys clicking]
Ah!
- Ah.
- What do you got?
- Double mocha
latteccino, no foam.
- I meant the security footage.
- Ah, well this is all we
got before it turns to snow.
[static buzzing]
- Can you zoom in
on the forearm?
- That is not possible.
- Piece of cake.
- [Frank] Freeze that.
- Ooh!
The force is strong
with this one.
- [Rocky] Hashtag mojo.
[soft rock music]
♪ Crawling, under my skin
♪ Always drawing me in
♪ I won't stop
remembering it all♪
♪ Broken to little pieces
♪ The temperture increases
♪ Now we have
to break it off ♪
[hand knocking]
- Hi, I'm here to
see Mr. Stanton.
[heels clacking]
[door thudding]
- [Cyrus] I'll be right down.
[soft rock music]
[heels clacking]
- In my 20s, I taught science
at an orphanage in Haiti.
Spring of '94, best
time of my life.
Six months later, every
child in these photos
was killed by Hurricane Gordon.
It was at that moment that I
decided to dedicate my life
to the science of predicting
and controlling nature.
- Professor Conrad
felt the same way.
Still no word about him?
- Sadly, no, but we are
continuing with the search.
Please.
- So, you think
he was taken, then?
- One would assume.
He would have
contacted us by now.
- By any chance, have
you found that notebook?
That's what they'd
be after, not him.
- Nope, why is it so important?
- Well, Tesla was a genius
100 years ahead of his time.
But later in his life,
he became very secretive
and never published his
most amazing discoveries.
Those discoveries were
thought to be written
in a lost journal.
Now, in the right hands,
it could revolutionize
the 21st century.
But in the wrong hands...
I'd like to show you something.
[footsteps pattering]
We've been working
on ways to create
out-of-phase reverse
seismic waves.
Do you know how they
put out a forest fire?
They start another one,
it's called a backfire.
And when those two
fires converge--
- They cancel each other out.
- Precisely.
There was a 7.0
earthquake in Chile,
it devastated an entire village.
With what we know now,
we probably could have
reduced a lot of that damage.
- If you had Tesla's notes.
- We might've saved
the entire region.
[dramatic music]
- Do you know that this
one has a scratch on the T?
- Did Stuart ever show you a
reverse wave like that before?
- No. [clears throat]
No, this is quite something.
But if you can
stop an earthquake,
doesn't that mean you
could start one too?
- That's why that
notebook should never
fall into the wrong hands.
[suspenseful music]
- Well, I will continue looking.
If I find anything,
I'll let you know.
- Perhaps we can assist
you in your search.
- Oh, I work a lot
faster on my own.
- As you like, I'll have
one of my men show you out.
Time is of the essence.
[suspenseful music]
- Oh no.
Paul.
[suspenseful music]
Oh no.
[Esther sighs]
[heels clacking]
[phone ringing]
[hand knocking]
That was fast.
Oh.
- Not what you expected.
- Agent Ward.
No, sorry, come in.
[Esther clears throat]
- What, are students
stealing test answers again?
- I wish.
It looks like I might've
upset the wrong people,
and I could be in some trouble.
Maybe you could help me?
- Can we get some coffee first?
- Oh, yeah, of course.
Sorry again about the mess.
- No, just relax, I'll get it.
[footsteps pattering]
- Mm.
This is so good,
this is my coffee?
- Actually, I carry
packets with me.
Let me tell you,
there's nothing worse
than being on an all night
stakeout with bad coffee.
- Mm.
I wish I had this while
I was writing my thesis.
- Well, getting back to it.
So, you think this FIT
group has Dr. Conrad
because you saw his watch there.
And they might be planning
to set off an earthquake
under L.A. during the G-20.
And they need the professor's
research to do it.
And if they can't find it, well.
And your brother
might be missing,
but maybe he just left
the room like this
after a PTSD attack,
and maybe he's just
back on the streets.
- Okay.
[sighs] I know how it sounds.
Do you think I should
call the police?
- With a story like this?
- Well, do you
believe me at least?
- Can I call you Esther?
I think we got off on the
wrong foot the other day.
I looked you up.
You're a very bright lady.
So, no, Esther, I don't
think you made this up.
And, yes, I can help you.
The FBI is determined to
prevent the professor's research
from falling into
the wrong hands.
- So, what do I do?
- Well, if you can find this
notebook or Stuart's research,
we could use it to set up
a sting on this FIT group
and find your professor.
But what you've just told me
isn't enough to get a warrant.
[exhales] If you do find
anything, give us a call.
We'll get your professor
back, it's what we do.
- Of course, thank you.
Oh.
- I thought you wanted my help?
- I didn't call him,
he just showed up.
- Right, the FBI always
gets their man, or woman.
Campus cop just gets
to wait in line.
- Where did that come from?
- I don't know.
Maybe I was under
the impression that...
Forget it.
- Well, he wasn't
much help anyway.
- But you still didn't
answer my question.
- Yes, I want your help.
- I just wanted to hear it.
Looks like quite the mess.
You didn't call me over just
to help clean up, did you?
- No, someone broke in here
and they took that notebook.
- Oh, it's gonna cost
you a big library fine.
- This isn't funny.
I have almost gotten killed,
my brother and my professor
are missing, and
this group is trying
to create this earthquake
that could collapse all
of downtown during the G-20.
- Okay, what
proof do you have?
- [sighs] Well, I
went to this group
that the professor
used to work for.
It's called FIT, and they
had his pocket watch there.
He, he would never
leave it behind.
- And?
- Well, and they
wanted the notebook
that has all of the
formulas that they can
create the big earthquake, and
I had it, and now it's gone.
And now I have nothing
to bargain with
to get the professor back.
- Well, if this FIT group
didn't take it, then who did?
- I don't know.
Are you gonna help me or not?
- You could always bluff.
- What?
- You say you need
this notebook to trade
to get the professor back.
Call him, tell him you have it.
- Then what?
- I don't know,
but we'll figure something out.
But first, we're
gonna need a team.
[upbeat rock music]
[computer keys clicking]
[computer beeping]
- Oh yeah.
[upbeat rock music]
[wings flapping]
- Rocky, again with the wings.
- You said full battle gear.
You want this domain
protected or not?
- This is such a bad idea.
- What's with the outfit?
- She's a LARPer, a
Live Action Role Player.
Weekend warrior.
Teams, costumes, plastic
swords, the whole nine yards.
City parks become
galactic battlegrounds.
Save the universe.
- [Both] Save the Universe!
- Hey, she's the best
hacker in school, you know.
- And my mojo is
better than yours.
- And your mojo is
better than mine.
- All right, guys,
let's do this!
- Pull up the schematics on FIT.
- All right.
Dude, this used to be
a private mental asylum
for the wealthy.
The basement is where they
keep the silver spoon wackos.
- Well, the labs
are in the basement,
so I bet that's where
the professor is.
- Okay, we park
the van out front.
Esther is gonna tell 'em
she found the notebook,
and they'll let us in.
Paul, you sneak onto the grounds
and find an entrance
through the back door.
Rocky, you hack into the wifi
and set off a fire
alarm at precisely 8:05.
- Fire alarm, pfft,
I got it in my sleep.
- Okay, when the alarm goes off,
everyone will exit the building.
The electronic door locks
will automatically open,
and the professor gets out.
Paul, you'll help him escape
to our van in the street.
And Esther keeps Cyrus busy.
Foolproof.
- I don't like it.
- Well, do you
have a better idea?
- Suppose the guards
take the professor?
- Then this is our backup plan.
- A video camera with
a wifi geo-tagger.
Put this on, it looks
just like a brooch.
If the professor is there,
a picture of him will
help get a warrant
to search the building.
Or hopefully you can get
Cyrus incriminating himself.
- These contacts.
These contacts will let you
see the full
electromagnetic spectrum,
not just visible light.
- And what will that get me?
- Body temperature
displays, heat signatures.
You can see through walls!
- Night vision?
- Of course.
You can even see invisible
sonic frequencies.
Sonic gunfire.
- I want some!
- Patience, grasshopper.
Okay?
In good time, you
will all get them.
- Wait, what if the professor's
cell doesn't unlock?
[computer keys clicking]
- Combo locks look like this?
- Uh huh.
- Oh, no sweat, they're
Smith Lock, old issue.
This will confuse the lock
chip, opens it by default.
- This is military,
where'd you get it?
- eBay.
- Are we ready to rumble?
- Let's do this.
[hands clapping]
[thrilling music]
All right, we're
here, get to work.
[computer keys clicking]
[hand knocking]
- Ms. Dahlset,
lovely to see you.
We've been expecting you.
[Esther clears throat]
Please follow me.
[computer beeping]
[computer keys clicking]
[footsteps pattering]
- Is it safe down here?
- Oh, yes, they're just
running a test in that lab.
So, we shouldn't stay too long.
They're on an extreme deadline.
If you please, may
I have the notebook?
- Oh, actually, I didn't know
if it was the real thing.
So, I took some photos
of some of the pages.
What do you think?
- Well, if those aren't
Tesla's initials,
they're quite a good forgery.
If you don't mind, I'm
gonna have to keep this.
- Wait, actually, I do mind.
I was just gonna text a
few friends about dinner,
you know, but.
- Ms. Dahlset, I think it's
time we stopped playing games.
I believe this is what
you're looking for.
[suspenseful music]
- [gasps] Professor.
Are you okay?
[Professor groans]
- Expecting something?
A fire alarm, perhaps?
Oh, yes, we've been
tapping your phone.
Let me make this simple.
Tell me where the
notebook is or die.
[crickets chirping]
[devices beeping]
[computer beeping]
- It's 8:05, where's the fire?
- The wifi's dead,
I can't do it.
[siren blaring]
[dispatcher chattering]
- You're gonna have
to move the van.
- We're picking up someone.
- No parking, no standing.
Move, now.
- Yes, sir, officer.
[door closing]
[suspenseful music]
[engine revving]
- No, Loki, you will
not win this battle.
[suspenseful music]
- What did they do to you?
- [sigh] Some kind
of sonic torture.
Brain feels like it's
been in a microwave.
- You used to work
with these people?
- They weren't always like this.
We were trying to save lives
by stopping earthquakes.
- They're starting them,
they're killing innocent people.
I mean, collapsing downtown?
- That wasn't part
of the original plan.
We were gonna fix
nature's flaws.
Just trying to help
its evolution.
- Sounds to me like you
were trying to play God.
- I was just trying to use
my science to perfect nature.
- And the goal being
what, to better humanity?
I mean, it seems like
you get to decide
who lives and who dies.
The weak, like my brother.
What, he's just tossed aside?
- FIT is targeting the G-20.
- Yeah, we know.
Can we stop it?
- Maybe.
But not from here.
[suspenseful music]
[door beeping]
[computer beeping]
[computer key clicking]
[door beeping]
[door closing]
- Keep it on him.
- No, no, no, no, please!
- Wait, no, hey!
- On your knees.
- Why are you doing this?
- The human race has to evolve.
- By destroying Los Angeles?
- By replacing leaders who
don't share our beliefs
with those who do.
- You'll never get
away with this.
- It's an earthquake,
a natural disaster.
They'll pin it on
the usual suspects.
Mother nature,
the universe, God.
Now, if you please, where is
the rest of that notebook?
- Why, so you can create
even bigger disasters?
- You don't seem to be
grasping how this works.
[gun buzzing]
The notebook.
[Professor groans]
The notebook!
- I don't have it.
- Again.
[gun buzzes]
[Professor groans]
- No, don't, stop!
- Where's the rest
of that notebook?
The professor knows
better than anyone,
we as a species are on
the verge of extinction,
and the remedy lies
within that book.
You see, we can no longer
be subject to the whims
of these inept politicians,
whose policies maintain the
survival of the weakest.
We need to establish
a new world order
where only the fittest may rule.
- No, no, we all have value.
People are created equally.
- We weren't created.
We're merely a product
of time and chance.
Either we take control
of our own destiny,
or we go the way
of the dinosaurs.
- What about people
that, that are deaf, hm?
Or maybe not as smart?
We just do away with them.
- I think Nietzsche
had it right.
If we are to build a superhuman,
we must first eliminate
those who are flawed.
- Cyrus, please, this isn't
what we set out to do.
- Shh, but it's what we must do.
Now please, let's make
it easy on all of us.
Where's the rest of that book?
[suspenseful music]
Have it your way.
[gun buzzes]
[Esther screams]
- No, no!
- Give her a blast
every five minutes
until she changes her mind.
[device beeping]
[device humming]
[beam blasting]
[suspenseful music]
[distant gunshots popping]
[radio buzzing]
- [Radio Dispatcher] Scout
clearing path, two clicks.
Zero two niner for the base.
[Dispatcher mutters]
[gunshots popping]
[suspenseful music]
IED!
[explosion blasting]
[body crashes]
[suspenseful music]
[dramatic whooshing]
[Paul screams]
[man groans]
[fist smashes]
[body thudding]
[man groaning]
[footsteps pattering]
[air whooshing]
[men groaning]
[suspenseful music]
[taser buzzing]
[man panting]
[door beeping]
[lock clicking]
- [Esther] Paul!
Paul.
[suspenseful music]
- I'm here to save you.
[computer beeping]
- I'll give them
the wrath of Khan.
- In English?
- Hack into water and power,
and shut down the
block's power grid.
- Do it.
[computer beeping]
[door beeping]
[door clicking]
[suspenseful music]
- I'm gonna make
sure you enjoy this.
[suspenseful music]
[fist smashing]
[man groaning]
[body thudding]
- See, for every action,
there's a reaction. [groans]
[suspenseful music]
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
[suspenseful music]
[footsteps pattering]
[door beeping]
Hold this.
[alarm blaring]
[computer beeping]
- Do not let them
leave the compound.
- Yes, sir.
[alarm blaring]
[suspenseful music]
[footsteps pattering]
- Wait, are you kidding me?
[weapons blasting]
[computer beeping]
- Give him the
wrath of Khan, now!
[computer beeping]
[weapons blasting]
[suspenseful music]
- Come on guys, hurry up.
Let's go. Glad to see you.
- Let's go, guys.
- You'’re a life saver.
[lips smacking]
[Frank chuckling]
[engine humming]
[thrilling music]
- It was an earthquake,
a natural disaster.
We'll pin it on
the usual suspects.
Mother nature,
the universe, God.
- [Esther] Wait, stop!
- If you please, the rest of
the notebook, where is it?
- [Esther] Why, so you can
create even-- [button clicking]
- I've seen enough.
You did the right
thing in coming to me.
- So, now you get a warrant.
- Well, we already have
a team on the way.
[phone ringing]
Talk to me.
Gone, what do you mean
everything's gone?
- Gone, it's impossible.
- Yeah.
They must've had a contingency
for something like this.
- So, what now?
- Well, we tighten
security in the G-20,
and we start to track them down.
- No, I heard that they
can remotely access
the HAARP arrays, which means
they could set off this quake
from anywhere in the city.
- Well, then you and the
doctor better come up
with some whizzbang
way to stop this thing.
You still haven't found that
elusive notebook yet, have you?
- Ngh-ngh.
- How is the doctor?
- He's pretty shaken up.
- Well, I'd still like to
see him as soon as possible.
In fact, I'd like to see the
whole team for a debrief.
Could you get them
here within the hour?
- Sure, we can do that.
- Good.
Oh, and Frank.
I owe you an apology.
I underestimated you.
You're a good cop.
No hard feelings?
- Freeze that.
[computer beeping]
[energy whooshing]
[suspenseful music]
- None at all.
- See you shortly.
- I think that went really well.
- We need to get outta here.
- What?
What's wrong?
- Did you see the
lighting tattoo?
It's the same as the
video on the break-in.
- Wait, you think
he's working for FIT?
- Absolutely, come on.
[suspenseful music]
Come on.
[heels clacking]
[letters clicking]
[suspenseful music]
- So?
- Colin is definitely involved.
- Then we go to the police.
- No, I'm not so sure
that's a good idea.
- Look, if the FBI
has been compromised,
then you can bet the
police have been, too.
FIT's got people everywhere.
- We're gonna have to
do this all ourselves.
- Are we safe here?
- It's a homeless shelter,
they're not coming here.
- So, do we have a plan?
- As a matter of fact, we do.
You see, they're planning to
trigger a destructive seismic
wave in one direction,
so we will generate
a similar wave
in the opposite direction.
- Oh, sorta like the
noise canceling earbuds
that I use to drown out Frank.
- Oh, something like that.
The fact is that
the result will be,
there'll be no wave, or at least
a significantly weaker one.
- Paul.
You were amazing today.
- Yeah right.
- No, I mean it.
It was nice getting to hang
with my big brother again.
- Oh.
I had this.
Meant to return it.
- [Esther] Oh.
[gentle music]
Come on.
- Professor, before
you lay out the plan,
I think I can speak for
all of us when I say
we need to know
where your heart is.
Tomorrow's not a drill.
Our lives are on the line,
along with all of L.A.
Is your allegiance still
with FIT or with us?
- Fair question.
I, uh, I need to
apologize to all of you.
[sighs] As you know,
I'm a pompous, arrogant,
old-fashioned academic.
I haven't treated you with
the respect that you deserve,
well, anyone deserves for
that matter, until today.
From here on in, I
will be honored to work
alongside each and
every one of you.
[hand patting]
So, shall we stop this thing?
- I'm in.
- In.
- Well, I'm like
totally in. [laughs]
- Oh, well, I'm
like totally in, too.
[group laughing]
- [Together] Yeah!
[thrilling music]
- [George] At least
without the notebook,
they can't create
a bigger quake.
- [Professor] Yeah, but
they still could collapse
most of downtown.
[thrilling music]
Even without Tesla's notebook,
FIT's been able to
assemble three HAARP arrays
located on freighters
about 12 miles offshore.
And each one will fire
a high-frequency pulse
into the ionosphere.
When it bounces back to Earth,
it'll trigger a
vertical seismic event
onto Los Angeles.
- To stop this,
the Professor and I
will drive to the
mountain bluffs in my van.
We'll set up a microwave dish
to radio the beta
freighter's control system.
- And once I've hacked
into the beta array,
I can send out a counterwave
to cancel out the alpha.
Unfortunately, the gamma
freighter's too far away.
Esther and Paul,
you guys will break
into west side command
that sends signals
to the freighters.
- Here.
Put this virus into their system
and it will stop the gamma.
- Beta down, alpha down,
gamma down, we win!
No earthquake!
[Professor chuckles]
[hands slapping]
- Guys, I hate to
be a spoiler here,
but I'm not exactly the
best in an earthquake.
- Hey, you'll be fine,
I'll be with you.
- And where's this
FIT's command post?
- And what about the guards?
- Yeah, well, I got a quick
look at their schematics,
and I think it's located
somewhere in an industrial park,
somewhere here on the Westside.
Once they send signals
to the freighters,
I'll be able to triangulate
its exact position.
- So, we stage here and
wait for your signal.
- Yeah, but what
about the guards?
We'd need an army
to get past them.
- I have an army.
- The role players?
Oh no.
- Hey, flatfoot.
Me, Dragonovich and Thing Master
defeated the Queen of Darkness
and a quarter of the
universe last week.
This is child's play.
- Yeah, wait a minute,
she's onto something.
We can overwhelm the
guards with numbers.
I mean, they're not gonna
shoot a bunch of
superheroes, right?
- Yeah, the last thing FIT wants
is attention from
the police, right?
- Frank, how many burgers do
you think you could wrangle up?
- Why?
- I have an idea.
- Save the universe?
- [Both] Save the Universe!
[suspenseful music]
[letters clicking]
- In a few hours, 20 of the
world's most powerful leaders
will meet to determine the
future of our economies.
The security here is so tight,
not even the media
is allowed inside.
[boat horn honking loudly]
[suspenseful music]
- Try to the left a bit, left.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, hold it, hold
it right there.
[computer keys clicking]
Yes, there we go.
Hello, my lovelies.
All right, Cyrus's people
have linked to the freighters.
[computer keys clicking]
Tell 'em it's a go.
- Game on.
[suspenseful music]
[seagulls cawing]
[people chattering]
[suspenseful music]
[phone dinging]
- That's the signal!
- Company, move out!
[group shouting]
Let's head out!
[group cheering]
[suspenseful music]
[computer keys clicking]
- Yes, sir.
We have commenced countdown.
The array is at 75%.
I understand, we will not fail.
[suspenseful music]
- All right, I'm in.
I just need to make a
couple more calculations.
But I can't send the signal
until they activate
those other arrays.
[suspenseful music]
- Professor, we have company.
- [sighs] You're gonna have
to get me two more minutes.
Just two minutes.
- Can't let you do
this, Professor.
[gunshot blasting]
Who brings a taser
to a gunfight?
[thrilling music]
[taser whacks]
[Colin groans]
[thrilling music]
[men grunting]
[fists smashing]
[suspenseful music]
- Hey, I got a situation
here in the alley.
I'm gonna need back up.
[thrilling music]
- [George] Round one, fight!
[energy whooshing]
[man groaning]
[thrilling music]
[men grunting]
[fists smashing]
[weapon buzzing]
[thrilling music]
This is not part of the plan!
[people shouting]
[thrilling music]
- Come on.
You guys go, we got this.
- It's payback time.
[people shouting]
- Go, go, go!
[alarm blaring]
[thrilling music]
- It's okay, keep
working, keep working.
Stay at your stations.
Let's get some
security at the door.
[alarm blaring]
[fists smashing]
[Colin grunting]
[foot smashing]
[thrilling music]
[gun cocks]
- Like I said, I
can't let you do this.
- If you're not
FBI, who are you?
- No, I am, but there's
just a few of us who wanna
be on the winning side
when the dust settles.
Now, I don't want
to have to kill you,
so please take your hands
away from the keyboard.
[thrilling music]
[computer keys clicking]
Don't test me!
[gun whacking]
[thrilling music]
[fist smashing]
[gunshot blasting]
[men grunting]
[shoulder thudding]
[men groaning]
[thrilling music]
[energy beam whooshing]
Shoot to kill!
Shoot him now!
[thrilling music]
Where are you going?
Stay put, stay put!
[beam whooshing]
Get your weapons!
[elbow smashing]
[body thudding]
Why isn't this working on him?
- He's deaf!
Move aside, genius.
- Where did everybody go?
- Don't even think about it.
Hands.
[thrilling music]
Take a seat!
[letters clicking]
[thrilling music]
[men grunting]
[fists smashing]
- Just keep him busy,
I'm almost there.
- What do you think I'm doing?
[men grunting]
[fists smashing]
[computer keys clicking]
[knife whooshes]
No!
[Professor groans]
[body thuds]
No!
[thrilling music]
[taser buzzing]
[Colin groaning]
[body thudding]
[thrilling music]
Tesla power, baby.
Professor!
Are you okay?
- Please, just push!
Push the send button! [groans]
[button clicking]
[ship rumbling]
[parts crashing]
[alarm blaring]
- So much for your
alpha and your beta.
- Maybe you've forgotten.
There's a solar array
that hasn't fired.
- Not for long.
[button clicks]
- No, no, no, don't do that!
[alarm blaring]
[gunshot blasting]
- No!
[weapon rattles]
- Sometimes you have to do
things the old-fashioned way.
Now, move away from the
console, Ms. Dahlset.
[computer beeping]
[satellite humming]
[beam blasting]
[ground cracking]
[towers crashing]
[ground rumbling]
[computer beeping]
[Professor muttering]
[thrilling music]
[walls rumbling]
[stones crashing]
[computer beeping]
[thrilling music]
- What have you done?
[buttons clicking]
You think you can stop us.
You haven't stopped anything.
This is much bigger
than you, you know it.
We will weed out the weak.
- Weed this.
[beam blasting]
[Cyrus gagging]
[thrilling music]
[Cyrus groaning]
[body thuds]
- Paul, are you okay?
- A flak jacket.
I couldn't listen to that
blowhard another second.
- Come on.
[walls rumbling]
[hands thudding]
- I can't see.
- Yeah, how does it feel
to be a weak one, huh?
An expendable.
- You lose.
[alarm blaring]
- Mission complete?
- Negative.
[alarm blaring]
[computer keys clicking]
- Wow, impressive firewall.
[alarm blaring]
[computer beeping]
The clock's skipping beats.
We gotta go.
[alarm blaring]
[computer beeping]
[flames roaring]
[walls rumbling]
- Paul.
Paul, Paul, look at me.
It's your sister,
you're gonna be okay.
We've gotta get outta here, run.
Go, go, go, come on!
[walls rumbling]
[thrilling music]
[explosion blasting]
[group groaning]
- You guys okay?
[Esther groans]
[Rocky groans]
- Are you okay?
- That was awesome!
- Yeah!
[lips smacking]
[siren wailing]
[people shouting]
- Hey, what about the burgers?
[hand tapping]
[Esther laughing]
- You guys earned them.
Let's go get those burgers.
[group cheering]
[phone ringing]
[solemn music]
- [Reporter] A
3.2 tumbler rocked
Downtown Los Angeles today,
temporarily halting
the G-20 Summit.
Caltech reported it could
have been much worse.
The vertical shift
fault could have
brought the entire
central district down.
[somber music]
[footsteps pattering]
- Stuart's last words
were, "Thank you."
He didn't have a wife or kids,
but he said that you were the
closest family he ever had.
- This garden was
like a home to him.
He asked that his
ashes be spread here.
[phone beeping]
[lid clanging]
[ashes rattling softly]
- He was proud of you, you know.
- I know.
I feel like that's
why I owe it to him
to continue his work and use
it as he originally intended.
- So, what did the FBI
say about Colin?
- The usual stonewalling.
They can't comment on an
ongoing investigation.
What about you?
- I asked Paul to come stay
with me while he was in rehab
and looking for a new job.
- What type of job?
- I don't know.
But I'm thinking about putting
together a platoon of vets
to take down mad scientists.
[group laughing]
You?
- Continue taking night
classes to get my law degree.
Staying in town.
- In town is good.
- [George] Oh.
- Oooh!
[George laughs]
[Rocky laughs]
All right, you guys ready?
[somber music]
[gravel crunching]
Wait, did we ever
find the notebook?
- Well, the formulas in
there could literally
change the balance of
power of the world,
so if FIT doesn't
have it then who does?
- What, the notebook?
Oh, I hid that.
- [Group] What?
- What, so they couldn't
connect it with you.
Look, I think it's
caused enough trouble
and maybe it needs to stay lost
for a few more generations.
I hid it with Vic,
one of the vets.
No one will ever find it.
Believe me, the future
of mankind is safe.
[thrilling music]
[bag rustling]
- [Man] Bring me the book!
[suspenseful music]
[thrilling music]
[somber music]
[helicopter propellers whipping]
[thrilling music]