Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
(big band intro)
(indistinct chatter)
(man) Hey, that's a great idea.
- (man 2) Clear the way!
- (alarm ringing)
(big band, jazz music)
(tires screeching)
(siren wailing,
horn honking)
Whoo!
We have a third-alarm call
from the Clock Tower!
There are people
trapped on the top floor!
(barks)
I'm not Georgia.
I'm Captain Georgia!
(gasps) It looks like a bad one!
Hurry, Probie!
We have people to save!
(gasps) Look out!
(screams)
(grunts)
Whoo-hoo!
- (gasps)
- (train bell rings)
Ember, stretch a line,
hook up to the hydrant
and extend the ladder.
I've got to get
to the top floor.
(both screaming)
Whoa!
(screams)
(giggles, gasps)
- (dog whimpers)
- (screams)
(giggles)
(gasps, screams)
(screams)
- Aaah!
- No...!
(Georgia) You see
that amazing girl?
Well, it's me, Georgia Nolan.
And this is my faithful dog,
Ember Nolan.
She's sweet, right?
Oh, and by the way,
the man freaking out
is my dad, Captain Shawn Nolan.
Let me tell you about him.
Captain Shawn Nolan
was the best
and bravest fireman
in the whole wide world
of New York.
(gasps)
He saved so many lives.
- He was a legend!
- (all) Yeah!
(Georgia) But he couldn't save
my mom when she had a baby...
who was me.
At first he tried to be
a fireman and a dad
at the same time.
Oh! No! No, no, no, no!
That was very difficult.
- (sighs)
- (giggles)
So he became a tailor instead,
like his dad.
He said he didn't mind because
he loves me so, so, so much.
Along with Ember, we have
a super great life together.
And now I'm training to be
a fireman and save lives
just like my hero
Captain Shawn Nolan used to do.
It's my dream. It's my destiny!
- Oh!
- (clanging)
Emergency
at the chemical factory!
- Georgia, no!
- (crashing)
Emergency!
Fire on the zip line!
- Georgia, no!
- Whoa!
- (smashing)
Emergency on Brooklyn Bridge!
- But I got it...
- No, Georgia, no!
- ...under control!
- No!
(whimpers)
(soft music)
- The doctor says it's nothing.
- Stop with that!
- (Ember) Oh?
- You could've broken your neck.
But Ember was the fire truck.
- And we had to go save people!
- Georgia, enough!
No more rescues inside the house
or on the street,
or at the bottom of the sea,
or on top of a mountain,
in the jungle, in the desert,
or on the moon.
Dad, there can't be a fire
on the moon. There's no oxygen.
I know that.
(breathing hard)
Listen to me. No more
fireman games anywhere at all.
But I have to train
to be a fireman
if I want to save lots of people
just like you.
Georgia, I'm a tailor now.
I don't save people from fires.
I save them
from holes in their pants.
Do you think
I would be a good fireman?
Yes, you'd be a great fireman.
You have the heart for it,
but... (sighs)
In that case, no one
can stop me. Not even you.
(Ember whimpers)
I have to tell her, Ember.
(sighs)
The longer we wait,
the worse it will be.
(sighs)
Nice hat.
I may need to borrow it
for the spaghetti later, though.
Or else there'd be
a meatball emergency.
Yeah. (chuckles) Funny.
Georgia...
Do you know why we say fireman
and not firewoman?
To save time?
No, Peanut.
Because girls aren't allowed
to be firemen.
- It's against the rules.
- Why?
Well, people don't think
girls are strong enough
for such a dangerous job.
But I'm training
so I get really strong.
And I'm brave.
As brave as any boy.
You know I am.
I do know. There's no one
who deserves it more.
But I'm afraid
those are the rules.
- Will the rules change?
- I hope they will.
But these things
can take a long time.
And I wouldn't want you
waiting around
for something
that might never happen.
But you can be a seamstress
and work with me!
Is the sewing machine on fire?
No.
In that case, no, thank you.
Georgia, I don't how else
to say this:
you will never be a fireman!
(soft gasp)
- Oh, I'm sorry, Peanut.
- (sighs)
I know it's unfair.
(whimpers)
(sighs)
(soft music)
(Ember whimpers)
(Shawn sighs)
I know.
One day I'll have to tell her
the whole story...
Just not yet.
Okay, Ember, let's go.
(whimpers softly)
(whispering) I promise
I'll always protect you.
(growling, grunting)
(grunting)
(crying)
(crying continues)
(dramatic music)
Approaching the auditorium now.
It's just like the other fires.
Colored smoke, intense light,
and the same strange music.
(man over radio)
Enter with extreme caution.
You know what happened
to the others.
- Send water.
- Sending water.
Wait for my order
to open the nozzle.
We're going in.
(dramatic organ music)
Georgia! Come on!
(gulps)
Ooh! Yes!
Oh, yeah, hmm...
Georgia, this is your last call!
- Morning, Daddy.
- Finally. Now hurry up and eat.
We have sew much to do today.
Argh, you're hilarious.
You have me in stitches.
Oh, you're as cute
as a button.
Well, we are
cut from the same cloth.
(lively jazz music)
(yawns)
(radio) We interrupt
the Champion Spark Plug Hour
with a special news flash.
Yet another Broadway theater
has been hit by the arsonist.
Mayor Jimmy Murray
wants everyone to calm down.
He had this to say
earlier today:
(Jimmy) Everyone needs
to calm down.
(radio stops)
You know what we need?
Here is Georgia Nolan for WKBZ
interviewing Shawn Nolan.
I heard you hit
a new alteration record today.
Is this true?
Before I answer,
have we punned out yet?
Of course not.
In that case, it seams
I'm going to be inducted
into the sewing
hall of fame.
(chuckles) Nice one.
- (honking)
- (gasps)
(siren wailing)
Do you think it's the arsonist?
I don't know. Anyway, I'm happy
you're not on that truck.
- What do you mean?
- Well, don't you remember?
When you were little,
you wanted to be a fireman?
- Did I?
- Pff...
Oh, yeah. Very, very badly.
That's silly.
Girls don't get to be firemen.
Yeah. You could have lived
your dream if you were a boy.
Come on, lazybones.
- (Georgia grunts)
- (Ember snores)
Ember! (grunts)
- Stop!
- (whines)
(Georgia panting)
Girls can't be firemen?
- Give me a break.
- (yawns)
You wanna know
what I think, Ember?
Well, I'll tell you anyway.
All these years of training
at night, in the cold,
in the rain, in the snow
are finally gonna pay off.
I've worked and worked
and worked
and now my chance is coming.
I can smell it.
Can you smell it?
(whimpers, sniffs)
Smell harder.
- Wait. I hear something.
- Huh?
Ember, shh!
Oh! Look.
Look. The police.
Wh...? Ember. Ember.
Jimmy Murray.
That's Jimmy Murray,
the mayor of New York!
- Shawn!
- What's he doing here?
Dad?
- (Shawn) OK.
- They know each other?
I'm going down!
Oh, Ember, don't fuss.
They'll never see me.
(screams silently) Ooh!
- Oh!
- (Jimmy) Listen to me, Shawn.
This arsonist has already
burnt 40 theaters.
And get this, with no flames,
just blue and red smoke.
And creepy music.
(Shawn) The newspapers
spoke of missing firemen...
(Jimmy) Nah, idle gossip,
maybe one or two.
- Hah!
- Come on, Jimmy, spill it.
(Jimmy) Alright. All of them.
- (whispering) All of them?
- (Shawn) What do you mean?
The firemen that go into the
theaters, they don't come out.
- They just disappear.
- (Georgia gasps)
You're telling me
that all the firemen
in New York have vanished?
(grunts)
All but one.
Oh, no, no, no, Jimmy.
I know what you're gonna ask me,
but I'm out.
Hey, Shabbat Shalom, y'all!
How ya doin'?
Don't forget to vote Jimmy
Murray! Polls open on Tuesday.
Not Saturday.
Good, right?
You got it? Okay.
No excuses, now.
The show must go on!
I gotta do something now.
So I need you to run
the fire investigation,
just for a few days,
for old times' sake...
whaddya say ol' buddy,
ol' pal o' mine?
Oh, please, don't say...
- No.
- No?
(screams silently)
I appreciate the offer, Jimmy.
But I'm a tailor now.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Listen,
I know why you left, Shawn.
But this is your chance
to get over what happened.
Finish your career with a bang.
(sighs) I'll never get over it.
- Hmm.
- Good night, Jimmy.
(relieved sigh)
The whole city is in danger.
Nobody's safe...
not even your daughter.
(sighs)
- I'll need a team.
- Yes!
Oh-ho-ho...
As many guys as you want.
No, no, no. A small team.
Just a chemist
and a driver, a fast one.
And I want all the evidence
you've got.
Photos, samples, everything.
- Done and done!
Your team will be at the
firehouse tomorrow, Shawnie.
Excuse me. Captain Nolan.
(engine roaring)
- (barks)
- I'm okay.
I'm okay.
(whines)
(Georgia) Oh, my gosh! What kind
of tailoring emergency?
(Shawn)
It's a corduroy disaster.
(gasps)
That does sound serious.
I know, so I have no choice
but to leave you alone
for a couple of days,
and I'm worried.
Relax. Everything will be fine.
Ember will protect me.
Hmm?
Honey, you know what?
Don't work. You know?
- Take a personal day.
- Oh!
I didn't know
we had personal days.
We do now. You stay home!
Of course.
I have a radio. I'm all set.
Dad, go deal
with that corduroy disaster.
- Wait, wait, wait!
- (door bangs shut)
(muffled) Okay, okay!
- Uh, love you! See you tonight.
- So, here's the plan.
(whimpers)
I join Dad's team,
I catch the arsonist,
I save the city,
they change the rules,
and I get to be
the first fireman... woman.
(groans)
For hair,
a mix of engine oil,
black shoe polish and honey.
Marshmallow in the cheeks
to form the jaw.
Putty for the nose.
For thighs, a mix of sawdust
and cucumber peel.
Pillows in the shoulders.
Egg crate
for the stomach muscles.
Mango for the biceps.
(coughs)
(gasps for air)
Don't worry, Ember.
Dad won't recognize me.
(grunts)
And for the mustache,
carpet fringes.
(masculine voice) Huh. Hello.
Why, yeah, I do fight fires...
with my bare hands.
(gasps)
Thanks for giving me
a better idea.
(whimpers)
(masculine voice) Hey, sister,
looking for a mister?
(chuckles)
What?
Oh!
Okay. Too much.
Too much.
I knew it was too much.
I said it.
(♪ Wham!: "I'm Your Man")
♪ Baby ♪
♪ I'm your man ♪
♪ Don't you know that, baby ♪
♪ You bet ♪
(gasps) Creep!
♪ Do it with me ♪
♪ If you're gonna do it
do it right, right ♪
- ♪ Do it with me ♪
- Oh!
♪ If you're gonna do it,
do it right, right ♪
♪ Do it with me... ♪
Uh, you're squishing
my mangoes.
♪ Wanna take you,
wanna make you ♪
♪ But they tell me
it's a crime ♪
♪ Oh, everybody knows
where the good people go ♪
♪ But where we're going, baby ♪
- ♪ Ain't no such word as no ♪
- Aaah!
- ♪ Baby, I'm your man ♪
- Wow.
♪ Don't you know who I am? ♪
♪ Baby, I'm your man... ♪♪
Manhattan, here I am.
Whoa.
Extra! Extra!
Read all about it!
Panic grips city!
Arsonist strikes again!
Plus: the Chrysler Building
is now the tallest building
in the world!
- And couple does the jitterbug.
- Wow!
Hey, excuse me. Hey.
Hey. Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'm looking for the Times Square
firehouse. Hey...
- Hey! Whoa! Hey!
- Watch it, okay!
- Go back to Jersey, you bum!
- Whoa!
Hey! You want a pickle?
We got, uh, garlic,
and, uh...
extra garlic too.
Smells like it.
Um, could you point me
in the direction
of the Times Square firehouse?
Sure, so, uh, what you wanna do
is take your first right
onto Who Cares Street.
Then head straight down to, uh,
oh, what is it again?
Oh, right.
Do-I-Look-Like-a-Map Boulevard!
Whoa! Thank you, sir.
That's so kind of you.
Lousy tourist.
Didn't even buy a pickle.
- Garlic pickle?
- Argh!
(man) Taxi! (whistles)
(soft music)
H... Hello? (clears throat)
(masculine voice)
I mean, hello!
Anyone here? (gasps)
(chuckles)
(epic music)
(grunts, chuckles happily)
(hums)
Hey!
Hi!
Ting. Pooh!
(horn blares)
(clears throat)
Huh...
Oh!
(chuckling)
(gasps)
Huh...
Are you one of the volunteers?
(clears throat)
Mm-hm.
Do I know you?
Mh-mm-mm-mm-mh.
Come on, then. You're late.
(relieved sigh)
(frame clanging)
Pfff!
Okay, I'm Captain Shawn Nolan
and I will be running
the fire investigation.
We have an arsonist to stop
and we have 800 firemen to find.
Now, I know you aren't
professionals and it's a...
Oh, yes! Yes!
An amazing speech!
Goosebumps!
I'm telling you.
(whispering) We have no time.
Let me introduce your team.
Now, here's the brains
of your operation, Ricardo.
- Your chemist.
- Actually, sir,
I would describe myself more
as a physicist,
given my experiments
on Einstein's theory of quanta
in photoelectric effects
in kinetic energy.
- (gasps)
- That's my man!
He talks like a calculator.
Where did you graduate
college, Ricardo?
Actually I, uh, do my research
at home in my basement.
- Hmm...
- Where I live with my mama.
- (Shawn growls)
- Very nice.
Home school. Amazing.
You did that with your kid,
right, Shawn?
Oh... yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jin's your driver.
Fastest cabbie in Manhattan.
Everyone knows him as
the Checker Cheetah of Chelsea.
Yeah, I'm the Cheetah.
The Cheetah? How old are you?
- Fifteen, sir.
- Fifteen?
- Twenty-one.
- You just said fifteen.
No, I said twenty-one.
- He said fifteen.
- No, no, he said twenty-one.
Oh... And who's this third one?
I only asked for the two.
- Wait. You didn't find him?
- Me? No. Who are you?
Oh, me? Uh, I'm Georg...
uh, Georg...
Gior-gio,
Giorgio, Giorgio. Joe!
I'm Joe! I'm Joe!
I'm a fireman.
I'm Joe the fireman!
Fireman Joe.
(chuckles, grunts)
(farts)
A fireman?
Are you sure I don't know you?
No! No, no.
I live, I live, uh, far away.
Uh, I'm a man.
And I'm strong.
- I'm strong!
- Take him.
- I'm a fireman.
- He has experience.
Alright. Welcome...
Ugh.
- ...aboard!
- Ho!
Oh, uh, I'm a sweater.
(chuckles)
Uh, and I eat a lot of mangoes.
- A lot of mangoes.
- Can I uh, talk to you?
- You can taste it...
- Tell me this is a joke.
Nah, they're the only ones
who accepted
this suicide mission.
I mean potentially suic...
You know what I mean.
- I'm strong and a fireman!
- (alarm ringing)
Okay, team, suit up!
Suit up! Suit up!
- Excuse me? For what?
- Maybe a fire?
Oh!
(rapid breathing)
Ooh!
- Oh, good gravy!
- Good luck, my friend.
City is counting on me!
I mean, you. Counting on you.
I'm actually doing this?
Hoo!
(Ricardo reciting a prayer)
(chuckles)
Come on, you know
there's an alarm, right?
We shouldn't be wasting
our time.
(tires screeching)
Hey!
Easy there, Cheetah!
Relax.
I'm an expert driver.
In a cab, not a ladder truck!
One's red, one's yellow,
same diff!
The Cheetah's back!
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wrong way!
Turn around! Turn around!
But this is my shortcut.
Normally I'd ask for a tip.
Normally a fifteen-year-old kid
doesn't drive a ladder truck!
I'm twenty-one.
In Cheetah years?
- Yeah, baby!
- Are you okay?
(Ricardo vomits)
(gasps) Oh no!
Oh! No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, not good.
(jazz music)
Nice. Wha...
That's it. Whoa, whoa.
Whoa! Oh...
Beautiful butt hair.
Ho-ho-ho-ho!
Oh, I could be
doing alterations right now.
Whoa... Whoaaa!
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa!
♪ I got pickles in my pocket
and I don't care who knows... ♪
Help me! Help me!
Help me, please!
(Shawn) Watch out!
(Ricardo) Dividing
the width of the truck
by the width of the road,
I calculate
a 99% chance of death!
(Shawn) Jin, did you hear him?
Jin, did you hear him regarding
our chances of survival?
Jin, stop the engine!
Jin, stop this truck!
Stop the truck! Jin! Jin!
Captain, look!
We saved 12 seconds!
No more shortcuts allowed!
No more shortcuts allowed.
Okay, the theater is
on the next block. Get ready.
Tanks on and follow my orders.
- Any questions?
- What?
Oh, hi. What did I miss?
The street!
(all yelling)
Oh, Captain, are we there yet?
- Not yet.
- Hmm...
Whoa!
- Wow!
- Wh... What is it?
I don't know... Ricardo?
It could be potassium or copper
acetate, maybe lithium chlorate.
But that would only make sense
for the flames, not the smoke.
I need to run tests.
At home. With mi mama.
Arsonist,
we're coming to get you!
Yeah! We're gonna kick
your flaming multicolored butt!
Yeah!
(laughing)
- Hmm.
- Captain, what's going on?
Some arsonists like to come back
to the scene of the crime,
so keep your eyes peeled.
(Georgia) Keep my eyes peeled,
got it.
Hmm...
Who is that?
(high-pitched voice) Only the
most luminous star on Broadway:
Laura Divine.
(clears throat)
Captain Neil, Chief of
the New York Police Department.
Shawn Nolan.
Happy to have you on
the fire investigation, Captain.
With you here, the police,
led by yours truly,
can now focus
on finding the missing firemen.
Glad to be of service, Captain.
Amazing!
We secured the perimeter,
and there are no civilians
inside the building.
- Empty!
- Thank you, Captain Neil.
Okay, I'll go see
what we're up against.
- Joe, stretch a line.
- Right away, Captain.
Ah!
Really hope no one saw that.
(grunts)
Slow down, Joe!
Did you even check the...
Aaah!
(sighs)
The water pressure.
(screaming)
(laughs)
That's one crazy hose.
It's not the hose.
- (screaming)
- (Jin) Stay calm!
Stay calm!
Okay, panic! Panic!
I miss my mama!
I want to go...
(screaming)
It will be fine!
I'm coming, buddy!
Eeeh...
(panting)
You said you had training.
- I've been training for years.
- Where, clown school?
Never mind. Come with me.
We're gonna water the front.
But if the smoke
contains cyanogen,
you'll die of hypoxia
in only 29 seconds!
That's why I need you
to collect smoke samples.
And that's why I'm going home!
- (birds chirping)
- Great!
Okay, we all know
that firemen who go inside
burning theaters disappear,
they vanish,
but that will not happen to us
because we will stay outside
watering the front
until the fire is out.
Then and only then will we
go inside and look for clues.
Okay?
Jin, extend the ladder.
- Extend the ladder!
- Ugh!
(sighs)
On it like a bonnet.
Let's get vertical, people.
Top floor: ladies' hosiery,
Brylcreem,
and arsonists.
(whimpering)
(dramatic music)
(panting)
Get a load of me.
- I'm a natural.
- Oh!
Jin, wake up!
Wake up, please!
- He's asleep! Jin!
- Stop, Jin!
- Hold on!
- Whoa!
(clattering)
(both grunting)
(coughs)
How is this possible?
I have no idea!
Back up.
We shouldn't be in here.
That wasn't the plan.
We're getting out now!
Captain!
Captain, I saw something move.
- Never mind that now. Come on!
- I got this!
No, no, no! Joe, that's an...
Oh, for Pete's sake!
What is it,
ignore the captain day?
(coughing, rapid breathing)
(dramatic music)
Ahh!
(coughs)
(panting)
I know you're here somewhere!
You show yourself!
(panting)
(hissing)
I thought I disposed
of all of your kind.
You... You don't scare me.
Yes, I do.
Aaahh!
In the name
of the great city of New York,
you're...
you're under arrest!
How cute. Here.
- Catch.
- Oh!
Aaah!
(loud orchestral music)
Ah!
What was that?
(shaky breathing)
The arsonist.
Were you planning
on dancing with him?
Stop that!
We have to get out of here.
Right now! Come on!
(coughing)
Oh, thank goodness!
They're alive!
They're alive, everyone!
- Come quickly! Quickly!
- (coughing, gasping for air)
You...
- (Jin) You just saw a ghost!
- (Ricardo) A ghost?
Okay, that's where
I draw the line. The occult?
- I am done!
- I don't know what it was.
What I do know is I almost
caught the arsonist.
Hey, Captain, I was just
telling them abo...
Telling them what?
That it was a fiasco?
Actually, Comandante,
I would say it's a success
considering we are still alive.
Of course you're alive.
You ran!
True, but in my defense,
I didn't get very far.
Firemen go in together,
stay together,
come out together.
- That's how this works.
- Yes, Comandante.
And Jin, explain to me
how you fell asleep.
Not me, Jackson.
The Cheetah never falls as...
(snores)
(sighs)
What? Oh, hi.
What did I miss?
Oh... Okay.
Sometimes I "faint"
when my emotions are too strong.
I was "fired" by the cab company
for "allegedly"
running over a newsstand.
I guess I "should" have
told you, Captain.
(long exhale) Hmm.
Anybody got anything else
to tell me?
- Mm-mm.
- No, Captain.
We won't disappoint you again,
Captain.
I wasn't talking to you, Joe.
You lied to me, and that's it.
I don't wanna see you
around here ever again.
(clears throat)
Captain, Nolan.
My men haven't seen
any more signs of smoke.
You're clear to enter
and start your investigation.
Thank you, Captain Neil.
I'll use the stage door.
Captain! Captain!
Go back to wherever
you came from, Joe.
I just wanna say you're right.
I'm not a real fireman... yet.
But it's all I've ever wanted.
I've read every single book
and I train every single day,
but firefighting for real is...
well, it's a lot different.
Of course it's a lot different.
It's not a game.
And pretending
you were a fireman
put all our lives at risk.
I'm a father, Joe.
I need to go home at night.
You understand me?
Yeah. Yeah. Believe me, I do.
But I really wanna help you
stop the arsonist.
Please, please give me
another chance.
(sighs)
Hmm.
(door creaks)
Complete honesty from
here on in. Do you understand?
Oh, thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Yeah, yeah. Okay.
Now follow me.
(under her breath) Yes!
Cheetah loves that guy.
He's the cat's pajamas.
(snores)
Oh...
(Shawn) What is going on?
This isn't normal, is it?
No...
We're about 40 miles
from normal.
- Um...
- Oh!
Sorry.
(uncomfortable chuckle)
(Shawn) Everything is burnt to
a crisp and yet still standing.
How could the fire
burn the entire auditorium
but not destroy
the rest of the theater?
That's the question.
Mm-hm...
It's burning, but it's cold.
- Don't touch it...
- Oops.
Unless I say you can.
Could have been worse...
(gasps)
- (chuckles nervously)
- Good grief...
Okay...
To collect clues,
you have to use your senses.
Touch... Sight.
Sound...
(retching)
I didn't say taste.
I was gonna say smell.
(sneezes)
Do you think that's
what happened to the firemen?
I... I mean, vaporized?
Hmm. One step at a time.
First we have to figure out
the origin of the fire
to know what happened.
The origin, got it.
Each fire has a story.
We are looking for various
marks and patterns
imprinted by the smoke,
heat, and fire.
And when we find these patterns,
we can trace the path of fire
back to its origin.
Good golly.
Hey!
Am I boring you?
- Dad!
- What?
Uh, had, ha...
I had... I have... Pfff!
I have something to show you.
Come here!
Uh...
This better be good, kid.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's good.
Come here. Look.
Hurry up. Come on.
Look! Look at the impact!
(Shawn) Whoa...
Whatever it was,
it was thrown from here...
From the stage.
He's not an arsonist.
I mean, he is, but he sees
himself as a performer...
Doing a show,
with lights and music.
Interesting... but just a theory
unless we can figure out
what caused that impact.
Hmm.
This?
Hmm?
The arsonist threw it at me.
Mm-hm.
You just found
the origin of the story.
Well done, son.
I like that you call me "son."
(chuckles)
Firemen are a big family.
Let's take this back
to the firehouse.
Huh. Origin of the story!
Yes! Ooh!
(clears throat)
Sorry...
Something in my throat.
(Shawn) Hey, Joe, come on!
(locker door bangs shut)
Ah, this is great!
We'll give it to Ricardo first
thing in the morning to analyze.
I haven't seen you
this happy in a long time.
Yeah? Well, you've known me
since this morning.
Oh, of course. It's just,
uh, I feel like I've known you
my, you know, my whole life.
Yeah, really?
- Oh, God!
- Ow!
Say hello to the brave men
who are going to bring
the arsonist to justice!
(reporters ask questions)
You called the press, Jimmy?
Sorry. City Hall leaks
like a sieve.
Let today put an end
to the rumors
about there being fewer
and fewer firemen to protect us!
- See, here...
- Oh!
... is Joe,
a truly unique fireman.
He's strong.
He's a real man.
Don't look at me.
You look into the camera.
You're working
for my re-election.
- Look happy. Now go!
- You're crushing my hand! Oh!
Don't forget to vote
Jimmy Murray.
Polls open on Tuesday!
The show must go on!
Captain, Jimmy is using
this crisis to get re-elected.
Yeah, tell me something
I don't know.
Okay. I... I think
he's the arsonist!
(chuckles)
Jimmy? No way.
He'd sell out his own
grandmother to get re-elected.
Actually, he did. She's doing
three years in Sing Sing...
But arson?
Nah, he's not that kind of guy.
- I know you're friends, but...
- Don't run, Joe.
- Firemen walk with purpose.
- But I am walking.
It's an expression, son. It
means don't jump to conclusions.
Oh, yeah, no, I knew that.
I knew that.
No, you didn't.
But I like your spirit.
Alright, Joe, go home.
Come on. Tomorrow will be
critical and I need you rested.
And, yeah, I'm happy.
I've missed all this.
I knew you did.
And you gave it all up for me.
Hoh! Hoh!
Gotta fly!
(lively jazz music)
Oh!
Oh! Hey! Hey! Ember!
- Ember!
- (barks)
Hey! Hey! Hey, Ember!
- Yes! Yes! I'm home!
- Hey!
Hooo! My little
doggie doggie-doodoo.
How are ya?
Did you girls have a nice day?
What's this smile
you're giving me. That's sweet.
Hmm?
(panting)
Let's go see what Georgia's
been up to, shall we?
She won't believe
the day I've had.
Upstairs.
Hey, Georgia, I'm back!
I'll be right up!
(panting)
(Georgia) Hey, Ember!
Stall him!
Stall him, please.
(Shawn) Georgia?
(knocking)
Are you there, Georgia?
(barking)
How was your day?
(whimpers) Ruff!
Yeah, mine was
pretty rough too.
(chuckles)
Can I come in?
(grunts)
- Wha...?
- (whimpers)
- Hey, Dad. How was your day?
- What?
I'll be with you
in one second?
Did you see that, Ember?
(whimpers)
Gotta switch to decaf.
(panting)
Wow. You're so good
under pressure.
(whimpers)
Dad, tell me everything
that happened
with the corduroy crisis.
The what? Oh, right!
The corduroy crisis!
Oh! Oh! It was...
It was... terrifying.
The lines, they were going
the wrong way.
- And there was the texture...
- Oh, wow...
What?
I just think you're amazing,
and I think I'm lucky
to have you as my dad.
(soft chuckle)
Well, it'll be over soon,
and we'll get back
to our quiet,
safe and peaceful little life.
Tsk. I can't wait.
(dramatic music)
Sorry, boys.
Last-minute change
in the program.
I have to deal
with the last four of you.
Then I'll be ready
for my grand opening.
But this time, all of New York
will be my stage.
(gasps)
(Shawn, whispering)
Have a good day, my love.
(yawns) Dad!
Dad, how are you?
(clears throat)
I've been thinking.
In... in... in... my sleep,
in my dreams.
Why don't you take Ember
with you today?
- Huh?
- She'd love it.
Look how happy she is!
- (barks)
- Aren't you so happy, Ember?
Oh, you're so happy!
Yes, you are. You're so happy.
I... I can't take her.
Who would look after you?
Dad, stop treating me
like a baby. Don't you trust me?
- Of course I do, but...
- Then prove it.
Take her. It'll be good
for my independence.
Are you all right, Peanut?
Do you want me to call a doctor?
Oh, no, no, I'm good.
(forced laugh) Huh. Hmm...
- You'll stay home all day?
- Tsk. Just like yesterday!
Okay, then. Ember, let's go!
(growls)
Bye, Ember.
See you later.
Yes, I will.
Oh, yes, I will.
- Yoo-hoo!
- Huh!
- (laughs)
- You again?
Argh! Do I look like a taxi cab?
(yelling)
(gasps)
What in the world...?
Buenos dias, Comandante.
Hey, chief! We gonna nab this
no-goodnik fire ghost or what?
Morning, Captain!
One cream, two sugars, right?
Hmm. Yeah, that's right...
We came in early to get
a jump-start on things.
- Hmm.
- Oh, what a sweet doggie.
- Hello, boy. What's your name?
- It's Ember. She's a girl.
Oh, Ember.
I'm so happy you're here.
We're gonna have an amazing day.
(barks)
So that's how it's gonna be.
(growls)
Captain, Rick is analyzing
the fireball.
He's trying to find out
why it didn't explode.
Inside the ball,
there's a mixture of sulfur,
charcoal
and potassium nitrate...
plus a trace of nitro glycerin
and sorbents.
Translation, please.
(grunts)
Gunpowder and dynamite.
- (spits)
- Oh, hey, don't worry, Captain.
The glass is unbreakable.
- Oh, I see.
- And over here...
Jin is making some amazing
improvements to the truck.
It's Cheetah.
I already added my hanging dice
and my wooden-bead seat cover.
So, Captain, can I drive?
- Of course you can't drive.
- What? But I'm the best driver!
(snores)
Am I the only one
who sees this as a problem?
Jin is awfully fast
when he's awake.
And he does know
all the quickest routes.
Amazingly, I need a driver
who's always awake.
- (snoring)
- So, look what we've installed.
- (bell dinging)
- Ow!
What? Oh, hi.
What did I miss?
Nothing. You can drive.
Skiddle-dee-do!
The Cheetah is back!
Captain Neil delivered all
the evidence compiled so far.
Photos, samples,
even audio recordings.
There's only the one theater
left on Broadway.
The mystery is,
how does the arsonist
get into the theaters
when there are
police everywhere?
Isn't it obvious?
He's a ghost!
Huh? A ghost?
Aah! Oh...
(scoffs) Can you drop
the silly ghost theory, Jin?
Okay. Let me try.
Nope, I can't. It's too good.
Enough! We only have one more
chance to catch the arsonist.
- Ricardo?
- Hmm?
You take a shower.
And then keep analyzing
that fireball.
Okay, Comandante.
Jin turn this truck
into a rocket.
Done and done, Captain.
- Good briefing, Joe.
- Thank you.
You come with me.
I'm gonna train you.
(humming happily)
Welcome to the fire
simulation room.
Ooh... It's really hot.
(small cough)
(Shawn) Temperatures can reach
2,000 degrees.
Relax. Get to know
your worst enemy.
He is fierce...
- Oh!
- Powerful.
Hey! Where you going?
Okay. I can do this. Give it to
me. What have you got?
- I can do this.
- Okay. Okay, Joe, relax.
I know you're strong
and in excellent condition,
but technique... Wait, wait!
That was a back draft.
I told you, don't run.
Walk with purpose.
But firemen have to be...
fast and brave.
(grunts)
You take recklessness
for bravery.
(panting)
(lively jazz music)
- Aaah! Oh!
- Reckless.
You didn't analyze the situation
or assess the risk.
That's not bravery,
it's just stupid.
Um, I think I get it.
Can you pull me up now?
I'll think about it
a little longer.
Captain... Captain,
that's not funny. Come on...
Captain!
(Shawn) Very impressive, Joe.
- You're a fast learner.
- Oh, thank you, Captain.
That means so much
coming from you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Don't get distracted.
- You keep the nozzle turning.
- Yeah, yeah!
Of course, Captain.
Sorry, Captain.
It's funny,
you remind me of my daughter.
- Huh?
- She's about your age.
Really? Yeah, that is funny.
(forced chuckle)
Hmm. Yeah, she wanted
to be a fireman too.
But you don't think girls
should be firemen?
No, of course
they should be firemen.
So why didn't you teach her
what you're teaching me?
- It's complicated.
- Why, because she's a girl?
No, because she's my daughter.
I mean, I love her
and I worry about her
every second of my life.
- Aw.
- And I have to protect her.
I mean, she's lots of attention,
she's delicate,
she's sensitive,
the world freaks her out...
Aaaah!
Hey! What the heck was that?
Sorry, Captain.
Yeah, you'll see
how fragile I am.
(sirens wailing)
It's the Lyceum,
Laura Divine's theater.
- Hurry, Jin!
- The Cheetah's on it!
- (snores)
- Hoh! Hoh! Wake up, Jin!
(Georgia) On it!
Hey! Easy on the ol'
pie hole there.
Well, that works...
Ricardo, how's it going?
Are you getting any closer?
Hold on.
(muffled) Can I call you later?
(alarm ringing)
(Divine) Pauline, turn that off!
(Pauline) Right away,
Miss Divine!
(Divine) Okay. From the top!
(cabaret-style music)
♪ Baby, look at me ♪
♪ And tell me what you see... ♪
All that smoke on stage
must have tripped the alarm.
I thought you shut
all the theaters, Captain Neil.
We did! We've kicked
Miss Divine out four times!
And this is the fifth time
she's come back.
♪ Don't you know who I am? ♪
♪ Remember my name ♪
♪ I'm gonna live forever ♪
♪ I'm gonna learn how to fly ♪
♪ I feel it co... ♪
Stop! Stop! Stop!
I have replicas of every tiara
she's worn
since she took Broadway by storm
20 years ago, mm-hm!
The star is never
out of the spotlight!
You think I like hanging here
like a side of beef?
- Reset me!
- Yes, Miss Divine!
Right away, Miss Divine!
Joe, go talk to that poor lady
working the ropes
and see if she has
any information.
- Hmm.
- I'll take the drama queen.
- Oh! Where are we going?
- I meant Miss Divine.
Ahem! Of course. Hmm!
♪ Baby, look at me ♪
♪ And tell me what... ♪
Whoa!
Ms. Divine!
Captain Nolan from the FDNY.
- May I have a word?
- Lights!
Talk fast or there's a chance
I may lose
my signature good humor.
The police evacuated
your theater
for your own safety,
Miss Divine.
Huge fan!
(Shawn groans)
There is a very good chance
that this theater will go up
in smoke like all the others.
My premiere is in three days.
Have you ever heard
what the show must do?
- (soft chuckle)
- Umm... Go on?
That's right!
I don't know
who you think you are
or where you come from, but...
- Ahem!
- Oh!
So, Pauline, is it?
- You work for Miss Divine?
- Yes.
Her personal assistant
for two months now,
but I've been kicking around
Broadway for 20 years.
Uh-huh.
Just don't have much
to show for it.
Anyway, you must be part
of the mayor's heroic fire team.
That's right. I'm Joe.
Oh, I saw your photo
in the paper.
I never forget a handsome face.
(laughs) No, no... Ahem.
Oh.
Oh... Uh, thank you.
I'm so glad you're here, Joe.
I'm a little jittery.
Actually, very.
But nothing scares Miss Divine.
Say it!
Unless I'm the arsonist?
Uh, well, I'm just doing my job,
Miss Divine,
covering all my bases.
I grew up cleaning houses
and babysitting for rich people
who told me:
"Now, don't you kiss the baby,
Miss Laura."
"Don't you eat off the china,
I saved every penny I earned
so I could get out of there
and come to Broadway.
- And when a dancer quit...
- (gasps)
...guess who was ready
to step in and save the day?
- You were.
- Yes.
Now, respectfully,
get the heck out of my theater.
Pull me back up, Pauline!
Right away, Miss Divine!
(grunts)
Miss Divine, I can't let you
continue to rehearse.
You gotta come with me.
Would you say something?
Will you sign my face?
Not that!
I wanna fly! Yes!
Yes! Higher!
Yes, Miss Divine!
I wanna fly!
(grunts)
Higher!
- (clicking)
- (Pauline) Whoa!
(screams)
Pauline!
(shouts)
You just clipped
the wings of an angel!
(sobs)
Oh... I feel like a failure
in my life.
There's nothing I can do.
Oh, Pauline,
please don't worry.
I'm... I'm pretty sure
she's gonna recover.
(Divine) Get me
out of here right now!
Miss Divine, there is
no need to get upset.
Everything is gonna be fine.
(whispering) Where's the crane?
Don't worry, Miss Divine!
Get me the crane.
See?
Sounds like she'll recover.
- I mess everything up.
- Don't be so hard on yourself.
Maybe this is a sign
that it's time
you follow your own dreams.
I never gave up on mine.
Easy for you to say.
You're a man.
Not really.
(whispering) I'm all girl.
My name is Georgia.
Georgia?
What an amazing costume.
The mustache is very convincing.
It's my dog's butt hair.
It was the only way.
If I catch the arsonist, they'll
have to change the rules.
Then I'll be
the first fireman woman.
Oh...
The first... firefighter.
Firefighter.
Yeah! I love that.
- You're very inspiring.
- Hmm.
(humming)
(sighs)
It's not the first time
you've seen him here?
No.
He's always sneaking around.
Hmm. Okay.
Psst! Be careful...
Joe.
(humming)
(panting)
Hmmm.
(plays simple melody)
(dramatic organ music)
The music...
- Aah!
- (coughing)
I'm so sorry, Captain.
Are you okay?
I'm really, really sorry,
but we have to go back
to the firehouse, okay?
- Can you breathe?
- (coughs)
I hope you have
a good explanation.
I do. I really do. I am so sorry
for your... for your throat.
Experiment number 26:
integrating the music recorded
at the scene of the fires.
Here we go.
(music starts)
Oh, you were right, Joe.
The music,
it activates the fireball.
Jiminy cricket!
(Ricardo) Oh...
I've never seen a material
create light
in reaction to sound.
- The work of a true artist.
- Or a ghost...
- Bu-bu-bu-bu-bu.
- Mm-hm?
- From the future.
- (sighs)
No, no, no. Ember.
Ember, come back. Sit here.
- Sit here with me.
- Approaching 90 seconds.
(clinking)
(all) Oh! Oh! Oh!
Ember! Ember? Captain, Jin,
get down, get down!
What's going on?
What's happening?
The light has hypnotized them!
The last five notes
cause the explosion!
- (Ricardo) I cannot move.
- Rick! Rick, it's spreading.
We have to get them
out of here right now!
I cannot move.
I cannot move!
Hey, it's okay. It's okay
to be scared. I'm scared too.
But you can still be brave.
Rick. Rick, look at me.
Go in together, stay together,
come out together.
Come on!
Okay. Okay.
Oh, wow. I didn't expect that.
(yelling)
(panting)
Oh, I did it. I did it!
Yes, I did it!
Looks like the training
paid off, Dad.
Captain Neil, we know
how to stop the arsonist.
I repeat, we know
(Neil) Oh! That's fabulous.
We are on our way
to Laura Divine's theater.
But Captain Nolan wants you
to evacuate all of Midtown.
(Neil) I'm all over it!
Guys, I'm sorry
I was hard on you.
I expected nothing, and at first
that's exactly what I got.
But this turned out to be
a pretty darn good crew.
Ricardo, you saved us in there.
Thank you, Captain.
But perhaps this bravery
was always inside of me,
and it was Joe
who revealed it with...
(vomiting)
Big truck... sick.
I... sorry.
- I'm better now.
- Ugh.
And you too.
Amazing work, Joe.
Thank you.
(siren wailing)
Captain Nolan.
Good to have you here.
We'll have the perimeter
secured in a quick 10 minutes.
We have everything
under control.
Thank you, Captain Neil.
I'll get my men in position too.
- Are you ready?
- (all) Yes, Captain!
Okay, team, I want 10 lines,
inch and three quarters.
Open all the nozzles
in the auditorium
and lock them
between the seats.
I want all of them
targeting the stage.
As soon as the alarm starts,
we turn on the water
and we drown that arsonist.
- Great job team.
- Thank you.
Yeah! (laughs)
(Shawn) Hey, Captain Neil.
Georgia!
Oh, sorry!
Joe!
Pauline!
- Where you going?
- I got fired.
But I'm happy!
You were absolutely right.
It's time for a change.
- Time for me to shine.
- Well, I'm happy for you.
Good luck.
You too, Georgia.
Well, then, this is goodbye.
I just need to fetch my lucky
slippers and then I'm off.
I'm done with New York.
Okay. Well, hurry.
The police are shutting down
all of Midtown.
(pickle guy mutters)
(officer)
Everybody move back.
Hey, you, pickle guy!
Get outta here!
Oh yeah, sure.
I understand. I understand.
- Oh...
- Don't boss me around!
- Hmm...
- (alarm ringing)
He's here. Turn on the water.
Darn it! We've been tricked!
The fire isn't coming
from the auditorium this time!
- Where is it?
- Everywhere!
It's a trap! Abort!
But Pauline just went inside!
I have to save her!
(sighs)
Get ready! We're going in!
(ladder rattles)
(coughing) Come on!
Pauline!
Where'd she go?
Can you see her?
- (coughs)
- You go right, I'll go left!
And use your hose so you don't
get lost in the smoke.
Okay, Captain.
Pauline!
(coughs)
- (panting)
- Pauline, I've got you.
(grunts)
- I thought I would perish.
- (coughs)
- Aaah!
- Pauline!
Save me! Save me!
- Don't let go!
Georgia! Georgia, I can't...
Georgia!
Pauline!
(grunts)
- Stop!
- But Pauline's down there!
- She might still be alive!
- It's too late.
No, I can't risk
losing you both.
We have to get out.
That is an order!
Come on!
(sighs)
(Ember whimpers softly)
I wanted to be a fireman
to save people.
Sixteen years ago, just after
I'd been made captain,
there was a terrible house fire
with a young couple
trapped inside.
When we got there,
we hacked at the walls,
trying to get them out,
but it was too late.
I couldn't save them.
I didn't know how I could go on.
I was devastated.
And I needed to...
I needed to be there
for my daughter.
She was so little then and I...
Anyway, my battalion chief
told me that if I...
wanted to be a real fireman,
I'd have to accept that
sometimes bad things happen
and there's nothing more
you could do.
You have to let it go.
Shawn!
Congratulations!
- For what?
- The auditorium!
- It's saved!
- We lost someone, Jimmy.
And the arsonist
is still on the loose.
Oh, I know, I know.
Terrible, terrible.
I gotta do something.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna put the police.
The police are taking over.
What? No!
I have to stop the arsonist.
Jimmy, don't do this.
We still don't know
where the firemen are.
- Hey!
- The police will find them.
As for the arsonist, he doesn't
have any more theaters to burn.
He's finished. And I have places
to go and people to see.
So, Shawnie, get some rest,
and thanks for the great show.
Show?
Oh, by the way,
I've been re-elected!
♪ Four more years
Four more years... ♪
- I know he's your friend...
- Yeah, whatever.
We stick to him
like white on rice.
Like stink on diapers.
- Hmm.
- Too much, right?
Yeah, too much.
(soft jazz music)
(teeth chatter)
Hmm.
- (teeth chatter)
- Shhh! Hmm.
(whispering)
Three, two, one...
(grunting)
- Hmm?
- (groaning)
- Don't.
- No, I got this, I got this.
Okay, get out of the way, son.
- (grunting)
- No, no! No!
(grunting)
(distorted yelling)
(yells)
(distorted yell)
(distorted barking)
(distorted yelling)
Aaah!
- Dad!
- Dad?
- Cupcake!
- Cupcake?
(both yelling)
- Get it open!
- There's no handle!
Get it open!
Get it open. Get it open.
Good job, Ember.
(echoing) Cupcake?
(Divine muttering)
At least she hasn't lost
her voice.
Jokes, huh?
We'll see how hard you laugh
when you're scrubbing toilets
at Yankee Stadium.
(Divine yelling)
Cupcake, look at you!
- (grunting)
- Look at you, my cupcake.
What are you trying to do
to my fiancée?
Fiancée? I think there's been
a terrible misunderstanding.
We, uh, we... we kind of thought
you were the arsonist.
The arsonist? Me?
It's just you were always
sneaking around the theater.
Only because I love this woman
and we can't be seen together.
Oh, yeah, of course,
I totally understand.
- Society has to change.
- No, no, no, not that.
She doesn't wanna
be seen with me.
Of course I don't wanna
be seen with him!
It's bad for my reputation
to be seen
with a sleazy
double-dealing scoundrel.
But I'm your sleazy
- (barks)
- Oh, cupcake.
Captain! Look!
The firemen must be
down here somewhere.
(Jin) Hey, Cap,
everything alright?
Jin! Get down here
and help Jimmy and Laura!
Call Captain Neil.
We found something.
Sorry, Jimmy, but we have to go
search this subway tunnel.
Congratulations. She'll make a
charming first lady of New York.
When she's back in one piece.
Out of my sight!
(Divine) Aaah! My arm!
Oh! Oh, it hurts.
(Georgia) Hey, hey, Captain,
where are we?
(Shawn) The track
for the BMT train.
Okay. Okay.
- Which way, Ember?
- (sniffing)
(barks)
Go! Go!
Joe...
I think we just found
the lair of the arsonist.
(Georgia) What is this place?
(Shawn) It's an air
distribution chamber.
This must be
where he rehearsed his show.
(Ember whining)
It's hooked up to the fan
like a turbine.
Must take a crazy
amount of energy
to create those fireballs.
Hmm.
- Captain, come here!
- Huh?
Rejection letters.
From every theater on Broadway.
"You belong in a loony bin,
not a theater."
Yeah... PhD in chemistry.
The scientist is a failed artist
who's looking for revenge.
(gasps)
Broadway was just the rehearsal.
The real performance
is happening tonight.
From the top
of the Chrysler Building.
(whimpers, barks)
What?
Hey! I think we found them!
- They're alive!
- Oh, we did it!
We did it! We did it!
We did it!
We certainly did.
I couldn't be
more proud of you, son.
Well, actually...
(chuckles)
...daughter?
(whining)
Look, I know...
I know it was crazy,
I know I promised to give up
this dream, but I couldn't.
And doing this was the only way
to prove myself.
To you. To everyone.
Well, no, you see,
you said that Joe
is an excellent fireman!
I mean... I mean, he's me,
and I'm him, and when
you give me your blessing,
they're gonna have to
change the rules.
- No!
- What? No what?
No, you can't be
a fireman, Georgia.
No matter how good
and strong you are.
- What do you mean?
- I will never allow it.
Oh! But it wasn't a problem
when I was Joe.
Yes, but it's a huge problem
when it's you.
- The job is far too dangerous.
- I don't understand.
You know it's all
I've ever wanted.
You gave this passion to me.
It's in my blood!
It's not in your blood!
What do you mean?
(sighs)
I'm not your real father,
Georgia.
Of... of... of course you are.
I'm not.
(sighs) Do you remember
when I told you
about the couple
I couldn't save 16 years ago?
Even though
they were trapped...
they managed to pass
their baby daughter to me...
three months old.
Her name was Georgia.
I swore to them
I would always protect her.
(whimpers)
If you become a fireman,
I can't keep that promise.
Look at the danger
you're in now.
You used "girls can't be
firemen" to lock me up at home.
That was the only way
I could think to protect you.
- I'm sorry, I was wrong.
- (ball clanging)
(barks)
Georgia!
(dramatic organ music)
(Georgia) What happened?
What happened?
(grunting softly)
Dad! Dad!
People despise change.
Even those
who are closest to you.
- (barks)
- No. Ember! Ember! Ember!
Wait! Wait! No!
Ember, come back!
Ember! Ember!
Ember, wake up.
Wake up, Ember.
I hate little dogs.
Sorry.
Wait... Pauline?
Pauline is dead.
My stage name is Supreme Fury.
What'd you think of my
little death scene? Too much?
We have the same enemies,
you and I.
The ones who say
my art isn't art,
that women can't fight fires.
We are stuck
in their stupid world,
held back just because
we wanna do something
that's never been done before.
Your father... is one of them.
If we wait for them
to catch up,
we could wait our entire lives.
We don't have time for that.
That's why we have to act now.
We'll burn it all down
and start over.
(panting)
The thing is, Pauline...
I might never be a fireman,
but I have the fire in my heart,
and no one can change that.
Not even my father.
Wrong answer, sis.
You're clearly not ready
for center stage.
Too bad you'll miss
my grand finale.
Dad, wake up! Dad! Dad!
Dad! Dad, don't worry,
I'm gonna get you out of this.
Dad, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
Dad! Wake up!
Dad! No!
- No!
- (barks)
- What?
Oh, Ember!
Oh, thank you.
Thank you, Ember.
(grunts)
(barks)
Oh, Dad. Dad, come back!
Come back, please!
Dad, you can do this.
You can do this, Dad.
(grunts)
Dad! Dad!
Dad, come back! Please.
(panting)
(crying)
I smell mangoes.
- (coughs)
- (laughs)
Oh... very funny. Very funny.
You saved me.
Just...
Just doing my job, Captain.
Just doing my job.
I'm so sorry I held you back.
My captain told me that
if wanted to be a real fireman,
I'd have to accept that
sometimes bad things happen,
and there's nothing more
I can do.
You have to let it go.
The day that you were put
in my arms
is the day my life began.
I love you, Dad.
Okay, you find Pauline,
go find the team,
and call Captain Neil.
Ember and I will release
the firemen.
- (barks)
- Are you sure?
Yeah, go save our city,
Georgia.
Looks like I'm gonna have to
get used to this.
Captain Neil here.
Great job, everyone.
We've stopped
the arsonist's van
300 feet from
the Chrysler Building.
- Yes!
- This is a great day
for the city
and for New York's finest.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Come on, I told you.
- Mangoes and Ember's butt hair.
- Ugh!
Did everything smell
like dog butt?
Look, can we talk
about this later?
I wanna be there for the arrest.
But why, when your chances
of actually becoming a fireman
are approximately zero percent?
Life isn't about percentages,
Ricardo,
and it can't be zero
'cause I'm doing it right now.
- Boom!
- You inspire me...
85 percent!
Me too, Joe.
Georgia, I mean.
Sorry, I gotta get used
to it, Joe.
Georgia. Georgia. Georgia.
(Neil) Mayday! Mayday!
She's throwing fireballs.
There's smoke everywhere.
Oh, I can't see anything!
No, no, no. We have to stop her.
We have to stop her!
(dramatic organ music)
Oh! The police cars!
And the police!
They're hypnotized!
And nobody to give me
a speeding ticket!
(Ricardo) Oh, no, no!
(coughs)
- There she is!
- I see her.
No, no, no, no, no!
Come back! Come back!
(grunts)
Oh! What is she doing?
I've no idea,
but I think I'm in love.
Oh, this is no bueno.
- (engine roaring)
- (cackles)
(tires screeching)
(balls rattle)
(hissing)
(grunts)
(brakes squealing)
Thank you for the ride, sir.
Stop talking and save my city.
Hey, Captain, you made it!
- Where's Georgia?
- Oh... about that.
There is only one elevator.
And the stairs
are not finished yet.
I need to get up there now!
(hissing, clicking)
Let the show begin!
Seriously?
Aaaah!
Georgia!
Ah...
Oh, what...?
What? Georgia...
Georgia, where are you?
- Come over here, quick!
- Georgia...
Hurry up!
Are you alright, Captain?
No... My daughter is up there.
Oh, dear heavens!
- Not there....
- Listen to me, men.
I want you to surround
the building.
Here.
Another construction elevator.
From up there I could...
Get me some ropes and a grapnel.
Uh... are you serious, Captain?
(grunts)
Georgia. Georgia!
Ah!
(grunts)
(panting)
(hums)
(organ music)
90 seconds to stop her.
(plays dramatic tune)
Where are you, Pauline?
85 seconds...
There! Yes!
(panting)
No! Georgia, look around you.
Don't run.
Please don't run.
Don't run. Don't run, Georgia
Nolan. You're a firefighter.
75 seconds.
You walk with purpose.
Think.
You won't make it in 70 seconds.
She's too high.
Think.
Take a look around.
65 seconds.
The power!
Yes!
Where's the plug?
There!
Yes! 60 seconds.
Can I make it?
Platform, pulley, ladder,
beam, ladder.
It's possible. 55 seconds.
That's great, my love.
(grunts)
(yelling)
Yeah, yeah... No!
No... No. Argh!
Okay. Um...
Easy. One foot
in front of the other.
One foot in front of the other.
Whoa!
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven. Six.
Five.
Four!
Three.
Two.
(music stops)
What? Argh!
- Hey!
- Argh!
Show's over. Huh.
Yes!
(grunts)
No! Georgia!
Whoa...!
Nobody stops my show, Georgia,
not even you.
It's my time.
(grunts)
So we're gonna take it
from the top.
(tires screeching)
Cheetah. At your service.
Need a lift, Captain?
(chuckles)
Pauline! Please stop!
Pauline, you're too...
you're too close to the edge!
Oh, you have no idea, honey.
Aaaah!
You ruined everything!
We could have changed the world!
We are changing it.
We have the same fire
in our hearts.
Don't you see?
But... But you use yours
to harm people.
I use mine to save them.
Yeah?
How are you gonna do that?
Gonna drop me
like the last time?
(panting, grunts)
To calculate
the horizontal distance,
I'm using 9.81 yards
per second...
Oh, never mind, just go fast!
Here comes the Cheetah!
(all yell)
(tires screeching)
(laughs)
Ah!
You see, Pauline?
Firefighters are one big family.
(screams)
Thought maybe
you could use a hand.
- Hi!
- That'd be nice.
- How are you, Probie?
- Yeah, feelin' good.
Feelin' good, Captain.
Um... Uh...
(footsteps approaching)
Dad!
Do I look like a firefighter?
- You are a firefighter...
- Oh...
I can't believe what
a beautiful woman you've become.
I've wanted to give this to you
for the longest time.
It's... It's everything that
I found out about your parents.
And... now it's for you.
Oh...
Wow...
(chuckles)
I look like my mother.
And a little like your father.
My dad's name is Shawn Nolan.
He's the greatest dad
in the world
and I wanna be just like him.
(whines)
- I love you, Joe.
- What?
I'm kidding. I'm kidding!
But that... that Joe
was really something.
- Always smelled of mangoes.
- Oh, cut it out!
Ember, were you in
on all of this?
Of course. It was all her...
idea... actually.
(whimpers)
(crowd cheering)
I vowed to keep you safe
and I was able to deliver
on that promise
thanks to the heroic men
and women, heh, heh,
who stand before you today.
Don't look at me.
You look into the camera.
Ow! You're crushing my hand.
I know. I know.
It's an honor
to decorate each of them
with a gold medal,
for their bravery in protecting
the greatest city on earth.
We couldn't have done it
without you, Ricardo.
Thank you, Captain.
Please wish me good luck.
I'm going to college next year.
Well, I'm 100% sure
you're gonna do great things.
Although given my age
and my social issues,
I wonder if I have a 93% chance
of being bullied and...
- Ricardo?
- You are right. I can do it.
You showed great courage, Jin.
This is going right next
to my medallion.
- You're driving a cab again?
- Yes, sir.
I'm working on my emotions.
Did I mention I'd like
to take your daughter out?
Hey, Jin, pump the brakes.
Oh! Sure. No problem, Captain.
No, take all the time you need.
Good job, Nolan.
Thank you, Captain Nolan.
(whispering) I love you.
(whispering) I love you too.
Oh... Now that's true
New York spirit.
Excelsior!
Everyone with me!
I'm not crying.
I just got some...
some pickle juice in my eye.
You're crying!
(sobbing)
- (alarm ringing)
- Huh?
(pickle guy) Half-priced pickles
for everybody!
Not you!
But everybody else!
(♪ Amerie: "Gotta Work")
♪ Sometimes it's gonna be
days like this ♪
♪ Sometimes it's gonna be rain
like this ♪
♪ Sometimes you're gonna feel
pain like this ♪
♪ Sometimes you gotta work hard
for it ♪
♪ 'Cause when
you're feeling low ♪
♪ And you can't get no lower ♪
♪ That's when you know
you're close ♪
♪ Sometimes
you gotta work hard for it ♪
♪ Yeah, woke up
in the morning ♪
♪ It's another cloudy day ♪
♪ But that never mattered
too much to me ♪
♪ Hey! 'Cause it's still
a new beginning ♪
♪ And I know I got it in me ♪
♪ Had my share
of ups and downs ♪
♪ But now I know
I can do anything ♪
♪ Sometimes it's gonna be
days like this ♪
♪ Sometimes it's gonna be rain
like this ♪
♪ Sometimes you're gonna feel
pain like this ♪
♪ Sometimes you gotta work hard
for it ♪
♪ 'Cause when
you're feeling low ♪
♪ And you can't get no lower ♪
♪ That's when you know
you're close ♪
♪ Sometimes
you gotta work hard for it ♪
Uh! Give it to me!
♪ Some people think
I'm aggressive ♪
♪ 'Cause I know what I want ♪
♪ But that never mattered
too much to me ♪
♪ Show me somebody
without a goal ♪
with no control ♪
♪ 'Cause life's for living
So go and get it ♪
♪ But when times get rough
Remember nothing comes free ♪
♪ Sometimes it's gonna be
days like this ♪
♪ Sometimes it's gonna be rain
like this ♪
♪ Sometimes you're gonna feel
pain like this ♪
♪ Sometimes you gotta work hard
for it ♪
♪ 'Cause when
you're feeling low ♪
♪ And you can't get no lower ♪
♪ That's when you know
you're close ♪
♪ Sometimes
you gotta work hard for it ♪
♪ Days like this ♪
♪ Rain like this ♪
♪ Gotta work hard for it ♪
♪ Gotta work hard
for it ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
(laughs)
♪ Do it 'cause I love it ♪
♪ Oh! ♪♪
(jazz music)