Downloaded from
YTS.MX
(whooshing wind sounds)
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
(bell rings)
(foreboding music fades in)
(crickets chirping. dogs barking)
(footsteps walking across grass)
(footsteps walking across road)
(dark foreboding music)
(typing sounds on keyboard)
(feet landing)
(dark foreboding music)
(footsteps walking on grass)
(flashlight clicks on)
(shed door rattles)
(shed door slides open)
(suspenseful music
- This one might get me 20 bucks.
(ominous music)
(bag rustles, tools rattle)
(backpack zips up)
(toolbox crashes loudly to the floor)
Shit! Shit! Shit!
(ominous music)
(keyboard sounds)
(footsteps running across grass)
(wood fence creaking)
(feet land with a thud)
(hinges squeaking)
(suspenseful music)
(shovel scrapes wood)
(footsteps walking down street)
(dialing on phone)
(phone rings)
- Hey, hey Keith.
- [Keith] What?
- Man, I'm a little low on funds
[Keith] Oh Yeah?
but do you mind if I
give you what I've got
and you front me the rest?
Come on man. I'm jonesing.
- [Keith] Seriously, again? fuck no!
- Keith? Keith?
Shit! Dammit! Asshole!
(Ominous music)
(twigs break and crackle)
(dogs barking in the distance)
(footsteps walk quickly down street)
(leaves rustle)
(stone lands on pavement)
(intense music)
(shovel hit to the face)
(body hits ground)
(body dragged across leaves)
- Ugh...uh...
What the fu--!
(blood spattering)
(shovel impacts)
(intense, sinister music)
(jacket unzips)
(shirt ripping)
(finger dips in blood)
(intense, sinister music)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(birds chirping, wind blowing)
(alarm beeping)
(alarm button smacked)
(light switch turned on)
(light drums in background)
(television turns on)
(weatherman speaks in background)
- Let's see what you got for me today...
(commercial plays in background)
(typing sounds on keyboard)
(dark, sinister music)
What the hell?
(flips through pages in the Bible)
They defiled themselves
by their evil deeds
and their love of idols was
adultery in the Lord's sight.
(bible slams shut)
(Clara types angrily on computer)
(Clara clicks on an email)
(typing sounds on keyboard)
(gentle synth music begins)
(music intensifies)
(synth music continues)
(music ends)
- [Announcer] From
Channel 5 Eyewitness news,
this is a special report.
- [Reporter] Good Morning.
Investigators are currently on the scene
of what appears to be homicide.
Late last night, a man was
brutally beaten to death,
and it wasn't until early this morning
that a passerby discovered his body.
The victim has been identified
as 26-year-old Marcus
Daniels of Eden, Tennessee.
Unfortunately, officers
are not being forthcoming
with the details of the
brutal nature of this attack.
However, as more information is released,
we will keep you, our viewers, updated.
This has been Dinah
Knight with Channel Five,
Eyewitness News, Oak Ridge.
- [Announcer] We now return you
to your regularly scheduled programming.
(television turns off)
- Oh, shit!
(door bell rings)
(footsteps down the stairs)
- Good Morning, Deja
- Good morning Mr. Banks.
Is Clara ready to go?
- She's running late as usual.
If you wanna come on in and
wait, she'll be ready in a few.
- [Deja] Okay, cool.
- [Mr.Banks] So anything new?
Are you guys staying out of trouble?
- Of course.
- Okay.
Hey Deja, I just made some coffee.
Did you want some?
- No, I'm not a coffee person.
- You know I drink so much coffee,
my blood type is caffeine positive.
- Good one. Mr. Banks.
(clock ticks)
- Hey Deja, I got to leave
would you do me a favor?
Have Clara pick up
some Halloween candy for me after school.
- All right.
- Thank you.
I got to leave and go
out of town for work,
I know I'll forget.
Thank you.
- No problem. See you.
- Bye.
(gentle music)
(virus scan alert chime)
(suspenseful music)
(clicks mousepad)
- What?
What's this? I didn't
know you were into girls.
- I'm not. I just borrowed some pictures
from the nice ladies on the internet.
- Okay...but for what though?
And we were those people
we were talking to?
Some of those messages were hella dirty.
- It's just a game I play.
- A game? That's no game I know of.
- I made it up.
I went onto one of those
lonely hearts sites
and started messaging random guys.
- So how do the pictures come into play?
- Well, those women are who
they think they're talking to.
- So you're catfishing guys?
- Yeah! It's pretty great.
I send them dirty pictures and messages
and in return they send me free stuff.
- They're sending you things?
They're buying you things?
- Yeah. Oh, where do you
think I got this new top?
Thank you Skydaddy13.
- They're sending things to your house?
Isn't that dangerous?
- No, they don't send things to my house.
They send me e-gift cards
and then give me the code.
I'm not that stupid.
- So what do you do when
they want see you in person?
- Well, that's when
Jezebel Reigns disappears
like a thief into the night, pun intended.
- Girl, you're crazy!
- Crazy good at getting free stuff!
- Geez...
- Are you done?
- Um...Almost.
- You're making us late, hurry up.
(birds tweet)
(car speeds by)
So how long have you been
catfishing those guys?
- About eight months now.
- And how many?
- Currently only two.
At one point there were four,
but the other two weren't falling for it.
- Doesn't your dad think it's weird
that you keep getting all
these packages in the mail?
- A UFO could land in our backyard
and my dad wouldn't notice.
- Speaking of your dad,
he told me to ask you about
getting some Halloween candy,
something about him being
out of town this weekend?
- And that right there is why
he never notices anything.
He's always working.
Ever since mom died, he's never home.
And Halloween isn't
even until next Friday.
- Maybe he just has a lot on his mind.
(gentle music plays)
You know I'm here for you, right?
- Yeah. I know.
That's why you're my bestie.
Thanks again for picking me up.
My car is not gonna be out of
the shop until next Tuesday.
- Girl, I got you anytime.
(upbeat music)
(truck drives by)
- So, how are you and Shawn?
- I don't really talk to him now and
I need to focus on school.
- Really though? He was so cute.
- Yeah...
(upbeat music)
- What are you looking at freak?
- Deja!
- Oh, It's fine Clara.
So I hear you're applying
for Princeton, Deja.
(quick typing on computer)
(slams computer shut,
shoves it in backpack)
I hope you can make the grade.
- I don't need your hope,
I know what I can do.
- Sorry.
- What was that all about?
Why do you hate him so much?
- He creeps me out.
He gives me creepy stalker vibes.
- He's not that bad.
- Says you. I call it like I see it.
- Mmm hmm...
So see you in second period.
- You ready for that test?
- Honey, I was not only born fabulous,
but always on the ready.
- Dork!
- Only dork I see is the one approaching.
See you.
- See you.
- Quit... stop, you know I hate that.
- I just can't help it.
You're so hot.
- I know I am. So you
coming to my game later?
- I can't, I have to work on
the trunk or treat display.
- Lame. Is your dad gonna
be home this weekend?
We could study the human anatomy.
- Perv. It's girls only this weekend.
- Call me "Chadra."
I'll make you a bikini
out of whipped cream.
- (laughs) Girls only. I mean it Chad.
- Whatever you say babe.
You're missing out on my craft skills.
- I'm sure they're at expert level.
Text me later?
- Will do.
Watch where you're going Jesus freak!
- Good morning to you too, Chad.
(lockers closing in background)
(writing sounds)
- Hey, I'm sorry about Chad earlier.
He gets defensive when he's embarrassed.
- It's okay, sometimes you just
have to turn the other cheek
on little things like that.
- I'm still sorry he pushed you.
Your presentation looks really
good. It has a lot of detail.
Mine's awful.
Where did you learn to do that?
- Oh..um...My Mom is a computer
programmer at Oak Ridge and
she's been teaching me
how to do these things since I was five.
It kinda became how we bonded.
(knock on classroom door)
- Excuse me, Ms. Blaylock,
Micah Green is needed in
the principal's office.
(students jeering and laughing)
- Class! Class that is enough.
- Dammit
- [Student] He's always in trouble.
- Thought you were funny
with your little trick huh?
Whose laughing now?
Dick.
- Bitch.
- Well, come in.
(light airy music)
- Do you know why I
called you in here today?
- 'Cause you missed
seeing my handsome face?
- Mr. Green, this is not a time for jokes.
The allegations made against
you are very serious.
Do you have your laptop with you?
- Yeah.
- May I have it, please?
(unzipping backpack)
- Can I have your password please?
- Can't remember all of a sudden.
- Now, Mr. Green...
(Mrs. Roberts begins typing on the laptop)
- It's okay. I've already
accessed what I needed.
The IP address matches.
- Mr. Green...your
actions are very serious
and it is illegal.
I'm gonna have to inform the
authorities, your father,
and suspend you as well.
- May I make a suggestion?
In lieu of calling the authorities.
Why not have Mr. Green help out
with the preparations
for the trunk or treat?
I find community work
to be very educational
for our youth.
Idle hands are the devil's
playground after all.
- I'm still going to
have to call your father
and suspend you for a week.
Wait outside my office for your father.
And Mr. Green, there
cannot be a repeat of this.
(door slams)
Thank you so much for your help, Betty.
- Oh, that's fine.
I'm always happy to help.
I had to pick up some art supplies
for the trunk or treat anyway.
I better be off, lot's to do
before I have to pick up Jacob.
(gentle music)
(dials phone number)
- Mr. Green, there's been an
incident here at the school.
We need you to come pick up your son.
(bell rings)
(background hallway chatter)
- I got some tea to spill.
So stalker boy hacked into
the school's main computer.
- Seriously, how do you know that?
- Our progress reports were
passed out today in class
and I had all F's,
I've never gotten an F in my life.
Stupid bustard gave himself away
with a snide ass remark this morning.
- Holy crap. Are you serious?
- Yes, those are my grades Clara.
He screwed with my grades.
I'm trying to get into Princeton, okay.
This is not okay that he would do that.
- [Mr. Green] What the
hell were you thinking?!?
You listen to me boy. I am
damn tired of your shit.
I had to leave work to come down here.
- Sorry!
- You're sorry? I'm losing money
because of your horse shit.
And you think sorry is
gonna make up for that?
You're gonna be sorry.
Get your ass in that truck.
(tense music)
- I feel so bad for him.
- I don't. He did it to himself.
We still on for this weekend?
- Yeah, Kimmy's coming over after work.
- Okay, cool. You ready for this test?
- [Clara] You know with
all that commotion,
I almost forgot about it.
Let's just get it over with.
(truck rumbles down road)
- Boy...you are lucky I
did not get fired today.
- I already said I'm sorry.
- Bullshit! I am sick of your shit Micah!
- [Micah] Like mom was tired of yours?
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
- Now what the hell did
you just say to me?!?
- Like mom was tired of yours!
- Look around you, Micah.
Your Saint ain't here.
She didn't want you either.
- Because of you!
You're always drunk. You
gamble all of our money away.
Mom left because of you!
Mom knew she-
(punch thuds)
- You watch how you speak to me boy.
(tense music)
Micah...you get your ass here boy!
- Shit!
(truck engine revving)
(truck speeds away)
(car pulls in and parks)
(door chime dings)
(cheerful music plays in background)
- Hey Kimmy, I called that
prescription in earlier.
- Oh yeah, yeah...I have that
right...right here for you.
Don't worry about it.
- Thanks
- Hey Mrs. Roberts.
- Hi Clara, it's nice to see you.
- I just have a few things to
grab, so I'll be right back.
- Yeah, I'll just work on that right now.
What up, loser?
- Hey Kimmy.
- Hey
- Are you still coming over tonight?
- Ugh! Do I have to?
- Yes.
- You and Deja with me wanting
to come over all the time.
I mean, I guess I'll come over,
but you know I have to finish up here,
just be a couple minutes, is that fine?
- Could you bring some art supplies?
(paper bag ruffles)
- Do I look like I have art supplies?
- Not really.
- What are you doing with this?
What is this? Are you
trying to check out here?
- [Clara] Yes
- This is not a checkout counter, Clara.
- [Clara] Okay well...
- This is a pharmacy counter, Clara!
- [Clara] The customer's
always right, Kimmy.
- You can't check out if there's
no checkout machine, Clara!
[Kimmy] ...just gonna buy
candy at my pharmacy counter..
I hate this store. I just really
want to die all the time...
- Hi, Mrs. Robert, how are you doing?
Did you find everything okay?
- I did thank you.
- All right, let me take
care of that for you.
Okay, are you gonna be gardening today?
- Hoping to get started.
- All right, that sounds great.
Sounds like a lot of fun.
Here's your prescription,
that's gonna be 89.95.
- All right, there you go.
- There you go.
Will you need a bag for this?
- Oh, I should be fine.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
(credit card machine beeps)
- Clara, will we be
seeing you and your father
at church this Sunday?
- Of course. We'll definitely be there.
- Good, it'll be really
nice to have you both back.
We missed you.
And thank you both for offering to help
with the trunk or treat
the children of Eden will
be so thankful, I know I am.
- Of course, we're more
than happy to help.
- Uh huh...yeah...
- Great. All right,
well, I gotta get going.
Oh, before I forget, can I get your email?
I'm gonna send you some
ideas for the display.
- Okay, yeah sure. Do you have paper?
- Mmm hmm..
- Yep.
- Really appreciate your help.
- [Kimmy] Oh yeah...I
totally wanted to do that.
- Great.
- Okay...
- All righty.
- Thank you.
I'll get that out to you tonight.
- Okay. Cool.
- All right. Have a good day girls.
- [Kimmy] You too!
- I don't remember volunteering for that.
- You didn't, I volunteered you.
- Okay, so how are you paying for this?
- Cash.
- Oh, do you have cash?
- I do have cash.
- [Kimmy] I'm very impressed with you.
- I bet you are.
- I will be taking that and
I will be keeping the change
'cause someone needs art supplies, right?
- See you later.
- [Customer] I'm here to
pick up my prescription.
- Absolutely, can I get your last name?
- Hey hooker, you forget about me?
- Definitely.
- Dick.
(car engine cranking)
- Stupid prick. You're so stupid.
God I am so tired of you.
"Oh...your saint ain't here"
- because of you, you drunk!
(low ominous music)
Hmm...Silver lining after all.
(camera taking photos)
(low ominous music)
(low drums play)
- So Kimmy, did you know?
- Did I know what?
- About Clara's half naked
women she shares online.
- My God, I didn't know you swung my way.
- I don't.
- Well, you should. Come to
the dark side we bake cookies.
- As much as I love cookies and you Kimmy,
we both know I'm strictly dickly.
- So what are you doing?
- She cons stupid dudes for money.
- Now, I like to think of it
as I fill one of their needs
and they fulfill my material needs.
Not my fault they're stupid.
(Kimmy lets out a long sigh)
- You should really read this book.
How are they falling for this?
I mean, it's pretty simple.
I send them pictures and
they send me gift cards.
Everyone's happy.
- So does Chad know about this?
- No. And he isn't going to.
I mean, they're not my pictures,
so it technically isn't even cheating.
- Girl, you're pulling out
every excuse from the book.
- Only the good ones.
- Now are we gonna get started on this?
- Uh...I guess...
- What's the theme?
- Um...Actually, let me check.
Looks like angels.
- Angels.
(all laughs)
- Oh God, we're all screwed..
(Girls all laugh loudly)
- Hey hun? Dinner's ready.
- Okay, I'll be done in a second.
- What are you watching?
- Oh, uh "Mean Girlz".
- That doesn't sound like
a very wholesome film.
- It's not, but it reminds
me of the kids at my school.
- Is someone being mean to you?
- No, everything's fine, I promise.
- Okay. Now go eat.
- Okay.
(upbeat music plays)
- Heavenly Father, we
thank you for this food,
we pray that it will go to
the nourishment of our bodies
the way your word nourishes our souls.
We thank you for the
blessings that you granted us
and pray that you continue to guide us,
In Jesus name we pray, amen.
- Amen.
- Did you do something
different with the potatoes?
- Yes, actually. I'm
trying out a new recipe.
(Mr. Roberts breathes in deeply)
- Well, if it tastes as
good as it looks and smells,
we have a winner.
- That's sweet. Thank you.
Jacob have you decided whether or not
you'll be joining the
boys youth group trip
for winter break?
I hear they have a great time.
- I don't know, I'm
not really into skiing,
but some of the boys
talked about the Aquarium.
- Oh the Aquarium?
That's where your mother and I
went on our anniversary last time.
I think you'll like that.
- Penguins are my favorite.
They're just adorable.
- You say that about all
of God's animals though.
- Yes she does.
- Yes. That's because I
love all God's creations.
- Betty, that is not what
you said about that snake
we found on the shade last fall. (laughs)
(Mrs. Roberts shudders)
- Okay, maybe most of God's creations,
just not the slithering kind.
Besides it reminds me of
the serpent in Genesis.
Just evil.
- Now, hon. Even the serpent
has a purpose in God's plan.
- That's true.
What about you honey?
Have you finished your
sermon for Sunday yet?
- Um...not quite...
(water faucet running)
(intense, ominous music)
(pill bottle rattles)
(typing sounds on keyboard)
(gentle music plays)
- Hey hon.
- Hey, beautiful. What's up?
- How long you gonna be?
- Not long, just got a
little bit more to go.
- What's your topic this Sunday?
- Temptation.
I figured with the holidays
just around the corner,
temptation is gonna be in abundance.
- Mr.Roberts?
- Yes.
- Might I tempt you into coming to bed?
- Mrs. Roberts, are you coming on to me?
- What, I'm just fulfilling
my wifely duties.
Maybe I can show you what that entails.
- Amen.
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
(Jacob types on keyboard)
- [Mr. Roberts] Hey Jacob,
could you come help me out for a minute?
(gentle music)
- Oh Frank, always forgetting
to shut down your computer.
(gentle music)
(ominous music)
(mousepad click)
(laptop slams shut)
(Mrs. Roberts sighs)
(Mrs. Roberts is chopping oranges loudly)
- Well, that smells great, hon.
- You left computer on again.
- Hmm..I did? My mind was a
little distracted last night.
Did you get a chance to look
over my sermon for tomorrow?
- Yes, I did. It was insightful.
- Still have a few tweaks to make on it,
but I think it'd be a great sermon.
- Maybe you should take
your own sermon's advice.
- I'm sorry hon, what was that?
- Just that I hope the weather's nice.
I really wanted to prune the
roses before our first frost.
- The weatherman says it's
gonna be sunny and 72º today.
- That's good to know.
I'm going to go wash up before I eat.
(water running)
(Mrs. Roberts weeps)
- Hey mom, can I borrow
the laptop for a project?
- Yeah it's fine. I don't care.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah honey, I'm fine.
Got some soap in my eyes. Silly, I know.
Your breakfast is ready
for you in the kitchen.
- I'm gonna eat in my room.
I wanna get this project done.
- That's fine. Can you help
me in the garden later?
- Sure thing.
(gentle music)
(medicine bottle rattling)
- [Deja] We've looked at so many of these
I'm becoming cross-eyed.
- I thought that was just your face.
- Shut up. Seriously
Clara can we just wing it?
- Well, aren't you just punny?
- I thought so.
(email chimes)
- What's that?
- It's just a new message.
- Uh huh, I wanna see.
- Yeah, me too.
- Fine.
- Anything has to be better
than this current craft hell.
- Oh, he's thinking of you.
- Uh, shut up.
- Give me.
- Oh my gosh, what are you typing?
- You'll see.
Done and sent.
- Good Lord, let's see what you wrote.
- You scandalous hussy.
You wrote it like an erotica novel.
- I'm scandalous?
She's the one who's been
stringing him along.
- Ugh...
I'm thinking of you. I wanna
put your hands on my body
and your lips on mine and put your member?
- Member?!?
- Really, really that's
what you're focusing on.
- I mean, it's just weird.
- Just like you.
- Come on ladies, we need
to focus on why we came here
and that is to make a heavenly display.
- Fine, but I still
have glitter stuck to me
from last night.
- Glerpies. Glerpies.
You have glitter herpes.
- Come on! We're never
gonna get this done!
- (laughs) It's a joke. It was funny.
(email chimes)
Oh, it looks like he wants
to use that member in person.
He said he can make your
dreams into a reality.
- Oh Girl, he wants to be
the new member in your club.
- Mmm. Uh uh. Shut up.
- You're blushing!
- No, I'm not.
- Yeah you are.
- You're a virgin.
- No, she's slept with Chad before.
- I mean, we've done
things. Just not that.
- Hmm...that's not what I heard.
- What did you hear?
- Don't make me tell her!
- Just tell me!
- Fine. Just don't shoot the messenger.
Chad said that he slept with you
under the football bleachers.
- What?
- Are you okay?
- No! How could he do that?!?
- What are you going to do?
Clara?
(typing on cell phone)
(Clara slams phone onto bed)
- I just dumped him.
- Really?
- Yeah. I can't believe
he would do that to me.
- He wasn't good enough for you anyway.
- I feel so dumb.
- I mean, don't feel
dumb, it's not your fault.
And he's the dumb one
for losing you, I guess.
(email chimes)
Do you want me to respond to this?
- Yeah.
Tell him my car's in the shop
and that I'll talk to him later.
- Okay.
- By the way, uh, Dej can you take me?
- Wish I could, but mom will have the car,
dad's is in the shop, but I
could Uber with you though.
- Thanks.
(text message chimes)
(ominous music plays)
(creaky door opens)
- Micah!
Micah!
Get up! I said get up!
- What?!?
It's Saturday.
- "Oh it's Saturday."
Because of that stunt
you pulled yesterday,
I get to pull an extra shift at work.
If I got to work, you do too.
Now get up!
(Micah groans)
I want you out in that
truck in five minutes boy.
Do not make me wait.
(light airy music)
(water faucet turns on in adjacent room)
(electric razor turns on in adjacent room)
(cars passing on highway)
(truck pulls in)
- Dad's waiting on you
in the back Mr. Green.
- Wait here.
- What is it, bring your son to work day?
- Look who's talking.
- Difference is my dad owns this place.
- Whatever dude.
(air wrenches humming)
- Come on back Micah.
Ohhhhh...I need to start this brake job.
I want you to sweep these
floors, wash the windows,
take out the trash and
clean the bathrooms.
All right, all the cleaning supplies
are over by that closet.
Don't just stand there.
Get to work, come on.
"Lurkers" by Ok Otter
♪ Everybody wants to see ♪
♪ What they will do to me ♪
♪ They'll be up early ♪
♪ Drive into town ♪
♪ To get a good seat ♪
♪ Bite to eat ♪
♪ Run out of time ♪
♪ This is now my cleansing ♪
♪ No alibi ♪
♪ Why even try ♪
♪ My god ♪
♪ Hold on who put you in charge ♪
♪ I see nobody ♪
♪ I see nobody, no ♪
♪ Slip of the tongue up on your feet ♪
♪ But in the end you'll answer to me ♪
♪ The louder you plead ♪
♪ The harder you pray ♪
♪ I want you to know this happens today ♪
♪ You ask who put me in charge ♪
♪ I need nobody ♪
♪ I need nobody, no ♪
- Hey, I'm done.
- What are you doing?
- Just changing the mats in Clara's car.
- Well aren't you a good boyfriend.
- I'm not dating that skank.
- I just saw you two yesterday.
- I dumped her and she's gonna pay for it.
- That doesn't make
any sense you dumped...
You know what? I don't even care.
Where's my dad?
- He's out front.
(light airy music)
(beer can clangs in bed of truck)
(Kimmy snores)
- Wow. We did really well guys.
- We?
- Yeah, it looks great.
- Yeah. And you know what?
I think it looks really good.
- I'll be happy to
never see glitter again.
- Same.
- Yeah.
- What time is it?
- It's already 6:30.
- I got to go.
My mom needs a car back by seven.
- Yeah, you know, as much
as I would love to stay
and like stick more dolls
on boards with you guys,
but like I got to go.
- You're gonna be all right Clara?
- Yeah, I'll be fine.
Uh, Dad's gonna be back soon.
You know what? Let me walk you out.
- [Kimmy] Thanks bro.
- [Clara] Uh huh...
- [Kimmy] Angels. Wow.
- [Clara] You're not an angel.
(car pulls in garage)
(birds chirping)
- [Mr. Banks] Did you
get your display done?
- Yeah, we did.
- Good.
What's wrong? You not like it?
I thought...I thought
that was your favorite.
- It is, I'm just really not hungry.
- Is everything okay?
- Yes.
No.
I don't know.
- What's going on?
- Chad and I broke up.
- Really? How come?
- Because he's stupid.
- Something happen that
I need to know about?
- No. I don't wanna talk about it.
Can I please be excused?
- Yeah. At least eat your fortune cookie,
always time for a fortune cookie.
Who knows, that may be some good news.
(light airy music)
- Every action has consequence.
Shittiest. Fortune. Ever.
(light airy music)
(Clara sighs)
(drums play softly)
(typing on keyboard)
(mousepad click)
(brush strokes)
(dogs barking outside)
- Hey champ could you make
sure the laptop's charged
before you go to bed?
- Sure thing dad.
- Thanks.
I'm gonna turn in for the
night hon, you coming?
- I need to finish this,
I'll come to bed later.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Just don't forget to
take your medication.
You know you don't feel right without it.
(medicine bottle slammed on floor)
- Good night son.
- Night dad.
(ominous music)
(dogs barking outside loudly)
- Barking...
Stop barking...
just stop barking...just..why
does it keep barking?
Stop barking!
Why? Why even have a dog if you're
not gonna keep it inside...inside?
(dog growls disturbingly)
- Are you okay?
- I just want it to stop...
- They just don't care.
- The thought of anybody...
(dog growls disturbingly)
- Barking all night...
- Barking all night
(dog growls disturbingly)
- Why won't it stop?
...won't stop barking!
- Shh...I'll go talk to the neighbors.
(light airy music)
(dog barks)
(dog continues barking outside)
(dog yelps in pain)
(door opens and closes)
- [Jacob] You shouldn't hear
the dog barking anymore mom.
What did you do?!?
(Mrs. Roberts weeps)
- It doesn't look that deep.
(light airy music)
come on, let's get you to bed.
(dark ominous music)
- Love you, Bett.
♪ This little light of mine ♪
♪ I'm gonna let it shine ♪
♪ Let it shine, let it
shine, let it shine ♪
[Churchgoer] Good morning.
- Who are you saving the seat for?
- Saving it for Clara.
- No!
- Why not?
- I, um...
- Her father's coming today.
She should sit with him.
- Oh, okay.
(light airy music)
- Now for 40 days and 40 nights
Jesus prayed in the
desert, no food, no water.
Three times, Satan came to tempt him.
Now we read Matthew chapter 4, verse 4,
Jesus reply after Satan had told him
to turn some stones into bread.
And though He was hungry,
Jesus replied to Satan,
"Man shall not live by bread alone,
but by every word that proceeds
out of the mouth of God."
Jesus showed us that even though food
could sustaining the body for a time,
it can not sustain the spirit.
To separate yourself from God
is to create spiritual starvation.
Now temptation can come in many forms.
Like with knowledge...the
serpent tempted Eve in the garden
Or from those you trust,
like Samson did Delilah with
the secret to his strength.
It is why we must turn
to the word of God...
for guidance when we're lost,
strength when we're weak,
for discernment when we're
offered things from others.
To be aware of wolves in sheep's clothing.
And it is only then
through Him and only Him
that we can overcome temptation.
Now, let us pray.
Please bow your heads.
Heavenly Father we come before you now...
- We're so glad you and
your dad could make it.
I know.
- What?
(ominous music)
Mrs. Roberts, you're hurting me.
- I'm sorry, I guess I just
don't know my grasp sometimes.
I just meant that I know
I'll be seeing more of you...
- Yeah.
- Helping out with the trunk
or treat this Thursday!
- Of course, definitely.
Um...I'm gonna go catch
up with my dad now.
- You should probably go catch up.
- Yeah.
- Good to see you.
- [Churchgoer] Great service...
(Birds chirping)
(instant message chimes)
(typing on keyboard)
(phone rings)
- Hey Dej. What's up?
- [Deja] Not much just bored.
- Same. So going back to
church today felt really weird.
- [Deja] Yeah, I agree.
You should have seen the
look on Mrs. Robert's face.
If looks could kill, you'd be dead.
(instant message chimes)
You would swear you were
sleeping with her husband.
(instant message chimes)
- Um...Mrs. Roberts really
creeped me out today.
Usually she's so sweet,
but today she seemed off.
- [Deja] That whole family's off.
Super nice people creep me out.
Nobody can be that nice all the time.
- I guess. Are you still
coming over tonight?
Dad's heading out of town soon.
- [Deja] Yeah, once my mom
picks me up with the car.
- Okay. See you later then.
- [Deja] All right. Bye.
(tense music coming from television)
- [Clara] Watch out! Those birds are nuts.
- Shhhhh!
- Did you know that in Australia
they have an actual swooping season?
Magpies attack people
just like in this movie.
- [Kimmy] Oh my God. You're such a nerd.
- Didn't know...now, shhhh!
(door bell rings)
(Clara and Deja gasp)
- It's just the pizza. I
completely forgot about it.
Oh, hey, could you come inside
so you don't let the bugs in?
- Sure, didn't know you lived here.
- I didn't know you delivered pizzas.
- My parents wanted me to learn
more about responsibility,
so... now I have a job.
Your total will be $14.95.
- Keep the change.
- Thanks. See you around?
- We have computer lab together.
- Oh, you're right. Bye.
- Bye.
- I'm so stupid. Why did I say that?
(ominous music)
- You'll never guess who
delivered our pizzas.
- Who?
- Jacob.
- Really? I never pictured
him as a delivery boy.
- Well, what did you picture him as?
- Hmm...future politician.
You know it's the hair.
- (laughs) I don't know maybe a...
(banging sound on back door)
did you guys hear that?
- It's probably the birds
coming to end us all.
- Very funny.
- I am funny...I'm really funny.
- But I didn't hear anything.
(scratching sound on front door)
- That.
- It's probably just a twig or something.
- Or a bird.
(banging sound on front door)
- Okay, definitely not a bird.
(baseball bat rattles around in closet)
- Clara I don't wanna end up
like the next slasher film.
Clara don't!
- Seriously Clara, why don't
you just call the cops?
I'm not trying to die today.
- Clara don't!
(suspenseful music)
(front door opens quickly)
- What the fuck?!?
(fire sizzles as water is poured on it)
- You don't think it was Jacob do you?
- No, it wasn't him.
- How do you know?
- I just do.
Look, I need to clean this up
or my dad's gonna freak out.
- Hello? Is anyone out there?
Whoever you are you're not funny.
(ominous music)
(leaves crackling in the distance)
Don't do that!
- Sorry!
Did you see anything?
- No, just heard a noise,
probably just a cat or something.
Let's just get this done,
I wanna go back inside.
- Okay.
(sweeping sounds)
Ugh...gross.
(door shuts loudly)
I think I've had enough
scary movies for one night.
- Honestly, I was just
about to say the same thing.
- Wanna watch something funny before bed?
- Read my mind.
(both laughs)
- Well, I think that's
enough fun for tonight.
I'm freaked the fuck out and
I have worked in the morning.
So I will be taking this.
- Deserter.
- I'm a survivalist.
- "Bock bock".
- "Bock Bock"..nuhhhh...See
you guys later.
- What a weird night.
(ominous music)
(gossip and chatter in the background)
- Why is everyone staring?
- I don't know.
(ominous music)
- [Mean Girl #4] No way, I'm
not doing that. That's mean.
- [Mean Girl #3] Fine. Then I will.
Skank.
- What did you say?!?
- I said... skank!
- What's that?
(mean girls laugh)
You guys are dicks!
[Mean Girl #4] - We didn't print them.
- Damn, look who's
desperate for attention.
Is that how you get guys now?
- If I find out you had
anything to do with this,
I'll beat your ass.
- I'm not afraid of you.
- You should be.
- I like you all fiery, Deja.
Maybe you could show me in another way.
(thud to Chad's groin)
(Chad groans)
- If you ever bother her
again, I'll kill you!
- Damn dude, you just got dropped.
- Shut up.
- Aww, we both know you
ain't got none anyway.
- Just another psycho...lets go.
(gentle music)
- Clara.
Are you okay?
- No, I'm not.
- Okay. Why don't you come
and take a walk with me
and we can talk where
there's less prying eyes.
Come on.
Look, we can go over there
and talk on that bench, okay?
Come on, I have some time.
(gentle music)
Come on, we have a seat.
Do you wanna tell me what happened?
- It's embarrassing.
- I can't help you if you don't let me in.
I do want to help.
But there's nothing covered
up that will not be revealed
and hidden that will not be known.
- What?
- The Bible verse at the
bottom of the picture,
Luke 12:2.
- What does it mean?
- Well, Clara, it looks
like somebody thinks
you have a secret they want shared.
Do you have a secret, Clara?
- What? No!
Why does it even matter?
Somebody took my picture
and shared it without my permission.
I'm gonna go call my dad.
Um...Thanks for sitting with me.
(ominous music)
- Lying lips are an
abomination to the Lord.
- [Mr. Banks] Honey, did
Chad take these photos?
- No, I don't know who did it.
- [Mr. Banks] Okay, well
I'm literally rushing to
check out of the hotel now and head home.
- No, you don't need to rush home
but can you call the school?
I can't go back there.
[Mr. Banks] - Yeah, I'll take care of it.
- Okay, thanks.
[Mr. Banks] - We'll figure
this out, sweetheart.
I love you. Be safe and
you remember you call me
if anything else happens, okay?
- Okay. I'll see you Thursday.
(somber music)
(typing on keyboard)
(instant message chimes)
- Are you kidding me? What's
with all the victim shaming?
(typing on keyboard)
(instant message chimes)
(intense ominous music)
Yes you are.
This day fucking blows.
(door bell rings)
(gentle music)
- Hey.
- Come in.
- You all right?
- No, I'm mortified.
I can never show my face there again.
- We could get you a mask.
- You're not helping.
- Sorry.
Just trying to lighten up the mood.
I, um...
got your homework.
- Thanks.
- What did your dad say?
- Honestly, it was like an interrogation.
- Really?
- Yeah. It seems like everybody's
pointing the finger at me.
It's not like I asked for this.
- Who's pointing the finger at you, Clara?
- Just stop, okay?
It's it's fine..just..I want to be alone!
- All right, then I'll go.
- Deja wait, wait come back.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have yelled at you.
- It's okay, I get it.
I would want to be alone
after a day like today.
- Thank you for bringing me my homework.
- No problem.
You still want me to
come with you tomorrow
to pick up your car?
- Of course.
- All right.
- See you later.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
(ominous tone)
(dogs barking in the background)
(water boiling)
(crackers breaking)
- Looks like it's just you
and me again tonight, Fish.
(knocking on door)
Hello?
Is anybody there?
(ominous music)
Whatever.
(Clara sighs)
(light switch clicks off)
(intense ominous music)
(water running)
(suspenseful music)
(music plays on earbuds)
(ominous music)
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music intensifies)
(music stops suddenly)
(ominous music)
- What the hell?
(doorknob rattles)
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music intensifies)
(doorknob rattles violently)
(screams) I thought you
were here to kill me.
- What the hell happened?
- I woke up in that was in my floor.
- Is that blood, who did this?
- I don't know.
- We should call the cops.
(phone dials 911)
- [911 Responder] Eden
911, what's your location?
- Hi, this is Deja Parker,
I'm at 1975 Hallow
Drive, um, someone has...
- You think it was a prank?
- No, I don't.
- All right, ladies,
it looks like everything's clear in there.
If you guys have anything
else you'd like to add,
just feel free to call
down to the station.
- Um...okay?
- All right. Thank you.
- Bye.
Seriously, that didn't
make me feel any better.
I thought they would've
had the whole team out here
searching for fingerprints.
- I guess that just happens on TV.
Are you gonna call your dad?
- There's no point.
He'll probably just think it was a prank
just like the stupid cops.
- I guess, but don't you think it's weird
it said Jezebel like your email?
You sure you didn't attract a stalker?
- That's not possible,
how would they find me?
- I don't know.
(car horn honks)
What are they doing here?
- Hey, Mrs. Roberts.
Jacob.
- Hello, Clara dear.
Just coming by to check on you.
You know, after yesterday.
- Oh yeah...uh, thanks...
- We were actually just leaving.
We need to go pick up Clara's car
and our Uber will be here any moment.
- Oh, we can take you guys, right mama?
- Of course, I'd love to.
- We really wouldn't wanna
take up too much of your time,
but thank you so much.
- Nonsense, we're already here.
- Oh, okay. Uh...Sure. Yeah.
- Great.
All right. Come on girls.
(van pulling in off busy highway)
- [Clara] Thank you so much for taking us.
- [Mrs. Roberts] No problem, girls.
- So what are you wearing?
(air wrenches in the background)
Sounds hot.
So you ready for me to come over later?
- He's such a pig.
- I just wanna get my car and go.
- I got this.
Are you serious? Why
are you so lame, Chad?
- Why you got to be such a bitch, Deja?
- At least I don't pretend to get action.
- Guys, just stop!
I wanna get my car and go.
- Pfft! What car?
- Oh, hey Mom, Clara forgot her phone.
I'm gonna go bring it to her.
I'll be back in a minute.
Clara, you forgot your phone in the car.
- Wow. So you dating this Jesus freak now?
You really move on to dick fast, huh?
- What is wrong with you?
- Thank you, Jacob.
- Um...Do you guys have a bathroom?
- Yeah, it's along the
side of the building.
- The bathroom isn't on
the side of the building.
- I know
- You're so mean.
- And you're such a skank.
- Micah, can I get those keys
before I end up with an assault charge?
- [Micah] Yeah.
- You just need to sign right here.
Let's see, James Burke,
Christopher Wilson,
Misty Bowles, Clara Banks...
sign right there and you'll be good to go.
- Hey, you okay?
- Yeah. I tripped on the way back here.
- Hon, you got something on your shirt.
- Can we just go?
- Yeah.
(car engine cranking)
- I know...
Why would he call me that?
I don't understand!
(radio static)
- [Reporter] It's 5:30. This is Tim chase.
The Eden Police Department
is investigating
the second murder to occur
within the last seven days.
A spokesperson for the department said,
it's the first time in 22 years
that back-to-back murders have occurred.
Now they state there's no cause
to think the murders
are in any way related?
Well, we'll just have to
take their word on that,
but keep your doors locked
tonight, Eden. Be safe.
Let's lighten things back up now.
Continuing their run in the
number one Billboard spot,
it's Sabell with the song...
- Maybe that psycho will get Chad next.
- I wish. He's such a dick.
I can't believe I dated him.
(car veers around curve fast)
(engine accelerating)
- He was just foul back there.
Speaking of foul, it smells
like something died in here.
(bottle sprays)
Well, that didn't help,
now it smells like death and flowers.
- Just my freaking luck.
Can this day get any worse?
(car speeds by fast)
- Forget that jerk, he isn't worth it
and he definitely isn't worth our lives.
Slow down, speedy.
(brake pedal goes to floor)
- Uh...Dej?
- Clara, slow down.
- I can't!
- What?!?
- The brakes aren't working!
(pneumatic air sounds)
Deja, what do I do? Nothing is working!
- I don't know, I don't know!
Oh my God, we're going
to hit them! (screams)
- Clara, we're going to hit
the pole! Oh my God, Oh my God!
(parking brake pulled)
(car crashing)
(car idles)
(car ignition turned off)
(ominous music)
(birds chirping)
- Mom? we were just in an accident.
We're at Old Blair road...Old
Alabama/Blair road...
Okay.
(ominous music)
Clara?
My Mom is coming.
- Okay.
Um...I just need to get my purse.
(keys jerked out of ignition)
(ominous music intensifies)
- [Deja] What's wrong?
- Oh my God...what?
- What's that?
(Clara panting)
(birds chirping)
(police sirens)
(gentle music)
- So Ms. Banks, can you think of anyone
that would wanna hurt you?
- No, I get along with most people.
- [Investigator] Most people.
- I mean recently my
boyfriend Chad, and I broke up
and he did send me a text
saying that I would regret it.
- What?
- Is this the same Chad
that works at the garage
that recently worked on your vehicle?
- Yes.
- You didn't think to tell me about that?
- Dad...it's fine.
- Okay.
Well, Ms. Banks, I think
that's all we need for now.
- No, it's not.
You're gonna go arrest
this guy, aren't you?
- Mr. Banks first, we have
to question everyone involved
to further our investigation.
- He tried to kill my baby girl!
Do you understand that?
- Mr. Banks though I do
understand your anger,
please understand that we have to review
all of the evidence.
- Yeah.
- Clara, are you ready?
Let's go.
- Okay.
(tense music)
- If you ever come near my daughter again,
and I swear to God-
- Get your hands-
(both scuffle)
- [Detective] Hey! Hey! Hey!
I cannot believe this...
- Enough! Get in there!
Get in there!
Have a seat.
Do you even know why you
were brought in today?
- I don't know.
Maybe because my ex is a bitch
that whines over stupid shit.
- You think what happened was stupid?
- Yeah, since when was dog shit on fire
and a mouse prank
warrant an interrogation?
- Chad shut your mouth.
Listen, if you wanna charge
my son with anything,
you can speak with our lawyer.
- Sir, we are questioning everyone
that came in contact
with Ms. Banks vehicle.
We're not charging your
son with anything, yet.
But if you feel you need a
lawyer, no one's stopping you.
- Are we done?
- I have another question.
Chad, did you cut Clara's brake lines?
- What? No. Dad I swear-
- Son I know. Are we done yet?
- I have what I need at the moment.
- Then we're leaving. Chad let's go.
- Mr. Michaels, don't leave town.
I might still need some more information.
(crickets chirping)
- I cannot believe that
the day is almost over.
You want me to make you something to eat?
- No, I'm just gonna go up to my room.
- Clara, you know you
can talk to me, right?
- I know.
(sorrowful music)
I miss you mom...
I really need you right now.
(sorrowful music)
(cabinet shuts)
- I feel bad for the kid.
- Feel bad for whom?
- I feel bad for Clara, of course.
- Why?
- Well, she must be scared.
Accidents are always scary.
We should add her to our prayer list.
- I'll pray she stays
away from my husband.
- I'm sorry, what was that hon?
- I was agreeing with you.
- Well, I'll be back in a few hours.
- Where are you going?
- Uh...Bowling with the boys.
- Bowling, I thought that was on Friday.
- With Halloween being
on Friday this year,
we just thought we'd just
go ahead and go tonight.
- Oh, okay.
- Are...are you okay?
I can stay home if you'd like.
- No, go have fun. Tell the boys said hi.
- Okay
(ominous music)
(water dumped out)
(cup slammed on counter)
[Voice in Mrs. Roberts Head]
Oh, let's pray for Clara.
Yeah Clara must've been so scared!
Poor Clara, there's
nothing poor about that
husband stealing witch. (water splashing)
He never changes bowling
night, what am I thinking?
He's probably meeting
up with her right now.
(ominous music)
(dogs barking in the distance)
- Huh..Jezebel and Clara
have a lot in common.
Both are harlots.
(finger taps Bible)
But Jezebel fell and
one day Clara will too.
Everything unholy will come to light.
(door bell rings)
(impatient knocking on door)
(tense music)
- Clara?
What are you doing here?
- I think you know.
- No, I don't.
We're supposed to meet
at the church tomorrow.
- My sweet Bett...my
plans are not with you.
Is your husband home?
- You stay away from my husband.
I think I've been more
than patient with you.
- (scoffs) Funny you say patient,
we played doctor just the other day.
- What's wrong with you?
- Wrong? Nothing's wrong.
It felt so right.
- You bitch! Stay away from my family,
You stay away from my husband!
You are nothing but a harlot of Babylon.
- Um...Mom, who are you talking to?
- Clara is here.
- No, she's not.
- But she's right, no, no...she...
She's was right here!
I...uh...
No... she was right here!
My God...I..
(pill bottle rattles)
- [Jacob] Do you want me to
help you walk you to bed?
- No. I'm fine, it's...um...
It's okay. Goodnight.
Don't get too close to Clara, son.
She's a weed in God's garden.
(birds chirping)
- Hey guys?
- Oh my God, Clara.
- I am so happy you're not dead!
- Me too.
- Oh man, I was so worried about you.
(Pickup truck passes by)
[Deja] - Feel better?
[Clara] - Yeah
[Kimmy] - Seriously...can
you learn how to drive?
- What is he doing here?
- Mr. Green, I'm so glad you're here.
Well, we shouldn't be here too long today.
We'd like to put up
most of the decorations
right before the event starts,
but things like the banners
we like to put up the day before.
Jacob, can you help me with that ladder?
- Okay.
- You can join the rest of the group.
I'm sure you already know everybody.
- Hey.
- Hey Micah.
- Hey..um...Deja, can I
talk to you for a minute?
- You can say whatever
you want right here.
- Okay...umm...
I..uh...wanted to say I was sorry.
- I shouldn't have messed
with your grades like that.
- What?!?
- He said he was sorry.
- And?!?
- So...you wanna tell me how you did that?
Because my grades could use
a little bit of a pick-me-up,
if you know what I'm saying...
- I...um...
- Don't worry.
I'm not trying to hit on
you. You're not my type.
- Don't take it personal,
no man's her type.
- That's true.
- Hey everyone, well, here's the banners
that we'll be painting.
Once you get that done,
we can hang it up above
the entrance, okay?
I have some stuff to do inside,
so if you need anything, just ask Jacob.
(banner stuffed hard into Clara's stomach)
- [Kimmy] Is this paint?
- [Clara] Yeah...
(gentle upbeat music)
- Wow. Great job guys,
it looks really good.
You have paint on your shirt, Kimmy.
- Oh man, this is my favorite jacket.
- I can get that out for you.
- No, it's fine. It's just a jacket.
- No, I insist.
Especially with all your help
today, I'll take care of it.
Good job guys.
- We did a really good job.
- Yeah we did.
- What do you think, Kimmy?
- Earth to Kimmy, you with us?
- No, you guys are really boring.
Did you hear about this
guy who got murdered?
- There were two murders,
and isn't that the one
that was on the news?
- Yeah, actually it was
behind your house Jacob.
- It was probably the guy
who broke into our shed.
He stole a shovel and a couple of tools.
Looks like Karma got him.
- Wow, you're the last person
I expected to hear that from,
aren't you supposed to be
all turn the other cheek?
- Back in biblical times,
you could kill a thief if
you caught them in the act.
- That's a little harsh.
- So are we gonna to put this banner up?
Or what?
(birds chirping)
- what is this?
- Jack O'lantern pancakes!
- It looks like a deranged clown.
- Well let's hope that
these deranged clowns
at least taste good.
- I love you, dad.
- I love you too.
So...uh...the sheriff
was here this morning
and they're still looking
into trying to figure out,
I guess, who was all
involved in that accident,
but, the stay away order
has been placed on Chad.
So he's not gonna be bothering you again.
- Thank you.
- I gotta protect my baby.
All right, so listen, after
we get done with breakfast,
I was thinking...maybe
we can carve our pumpkins
and keep those demons away.
- Honestly, that would be nice.
These are pretty good.
- Not bad for deranged clowns, right?
- Right.
(laughs)
"Ichabod" by Ok Otter
(upbeat rock music)
♪ Take the road through the trees ♪
♪ Kick through the leaves ♪
♪ Fear they may follow me ♪
♪ Oh Oh ♪
♪ There's a grass on the breeze ♪
♪ We have the needs ♪
♪ They are just ghost stories ♪
♪ Oh Oh ♪
♪ Even found Miami Halloween ♪
♪ Do you believe in each and every ♪
♪ Word that they say ♪
♪ Pull yourself together ♪
♪ Like you always do ♪
♪ They just wanna get the better of you ♪
♪ Ichabod, coming to get you ♪
♪ Unless we could gather away ♪
♪ The branches stray right there ♪
♪ I come this way ♪
♪ Oh Oh ♪
- Where is she?
- [Reporter] Eden Tennessee
has been plagued by several,
mysterious murders.
unfortunately, as of right now,
the police are unable to determine
who is the culprit.
(phone ringing)
(ominous music)
(phone continues ringing)
Come on!
- [Reporter] Approximately
10 PM last night
...residents of the windward area
reported a disturbance
that witnesses described...
- She better not be ditching us.
- [Reporter] Screams and cries for help.
When investigators arrived on the scene,
they were unable to determine
the cause of the disturbance.
(ominous music transitions
to gentle music)
(crowd noise in background)
(children laughing)
(popcorn popping)
- Trick or treat!
- What do you say?
- Thank you.
- 'Cause the devil might get you!
- Rawr!
(kids giggling)
- Man, I miss the good old days.
- Good old days?
- Yeah. You know, when people
used to go door to door.
- Mom says this is much safer.
- I guess.
(ominous music)
- You wanna see me die...
don't you?
You wanna watch me bleed.
(laughs manically)
- What?
(tense music)
(giggles manically)
- Uh...
- Hey! We're out of candy.
- I...um...
I'll be right there.
- Mrs. Roberts, we were wondering
if we could go see Kimmy?
- Yeah. It's fine, thanks for your help.
- Where are they going?
- To check on Kimmy.
- Is she okay?
- Well, she's supposed to be here today
and they still haven't heard from her.
I can stop at Clara's later
and check in on her, okay?
- Oh, Hey Micah, can you pack
this up in the van for me?
- Sure.
- Hey, thanks for your help today.
- No problem.
(gentle music)
- What the hell?
(suspenseful music)
- Shit! Dude.
Didn't mean to scare you,
mom wanted to know if you needed a ride.
- No, I'm okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah...I uh, I think I'll walk.
It's nice night for a walk.
(gentle music)
- [Clara] I can't
believe Kimmy ditched us.
- [Deja] She probably
didn't wanna be caught dead
in this angel costume.
- I guess...
- You sure you don't want
to go to the party with me?
- [Clara] Yeah, I think
I'll just stay home.
- All right. I'll head out then.
- Okay. Be safe.
- I will. Call me if you change your mind.
- I will.
Dad, are you home?
(ominous music)
(door bell rings)
I guess those masks are popular this year.
Aren't you a little too old
to be trick or treating?
(tense music)
You know what?
It's whatever, we have candy left anyway.
(tense music)
(door slams)
(candy grabbed hastily)
Oh, ha ha. You're so scary.
Just take the candy and go.
Let go of me, what are you doing?
Let go of... (screams)
(stabbing sound)
(kick impacts)
(wall impact)
(Clara weeps and pants)
(music intensifies)
(Clara gasps in pain)
(door shut and locked)
(knife scrapes along railing)
(tense music intensifies)
(doorknob rattles)
(doorknob unlocks and door opens)
(door creaks open)
(crickets and dogs in background)
(music stops)
(footsteps squeak)
(crickets and dogs in background)
(Clara weeps)
(tense music resumes)
- Please don't...
(Clara screams)
(knife impales wood floor)
(skull impacts against dresser)
(body hits floor hard)
(heartbeat pounding)
(ominous music)
(Clara sobs)
(suspenseful music)
(blood trickles down drain)
(shower curtain slides open)
(knocking on front door)
(Clara weeps)
(back door opens in distance)
(pounding on glass on front door)
(Clara gasps in pain)
(tense music)
(Clara drags her injured leg)
(music intensifies)
(Clara screams)
(stabbing sounds)
(rubber mask hits deck)
(Mrs. Roberts coughs)
- WHY?!
(blood gurgling sounds)
(Clara sobs)
(pencil lands in blood)
(gentle music plays)
(police chatter from radios)
- Okay, you're all set now.
When you get to the hospital,
you are gonna have to have stitches, okay?
- Okay.
- Here you go, sweetie.
This is to help you, okay?
Until you get to the hospital.
They will
get you another.
Alright?
- Okay.
Why are you here, Micah?
- I found something in the
back of Mrs. Roberts' van...
there were photos of you.
I thought you should know about it.
- Were you the one that
knocked on my door?
- No, I was on your front
step and I rang the doorbell.
And next thing I know there's
a pain in the back of my head,
and I woke up in the bush.
I would have never thought
Mrs. Roberts was...violent.
(gentle music)
(car pulls up and parks)
(Mr. Banks runs across grass)
(sirens blaring)
(Clara begins sobbing)
(gurney rattles as EMTs
bring out Mrs. Roberts)
(gentle music)
- [Reporter] For WGET, I'm Tim Chase.
Authorities this morning are
investigating a horrific scene
that occurred late last
night on Hallow Drive.
An Eden police departments spokesperson
said 18-year-old Clara
Banks of Eden, Tennessee
was attacked by Betty
Roberts, 42, also of Eden.
Ms. Banks suffered multiple stab wounds,
but was able to fend off her attacker,
which led to the death of Roberts.
Betty Roberts had no prior arrest record
nor history of violence,
but sources tell us she
is now the prime suspect
in two murders that occurred
earlier this week in Eden.
In a related story,
authorities are beginning
a search this morning
for Kimmy Nichols.
Nichols, 20 of Eden, went
missing the day before Halloween.
Nichols is a close friend of
Clara Banks (faintly speaking)
and attends Oak Ridge state college.
(ominous music)
(police radio chatter in background)
- So tox screening analysis
of Mrs. Roberts revealed
that she'd been given
the wrong medication...
resulting in severe side effects.
After looking at the deceased'
computer we found emails
sent to your daughter's email address.
It seems Mrs. Roberts had been
fixated on you for some time,
probably the result of the medication.
Side effects included paranoia,
hallucination, agitation...
(ominous music)
(upbeat music)
- Do you have a date tonight?
- No, no, no...
(upbeat music)
(students chattering)
- Maybe I do have a date.
- That's cute.
- Yeah.
(upbeat music)
- Carmel...
(ominous music)
- You okay?
- Mmm hmm...
(Clara choking)
Clara, what's wrong?
(candy crashes to the floor)
(Clara gasping)
- Clara?!?
What's wrong?
(Clara choking)
Clara?
Someone call 911 now!
(Clara gasping)
Oh my God...Clara!
(Clara gasping for air)
Somebody call an ambulance now!
(Clara coughs)
Call 911!!!
Clara!
(ominous music)
Clara?!? Clara!
- Is she okay?
- Call 911!
Clara!
- [Student] Oh my
goodness. What's happening?
(gentle somber music begins)
- Looks like angels. (laughs)
- [Kimmy] Angels... (everyone laughs)
- Hey hon, dinner's ready.
(Jacob taps keyboard to hide screen)
(gentle somber music continues)
- [Mr. Roberts] Hey Jacob,
could you could you come help me
♪ This little light of mine ♪
♪ I'm gonna let it shine ♪
- Stop barking.
(dog barking)
♪ This little light of mine ♪
(dog barking becomes a
crunch of bones and a yelp)
♪ I'm gonna let it shine ♪
♪ This little light of mine ♪
- Hon, you got something on your shirt
♪ I'm gonna let it shine ♪
- The brakes aren't working!
♪ This little light of mine ♪
♪ I'm gonna let it shine ♪
♪ Oh let it shine, let it shine ♪
♪ Oh let it, oh let it shine... ♪
"Bleed Me" by Rebuke
♪ Bleed, bleed me, ♪
♪ Dig under the surface to
find out what you can't see ♪
♪ Bleed, bleed me, ♪
♪ Hope all you discover in
there's suited to your liking ♪
♪ Fall down into the downfall ♪
♪ No Peace till pieces are gone ♪
♪ Dive further down than
just shallow you must ♪
♪ You get to the gallow,
you get turned to dust ♪
♪ Darkness brings light when
you hold life that tight ♪
♪ So breathe, just breathe ♪
♪ Bleed me ♪
♪ Just breathe...bleed me ♪
♪ The demons you'll face
in my depths of despair ♪
♪ Are the faces you're
painting when nobody's there ♪
♪ The strangers in lurking
when hurting to stare ♪
♪ Please breathe ♪
♪ Just breathe...bleed me ♪
♪ (Do you like hurting?) ♪