Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
LAW SOCIETY
MOBILITY INCLUSION CARD
That's it, my darling.
That's a handicapped spot!
I know, I park here every day.
That's not right!
Nobody disabled is around.
But your "darling" crapping
on the sidewalk
is a Class 1 infraction.
This is for the cops. Have a nice day.
-You're late.
-Because of an old lady.
The Big Boss started the meeting.
You're three minutes late.
Yes? Ah, Charlie.
Sorry, I was helping an old lady.
Fine. You were saying, Bertrand?
I was saying we can't work miracles,
nothing in the case file helps our client.
He raped her, that's it.
He'll get the maximum sentence.
So, what have you prepared?
Well, I'll say the only thing
there is to say. That he's sorry.
What do you think, Charlie?
Well, I don't know anything
about the case.
-It doesn't look good for us, but...
-But what?
It's rare to find nothing in a case file.
Excellent. Will you look it over
with Bertrand?
I'm very sorry, but I don't have the time.
Excuse me? I didn't get that.
-I'll have a look.
-Good.
-When is the trial?
-Tomorrow.
If you have a good horse, you make it run.
So, Frédérique, your turn.
The Mercier case...
The boss asked me to give you the summons.
He wants you instead of Bertrand.
So now he wants me to try the case?
The Bobigny courthouse?
That's out of town.
Charlie! Bobigny, tomorrow, 9:00 a.m.
Yes.
Found anything for the case?
No, but I have all night!
Don't forget dinner at your mother's.
She gets on my nerves.
You're tough. Your mother's nice.
Want her? You can have her.
You're kidding me!
This place is falling apart!
No, it's just the lightbulb.
This house is indestructible.
Your grandfather built it.
Of course, look.
No! Don't damage your inheritance.
Mom, I don't want the house,
I just want some light.
Anyway, you work too much.
-Here we go.
-If you worked less,
you might have time to start a family.
No, thanks!
Living alone isn't living.
Whose fault is that? You left Dad.
He was a real man.
Your father, may he rest in peace,
had his faults.
That's right! Tall, handsome, died a hero.
Well, come on, let's eat!
What are you working on?
A case I'm trying
tomorrow morning in Bobigny.
Bobigny? Ah, Bobigny.
I marched there in 1972
for abortion rights.
It's ready.
It was for the trial
of Marie-Claire Chevalier,
a 16-year-old girl who had had
an illegal abortion after being raped.
Her rapist reported it to the police
to get a reduced sentence.
Gisèle Halimi tried the case.
There were so many people
we couldn't get into the courtroom.
I'm so proud you'll be there.
Charlie? Charlie?
It's 7:30, you're listening to RFM.
It's March 8. No, it's not Groundhog Day,
it's International Women's Day,
so, ladies, enjoy.
-It's Bertrand!
-I'm here.
You can't miss me, I'm...
I'm on the blue bridge!
So, did you find anything?
Of course.
-Marie-Claire!
-Who?
-Marie-Claire Chevalier?
-No.
The trial in Bobigny in 1972?
Sure you're a lawyer?
Yeah...
He's guilty. What are you going to say?
-Morning.
-Huh?
You found something?
Can you tell me what you found?
-I have to pee.
-Right.
-Here.
-Good.
That's a good idea. I have to, too.
Pee, I mean.
-Sorry, it's an emergency.
-Seriously?
Who are those people?
-The press.
-Court is in session, be seated.
We'll proceed with drawing jurors.
Juror 15.
Miss Axelle Schneider.
Juror 12. Mr. Daniel Roskis.
Juror 12, come take a seat.
Juror 14, Mrs. Mauricette Sainte-Rose.
My client is a victim of a crime.
A horrible crime
-that must be punished.
-I'll tear her to pieces.
A crime that, today,
in the post-MeToo era,
we can no longer let go unpunished.
Fear must finally switch sides.
It's your responsibility
to make sure this predator
can't hurt anyone anymore,
which is why
I'm calling for 15 years imprisonment
-for this dangerous individual.
-It's good.
Today is International Women's Day.
Because women have rights.
Everyone knows this.
But men have rights, too.
And people tend to forget that these days.
Particularly, the right to have
consensual sex with a woman
without the risk of spending
15 years in prison
just because the woman regrets
having done it.
This woman maintains
my client forced himself on her,
but that's a lie! She's lying.
And I have proof of this lie in my file.
This woman knew him.
They had a date,
and this young woman showed up wearing
sexy underwear.
She even stated to the police,
quote, "that she was wearing
a red lace thong."
Like this one.
When a woman wears a red lace thong,
it's because she hopes
a man will find it, see it,
and take it off.
There was clearly no rape.
The was a consensual sexual relation.
And this thong
is proof of that consent.
Right now, I'm wearing cotton panties.
Do you know why?
Because this morning, when I got dressed,
I knew I didn't have a date.
I knew I was coming here
to the Bobigny courthouse.
That's why I'm not wearing this.
And I'm sure you're not, either, ladies.
This is why
I ask that you acquit this innocent man.
Don't worry, we'll appeal.
Charlie, how could you do that?
It's unworthy of a lawyer,
woman or man.
A lawyer must be able to defend anyone.
Yes, but not however you like!
The thong-consent defense
is a return to the Middle Ages.
-That's not the funniest part.
-What?
I'm not wearing cotton panties.
I'm wearing a thong.
Red lace.
THE "THONG" AFFAIR
A bizarre acquittal
is causing some anger...
...from the people of France
to the National Assembly.
It may be embarrassing to brandish
a thong here.
THE THONG OF CONSENT
How does a rape victim feel
having their underwear displayed in court?
THE THONG AFFAIR: FRANCE ANGRY
An incredible ruling
that will have consequences for future...
...rape victims.
Wearing a thong will be...
...from now on, considered
consent for sexual relations.
Here's our report.
Are the shots for you?
Drinking to forget my victory?
I wouldn't call that a victory.
You're jealous, I get it.
It's your case, but I'm the one on TV.
Do you realize what you've done?
You created a legal precedent.
Look, I did my job.
I defended my client. Period.
-The consequences are not my problem.
-Sure.
-Shots!
-Charlie!
-Hey, Noémie!
-Here I am!
Where's the guy from the other night?
Is he next?
-Hey, maybe!
-What?
To thank me for getting
his client off the hook.
I saw what you did on TV!
Bravo, another bastard goes free
thanks to you.
-Let's celebrate!
-No, no.
Come on, nothing heavy.
No, I need to behave.
It's almost therapeutic.
Come on! Trust me!
Come on!
Okay.
All right...
Okay. Besides...
We're all gonna die!
PRINCESS STREET
I'll be there in five minutes.
I just left Castel.
Sorry, it's an emergency.
That's my taxi!
-But this is my day!
-What?
We have one day a year,
best take advantage of it.
-Where to?
-17B quai de Conti.
Hey, I know you! You were on the news.
You're the lawyer who tries cases
against women.
That's me.
And you are...
TAXI DRIVER
IDENTIFICATION CARD
Hubert, the taxi driver.
You must love danger.
Taxi drivers make safer enemies
than women.
Yeah, I'm so sick of their #MeToo.
Well, there's still a lot of inequality.
Did you know only 2% of streets
are named after women?
Fascinating.
Guess which name is the most common.
What do you think?
A man. General de Gaulle!
With 3,903 streets and an airport.
Is this Cash Cab Wikipedia?
And for women?
Who has the most streets named after her?
-Don't care.
-No, Marie Curie,
with 999 streets.
Followed by Joan of Arc, then George Sand.
But only because people think she's a man.
Guess how many streets Joan of Arc has.
672.
She still got burned alive.
Know why she was burned alive?
Because she was crazy and heard voices.
No, that's what the books say.
-But I know the real story.
-Excuse me.
Could you just drive and...
Okay.
So...
It was because she wore pants.
Who cares about your history lesson?
Stop, we're here.
Those who forget the past
are condemned to relive it.
No, Winston Churchill.
Shit! You little shit!
My Louboutins!
What the hell am I doing here?
This is shit!
Stay away, pig!
What is it, pig?
Human!
The devil's in the pigpen!
Sir!
-Come back, please.
-The devil!
Devil's in the pigpen!
Nice piggy.
Nice piggy. Don't move. Sir?
Sir...
Sir?
Come back!
Don't move, piggy!
Help, anyone!
There it is! There!
Finally! Why did you lock me in?
You're under arrest, witch!
What the hell is this, Medieval Times?
Great costumes, guys!
-Move!
-What are you doing?
Harlot from hell!
Okay, I'm high.
You're cops, and I'm hallucinating.
Sorry, I'm not laughing at you.
I'm a lawyer, I know the procedure.
I'm in the drunk tank.
Yes, okay,
I took some therapeutic substances.
Silence, nasty woman!
Okay!
Therapeutic substances, my ass!
This isn't therapeutic.
-Explain that to Monseigneur Cauchon.
-Who?
We're all gonna die!
Noémie? Is that you?
-Did they arrest you too?
-Yes.
I'm Noémie! That's me!
If you could see your face!
What's with these hallucinations?
-What was in those pills?
-Pills?
Disrobe, witches!
-Come on!
-No!
Move it, I said!
-Faster!
-We're getting undressed?
Fine, let's get undressed.
Faster!
-Come on!
-Here we go.
-Move it!
-Everyone get naked!
Line up! Come here.
Move it!
Bishop Cauchon will check
if you bear the mark of the devil.
-You!
-Come here.
Not me!
Yeah, right. Cauchon just wants to ogle
the women's sexy underwear.
Or not.
Move it!
-You.
-Come.
Move it!
Not you.
Thank you, Your Lordship! Thank you!
Wait for me outside.
Move it!
What a pig!
I bet he's the one who ate my Louboutins.
-Move it!
-I'm scared!
Don't worry, it's just a medical check
before they lock us up. It's nothing.
-Move it!
-You.
No, I don't want to!
Noémie? Are you okay?
Move it!
The clothes of the devil!
No, they're Victoria's Secret.
Put your clothes on, witch!
-Okay, fine!
-Come on, move it.
-You.
-Let's go.
It smells like shit!
Faster!
Hurry up!
Move it!
This is itchy!
Is this burlap?
Sustainable clothing sucks!
So that's...
the van. Okay.
So, gentlemen, if it's possible,
I'd like to go feet-first.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Noémie! Are you okay?
Souvenir!
For posterity, my dear!
-These aren't my clothes!
-Shut up!
These aren't my--
These aren't my clothes!
Go!
These...
are not...
my... clothes!
This is ridiculous.
There's no point in fighting the cops,
you'll just make it worse.
I'm fighting injustice.
Well...
it looks really effective!
That's Rouen.
Oh, so pretty!
-That's nice!
-Daughter of Satan!
-Witches!
-Burn in hell!
Hedonists!
Burn them!
Are the dentists on strike in Rouen?
This is poo!
Okay, an immediate trial, girls.
If we confess, we'll be okay.
-What is your name?
-My name is...
My name is...
-Noémie!
I confess.
You confess to being a witch.
You shall be burned alive.
-Burned alive?
-Thank you.
-Thank you!
Did he say, "burned alive"?
These drugs are strong!
Next!
Joan of Arc.
Joan of Arc?
It's Joan of Arc!
Do you really believe
you are in a state of grace?
If I am not, may God put me in it.
If I am, may He keep me in it.
Why do you dress as a man?
To drive the English out of France.
You'll agree it's more practical.
It's against nature.
You're a man and you're wearing a robe.
But there are no English
to drive out here.
That's why I was wearing a dress,
but it was stolen.
Oh? Who stole it?
I imagine it was the English, to trap me.
Do you think God loves the English?
Yes, but in their homeland.
It was the English who branded
these clothes with the mark of the devil.
Levi's!
The mark of the devil!
No, it's just a jeans brand.
Enough!
Joan,
you have chosen to present yourself
with all the bearings of a man.
Pants, short hair...
And freedom of speech.
You shall therefore be burned alive
for heresy.
Guards!
Seize this virgin transvestite soldier!
Here we go. She never listens!
You're going to get tased
and face other charges
for contempt of court.
Next!
Your Honor, gentlemen.
-What is your name?
-Leroy, Charlie.
-You believe you're King Charles?
-Uh, no.
I was at Castel...
The castle of which lord?
-On Princess Street.
-What princess?
In the 6th Arrondissement.
Anyway, Your Honor, I confess.
Yes, I committed a crime.
I took some drugs.
I don't know which ones,
but they were really strong.
Sorry, but if you could see what I see.
The looks on your faces!
She was arrested wearing men's clothes.
Blasphemy!
The main charge is heresy.
No, heresy is for Joan of Arc.
For me, it's the consumption of narcotics.
Bishop Cauchon,
we notice that she's on the right path
for she appears before us
in women's clothes.
That's right, man.
Yes...
but under her women's clothes,
she's wearing undergarments
as red as hell.
I therefore ask
that she undergo a trial by water.
So be it. Take her to the bridge!
The bridge? What bridge?
-Next!
-What's this about a bridge?
Is it the Bridge of Avignon?
What is your name?
Feet and hands tied? Seriously?
Throw her in!
Luckily none of this is real.
Because this is really high, guys.
-The toes of Satan!
-Throw her in!
This is real!
If she drowns, she's not a witch.
I hope she doesn't drown.
That way we can burn her alive.
She's not coming back up!
-Another innocent woman!
-Fifth one this week.
Who are you? What are you doing here?
Who are you? What am I doing here?
François Blanchard, bank manager.
You're in my office.
Thank God, the nightmare is over.
She peed on my carpet!
Oh, no, it's the river...
Look, I just want to go home.
Fine with me. Get out. Out!
My phone, I lost it in the water.
Could you call me a taxi?
Also, I'd like to withdraw some cash.
Here's my card. Thanks.
To withdraw money
from your husband's account,
I need your husband's permission,
not this... thing.
What? No, from my account.
Your account?
Your husband let you
open an account in your name?
What's wrong with you?
You sound like my mom.
I'm a lawyer, okay?
I work. I have more in my account
than your crappy little bank.
So, give me 200 euros.
-200 what?
-200 euros!
Is this a joke?
Okay, I get it,
there's a hidden camera, right?
Let me tell you,
I don't find this funny at all!
Gérard!
Well!
I'll tell you what!
I'm going to send a strongly-worded email
to your management!
CREDIT BANK - BCE
A bum, stay away!
Mom? Dad?
Dad?
Dad! Dad!
How can I help you?
As you know, we're newlyweds...
You want to open an account for her?
No, I was thinking of a simple checkbook
on my account.
You're right. Women can't manage money.
You'll retain control.
Come into my office,
you'll be more comfortable.
-Dad!
-Gérard!
This isn't possible.
Dad is dead.
And this isn't real.
It's real!
You're crazy!
That's it, I'm crazy.
This is all in my head.
Hello! Where to?
You? I know you!
You're Hubert!
Yes, that's me. How are you?
Not good at all!
The drugs, the cart, the drowning,
-and Dad...
-Breathe!
And all this! The banker who wouldn't...
Breathe! It's normal.
You can't open a bank account or even work
without your husband's permission.
Because you're a woman in 1964.
'64?
What the hell am I doing in '64?
That's up to you.
Look, sir, I just want to go home.
Not yet.
How long will this madness go on?
Some get it quickly, others...
You could take a while.
I have cases, clients.
I don't have time for this!
You don't have a choice.
Okay, how much do you want?
-I have money!
-Not anymore.
Get in the car.
Who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
-Get in.
-Did I free your mother's killer?
-Okay.
I'm a lawyer
just doing my job.
What is this, voodoo?
I couldn't let you get my seats all wet.
What a nightmare!
No, just a journey.
Journey? To where?
Buckle up, here we go!
Oh, right. No seatbelts in '64.
My head.
I'm home!
No, I'm not home!
What do you want?
Thank you, sir! Very much.
For intervening.
But I'd rather you not come near me.
Don't come near me, I'm warning you!
I'll scream!
No, she wear...
pants.
Let me go!
What the hell is this?
No worthless cab driver
will decide what I do!
Okay. This all started
with a night out drinking.
So, I'll just do it again
and wake up at home.
I need some alcohol!
And...
What? What now?
What? Why are you arresting me?
For illegally wearing... pants.
Again? We already did this.
This isn't the Middle Ages.
Let me go!
Next!
-I want to leave!
-It's for a refill.
Here's my doctor's note.
Let me go, I need to drink alcohol!
As soon as someone brings you a dress.
-I don't know anyone!
-In all of Paris?
No, in this whole era.
-Come on, be nice.
-Next!
I'm going to die here.
She had the same mustache!
You! You may leave.
Just like that?
Without being burned at the stake?
Someone brought a doctor's note
authorizing your cross-dressing.
-What?
-Go on.
Go!
"Authorizing Miss Charlie Leroy
"to dress as a man for her health!
"Paris, April 6, 1850."
Where are you, Hubert?
I know this permit is from you!
No, it was me.
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
You're not from here, I can tell.
You don't know the rules.
We women have to help each other out!
-Have a nice day.
-No, don't leave!
-Let's have a drink.
-I'd love to.
I have all we need at my estate in Nohant.
-George, nice to meet you.
-Charlie.
I love your dress!
You can have it.
Gainsbourg!
Chopin!
Étude 3, opus 10.
Okay. I was wondering,
which illness permits me to wear pants?
-Loose organs?
-No.
Excessive hairiness?
No? Varicose veins?
Greed.
I had to pay off a doctor.
Pay off...
How do you earn a living, George?
I write books.
Wait, I'm getting drunk
with George Sand, the author?
Authoress.
Even if the cretins in the French Academy
removed the word
which dates back to the 14th century.
Oh, yeah?
They took it out of the dictionary?
Why?
Because those men think
a woman shouldn't write.
They're real...
doddery old men!
I'd call them sacks of shit!
I prefer doddery old men.
Of course you do. You're George Sand.
I'm so ashamed.
I've never read anything by you.
I've only written more than 260 books.
So it's strange we didn't
read you in school.
One day perhaps.
-After I die.
-No, George.
I have something to confess.
I'm from the future.
This taxi... driver
sent me to the past.
I went to the Middle Ages,
pre-history, and 1964.
Wow! What's the future like in 1964?
Well, no, '64 is in the past.
So, you're from the past?
Well, technically, yes.
But what I mean is that in my present,
which is your future, well, at school,
-we read Balzac.
-He's a friend.
-Victor Hugo.
-Alfred de Musset.
-He's a lover.
-You're sleeping with Alfred de Musset?
-Not anymore.
Who are you sleeping with now?
-Stendhal?
-No, he's a friend.
Now I'm seeing...
-Frédéric.
-Fredounet?
No!
-Who?
-Chopin.
You're sleeping with Frédéric Chopin?
You're a star-fucker!
See? We know the works of your friends,
your boyfriends, but not yours.
That's why I write under a man's name.
Female, male,
what's the difference?
A dick?
An unnecessary appendage.
Believe me.
I'm free, Charlie.
-Free in my head and my body.
-Okay.
Don't be scared. I know it's forbidden.
But this estate shelters
my freedom beautifully,
the freedom we must hide
from a puritanical world.
What's this mark?
It's a birthmark.
George, George!
I've never... with a woman, okay?
-No?
-No.
-So I think I might need...
-What?
Some therapeutic substances.
I have what you need.
Really? Okay.
This dress sucks!
I was thinking of something stronger.
There's nothing stronger.
Okay, so let's do it.
I'm drinking to go back
to the 21st century,
where you can wear pants
without going to jail.
In 150 years,
I'll probably be dead.
So, let's drink!
To freedom, to pants, and to women!
Bottoms up!
Charlie?
Where'd she go?
You tolerate us,
but we want to participate!
I'll remind you that women are excluded
from all political clubs
except here, with the Jacobins.
Well, clearly alcohol won't bring me back.
Calm down, ladies!
Women have no place in politics!
They're a danger to the revolution.
They corrupt men in their beds.
Women go over there!
You have no business here.
Doddery old man!
We didn't need women to take the Bastille!
Women go over there!
Go, go...
-Citizen Robespierre?
-What?
Without us, the King would
never have ratified your Rights of Man.
Men may have taken the Bastille,
but women took the King!
Is that true?
Thank you, ladies, for participating.
You can now return to your kitchens.
Seriously?
You go back to the kitchen!
This is 1793,
and we want to speak on the platform!
Here, here!
Citizen Olympe de Gouges,
you know very well women
cannot come up here.
If women can ascend the gallows,
they should also ascend the platform.
She's right!
I agree!
I'm a man and I ask to speak.
Who's that?
You may speak, Nicolas de Condorcet!
Sir, you're a mathematician.
Educate us on subtraction and addition,
but leave politics to us.
As a mathematician,
I know it doesn't add up
when half of humankind
is deprived of rights,
and the other half, their ideas.
Is it me or is he really sexy?
-It's a waste...
-Okay. It's only me.
-...to ignore women in the revolution.
-Bravo!
Let them have responsibilities.
And who'll speak on the platform
when they're home pregnant?
Seriously?
Or when they're temporarily indisposed?
No woman has ever proven herself
in politics.
That's mathematical, Mr. de Condorcet.
Firstly, citizenship is not only
granted to men of genius.
Just look at Robespierre!
Who said that?
Secondly, it's easy to attribute
skill and courage to men,
but what do you make of
female political leaders abroad?
For example...
Margaret Thatcher! Or Angela Merkel.
Michelle Obama.
I was thinking more
of Elizabeth of England,
Maria Theresa of Austria,
or the Catherines of Russia.
Them too!
Who are they again?
Thirdly, we cannot verify
whether women have talent
-if we do not allow them to express it.
-Bravo!
Nicolas, president! Nicolas...
A woman who speaks brilliantly
on the platform
could only be a man.
Let's find out!
I ask to speak.
Citizen Olympe de Gouges,
your request to speak is denied.
Then here's my Declaration
of the Rights of Woman
and the Female Citizen that I wrote
and I ask you to read.
You kick ass, lady!
Your rag will never be read
in this assembly. Guards, remove her!
-"Mothers..."
-Silence her!
"...sisters, female citizen
representatives of the nation, ask..."
Here!
Nicolas!
"...ask to be represented
in the National Assembly.
"Considering that ignorance, neglect,
or contempt of the Rights of Women
"are the sole causes of public misfortune
and corruption of governments
"have resolved..."
This is over!
You won't keep me from speaking!
Yeah!
Oh, Nicolas!
You're so... So...
Intelligent.
Olympe?
Today, no one was listening,
but history will remember us.
Well, don't get carried away, you two.
Because I didn't know you.
You're not in any book.
Danto, Marat, that moron Robespierre...
But Nicolas de Condorcet...
You're a high school
and a statue outside my building.
And you, Olympe de Gouges,
you're not even a small museum.
Even though you're right
about everything, it's crazy!
You need to create buzz
about your Declaration.
You're not getting it.
I'd need to explain the Internet,
computers, social media.
So, we put stuff on the feed,
then on our wall,
and people read it.
Great idea! We'll put posters
on all the walls in Paris.
-No one has ever done that!
-Let's do it!
-You'll risk the guillotine.
-I don't fear death.
Me neither. I'm a Highlander
in quantum-leap mode.
DECLARATION OF THE RIGHTS OF WOMAN
AND THE FEMALE CITIZEN
What's this about women who took the King?
Well, the women's march.
Never heard of it.
On October 5,
8,000 Parisian women marched up to
the Palace of Versailles to demand bread
and force the king to ratify
their damn declaration.
8,000, can you believe it?
8,000?
According to the organizers or the police?
-Same thing!
-Not where I'm from.
Where I'm from, the the Rights of Man
are for both men and women.
No, both men and women would be "human."
And their declaration
only gives voting rights to...
Men.
So that means the Rights of Man
is just for men?
You're a funny one.
That's crazy!
That's crazy. Men have been playing us
for fools for years?
Yes, but with this,
we're going to remind them we exist.
Those coprolites.
-What?
-Coprolite. Fossilized excrement.
I like that even more
than "doddery old man."
It's a sack of shit, but fossilized.
Yeah, but not all men are coprolites.
Oh, yeah? Like who?
Nicolas de Condorcet!
He reeks testosterone.
I'm going to do him.
Now's my chance, with my cool hat.
Citizens!
Citizen Olympe de Gouges,
you're under arrest for violating
the sovereignty of the people.
No! Leave her alone!
I'm a lawyer.
I demand to see the arrest warrant
to verify it isn't corrupted
by any procedural error.
Bunch of coprolites!
You owe us a modicum of...
Charlie, you're so, so...
intelligent.
Thank you.
What's this now?
What year is it?
1789, apparently.
No, what date is it today?
-March 8, 1982.
-What about Olympe de Gouges?
-Who?
-What happened to Olympe de Gouges!
Let go of me, crazy lady!
LIBRARY
Decapitated!
They decapitated her.
It's my fault!
I told he to put up posters.
And Nicolas? What did they do to Nicolas?
Hubert, why am I here?
And why the French Revolution?
Answer me, please!
Did you know Nicolas poisoned himself
to avoid the guillotine?
That's weird, the death penalty
has just been abolished by Badinter.
Weird, yeah. Two hundred years too late.
I've had enough of this.
I want to go home.
I want all this to stop.
Hubert!
There he is.
There you are!
Now, take me home!
-And where is that?
-Who are you?
The taxi drive you just hailed.
So, honey, tell me,
do you live with your parents?
Well, yes, in '82 I lived with my parents.
That was the year Mom left Dad.
I know where to go!
60 de Bretagne street, please
And we're off, darling.
Is that costume for a movie?
Well, you're very pretty, honey.
Nice costume! I like it.
Really. You're a sexy
little revolutionary.
Here we are.
That's 64 francs and 45 cents.
Yes, but I don't have any money, see?
I'll just go ask my dad.
A beautiful woman like you
doesn't have to ask her dad.
We can settle things like adults.
Come up here.
It's like ten bucks!
What would I do for ten bucks?
Don't worry, we'll find out.
You're going to get exposed
for the pig you are,
so you know what? Enjoy it while it lasts.
And remember this, #MeToo.
Hashtag what?
Get out of here or my dad
will kick your teeth in!
-Skank! Scumbag! Filthy whore!
-That's right.
Mom.
Oh, Dad!
My precious Dad.
Dad?
And for the first time in France,
this Monday, March 8, will officially be
dedicated to women.
It will be celebrated at the Elysée Palace
where the Head of State has invited...
Look what you made me do!
How could I have forgotten this?
It wasn't a birthmark!
You sick man! You burned me!
Mom! Mom!
You'll get one too!
Look what you made me do!
Get out!
Dad!
Whoa!
Hello, need a ride?
You knew!
You knew my dad was violent!
Why did my mom let me believe otherwise?
You believed it all by yourself.
How could I have blocked
that out all these years?
She actually left him to protect me.
She didn't want to tarnish his image.
Hubert! Take me back. I miss my mom!
Your mom?
The one you criticize all the time?
It's so funny having innocent people
wander around their past.
Those who forget their past
are condemned...
To...
Relive it!
Could you stop with the quotes, Yoda?
No, Winston Churchill.
Now hop in!
Okay, Hubert! I get it, I've had enough.
We're still well off the mark.
Look,...
These dresses really suck.
I told you, I understand.
I got it.
All men are coprolites.
My dad, my boss.
You! Which means, we can go home.
Him too?
Oh, Nicolas! No, not him.
You're right, all men are coprolites
except for Nicolas de Condorcet.
So, we still have a way to go.
That's enough, I'll take the reins!
Where are we? And when are we?
Paris, Dauphine Street, April 19, 1906.
What are we doing here?
Do I have to kill someone again?
You didn't kill anyone, history did.
You can't change that.
Who will history kill next?
Please tell me they have
speed bumps in 1906?
Pierre! Pierre!
Pierre!
Is that Marie Curie?
Don't tell me I killed Pierre Curie!
This can't be!
I'm sorry!
So sorry!
Hubert, come back!
Don't worry, he'll pull through.
I'll put him recovery position.
Then pull his leg out.
Like that.
It's nothing! Just a sprain.
There, nothing at all.
His passing is a tragedy for science,
particularly for the Sorbonne,
who has lost
an admirable physics professor.
We'll never find anyone to replace him.
No one truly understands the significance
of his work on radioactivity.
Radioactivity?
Is it really necessary to teach that?
Or even study?
I doubt it'll lead
to any major discoveries.
Sorry to interrupt, gentlemen,
but if they're looking
to replace Pierre Curie,
tell them to hire Marie Curie.
A woman? Come on.
-So what?
-So, miss,
a woman has never
held a post at a university.
And you are?
Aristide Briand.
Yes, your name rings a bell...
What do you do again?
He's only the Minister of Education.
-And you are?
-A woman.
Who is wondering why a woman
can't be a professor.
Because she's a woman,
and women can't teach men.
Clearly, with your view of radioactivity,
I understood you're a real champ.
But you, Aristide Briand,
do you want to be someone
no one remembers?
Like... him?
Or do you want to be a minister
history will remember...
because he appointed Marie Curie
to the Sorbonne?
Of course, with the sudden death
of Pierre Curie,
she's the only one who understands
their work on radioactivity, but...
She's a woman.
You were saying?
-Will she agree to it?
-Of course!
No.
You can't refuse!
I have research, two daughters to raise,
and a woman cannot be a professor.
Yes! You!
You'll be the most celebrated
woman in France.
You'll have schools and hospitals
named after you.
And 999 streets!
-You'll win the Nobel Prize.
-I already did with Pierre.
You'll get another one.
No, a woman has never won
a Nobel Prize in physics or chemistry.
You'll be the first!
Thanks to... all this!
Wait, I'm in Marie Curie's lab...
Marie, what's that?
It's not uranium, is it?
No.
It's radium.
It's millions of times more radioactive.
Radiation? Marie, guys!
-We need to protect ourselves!
-From what?
-Do you have any tinfoil?
-What?
Belts?
So, what's the first female professor
going to teach her students?
Bravo!
A female professor?
The world is upside-down!
Why not a female prime minister?
This may shock you, but it'll happen.
Her name's Edith Cresson.
Charlie, can you lower the blinds, please?
Yes, excuse me.
Okay, Hubert, I can go home.
I've understood.
So, to succeed,
a woman doesn't need a husband.
You're right, I already knew that.
That's not it.
To succeed, a woman needs
to run over her husband?
Okay, I still don't get it.
Allow me to introduce radium.
Oh, come on.
Enough with the radium!
She'll give everyone cancer!
Ladies and gentlemen, we must leave!
I'm so stupid.
Gentlemen, we must leave!
Fire!
-There we go!
-Move!
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Who are you?
I'm...
-The new maid, right?
-Sure.
-Are you sick?
-Nauseous every morning.
Are you pregnant?
Of course not, I'm not married.
-Did you sleep with someone?
-No.
Yes?
A little bit.
With who?
Well, my master.
-Esther!
-It's my master.
-Yes, sir?
-Thirsty!
-Yes, sir.
-Hungry.
Yes, sir.
Your master is Napoleon?
Well, yes!
You're going to have Napoleon's baby?
That's great!
That's crazy!
If I'm pregnant, what do I do?
Because unmarried women can't find work
and are banished from society!
Just get an abortion.
Abortion is a crime!
You can end up in prison!
Where are you from?
Yeah, sorry, it's the 1800s.
Anyway, I was wondering...
Does Napoleon sleep with all his maids?
Yes.
No, leave it.
I'll do it.
In your condition, it's better.
Give me your apron.
You can't change history.
But you can take advantage of it.
There she is, the sexy maid.
George Sand isn't the only one
who can sleep with celebrities.
Come in.
I'm the new maid.
I understand there's a tradition
with the new ones.
And I like to respect traditions.
Especially because it's been ages
since I've... been respected.
Traditionally.
That's enough. Bottoms up!
What the...
How dare you?
Do you know who I am?
Yes, Napoleon.
And you can grumble about it later.
Straddle up, Your Majesty.
Impossible, I have to work!
Hey! Impossible isn't French.
I love that!
I'm going to use it.
I know.
For a maid, you really...
Have it made!
-Got a condom?
-A what?
All's fair in love and war!
Oh, Your Majesty...
Can I call you Nicolas?
Let me introduce you
to the little corporal.
Nico...
Napo!
You're still working?
I'm writing the first Civil Code.
The Civil Code of 1804?
No, it's 1803.
Your code will be enacted next year.
This is the pen that wrote the Civil Code?
With your initials?
Can I keep it? Please, Napo?
Keep it. A gift from Napoleon.
Ah, women. You give them a pen
and they're happy.
"Woman is... eiuen?"
You have terrible handwriting.
No, not "eiuen," it's "given."
"Woman is given to man to make children.
"She is therefore her property
as a fruit tree belongs to a gardener."
You're putting that in?
Well, yes.
Thirsty!
I'm not your maid.
Yes, you are.
No, I'm not. Actually, I'm a lawyer.
Lawyer?
Yeah.
That's funny because
I'm the one who...
I reinstated lawyers,
and I didn't authorize women.
-Know why?
-I'm gonna enjoy this.
Because women are good for one thing.
Obeying their husbands.
Article...
Article 213 of my Code.
"The husband must protect his wife.
"And the wife must obey her husband."
That's funny!
Because Article 213 was amended
and today it reads that
"Spouses shall jointly
"provide moral and material guidance
for the family."
Today?
What is this nonsense?
Today? I just read it to you today.
Obviously not today, today.
Today in the future.
There you go.
That's why you'll never be man's equal.
You can't even understand time.
What's your problem with women?
Your mother's a woman.
Your future child may be a girl.
I got you pregnant?
What?
We slept together 15 minutes ago!
Are you stupid? Not me, Esther!
Esther?
Esther the mulatto?
-Mulatto?
-Guards!
That's right, he reinstated slavery.
Yes, sir.
Have Esther dismissed immediately.
-Yes, sir!
-What?
Dismiss a pregnant woman
and then abandon Josephine for sterility?
Josephine is sterile?
-Oops.
-Who are you, witch?
-Hubert, not witches again.
-Guards!
-Yes, sir?
-Arrest her.
No, no, because today
there's a Code thanks to you!
No more arbitrariness,
no more witch trials
or drownings or burnings.
Now you need a motive to arrest me.
She stole my pen with my initials.
Search her.
It'll be quick.
I don't think she has it, sir.
Search her dress.
It's so small.
I won't even waste time arguing.
So, what's the punishment?
An hour on the picket?
Seriously? Forced labor
for stealing a pen?
It was just a pen!
And I didn't even steal it.
This is not fair!
Okay, Hubert, I get it.
I freed guilty people, I know.
I won't do that anymore.
Quit shouting! You're a criminal like us.
You stole a pen, her, a skirt,
her, two apples.
-What did you do?
-I cheated on my husband.
You're going to break rocks for that?
Men break rocks.
What do women do in labor camps?
They give us to colonists
to repopulate the colonies.
I'd rather break rocks.
You don't get a choice.
27, come forward!
Number 27.
That's the one I want.
She's all yours.
No!
Get her!
Women are forbidden from public urinals!
Your weenie is too small
to see anyway, moron.
Public toilets for men only?
What do women do,
pee in the street standing up?
Thanks, Hubert!
It's the Liberation!
Hubert! Why am I here?
Fine, don't answer.
I'll find out by myself.
Pardon, excuse me.
Pardon. Here we go.
Hello, excuse me, what's going on?
Municipal elections.
And women can finally vote.
Today's the day women vote
for the first time?
-What's the day today?
-The 29th.
The whole date?
Month, day, year?
They can vote,
but they don't know the date.
It's April 29, 1945.
We got the right to vote so late?
Yes, and it's still too early
if you ask me.
We didn't.
-Sorry?
-Forget it.
-Go ahead, ma'am.
-I will, sir.
You're toxic.
Vote cast!
Marie-Louise Fèvre.
October 17, 1918.
Vote cast!
-Can I borrow it?
-Grandma?
Françoise!
-Lend your doll to the little girl.
-Mom?
Oh, Mom!
Françoise, come here.
Who are you?
Grandma!
Ma'am. I'm sorry, I'm just emotional.
I miss my family so much.
The war, Paris has finally been liberated
and the rest of France will be soon.
Yes, and soon the Armistice!
That'll be a big day!
Today's a big day, too.
By the way, who did you vote for?
I didn't vote.
My husband's not really for it.
But this is historic!
Gran... Ma'am, you can't not vote!
I did it, Mom. I voted for the first time.
My big guy. You're a man now!
Uncle...
Your son. Your son voted and you didn't?
-Well, yes.
-Mom, I put the paper in the envelope!
Hey, but I put it in the mailbox!
The ballot box, stupid.
I'm not stupid!
-Let me go!
-They're so young!
I'm not stupid!
That's enough, boys!
Stop, let's go. Monique, we're going home.
No, she's not going. She'd like to vote.
What are you talking about?
Yes, René, I'd like to vote.
If it's okay with you, of course.
Don't be ridiculous.
She said she wants to vote.
Hey, suffragette, don't give
her any wild ideas!
-Please, René...
-And you! Don't make me...
You used to hit Grandma?
What?
Françoise, never let a man hit you, okay?
Leave my daughter alone.
And don't marry Christian Leroy!
Repeat after me! Christian Leroy!
Christian Leroy.
Because those who forget the past
are condemned to relive it.
Winston Churchill said that.
No, he didn't.
Well, he will... soon.
Sir, your wife...
-Control her.
-She's not my wife!
"She's not my wife."
No worries there.
Wait,
if Mom never marries Dad,
I won't be born.
I just killed myself.
Mom!
Have you seen my mother?
Move!
Mom!
Mom? Sorry. Mom!
Have you seen my mother?
Mom?
Oh, Bobigny courthouse!
Oh, I'm...
Wide collars, turtleneck sweaters,
I'm not home yet.
I really hope they sentence
Marie-Claire's mother.
Marie-Claire Chevalier?
-This is the Bobigny trial? It's 1972?
-Yes.
That means my mom is here!
I hope they sentence her, too.
Her daughter's a harlot.
How can you say that?
You're a girl, you're the same age!
Is your headband too tight or something?
Anyway, if Mom's here
she must be on the other side.
-Out of my way!
-Yes, go.
Stay on your side, ma'am, please!
-My mother's on that side.
-No!
But I'm pro-choice!
Of course you are. Get over there.
Okay, obviously...
That's provocation!
That's provocation! Unbelievable.
This is pointless!
Simone Veil will legalize abortion
in three years.
No! This is provocation.
What now? If I go back, they'll kill me.
Let her in!
-Let her in!
-Go ahead.
Excuse me, do you know a Françoise?
-Françoise?
-Yes.
Of course. Hey, Françoise!
Someone's looking for you.
Oh, Mom!
Oh, sorry. You're going to be a mom!
That's great!
Yes, it happens to lots of women.
I was afraid you wouldn't
sleep with Dad. Well, the father.
I'm so happy!
Thanks.
And your daughter will love you
more than she says.
Okay, but it might be a boy.
I don't think so.
Girl or boy, it'll be the same name.
SLUT SPECIAL
CHARLIE HEBDO
So, that's why? I never knew.
That's crazy.
So, I am Charlie!
Okay!
Of course, you don't get the reference.
The hearing is public!
Let us in!
In his closing argument,
the prosecutor asked the judge to sentence
the mother of Marie-Claire Chevalier
to three years of prison.
Three other women risk prison as well...
The backstreet abortionist
and two friends
who helped pay for the illegal act.
So it's now up to counselor
Gisèle Halimi...
This is Gisèle Halimi's defense speech!
-Of course!
-We can't miss this!
I know, but they won't let us in.
Let us in! The hearing is public!
I have an idea. Excuse me, sorry!
Pardon, excuse me.
Excuse me, sir.
Hello, excuse me. I'm a lawyer.
This pregnant woman is my client.
-We need to get in.
-No.
What about for 50 francs?
-Do you have 50?
-Yes.
If you have permission, that's different.
-You're incredible!
-I get it from my mother.
I identify with Mrs. Chevalier,
with the three women present
in the hearing.
with the women marching in the street
and with millions of French women.
They're my family, their struggle is mine.
They're my daily practice.
It's always the same class, poor women,
vulnerable, not in a relationship.
I've been defending them for 20 years.
I've yet to defend
an important politician,
or the wife of a famous doctor,
or lawyer, or of a CEO,
or one of their mistresses.
Because you always sentence the same ones,
the Mrs. Chevaliers.
Now that's a defense speech!
Take a woman who find herself pregnant
because her contraception fails.
Suppose we forget to take our pill.
Yes, we can forget our pill.
Suppose we make a mistake.
A mistake in the choice of contraception.
Or the position of the diaphragm.
Failure. Error. Forgetfulness.
Do you want to force women
to create life through failure?
Through error? Through forgetfulness?
There are young women
who see their pregnancy through,
for complex reasons,
but let's say
it's because they respect the law.
Article 317.
They see it through to the end.
What do we do for them?
We call them whores.
Never mind the fact that
they have to abandon their studies.
It's true repression
that befalls single mothers.
This law, gentlemen, cannot survive
because it fundamentally
goes against women's liberation,
who have always been oppressed.
Women were slaves even
before slavery was born.
When Christianity became a state religion,
women became the "demon," the "temptress."
-In the Middle Ages, women were nothing.
-That's true.
And despite the Revolution,
when women emerged to speak
and go to the barricade,
they still weren't full human beings.
She couldn't even vote.
In the Industrial Age,
when women became workers,
she was exploited, as were all workers.
But exploitation that workers suffer
is in addition to the overexploitation
of women by men.
And this, in every social class.
Women are more than exploited.
They are overexploited.
And oppression, as Simone de Beauvoir
said recently...
It's Simone de Beauvoir.
-...isn't only about the economy.
-Hi.
I love what you do.
Oppression is an age-old strategy
upheld over centuries
to submit women to men,
housewives or courtesans.
Are you okay?
Yes, it's what she's saying, it's so...
Did you know, gentlemen,
that in the preamble to the Civil Code,
the authors wrote this,
the entire destiny of women.
"Woman is given to man
so she can make children.
"She is therefore her property
as a fruit tree belongs to a gardener."
That's Napoleon.
Look at yourselves, and look at us.
Four women appearing before four men.
Would you agree, gentlemen,
to appear before a tribunal of women
for the right to control your own body?
That would be insane!
Gentlemen, accepting
that we are so alienated,
accepting that we don't have
a right to control our bodies
would be accepting, gentlemen,
that we are no more than boxes,
receptacles in which we sow by surprise,
by mistake, by ignorance,
in which we sow sperm.
I'm going into labor!
Go on, continue!
Act like we're not here!
Come on, Françoise, let's go!
The baby's coming!
No, the baby's not coming.
You give birth in five days in Paris.
-Come on, hold it in.
-I can't.
-Squeeze your legs!
-Oh, no! It's coming!
The baby's coming!
This is my fault!
Why did I bring you in here?
You should've stayed
outside the courthouse.
Help me!
I'm not gonna deliver myself!
This isn't happening.
I'm gonna be born on the floor in Bobigny!
I see my head!
Charlie, I love you.
It's 7:30, you're listening to RFM.
It's March 8. No, it's not Groundhog Day,
it's International Women's Day,
so, ladies, enjoy.
I love you, too.
I'm fine, just talking to a statue.
I'm on the blue bridge!
I tried calling you,
but you didn't answer.
I don't have a phone.
-Find anything?
-No, you're right. He's guilty.
I know, but we need to defend him.
Do you know why this bridge
is called Marie-Claire?
Yes, because she was charged
with having an abortion,
-and then...
-You don't know.
No, I don't know.
Well, I feel bad about this,
but it's settled. Here
-your case.
-What?
No, you have to try the case!
You're gonna be great!
Yes, hello, it's Bertrand.
We have a little problem.
Hello!
Hey, Charlie! You can't ditch this client.
I'm not. He has a great lawyer.
And thanks to you, he'll be convicted.
Because he's a rapist, let's not forget.
And don't forget, because those who forget
the past are condemned to relive it.
Who said that?
-The toilets?
-No! Winston Churchill!
OUT OF SERVICE
After you, esteemed colleague.
Seriously?
It's stuck! Let me out, I have a hearing!
Here, your seat...
-Who are you?
-Counsel Leroy.
I'm replacing your lawyer.
Court is in session, please be seated.
-We'll proceed with drawing jurors.
-That's the wrong side!
Everything's fine.
The opposing lawyer is very nice.
-Juror 15.
-And he's terrible.
Miss Axelle Schneider.
-Juror 12, Mr. Daniel Roskis.
-That's my daughter.
Juror 12, take a seat.
Juror 14, Mrs. Mauricette Sainte-Rose.
There isn't much to say,
ladies and gentlemen of the jury.
This man raped a woman.
He knows it, I know it.
You know it, and his lawyer...
His lawyer will argue the contrary,
but that won't change anything.
You have to convict him for his crime.
Because, yes, rape is a crime in France.
Since 1980, anyway.
Thanks to one woman's fighting spirit,
a lawyer named Gisèle Halimi.
And it's important not to forget
that before,
raping a woman was only a misdemeanor.
Before, this man would never
have seen the inside of a courtroom.
He wouldn't even have been worried.
The victim would have been blamed.
Of course, this is only this man's trial.
But if he's sitting here today at all
it's due to a long journey
toward freedom and respect for women.
A long road paved by the fights of men
and women who are watching you now.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
I'm sure that, wherever they are,
they're watching you.
The Joans, the Olympes,
the Nicolases, the Georges, the Maries,
the Simones, the Gisèles, and...
and the Françoises.
They're all watching you.
Awaiting your verdict.
Don't disappoint them.
Fear must finally switch sides.
It's your responsibility
to put this predator where he can
no longer hurt anyone.
Which is why we are asking
-for 15 years of prison...
-Thank you.
-...for this dangerous individual.
-Oh, no.
I left my notes in the the file!
-What?
-Huh?
The defense has the floor.
Nothing! Everything's fine.
This is a thong.
A thong similar to the one
the victim was wearing
on the night in question.
And this thong demonstrates the intentions
of this woman when she met with my client.
When a woman wears this type
of undergarment, it's for one reason.
Right, ladies?
To seduce,
please, entice,
excite, turn on... Call it what you will.
But what's undeniable is that this thong
is proof of consent.
-I can't allow my colleague say that!
-You had your time.
The defense has the floor.
Now, quiet, or I'll have you removed.
-So, this...
-No!
Women have been quiet for too long,
and I'm shocked to hear such language
today, and in this courtroom, in Bobigny!
Counselor!
And you, Your Honor,
you shouldn't let it stand.
This will have consequences,
and you know it!
Counselor Leroy!
As I was...
Our actions today
will make history tomorrow.
We can't let this go
in the wrong direction.
Last warning!
No, the direction of history,
Your Honor, is simple.
This woman wanted to have
relations with my client,
so she chose a red lace thong.
Is this thong evidence?
Counselor Leroy!
It was never officially recorded,
so it's not admissible!
And even if it was, I can tell you
that this isn't a red lace thong.
-So, what...
-It's a coral lace thong.
How do I know?
Well, because today I'm wearing...
a lace thong...
that is actually red.
And believe me, I have no intention
of sleeping with my colleague
or any of you.
In any case, gentlemen,
if we follow the brilliant idea
of this lawyer, well...
you can all rape me.
With no consequences.
Since I'm wearing a thong,
that means I consent to
any sexual relation.
Is that clear, or do I have to take it off
and wave it around like my colleague,
so you'll understand
that this isn't consent?
That's my daughter!
-Mom!
-Charlie! Honey!
Oh, Mom! I missed you so much.
Since last night, my dear?
You we wonderful! I'm so proud of you.
No, I'm proud of you!
Tonight, I'm coming over for dinner.
And I'll even stay and eat.
Well, I'll leave you to it
and go get dinner ready.
-I'm so clumsy.
-Hey!
You're fired!
And I'll make sure no firm ever hires you!
You can't fire me, I quit.
I'm starting my own firm.
-You have no clients.
-Yes, I do. Yours!
We'll see who prefers
an old nag to a young horse.
I'm quitting, too!
Why did you quit?
I have no idea.
Bertrand...
Charlie.
-Yes?
-I have to tell you something.
What?
-We've worked together for a while now.
-Yes.
-What you did today was truly remarkable.
-Thank you.
What are you doing?
Did you think this was a romantic comedy?
That this would end with "they got married
and had lots of children"?
No, wait...
Yeah, maybe I got carried away.
Yes, you did.
Let's go, I'll drop you off at the office,
collect my things,
and you can try to get your job back.
-Good idea.
-Bertrand...
I should move out here.
Here? You wouldn't last a week.
Come on. Do you think
there's a mugger on every corner here?
-I don't know!
-My car's been stolen!
Oh, no!
No, you parked
in a handicapped spot again.
Who do you think I am?
It wasn't a handicapped spot.
-It was a delivery spot.
-You still got towed.
Taxi!
We can always take the subway.
The subway!
He's crazy. No, I'm not taking the subway.
Taxi! I never take the subway.
You should. It's easier.
And more ecological.
Well, I don't care about ecology.
-I don't pollute.
-You don't care about ecology?
Really?
-Winston Churchill once said...
-No!
One isn't born a woman; one becomes one.
Simone de Beauvoir
The Second Sex
One isn't born a feminist;
one becomes one. Charlie
Damn it, I'm pregnant!
And it's Napoleon's!
A film inspired by true stories.
For real.
THIS IS NOT A YES
NO MATTER HOW NAKED YOU ARE
ASK FOR CONSENT
# This is not consent
Article 2: All women wishing
to dress as a man
must present themselves to police
headquarters to obtain authorization.
Article 3:
This authorization will only be given
with the certificate
of a medical officer's legal signature,
and furthermore, with confirmation
from the mayors or police commissioners
with the surname, name, profession
and address of the petitioner.
Article 4:
All women found cross-dressing
who do not act in accordance
with the preceding articles
shall be arrested and sent
to police headquarters.
This Law was repealed in 2013.
to Pierre and Colette
Translated by: Stephen Williams