What? Oh, come on!
Thank you.
Oh, shit! Oh, fuck!
Fucking Alaska.
Get down! On your knees now!
Get down!
Okay. okay.
Okay. Yep. Oh, shit!
Oh, come on, Princess.
I'm cooperating.
I'm cooperating, okay?
Clear!
Gotcha.
Hey there, Winston.
How you been?
What?
I'm Madolyn Harris,
US Marshal.
You're a hard man
to track down.
A deal! I want to make a deal.
Let's make a deal.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's chicken noodle.
Throw him on the bed.
Oh, not the bedspread.
Not the bedspread.
It's crusty.
It's so... crusty.
Winston, you want
to make a deal?
Testify against Moretti.
Okay.
But I want full immunity
and lots...
and lots of protection.
All right.
Let me call it up the chain.
Okay.
It's Harris.
Yup. Clean capture.
Listen, he wants
to make a deal.
Uh-huh.
Copy that. Keep me posted.
What'd they say?
Get comfy. This could take
a couple of days.
Hey, uh, I don't want
to be that guy, but...
I have to use the facilities.
Oh, come on,
don't look at me like that.
These guys literally scared
the shit out of me.
What do you expect?
Can I have some privacy?
You might run.
Okay.
But if you don't
take off these cuffs,
you're the one that's gonna
have to do the paperwork.
Hey, Bob, Jeff.
Yes, ma'am.
I have a job for you.
* I wanna know who *
* Who was that awhile ago *
* You see, when I came in *
* Somebody ran
out of my back door *
* Had his shoes
in his pocket *
* Overcoat in his hand *
* Tell me, baby *
* Who was that man *
* I wanna know who *
* Who was that awhile ago*
Get in.
What the hell is this?
The charter, Winston. Get in.
Okay.
It's just you say,
"We chartered
a private plane,"
I'm thinking Gulfstream,
thinking Learjet,
you know, Jay-Z level shit.
Thought we'd be popping
bottles full of bubbly.
Not fucking Dramamine.
That's a jet.
I never said jet.
I said we got a private plane,
and that's what this is.
- No.
- Arms.
This isn't a plane.
This is a kite with seatbelts.
Honestly, I'd rather be
on Spirit Airlines.
Well, Winston, what do you
want me to say?
Next time, hide out in Miami,
maybe you get a jet.
You go full Unabomber on me,
drag me all the way
out to snow-blow Alaska,
our options get
a little more limited.
Doubt you can even
land a jet out here.
Yeah, well, it's a little hard
to go off the grid in Miami.
Yeah, and a lot of good
that did you.
You guys go ahead.
I'll be there in a second.
- Van Sant.
- It's Madolyn.
I was starting
to get worried.
Don't be.
We're just about good to go.
Is he cooperating?
- If I say no, can I tase him?
- Sure.
I'm right here.
I can hear you.
Three days in Motel Sucks.
He hasn't shut up once.
Oh, come on.
You loved every minute of it.
Don't tell me you miss being
behind a desk.
No. No. Seriously, Caroline.
Thank you for putting me
in the field again.
I know you have pushback.
Don't thank me yet.
Judge Martin recused himself.
I'll give you three guesses
who's on deck.
Stewardess, is there
a meal on this flight
or is it like just snacks?
Shut up, Winston.
Yeah, okay. Just snacks. Okay.
- You there?
- Uh, yeah. Replace with who?
- Judge hard-ass himself.
- Falco?
Yeah, I know.
And true to form,
he's not letting us
push the trial date again.
- You're kidding.
- Look, it's gonna be fine.
The team's standing by
to meet you in Anchorage.
Okay.
We'll be there in about...
We should be there
in about 90 minutes or so.
- Where'd he go?
- Good.
Moretti's lawyers are trying
to run out the clock on us,
but I've done the math.
We could still make New York
by morning, okay?
- Just get going.
- Yeah.
All right.
Call me from Anchorage.
By the book, okay?
Don't embarrass us.
- I gotta run.
So, any inflight entertainment
or do you know party tricks?
Deputy Harris? Daryl Booth.
Hope you like flying.
Beautiful day for it.
I gotta say, I normally
don't let my passengers
board before me.
It's for your own safety.
Ooh! No kidding?
What you packing there,
a Glock or...
We're in a bit
of a rush, Mr. Booth.
Yes, ma'am.
You sure you don't wanna ride
in the back there with him?
Absolutely not.
Yeah, it's just tough with
all the sexual tension.
I only meant, uh...
shouldn't somebody
be watching him?
Oh, he's restrained,
Mr. Booth.
He's not going anywhere.
Trust me.
Okay. Hey, you're the boss.
I just...
I never flew
a fugitive before.
Witness.
- What?
- Shut up, Winston.
I'm a cooperating
government witness,
- not a fugitive.
- Winston.
No, I'm just saying,
technically, we're all
on the same side.
Not another word.
All right, well,
we're looking at moderate
clouds and light wind.
And I'd appreciate if you
didn't address the prisoner.
Yes, ma'am.
Sorry, I just...
I never flew
a US Marshal before, neither.
I did fly
Marshall Faulk once, though.
That was real cool.
All right. Anchorage Center,
November 208,
uniform, uniform.
Ready for departure on
Crooked Creek, runway 34.
Roger that. November 208,
uniform, uniform.
Clear for takeoff, runway 34.
- Ready to go?
- Yup.
Whee...
Is it always this bumpy?
* How does it feel *
* To treat me like you do *
* When you've laid
your hands upon me *
You're not
digging the music?
Yeah, I know. But up here,
you got to have some tunes
to drown out the wind
and the wolves.
See? She gets it.
It's always turbulent up here.
It should even out
once we hit about 3,000 feet.
If you feel sick, don't worry.
You know,
the number of passengers
have left their lunch up here?
-Hello?
- I could open a snack bar.
Hello? Hello!
Can you guys even hear me?
What if I need to take a piss?
You a smoker?
- No, I quit.
- I'll take one.
Yeah, it ain't the same, huh?
Your neck okay?
- You got a scratch there.
- Oh.
Maintenance.
Occupational hazard.
Come on. Oh, come on.
- Why is he in chains?
- Come on!
He said he was a witness.
Why is he all chained up?
Because he's a flight risk.
I thought he said you two
were on the same side.
He's a liar.
What'd he do?
Okay. Forget I asked.
You gotta understand
my usual haul
is a drunken fishing party
or a bunch of suits trying
to experience true nature.
Golly gee,
I'm just a local yokel pilot.
I sure never seen a girl
as purdy as you
from the big city.
You been flying long?
Yeah, my dad
is a crop duster in Texas.
I got DDT in my blood.
Well, thank you.
I'm very uptight, controlling.
I'd love to be
in a relationship with you
so I could
completely control...
Well, that would work
just fine for me.
If we were cousins,
we'd already be married.
I came up here
doing summer charters
maybe 15 years ago.
Never left.
I'm rambling. Sorry.
My ex always said
I talk too much. I'm sorry.
Beautiful, ain't it?
That, it is.
Yeah,
you getting used to it.
Oh, hell.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, it's fine.
Nothing to worry about.
This piece of crap
keeps shorting out on me.
There's no GPS?
It's no big deal, really.
I mean,
it happens twice a week.
It's not serious.
I fly this route all the time.
75 minutes from now,
we'll be on the ground,
and you and your friend
or witness,
be on your way to Seattle,
I promise.
You don't think
we should turn back?
No, heck no.
I mean, it's your call.
I mean, I get paid either way.
There's some weather
moving in from the north.
We head back now,
it's probably gonna ground us
for a few hours.
75 minutes.
I know the way.
I'm gonna get you there.
How long you been
with the Marshals?
Uh, seven, almost eight years.
- You like it?
- It has its moments.
Whoa! What the shit was that?
We're all good.
- Sorry.
- Oh, it's okay.
Bird strike is all.
Not a big deal.
Unless you the bird.
Yeah. I better
get a little higher
in case there's more.
Well, can't go too high
or I'll pass out.
- You good?
- Is the plane...
Ah, the plane's fine.
I'm gonna have
to spend my evening
scrubbing blood off of it,
but could have been worse.
Could have been a prop chop.
I'd be picking feathers
out of the intakes all week.
Look at her. Ain't she great?
Dancing for
your entertainment.
Oh, come on now.
She's resilient.
Yeah, I know.
Look at me with them
ten dollar words, right?
Don't tell nobody.
But the fact is,
she just keeps dancing
through all the bumps
and turns and turbulence.
Nothing fazes her.
Gotta admire a gal like that.
Oh, shit.
Hey. Hey! Hey!
Can you hear me?
Oh, Christ. Uh...
Uh...
Oh, what do I do? Um...
- Hey!
- What was that?
- I... I need to talk to you.
- What?
Uh, I...
I dropped something...
Uh, on the floor by my...
by my foot.
- You'll deal.
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
I... I also don't feel well.
I don't care, Winston.
Suck it up.
No, it's like I feel
really bad.
Like I got a bad feeling.
I think we should turn around.
Just take some
deep breaths, Winston.
You'll be fine.
- What's wrong with him?
- Says he feels sick.
Oh, shit.
Here.
Try to keep it in the bag.
Okay.
What'd I tell you?
One on every flight.
What's our ETA?
About an hour-ish. Soon.
When are we gonna see
civilization again?
Oof. Around these parts?
Not until final approach.
How'd you know about Seattle?
- What?
- Earlier.
You said you'd have us
on our way to Seattle
before we knew it.
How'd you know
that's where we're headed?
Well, shit.
Where else can you go?
You ain't no Alaskan.
I can tell you that.
Ain't no way you're staying
in Anchorage. No offense.
In fact, if I had to guess,
I'd say you got that
Yankee blood.
Not much of an accent, but...
you remind me of this gal
I used to fiddle with.
Can I radio ATC on these?
I need to check in.
- Already?
- Protocol.
Yeah. All right. Sure.
Anchorage Center,
November 208,
uniform, uniform.
Come in.
Come in, Anchorage Center.
This is November 208,
uniform, uniform. Over.
- Anchorage Center?
- Nothing?
Must be the, uh, mountains
blocking the signal.
Should be fine
in another few minutes.
Oh, fuck.
Kinda spooky, huh?
Local pilots call this
Eskimo soup.
The flying community up here
must be a pretty small group.
Mm.
You must know the pilot
who flew me up here last week.
Uh, Jani... Janikowski?
Janikowski?
Oh, sure. Great guy.
Man, one time up in Nome,
he and I got our hands on
some nitrous
and a welding torch.
Well, like I said, great guy.
Yeah. Seemed like it.
Except she's a woman.
Hmm. Oh, you mean his sister.
And believe me,
I could tell you
some stories about her, too.
Well, you're not really
buying that, now are you?
I knew you were gonna be fun.
No, no, no, no, no!
Don't shoot him! We need him!
Oh, shit!
Yeah. Yeah.
He's got a knife!
Easy now.
I don't wanna kill ya.
A cold body isn't any fun.
What the...
I love it when
they play hard to get.
Yeah. You wanna play rough?
Ruff, ruff.
Oh, yeah.
You're gonna be a party, huh?
Yeah.
Oh, shit! Oh, fuck!
Oh, shit! Oh, fuck! Oh, shit!
Hey, shut the fuck up!
Mr. Moretti is very
disappointed in you, Winston,
and he wants you dead.
I haven't told them anything.
I didn't say one word.
I swear to God.
I know. Winston, stop. Stop.
Stop. I know.
I know, man.
You haven't said a word.
- I didn't say anything.
- Yeah. And now you never will.
Uh... I can pay you.
Come on, brother.
Have a little self-respect,
will you?
I'm serious.
A million dollars in crypto.
Completely untraceable.
You gotta let me go.
Do I look like the kind of guy
who deals in fucking crypto?
Fine. Then, uh, cash.
Whatever.
Hell, what does it matter?
We're talking about
a million dollars here.
Oh, yeah? You got all that
just squirreled away, huh?
I was Moretti's accountant,
so, yeah, I skimmed.
A million dollars?
You got some fucking balls.
Do you have any idea
how much money
I hid for that man?
'Cause he sure doesn't.
You wouldn't believe
how many people got a taste.
This one guy
in Sankaty, Massachusetts
got $25,000 a month,
for years.
All you have to do
is just let me walk away.
- That's it, huh?
- That's it.
Look,
what was your plan?
You were gonna fly us
to some abandoned airstrip
and leave us for the wolves?
No. Bears more likely.
This time of year.
And only after
we've had our fun.
You get the picture?
Okay. But here's the thing.
Who's gonna know? Right?
I mean,
I will disappear forever.
You get to say
you did your job,
plus you get a million
extra bucks in your pocket.
It's a win-win.
Wow.
And her?
What about her?
Look at her.
If you walk away,
she's still gonna die.
And then she's gonna die
because of you.
Oh, you have it in you, huh?
To cut her loose?
Just like that?
Oh, you didn't need those,
did you?
Not anymore.
You still look like a pussy.
You know what the difference
between me and you is, Twig?
I don't know.
A million dollars?
Ah!
Fuck! Oh, my God!
Have some fucking decorum,
you hear me?
I'm trying to have
a nice time.
Don't you dare
fucking disrupt that.
I hear you. I hear you.
I do this for fun.
I do this for free.
Titty twister. You like that?
- We're gonna have fun.
- Mm-hmm. Okay.
Hey.
* How does it feel *
Get up. You gotta wake up.
* To treat me like you do *
If you hear me right now,
you gotta wake up right now.
* When you've laid
your hands upon me*
* And you... *
- What the...
- You okay?
Winston.
There's no air.
- There's no air in here.
- Yes, there is.
You gotta let me out of this.
You gotta let me out.
- I can't do that, Winston.
- But there's no air...
- in here.
- Yes, there is.
It is way worse
getting raped by a bald guy!
- No one's raping you.
- Oh, you wanna bet?
Did you see
where the knife went?
Oh, God!
Oh, my God!
This is how it ends?
This is how it ends for me?
We're all gonna die!
Oh, God, please!
Please, I'll be good.
I'll be a priest and shit.
Get him off!
Get him off of you.
Come on, you can do it!
Get up!
Turn around.
You gotta pull on the things!
Pull on the... Pull up!
Oh my... Ah!
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Winston.
Are you okay?
Winston!
No! I'm not okay.
I pissed myself.
What are we supposed to do?
Just let me think
for a second.
- What are you looking for?
- The knife.
I need to get these off.
- Hey!
- What?
The first aid kit.
Fuck.
Come on. I can help.
Just unlock me.
- Not a chance.
- Really?
What do you think
I'm gonna do?
Attack the pilot?
Fine.
- Easy.
- You know what?
You got trust issues, lady.
I got it. I got it.
Thank you.
Okay. That wasn't
so hard, was it?
We need to get him into
the back before he wakes up.
Oh, fuck that. Shoot him.
He was gonna
fly into the wilderness
and murder the shit out of us.
Nobody's killing anybody.
Besides, we might need him.
For what?
You know how to fly a plane?
Oh, he's as sure as shit
not gonna tell us
how to do it.
Oh, come on.
Son of a bitch.
Need some help?
Damn it.
Thank you.
Now, do my cuffs.
You can still move in those.
- Fuck.
- Come on.
All right.
No sudden movements.
Me? It's not my fault
we're in this position.
Just pull.
Come on. Yeah.
Hold on.
Come on.
What are you doing down there?
Giving this guy a pedicure?
Fuck.
Come on. Come on.
God, I knew something
was off about this guy
from the minute
he got in here,
with those redneck platitudes
and that bullshit
Larry the Cable Guy accent.
Winston, I swear to God,
if you don't shut up...
- What?
- Nothing.
Bullshit nothing. Show me.
We need to move him.
Not until you show me.
Fine.
Oh. I guess someone
did his homework.
Oh, they got pictures of you.
Oh, they got a picture of me.
Wait. Wait a second.
This is my mom's house.
- Winston.
- Oh, my God. They could...
They could hurt her.
They could kill her.
We gotta warn her.
We gotta call her
and warn her.
Winston. Winston. Focus.
We can't solve anything
until we get help.
And we can't get help
until we move him
into the back, okay?
- Okay.
Okay. Okay. Sit him up.
Yeah.
- Come on. Really?
- For him.
Oh!
Cuff his hands
to that grab handle there.
Son of a bitch.
See how much
you like being cuffed up.
It's a fair fight, huh?
Okay. So...
- Oh, crap.
- Listen.
Oh, my God. We're so screwed.
Oh, my God. We are so screwed.
- Calm down.
- Oh, my God.
Calm down?
You're telling me
to calm down?
My mom has never
hurt a soul in her life.
She's gonna die
and it's gonna be my fault.
Do you get that?
Do you get how that must feel?
Listen. Listen to me!
We're gonna
figure this out, okay?
Your mom is still alive.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do. I do know that.
I know Moretti has no leverage
over you if she's dead, right?
- Yeah, I guess.
- So I know she's still alive.
I also know that
you can't change the past.
All we can do is choose
how to respond
in this moment, okay?
So I'm gonna get on the radio
and we're gonna get help.
For us. For your mom.
And then we're gonna
get you to New York
so you can testify
and put Moretti away for good.
But...
Where the hell are we?
At least,
let me sit up there with you.
Come on, I can help.
You really want to help?
How did you know about Daryl?
Just trying to keep us alive.
- Come on.
- Thank you.
You piss yourself again,
I'm sending you back.
That's all right. I'm empty.
Hello. Is anyone receiving me?
Can anyone hear me?
Mayday. Mayday. Mayday.
They're gonna send someone
to find us, right?
I mean, when we don't show up?
Oh, we're showing up.
Oh, yeah, no,
we're showing up. For sure.
But, uh, if we don't,
they know our route, right?
Our route? There's no way
he was taking us to Anchorage.
Yeah, you know,
I'm really starting
to question his honesty.
But look,
there's gotta be some way
they could locate us, right?
Like an emergency signal
or like a black box
or something?
Winston, the radio, the GPS,
he didn't want us to be found.
Hello. Can anybody read me?
- We're gonna crash.
- Mayday. Mayday.
Quiet. No we're not.
Can anybody hear me?
I'm on a plane
and I need help.
Help. Help.
Say again?
Yes. Hello. Can you hear me?
I can hear you.
Yeah, I read you. Say again.
Help. I need help.
This is an aviation frequency.
Yes, I know. I'm on a plane.
You don't sound like a pilot.
No, I'm... I'm not.
My pilot, he...
- Still there? Hello?
- He's in...
He's incapacitated.
Unconscious.
I'm flying his plane
and I don't know
what I'm doing.
- All right, I get it.
- Hello?
Frank put you up to this,
didn't he?
You're kidding, right?
What? No, I'm not kidding.
Please give me some help.
Oh. Oh. Oh, shit.
I'm sorry, okay.
Okay. First thing's first.
Um, did you engage your pilot?
What the fuck is he saying?
Yes. Yes, it's on.
Okay, that'll maintain your
heading and keep you level.
Just keep your hands off
the yokes for now.
What's your altitude?
Can you see?
It should be a big gauge
right in front.
Can you hear me?
Three. 3000 feet.
Okay, you're a little low,
but we're not going
to worry about that yet.
What's your location?
Uh, somewhere between
Bethel and Anchorage.
I don't know.
All I see is mountains.
I think we may have drifted
pretty far off course here.
Okay, well, I can't be too far
away if I can... you.
Can you see any landmarks?
You're breaking up a little.
Can you say again?
I said...
- Damn it, come on. Hello?
- Hello...
Hello? Hello?
- Hello? Can anybody hear me?
- He'll call it in, right?
Wait, what did you say?
He's got to call in
the situation, right,
the pilot guy?
He's got to call it in.
What?
Madolyn.
Where'd you leave your brain?
- Out here?
- It's a satellite phone.
Doesn't use cell towers.
Come on. Come on.
-Madolyn?
- Caroline.
Oh, God! Oh, thank God.
Listen.
You can't be
in Anchorage already.
No, no, no.
We're still in the air.
We've been compromised.
I can barely hear you, Mads.
Hello? Hello?
Hang on.
Hey, Chet, drop the muffin,
please, and get over here.
The rest of you
shut the fuck up.
We've been compromised.
The pilot wasn't
who he says he was.
- He's one of Moretti's.
- You think?
Wait, what?
I caught him in a lie
and he tried to knife me.
- Are... Are you hurt?
- I'm fine.
He's unconscious
and restrained in the back.
- And the witness?
- Winston, he's fine.
Yeah, never been better.
Thanks.
Mads, question.
Who's flying the plane?
- I am.
- You?
I'm flying this plane and I
don't know what I'm doing.
Okay. Okay.
Well, we just need
to stay calm.
I'm calm.
All right, so you are
flying the plane
and just so I understand it.
- How exactly?
- It's on autopilot.
We're sort of cruising
in a straight line.
I think he sabotaged
the navigation.
Sims, see if we can
track her on radar.
- Yes, ma'am.
- I need someone to help me
- fly this thing.
- Yup, we're gonna find
your pilot who's gonna walk
you through it. Sit tight.
Smith, get me a fucking pilot.
Okay, I'll wait for his call.
- Hey, hey, hey. My mom.
- Oh, yes, yes.
You need to send some officers
over to Winston's
mother's house, okay?
She may be in danger.
Okay, all right.
Don't worry. We're on it.
- I will call you back.
- Okay.
- So?
- Finding us a pilot.
Hey!
Y'all need a pilot?
Hot damn!
That taser's no joke.
We like our pilots crispy.
Tell me how to fly this thing.
Um, no.
I think I bit my tongue.
Although I was dreaming
that you were nibbling
on my nipple, Twiggy.
Was that you?
Or was that
just my imagination?
Who told you we were
moving Winston today?
I'll tell you what.
Why don't you come on
back here with me,
and I'll tell you
all about it.
We could play
hide-the-hot dog.
Easy now.
You're awful close
with that thing.
- Makes it hard to miss.
- Shoot him now.
- Yeah.
- Do it.
Also makes it more than likely
that that bullet's gonna
pass clear through me
and into the wall behind me.
Where the fuel line
and the fuel tank is.
You could put a hole in it.
Or it could ricochet around
right into
one of you fuckheads.
Yeah.
Now, I know
you ain't much for planes.
But surely you know
a thing or two
about how bullets work,
don't you?
Yeah.
Quite the pickle, ain't it?
Okay. I'll make you
a deal, chuckles.
You tell me
how to fly this thing,
I'll let you
go to prison in peace.
Pass. Option B?
I'll put it out there
that you turned on Moretti.
And you can go to prison
looking over your shoulder
for the rest of what'll be
a very short life.
Clearly you're mistaking me
for somebody
who actually
gives a fuck about that.
I've spent every
waking day in prison
looking over my shoulder.
You get it, Twig?
- You will.
- Yeah, no, I got it.
Come on, you really
wanna die out here?
Honey, you gotta
land the plane first.
At least, tell me
your real name.
You know what's the last thing
to go through your head
before crash landing?
Your ass.
- Oh, my God, he doesn't care.
- Or maybe his.
He doesn't care
whether he lives or dies.
- I care, Twiggy.
- He doesn't care at all.
This is Harris.
- I care about you.
-Hey there,
- Deputy Harris
-We're gonna die.
My name's Hassan.
He doesn't care
if he lives or dies.
I am a pilot with air traffic
control in Anchorage.
We're all gonna die with him
in this flying coffin!
Will you shut up?
I could shut up, yes,
but it will make it
harder to help.
No, no, no.
No, I didn't mean you. I...
Hassan.
Or if you like, Hassan.
And it's all good, Deputy.
Sounds like things
are a little tense up there.
Yeah, yeah,
you could say that.
Well, not to worry.
We're in this together now.
And we're going
to get you sorted out.
You got an airspeed
and altitude for me?
I... Yeah. 3,000 feet.
And airspeed is...
It should be just to the left.
With the green, yellow,
and red range on it.
Got it. Airspeed is at 120.
120 at 3,000. Roger.
And what are you
doing after this?
Excuse me?
Myself, I haven't
eaten all day.
You want to have
dinner with me?
Yeah, if you insist.
I mean, we should probably
focus on landing first.
You're paying, though.
Seems only fair
since you asked me.
Of course. Fair's fair.
That is a verbal commitment,
and I'm going
to hold you to it.
This day's looking up already.
At least for me.
Okay, so when you're ready,
you're just going to ease
that yoke to the left.
Nice and gentle.
Okay.
- We're turning.
- Stellar.
Now, I know you're anxious
to meet me and all,
but just keep an eye
on our altitude.
Make sure
you're holding steady.
Now, would you like me
to make the reservation?
You seem kind of busy.
I got this.
Now, pull back
on the yoke a little.
Okay.
- We're good.
- I have no doubt.
Now, there should be
a heading indicator,
first thing above the yoke,
looks just like a compass.
I see it.
Okay, when you hit southeast,
just straighten out the plane.
- How are you doing?
- Okay.
Straightening.
- Done.
- Stupendous.
Now, do me a favor and engage
that autopilot switch again.
- Okay.
- Fantabulous.
And you are good to go.
Keep an eye out
for the coastline.
When you hit it,
we'll bank left
and follow it south
towards Anchorage.
See that?
Practically home already.
- Thank you.
- No thanks necessary.
Believe me, the drinks
you'll be buying later
will be more than enough.
- Is that right?
- Oh, yeah.
I like to drink a lot.
Noted.
I'm going to hop off now
to save your battery,
but call this number
when you spot
the coastline, okay?
Or if you just miss
the sound of my voice.
- I'll be counting the moments.
-
You can call me
when you need me.
I'll be right here.
Just hanging around.
* How does it feel *
* To treat me like you do *
* You lay your hands upon me *
* Tell me who you are *
What were you waiting for?
Huh?
Why didn't you just
kill us and toss us out?
Fly all by my lonesome?
It ain't every day you get
a captive audience, you know.
Don't give me that.
I know people, Twig. And you?
Yeah, you like to watch.
Hey.
Hey!
If it's any consolation,
she's gonna watch, too.
It's going to be
a real picnic.
Winnie.
Why don't you
come on back here?
Why don't we start over, huh?
Who you want to be?
You want to be
the husband or the wife? Huh?
How come you ain't sweet,
like your mommy?
Your mommy's nice and sweet.
She's real sweet.
Just like mine.
She loved me,
but she just wouldn't shut up.
Come here, Winnie.
I wanna show you something.
You're gonna like it.
Maybe not at first.
But they always
end up liking it.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck!
Hey, Winnie.
After I kill you,
I'm gonna take the Polaroids
to show your mama.
Jesus, how does this asshole
know my mom's address?
You think Moretti had someone
in the Marshal's office?
I told that address
to the US Attorney
when we were talking about
witness protection. That's it.
I'm serious. I was careful.
No one knows that address.
Caroline.
Okay, so we're coordinating
with the military
to get search and rescue up.
It shouldn't be long now.
Now, I'm told you're a little
small and low for radar,
particularly with
all the mountains,
so I'm trying to scramble
some fighter jets,
get some extra eyeballs
out there.
Okay, we're headed
for the coast,
so maybe have them
sweep that first.
Yeah... Um, look,
there's something else.
Anchorage PD just found
what's left of Daryl Booth
in his apartment.
No eyes, no teeth, no fingers.
It sounds like someone really
took their time with him.
Someone talked.
Who knew about this op?
Uh, I mean, we had to notify
local law enforcement,
file a plan with the FAA,
alert the TSA, and...
They knew we were
moving someone,
but they didn't
know who, right?
I mean, who actually
knew about Winston?
Uh, well, the US Attorney,
the Director, obviously,
- the AG, the Deputy AG.
- And you.
Well, yes, of course,
but there's no telling
who else may have
accessed that information.
Did you see that?
What the hell is that?
I need to call you back.
We're not gonna make that.
You gotta pull up.
- Oh, my God.
- Nah, nah, you're fine.
You got plenty of room left.
Pull up.
- Come on. Come on. Come on.
- Pull up. Pull up.
- You gotta pull up!
- I am. I am!
- I'm telling you, it's fine.
- Come on, damn it!
- Shit. The autopilot!
- Come on!
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Come on. Come on.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Shit!
Yee-haw!
How fun was that, huh?
What a squeaker!
I don't know about you,
but I just made
a Jackson Pollock in my pants.
Hey, Winnie.
Did you make a poop?
Seriously, guys.
It's like the Museum of
Modern Art back here.
Hey, Madolyn.
I'm sure glad
you didn't kill Winston
while he was in your custody.
Oh, I'd hate for you to have
to go through that shit again.
- What is he talking about?
- Just ignore him.
Hey! What dumb fuck
put you back
in the saddle again, huh?
Seriously, what does he mean?
It means, Twig,
that I ain't the one
you should be worried about.
He doesn't know
what he's talking about.
Hey, Twiggy, I know
she killed her last prisoner.
Oh. Oh, no.
- What?
- Oh, shit. Oh, hell.
Was that supposed
to be a secret?
Oh, darling,
what's the matter?
No more foreplay?
How do you know that?
Whoa.
Well, it's true, ain't it?
- Whoa.
- Answer me!
Feels good
to let it out, right?
I get it.
I've been there too, baby.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
Of course I do.
Oh, you could tell yourself
you're different.
We're the same, you and me.
Fuck you.
We'll get there.
Oh, hell, come on.
I haven't even used
my safe word yet.
You know, it's "burned alive."
You still see her face? Huh?
When you close
your eyes, you do, huh?
Oh, I bet you still hear
her scream, don't you?
Her shrieks of pain.
Yeah.
Oh, I miss
these little moments.
Don't stop. Come on,
you're giving me a hard on.
I hope Moretti
does come for you.
Okay. When you're ready.
Two years ago,
we caught up with this
young woman, Maria.
She'd been
on the run for weeks,
and the DA convinced her
to turn against her boyfriend,
who was a cartel boss.
So we were holed up
in a shitty motel
until she could testify.
We'd been in the room
for three straight days,
and she wanted to take
a shower, unsupervised.
A moment of privacy.
It was against protocol,
but I let her.
So I shackled her to the tub
and stepped outside.
A sicario smashed
a Molotov cocktail
through the window.
I turned back and...
heat and smoke
and flames and...
And I ran.
But Maria,
with the shackles, she...
she...
And they put you on a desk.
They said they didn't trust me
in the field again.
Until now, with me.
Mads,
how you doing up there?
Caroline, the leak isn't from
the attorney's office
or the FBI.
It's from us, Caroline.
It's the Marshals.
All right.
How did you get to that?
Our pilot friend
knows my work history.
My personal work history.
Wait, hang on, Mads.
Everyone out.
- I need the room.
-Yes, ma'am.
Maybe we need to bring
the director in on this.
Yes, absolutely.
As soon as we get you down.
Well, how about now?
Look, the situation
is fluid at best.
We need to get you
safely on the ground
and into the hands of my team.
Your team?
Yes. You could trust them.
I vetted them myself.
You did, huh?
- What does Coleridge think?
- Why? This is my operation.
- You don't trust the director?
- Hey, I did not say that.
I'm saying that if the leak
is in our office,
as you say it is,
then we need to be careful.
We can't be sure who to trust.
You're right.
So let me get into this, okay?
You focus on getting
that plane down safely.
Mads, okay?
Yeah. I gotta go.
Hassan's calling.
Hey. How's it going up there?
Not great, huh?
You wanna talk about it,
let me know.
You can come back
and pay me another visit.
US Marshal's office.
This is Deputy Harris.
I need you to put me
through to the director.
I'm sorry. I'm afraid I can't
get a hold of him right now.
Tell him it's Deputy
Madolyn Harris calling
and that it's an emergency.
He'll know.
Director Coleridge
isn't here today, ma'am.
If you'd like,
I can put you through
to your supervisory deputy
or transfer you
to another department.
No, no, no. Listen to me.
Janine, I need
to talk to him right now.
I'm sorry, but he's...
People will die if you
don't get him on the line.
Oh, shit.
- Uh, let me see what I can do.
- Thank you.
Hey, Winston.
Talk to your mother lately?
- Ignore him.
- She's a sweet lady.
I hope she put
her dentures back in.
Janine.
Yes, ma'am. I've managed
to get a hold of
Director Coleridge.
I'm going to patch you through
to his beach house, okay?
- Yes, please. Thank you.
- One moment.
- Coleridge here.
- Sir, this is Harris.
I've been briefed, Deputy.
Where's Van Sant?
- Uh, sir, there's a leak.
- What? what?
Moretti has a mole
in the Marshal's office.
I could prove it.
And I believe that
it's Deputy Van Sant, sir.
Hello?
She went out
on a limb for you, Harris.
I... I know. I know, sir.
I'm aware of that. I...
I believe that
given my prior history,
she expected me to fail again.
Van Sant.
She's in New York, right?
That is correct.
Okay. Let me make some calls.
She has a team waiting for us.
She needs to be
contained and...
I understand, Deputy.
Believe me.
I'll shut her down.
From now on,
just call me directly
at my house in Sankaty.
Deputy?
I will. Thank you, sir.
The coast. You see it?
I see the coast.
Oh, my God.
Come on.
Hassan, we see the coast.
- Ooh! Fantabulous!
- The Coast. We saw the coast.
Ha-ha! You're making my day
over here.
Well, we aim to please.
Okay, so you're going
to bank left nice and easy,
and then just follow
that coastline to east.
Okay.
Banking.
Stupendous. Now be honest.
Is that landscape
not just stunningly beautiful?
Also, how's your fuel?
Uh, fuel's at 25 gallons.
And, yeah,
it's something all right.
- Hassan?
- Yeah, sorry. I...
Did you say 25 gallons
on both tanks?
Is that a problem?
No, no, no. Not a problem.
Just a data point.
Trust me.
This is good news, Deputy.
We're going to have you
on the ground in no time.
Now turn that autopilot on
and stay the course.
Okay, keep me posted.
Absolutely.
I'm here if you need.
What?
- Fuck.
- What?
Fuck!
That payoff
you told Daryl about.
Oh, you heard that?
I was bluffing.
I swear to God,
I would never sell you out.
- It's not in me to be able
- No, no, no, Winston, Winston.
You said that you were
paying some guy
25 grand a month.
Where did you say
it was going?
Sankaty.
Are you sure?
I thought those payoffs
were untraceable.
Well, the accounts are,
sure, but...
A couple years ago,
I was down in Florida
when Hurricane Michael hit,
so the payments
were a few days late.
It was no big deal,
except for this
one greedy idiot
sent me a transfer request
from an IP address
in Sankaty, Massachusetts.
- Why?
- Holy shit.
Come on. Come on.
Hey, Mad, what's up?
It's Coleridge. He's the leak.
What?
You gotta get out
of the office right now.
- Wait, slow down. Slow down.
- There's no time.
- Tell me about Coleridge.
- Winston handled his payoffs.
Oh, shit.
Listen to me. I called him.
Okay, and?
I'm sorry.
I should have trusted you.
Okay. What did you tell him?
That there's a leak.
That I thought...
-  Just say it.
- That I thought it was you.
Thought it was me. Fuck.
I'm sorry. Look, you've gotta
get out of there.
He's coming for you.
Okay. All right.
Just focus on landing
that plane safely, okay?
- I will handle this.
- Yeah.
And Madolyn,
you know I love you.
- But thanks a lot, bitch.
- Okay.
Fuck!
Okay, what is that?
Do you see that?
- What is that?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, I see it.
Hassan.
All ears, Deputy.
How can I help?
Uh, we see something.
It's like...
Uh... It's a... Like a boat.
- A fishing boat.
- A big ship.
- A shipwreck.
Oh, shiver me timbers.
We can work with that.
Can you see a name on it?
You gotta get me closer.
Okay, we're too high.
All right, if you
wanted to descend,
keep your pitch
at five degrees or less.
And make sure you stay
above 1,000 feet, okay?
Okay.
Uh, just a little bit closer.
Can you see a name?
Okay, okay, it says...
Fat Dancer?
- The Fat Dancer.
- The Fat...
The Fat Dancer?
That doesn't make any sense.
He took my glasses.
I don't know.
The Fat Dancer?
Odd name for a boat.
- The Fair Dancer.
- The Fair Dancer, yeah.
- That makes a lot more sense.
- The Fair Dancer.
The Fair Dancer.
Got it, okay, stand by.
We're running it past
the Coast Guard now.
Okay.
You know, I'm something
of a fair dancer myself.
I have no doubt.
Well, let's boogie.
Because the Coast Guard
ID'd the wreck.
We've got a pretty good fix
on your location.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
- They see us.
- Whoo!
We are grooving now.
Thank God.
It's a fucking
roller coaster ride.
Okay. I guess
we gotta land at some point.
Like a feather.
Now, if you'd be so kind
as to turn left
to heading 120,
that should
put you into Anchorage
in about 30 minutes.
- Okay, copy.
- Here we come.
- Turning 120.
Stellar. Hold that heading.
I'll call back
in 10 minutes or so,
and we can talk landings.
And the finer points of
tearing up the dance floor.
I can't wait. Thank you.
We're gonna get out of this.
We're gonna get out of it!
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
Twig! Pay attention.
This is the good part.
You ever see a face
turn this color before? Huh?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's for later.
Oh, you know what?
Let me get that for you.
Is that better? Oh, yeah.
I think I caught a rib there.
Maybe the spleen, too.
Don't worry. You don't
need a spleen to live.
Hey, you want to know
my name, huh?
Come on.
I'll give you three guesses.
Nope. No. That's not a name.
Come on. Guess again.
Guess again.
Nope. That's not a name.
I'm only gonna give you
one more try.
Shit!
Shit! Fucking bitch!
No one cares
what your fucking name is.
All right.
All right, let me see.
- Come on. Let me see.
- Okay.
Let me see. Come on. Come on.
Okay.
- Okay, it's fine.
- It's not fine.
- You're going to be fine.
Just put some
pressure on it, okay?
All right.
Let me put one of these on.
Sorry. Another one here.
All right.
- Okay.
- All right.
There's morphine.
You want morphine?
No, I'm scared of needles.
Yeah. Fuck it. Do it.
I'm dying. Aren't I?
- No, you're not.
- Don't lie to me. I am.
You're not dying.
Don't fucking lie to me.
Please.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
You're not dying.
I'm gonna get you
out of this, okay?
You just gotta breathe.
All right. It's coming.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
I'm feeling it
a little bit. Yeah.
- Okay. Great.
- Whoo. Whoo.
All right.
Keep pressure on it.
Thank you, by the way.
What did I do?
He would have killed me.
I told you to shoot him
when you had the chance.
Okay, keep pressure on it.
Oh, yeah.
Hello.
How are you
doing up there?
Listen,
Winston's been stabbed.
I... I'm sorry?
The pilot, uh, Booth,
or whatever his name is,
- he got free and stabbed him.
- Oh, my God.
And I...
I shot him with a flare.
A flare, okay.
- Hello?
- Yeah. Uh, copy. Stand by.
All right.
- Still there?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm here.
Okay, I couldn't reach
Deputy Van Sant.
What is the status
of the witness?
- Dire.
- I see.
Listen, we're gonna need some
real medical attention here.
Copy. Tarmac EMS
is on standby.
Okay. How far away are we?
About 18 to 20 minutes out.
- Is there anything faster?
- Uh...
- Hassan.
- Okay.
Technically, we can
increase your speed.
Great.
But it'll burn through
the rest of your fuel.
We have no choice.
Deputy, I need you
to understand...
Listen, if Winston...
If Winston doesn't testify,
Coleridge walks,
Moretti walks.
Understand, landing
will be more difficult.
Look, I'm not
losing him, all right?
Okay. Open up the red
handle marked "fuel mix"
and then push
the throttle all the way in.
Okay, approaching 160.
Now, keep an eye on that fuel.
I'll call you back
in a few minutes
with the landing procedure.
Okay.
All right, Winston?
Hang in there.
- I am.
- Not long now.
Winston, how are you doing?
You mean, like in general?
Uh-oh.
You're in trouble now.
Hang in there.
I'm sorry.
This is my fault.
This is all my fault.
That's the morphine talking.
No.
I could've done anything.
I was one of those guys,
like in school,
I could've done anything.
I could've gone to college.
I could've got a good job.
But, uh, I wanted it easy.
I knew what was going on,
about Moretti.
I'd say, it's not me.
I'm just some guy
moving numbers around
on a computer
in a fucking basement.
But I knew what was happening.
And I'm...
I'm so fucking sorry.
Um...
The paper that had
our names on it.
You know, with the addresses?
That's my mom's address.
Hey, don't worry about it.
Could you go to that address,
go see her for me?
Me?
Yeah, just go see her, please.
Tell her I did something,
you know,
that was good.
Just tell her I did
something good.
I don't know,
make some shit up, whatever.
Just, it would mean
a lot to her.
Please.
Yeah. All right,
I'll tell her.
Okay.
I did the right thing.
- US Marshals.
- Janine, it's Madolyn.
I need you to put me
through to Caroline Van Sant.
Oh. Um... Uh...
- Janine?
- Yes, one... one moment.
Harris, Coleridge here.
Coleridge.
I'll take it
from here, Janine.
Thank you.
Look, I'm afraid it looks
like you were right
about Deputy
Van Sant, Madolyn.
There was a car crash
and she was T-boned
leaving the office.
Madolyn...
She's dead.
Oh.
I'm so very sorry, Madolyn.
Fuck!
Well, I know
the other driver fled.
One of Moretti's,
I'm guessing.
I'm headed over there
right now.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
They must've been waiting
or I don't know.
Whatever I could do,
however I can help, please.
I know the two of you
were very close.
- No wonder you're in charge.
- What did you say?
You got this all wrapped up,
haven't you?
You got this all figured out.
Excuse me?
I know it was you.
I'm not sure where you're
going with this, Madolyn.
25 grand a month?
Check your records.
You got sloppy.
Oh, you wanna compare records,
Deputy Harris?
No one is gonna believe
a word you say.
A jury will.
- Careful, Harris.
- Careful?
- Be very careful, Harris.
You think I got
something to lose?
God damn it!
You're going fucking crazy.
Fuck you! Careful.
- Listen to me.
- You be fucking careful.
Deputy, talk to me,
god damn it.
- Calm down, Harris.
-
My pilot's calling. Fuck you.
I'll see you in New York.
Hassan.
Guess who we've got on radar.
Thank God.
You're 11 miles out
and looking good, Deputy.
Good.
Hey, do me a favor.
Hang up,
put your headphones on,
and turn your radio
to frequency 121.5.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, hear me?
Handsome, confident,
ATC controller looking
for an intrepid pilot.
Handsome, huh?
Land the damn plane
and see for yourself.
All right, Deputy,
let's bring it in.
Okay.
Winston.
Hey, hey, Winston.
- Almost there.
- Good.
You!
Stupid.
Why didn't you kill me?
Hey! Why didn't
you just kill me?
Because I'm not like you.
Oh, yeah?
I'm gonna tear you apart
into tiny little
fucking pieces.
They're gonna need
the entire forensics team
to identify you.
Oh, I'm gonna enjoy it too.
I might be high, but...
Is that another plane?
Hassan.
There's a plane tailing us.
Looks military.
Yes, solid copy.
It's one of ours.
They're going
to keep you company
the rest of the way.
It's a little protection.
That's good.
Protection?
What? You think...
You think it's there to help?
How exactly is it
supposed to do that?
It's there to protect
everyone else from you.
In case you veer off course
and crash into
a school or something.
- It's there to shoot you down.
- You're full of shit.
Who would you
rather lose, huh?
The three of us?
Or a bunch of kiddies
playing patty cake
in a schoolyard playground?
Hell, Twig.
Ain't you some kind of
accountant or something?
Do the math, you dumb fuck.
He's full of shit. Right?
It's not gonna happen.
We're going to land
this thing.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna land the plane.
I'm gonna enjoy this.
Hey, I see it.
Hassan, I see the runway.
Solid copy.
Got visual on my end.
Flight path is good.
Okay. Passing 1,500 feet.
Air speed's at 90 knots.
- Hassan?
- Yeah, I'm here.
Deputy, there's a crosswind
that kicked up.
I recommend
we try a practice run.
Winston.
Your chances of
a successful landing
improve with a practice run.
He's not gonna make it.
I barely feel a pulse.
- Still...
- We gotta land now.
I'm just trying
to bring you home,
but you're the pilot
in command.
It's your call.
There's no time.
I'm not losing him.
I'm landing this plane.
I'm gonna enjoy this.
Okay. You are clear to land.
Line up your nose
with the spot
on the near edge of the runway
and cut your throttle
back to 25%.
Throttle to 25.
I'm gonna enjoy this.
Deputy, altitude.
Altitude's at, uh, 1,000 feet.
- Flaps to full.
- Flaps.
I don't... I don't see flaps.
Hassan, where are the flaps?
It's there. A round gray lever
just to the right
of the throttle.
Got it. Flaps to full.
All right, Winston.
We're almost there.
Get off me!
Deputy, okay, even out.
You're drifting.
I ain't going to no prison.
You hear me?
Deputy, you copy?
You're drifting off course.
You need to even out.
What the hell
is going on up there?
Are those gunshots?
Deputy! Deputy!
Deputy Harris,
are you still up?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm here.
- Oh, thank God.
Okay, okay.
You're doing great.
- Now back to business.
- Oh, shit.
The engine just died.
Hassan, the engine.
That is because
you are out of fuel.
That's a good thing.
You are less flammable.
Oh. Oh, that's a relief.
Besides, you don't need
the engine to land.
- It's probably easier without.
- Oh, fuck.
Just keep it steady.
We are nearly there.
Okay.
Deputy, still good?
Yeah. Yeah. Passing 600 feet.
This crosswind is
knocking you off course.
Step on the right rudder pedal
until you straighten out.
- You mean the left?
- No, it's the opposite.
Oh, my God.
Okay, better! Hold that line.
- All right.
- 500 feet.
Oh.
Pull back
on the yoke slightly.
Okay.
100 feet. You got this.
Good luck.
Wait, that's it?
I'll see you on the ground.
We got a date.
I'll pick you up at 6:05.
20 feet. 10 feet.
Touchdown.
Oh, fuck!
Hey, Winston.
Winston. Winston!
Okay.
Hey.
Oh, cool. Did we land?
Yeah, we did.
Good job.
Ma'am, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
No, no, no. I'm not hurt.
Take him fast.
He's been stabbed twice.
He's lost a lot of blood.
Hey, we had another passenger.
Where did he go?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
He was flung from the plane.
He didn't make it.
Thank God.
Okay, easy with him.
- Nice and easy. Ready?
- He's lost a lot of blood.
- God.
- There we go.
Fuck off.
- Yeah, I'm good.
- You okay?
Thank you. I'm fine.
Thank you.
What the fuck? Oh, my God.
This fucking day.
Okay.
Milko!
Milko, what the hell's
going on there?
I said no gunshots.
I'm gonna ship you
back to Bulgaria,
you fucking moron!
Pick up. Pick up.
Milko, is it done?
No, Director Coleridge,
it's not done.
- Harris?
- But you are.