Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
And the answer is
four reichsmark.
So, if the German family
costs 5.50 reichsmark a day to live,
but the cost to feed and care
for one person with a hereditary disease
is 12 reichsmark a day,
what is the difference in value lost
to the German people?
Karl.
Well, if it costs so much
to take care of these people,
what do we do?
You kill them.
Does anyone have
a more productive and humane solution?
All right. Well, why don't we focus
on the arithmetic instead?
Well, we put zero here.
And we carry the one.
Six.
Give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive
those who trespass against us.
-Lead us not into temptation--
-Even the Nazis?
We all have a part to play, sweet boy.
Do you really believe
all that stuff from today?
That is only
the curriculum they give me, Peter.
We've talked about this.
You have to think for yourself.
No calculation
can measure the worth of a life.
But what I do know
is that I love you.
Will you stay until I fall asleep?
Of course.
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil,
for thine is the kingdom,
the power, and the glory forever and ever.
Amen.
You, there.
Where is the Weber household?
Do you know?
Subject lives here.
-Weber family!
-Now!
No.
One moment!
-No. I don't want to go.
-Remember.
-Weber family!
-Everything is at the barn.
Everything is at the barn,
and they will meet you there.
We know you are in there!
Kick in the door.
Move away!
Go, go, go! Now!
Looks damaged! Check the boards.
-It won't hold.
-Go around!
Back up. Back up!
It's okay.
You, look over there.
There are reports
of this barn being used for resistance.
Stay here.
I'll lead them away from you.
Search back there.
Over here!
-Out for a run, are we, huh?
Quite a day rounding up
all the loose ends in the cow towns.
Anything to say, boy?
Heil Hitler!
-Enough!
You're just saving us the trip.
-You kill them.