Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
They were left in cardboard boxes,
found near a bridge or on the sidewalk.
There used to be so many of them.
More than 30 of them in a shift.
We nannies had different tasks.
Some fed the babies milk.
Some did the laundry.
I looked after the babies.
I remember many of them.
These babies… I brought them up.
I held them in my arms
and fed them slowly,
as if they were my own children.
My heart ached
whenever I sent a baby away.
They'd be sent so far away.
What was to become of them?
Can you speak Chinese?
I mean, you used to live there.
What origins are you?
Like, what's your…
She was taken to Huazhou Welfare
Institute around December, 1999.
You gotta be more detailed…
I know it's like
finding a needle in a haystack, but…
Of course it's impossible to find them.
Yeah, I know it's quite difficult.
No, it's impossible.
You're talking about ancient history.
No, we don't keep such records.
Someone told my mom a baby photo online
looked like me and my sister.
I had to give birth secretly.
I don't know
where the midwife sent the baby.
Let's see if you recognize
the nanny in the photo.
I didn't even know you were Jewish.
My mom's Greek Orthodox,
so when I say I'm Greek,
it doesn't make any sense.
Do you know what's your real birthday?
I thought I came with a little tag
or something, but my mom,
she was like, "They guessed."
I did the 23andMe thing too.
But I haven't done anything.
But that's cool that you found them.
You're not gonna try?
'Cause you don't want to or just…
But where would you even start?
Are you meeting your mom or something?
I love to see that this can happen.
We grow red peppers here.
I've been farming since I was a teenager.
-Who taught you?
-My mom.
Our place is messy.
What's this right here?
That? When the one-child policy
was strict back in the days,
we were told to get these things.
Oh! It's the document for birth control!
After I gave birth to my first daughter,
I went back to work.
They would make me get "coil checks."
-IUD?
-Right.
They required you
to be examined every three months.
It was really strict back then,
not like now.
Have you ever thought about the life
of the daughter you gave away?
Whether she is living a good life?
Yeah. How can I not think about that?
So it was your second child
who was sent away.
-It was late in the night.
-At midnight.
Someone took the baby away.
Who was it?
We asked a neighbor.
He said he would find
someone to adopt her.
We wrapped her in a small blanket.
Did you talk to him after that?
He wouldn't tell us
who he gave the baby to.
He was afraid we'd want her back.
I know it must be a painful history
for you. It's not easy.
Right. That's the tube.
There's a black line to indicate
the amount of saliva necessary.
Okay, that's good.
We'll send you a report
even if the DNA doesn't match.
When you are listening
to other people's stories,
what they have been through,
I think you can understand a lot of things
that you never know
you would understand before.
They do love their kids,
they want to find their babies.
It's so sad.
We are on the Two Bridge
where Sadie was found.
Hello, auntie.
Has anyone near here ever…
-Found a baby?
-Yes, have you ever seen one?
-No, I haven't.
-You haven't?
No, I only sell things here.
I always knew
about the one-child policy 'cause…
And my parents, they almost gave up me,
because they don't want
to pay the penalty.
But I'm very lucky
because my grandparents,
they said, "No, we want to keep her."
So I just don't have
a very good relationship with my father.
I remember one time,
my father wanted to…
And he just wanted
to take my brother there,
and I asked him if I can…
It was very difficult for me
because you know you're not welcome.
You are in the wrong gender,
they don't want you, and you know that.
So that's why I feel
so connected with the girls.
A neighbor saw the ad. He saw the photo.
He told me, "That girl
looks like your daughter a lot."
How long have you been living here?
-Me?
-Right.
I've been living here since I was born.
I work in the rice fields.
So… did you make the decision
to give up the baby
before she was born or after?
I decided after she was born.
Because the village officials found out.
If we kept her,
it was going to cost us at least $8,500.
We were forced by the circumstances.
We had no choice at all.
I left her at the People's Hospital.
Next to the main entrance.
It was four or five o'clock
in the morning.
Because it would have been too cold
to leave her there overnight.
I left a note with her date of birth.
I left 300 RMB in her clothes.
Nothing else.
Just the money in her clothes.
That's what happened.
Of course I felt awful.
My own child
would be taken by someone else.
Doesn't matter if it's a boy or a girl,
it's my own child.
Did your wife know
that you were giving up the baby?
She knew what I was doing.
She was crying.
She couldn't bear it.
She wanted me to get the baby back.
I said I didn't know who took her.
Mom, cut up the onion for me.
Just that.
Cut it in slices.
Who taught you to cook?
I've taught myself
since I was very little.
You know, my mom doesn't cook.
I can only ask her
to help with simple tasks.
Do you work in the fields?
I used to. But not anymore.
I couldn't manage it. It's a tough job.
So, when did you find out
you had a little sister?
When I was in the fourth
or fifth grade, I think.
My mom, sometimes
she would talk to other people
about babies who got adopted.
She would ask around.
She talks about it less often now.
I had a chance to grow up
with my parents around.
I feel lucky.
But she didn't have
the same opportunity like I did.
I feel guilty.
It was my parents who made the decision.
But we are sisters, after all.
So, let me ask you,
where did you see the ad?
I saw it on my husband's phone.
I gave up a daughter in 2001.
We sent another one away in 2003.
Do you remember
if she had any birthmarks?
I didn't pay attention.
I only looked at her face,
which had no marks on it.
Hello. My name is Liu Hao.
Nice to meet you.
I don't want to be filmed.
We won't film you.
If you sit behind that,
they won't be able to see you.
I knew it was a girl.
I couldn't bear to have another abortion,
so I gave birth to the baby instead.
-You had the baby in a hospital?
-Right. I knew a doctor there.
He told me to wait
until I was about to give birth,
and then he would help me deliver.
Because if you went
to the hospital too early,
the doctors would find out
you were having an extra child.
When they took my daughter away,
I fainted and fell to the floor.
I have no idea where she ended up.
I know she wouldn't understand
or forgive me if I found her.
She wouldn't be nice to me.
Let me ask you.
Would you forgive me at all?
I ask myself this question.
My dad, he and his mother
didn't want me when I was born.
If she wants to forgive me, she will.
If not, let it be.
It is what my mom
had been through, you know?
My father wanted to leave her
because I'm not a boy.
Hello!
You said you know Sadie's nanny?
Oh, right, right.
I saw her picture online.
I'm a friend of the nanny.
That is awesome.
She has worked
in the orphanage for over 20 years.
Do you mind giving me her number
so I can contact her?
People never talk about these women
who took care of thousands of babies.
-Do you remember her?
-Yes, I took care of her.
This is what she looks like now.
Is she a good height?
-Yes. She's tall.
-I knew, just by looking at her picture.
She has long hair,
like many foreign girls.
Right. Long hair.
When you were a kid, did you think
about what you wanted to do in the future?
Not really.
People from the countryside
don't have dreams.
I can't write.
I quit school in the second grade.
Why did you stop?
We were poor with so many kids.
No money to study.
Life is much better now.
We even throw the leftovers away.
So, you remember her.
Yeah, I remember many of them.
She was skinny when she first came.
It was a freezing day.
A passerby found her on the sidewalk
and brought her to us.
I fed her gently in my arms,
as if she was my own.
I brought her up and had to send her away.
We nannies… We aren't cold-hearted.
My heart aches
whenever I send a child away.
They'd be sent so far away.
I'd think, "What's to become of them?"
Hello?
Good morning! Did you have breakfast?
Hi! Nice to see you, Mr. Xu.
When was the last time I was here?
In October.
I'm here to show you the test results.
It's here.
It shows that your DNA
doesn't match with the girl's.
You can take a look.
I won't give up looking for your daughter.
Because your DNA is already at the lab,
in the future,
if your daughter takes a test,
there will be a match.
It's okay. We're not giving up.
I know it's hard for you, auntie.
I'll keep searching.
I do not have a boyfriend.
You were found on the Two Bridge.
That is me. I didn't realize it at first.
First, I washed diapers.
Then I started taking care of the babies
from 2001 to 2005.
When did Sadie come to the orphanage?
In early December.
She wasn't wearing pretty clothes,
like the other babies.
She was no more than 5 pounds.
Although she isn't my daughter,
I raised her until she was adopted.
You are so sweet.
It's a shame you can't find your mom.
Please keep an eye out for us.
Please tell us if anyone reaches out.
Sadie used to live here, right?
Yes, in this room.
Thanks for bringing
so many gifts for the kids.
This is where the kids live.
Hello, everyone.
Say hi to your sisters.
How many babies
did you take care of back then?
After 2001, it was the peak time.
Over 200 kids.
The conditions in the orphanage
weren't optimal.
We had only two nurses and no doctor.
There were many babies.
We weren't able to take them
to the hospital whenever they got sick.
But since there wasn't a doctor,
we couldn't use prescription drugs.
So I went to medical school in 2002.
I gave her this vaccine shot.
I did for all the babies.
No.
She only cried
when she was taking vaccination.
She usually didn't cry.
She was outgoing and alive.
When Chloe first came to the orphanage,
how old was she?
We think she was born that day.
Who brought her to the orphanage?
It would have been
the local police department.
Hello, auntie.
-This is Lily.
-I recognize her.
-You recognize her?
-I do, I do.
This is her mother.
Can you tell us how long Lily lived here?
I brought her up until she was adopted.
When there were
too many babies in the orphanage,
we'd raise them at home
until they're sent away.
How many babies lived here?
Sometimes over 10,
sometimes just a few.
You were living in that room.
You were here.
She was a mischievous girl.
A bit naughty.
My grandma used to
tickle her and call her a bun.
I was sad that she was crying.
When I put her in her mom's arms,
she cried a lot.
I raised her
and grew feelings for her.
Lily and her mom got this for you.
Oh, thank you so much.
Auntie, please open it
and see what's in it.
Can you help me with it?
Can you?
This gift means a lot to her.
I see. I will have it on all the time.
Always.
I am grateful to her mom for bringing
her up to be an excellent girl.
Thank you.
So, we are heading
to the Yangmei Township.
Your finding place is
in a government building of that town.
So we'll go there first and walk around.
And then the family
that could be your birth family,
I will come over there
and tell them the results,
that it doesn't match.
That family really wanted
to find their child,
and that sister, that girl I talked to,
she really wants to find her sister.
This is the government building.
You were left on the stairs
to the entrance of the building.
Oh! You are cooking here, Chunjiao?
I haven't seen you in so long.
Why are you cooking so much today?
Because we have more than 20 people today.
-Are the workers coming today?
-Yes.
Mr. Chen!
Let me show you the report.
-Take a seat.
-It's okay.
It turns out your DNA didn't match.
It wasn't a match, was it?
Chunjiao?
The test results show
that the DNA didn't match.
No match?
So, Lily is not your little sister.
She isn't, is she?
I know you will find her in the future.
Even though I'm not sure when,
I think there's a chance.
Because as the technology develops,
DNA tests will be more and more common.
I don't wanna dwell on it.
There's nothing to do.
It is what it is.
However…
However, Lily is here today
with her cousins.
-I wonder if she's welcome to--
-Let's meet her, then.
Let's meet her. She also thinks
it's fate that brought her here.
-It's okay for us to meet her.
-Okay.
I'll let her know now.
-Lily.
-I recognize her.
You really look alike.
Does she? Does she look like me?
A little bit.
Hello, miss.
-Thank you.
-If you want, I can get more.
Come back to China anytime!
She looks like my daughter,
just like the photo showed.
Her eyes are like mine, right? Her eyes.
But she's not the one.
There's nothing I can do.
I hoped she was the one.
But it is what it is.
It is not up to what I say, right?
We have to go, Mr. Chen.
-Okay.
-Thank you, Mrs. Chen.
Much obliged.
His eyes were watering.
I feel like he's holding, you know,
because he's a man.
He can't cry.
Class is starting.
What is your nationality?
I am Chinese.
There are four people in my family.
My dad is a businessman.
My mom isn't working.
My sister is a college student.
Hello, auntie.
Let me show you the report.
It must be negative.
Where is my name?
Your name is here.
Look.
It shows "Matched."
You didn't match with Sadie,
but with another girl born in 2000.
Her name is Amanda Phillips.
Does she look like me?
I think so.
She speaks English.
Pardon?
I don't know English.