[suspenseful music playing]
[church bell tolling]
-[man over earpiece] She's here.
-[radio static crackles]
♪ ♪
Place the crypto wallet under the kneeler.
What about my money?
Your money will be delivered
after verification of the trades
on the blockchain.
Rutledge needs to be certain all
the bitcoin you promised is in the wallet.
My deal was payment on delivery.
You need this bitcoin
for your plan to work.
You pay me now
or this crypto wallet is mine.
I urge you to be reasonable.
Listen.
I am a reasonable person.
I don't know what you are planning,
but I'm not your errand girl!
[grunting]
[Bousquet] Stop her!
[dramatic music playing]
-Ma'am. Ma'am.
-[snoring]
Madam President, we have a situation.
Avid is on the move.
-[horn blares]
-[panting]
-[tires squealing]
-[Csonger grunts]
[people scream]
-[intercom buzzing]
-Hello?
[gasps]
I'm gonna ruin someone's day
over this, Manny.
I have no doubt, Madam President.
[speaking Hungarian urgently]
[grunts]
[people exclaiming, murmuring]
Shit! [groaning]
[President Sutton] Agent Darden.
[Darden] Madam President.
Avid is inside, ma'am.
Apprehension is minutes away.
-Make it quick.
-Yes, ma'am.
[Titos over earpiece] Rutledge,
she's headed your way.
[radio static crackles]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[techno music playing over speakers]
-[lively chatter]
Copy that.
They've got Avid, ma'am.
[Quoll yelps]
-[shushing]
-[muffled straining]
It's all right. It's all right. It's over.
There you go. Just relax.
Should've been more patient.
Mm?
[Sutton] You can't keep
letting her sneak out, Darden.
I'm sorry, madam.
Avid is approaching the Oval.
[gentle music playing]
A little much, don't you think, Mom?
Zip it.
[dramatic music playing]
[Darden] Make sure you get
that RFID hardware.
[agent] I'll take it, sir.
-All right.
-Check the drawers.
Uh, is this really necessary? Come on.
No, stop. Stop!
-I need this for school.
-Well, you should've thought of that.
Now it's evidence. Phone, too.
Give it to me.
I-I'm 18 in four months.
Am I never supposed to go out?
Not without Secret Service agents, Serena.
Not without protection.
And you're gonna tell us
exactly what you did to pull this off.
Please.
You have so many holes in your security,
I could've done it ten different ways.
You're so smart, and yet you use it
in all the wrong ways, Serena.
How am I supposed to use it
when I'm stuck in here like a zoo animal?
Well, Demetrius is stuck, too.
You don't see him pulling these stunts.
Because he doesn't have any friends!
-I have friends.
-They're all animated.
He knew I was sneaking out,
and he said nothing.
Don't look at me. I'm the good one.
-You're both grounded.
-I'm not 12.
-Prove it.
-You won't let me!
[sharp whistle]
[Derek] Enough!
It's 4:00 in the morning.
We are all going to bed.
[contemplative music playing]
You know I've had to work
twice as hard to get here.
Why do you need to make it harder?
-I didn't choose this.
-You don't get to choose.
And whatever you did to sneak out tonight,
you'll never do it again.
[dramatic music playing]
[panting]
Looks like Serena hacked in,
made her own RFID key.
She's smart.
Too smart.
[both grunting]
She doesn't know when to quit.
I wonder where she gets that from.
You're using power against power.
You need to offset my balance.
I can have you reassigned for sass.
Yeah, but not for another 15 minutes.
Take it easy.
If you're limping at the G20,
I will get reassigned.
-How's your knee doing?
-No complaints.
-Oh. Impressive coming from Army.
-Oh, yeah?
Think you Marines are tougher?
Not bad.
[Joanna] Of course Prime Minister Everett
won't have your back at the G20.
He's never liked strong women.
[Sutton] How will I get
consensus for my plan
if I can't even get
the support of Britain?
[Joanna] You'll find a way.
-You always do.
-Mm.
Did you get any sleep after the jailbreak?
-[Manny] Four minutes, Madam President.
-Okay.
You raised four teenagers.
How are you still standing?
-Gin.
-[laughs]
[Kelly] Your jacket, ma'am.
We also need to settle on an ensemble
for the welcoming ceremony.
-Mm.
-I'm thinking red.
It's your first international event.
I want them to focus on my plan,
not who I'm wearing.
[Kelly] What if we get you
into a comfortable pair of heels?
You can tower over everyone, hmm?
Do you want an honest answer?
[Joanna] No, he does not.
[Manny] Time to go, Madam President.
Thank you.
[cameras clicking]
As the 20 richest nations on Earth gather
to assess our global economy,
it's time we solve a hunger crisis
worse than any we've seen in decades.
In many sub-Saharan countries,
farmers don't have the access
to banking that we do.
So when it comes time
to buy seed for harvest,
they have to depend on cash that
they've stuffed in a sock or hidden away.
We want to offer them a solution
in digital currency.
It's secure and easy to use.
My uncle always used to say, "You can
give a man a fish and feed him for a day
or you can teach a man to fish
and feed him for life."
With the Together Plan,
that's exactly what we'd like to do.
And I implore all world leaders
at the G20 summit to join me.
The president will take questions.
[reporters murmuring "Madam President"]
Madam President, will your family
be joining you in South Africa?
My husband will join me as well as my
esteemed treasury secretary Joanna Worth,
who will be ready with cost-benefit
analysis to help the medicine go down.
[reporters murmuring "Madam President"]
Any comment on the video trending
of your underage daughter
being apprehended by Secret Service
at a Georgetown bar last night?
My family and I
deal with our matters privately.
[man] Madam President,
with all due respect,
how do we know
we can trust you to keep us safe
when you can't keep
your own house in order?
[contemplative music playing]
No more questions.
-[reporters shouting "Madam President"]
-Thank you. No more questions.
[reporters clamoring]
[clamoring echoes and fades]
Whatever plans you had
this weekend are gone.
You and your brother are coming
to Cape Town with us.
[thunder rumbling]
Why?
Is it 'cause of what happened
with the reporters today?
Why are you like this?
All you ever try to do
is make yourself look good.
Serena.
[sighs]
[dishes clatter]
[door opens, closes]
[newswoman over TV] Video of
Serena Sutton partying at a Georgetown bar
without her security detail is
making the rounds on social media.
She was later apprehended...
You're just adding insult to injury?
-Mm.
-Here.
-Thank you, baby.
-Mm-hmm.
[Sutton] Well, I got injury covered.
I'm looking for my daily dose of insult.
-[sighs]
-...has cast a shadow over
today's press conference
announcing the president's Together Plan
and opened her up
to more scrutiny from her critics.
She does not own the respect
of foreign leaders
and lacks the diplomacy
of every president--
-Mm.
-[TV clicks off]
[Derek sniffs]
[sighs] My daughter hates me.
She's a teenager.
She hates everybody.
[softly] Hey.
You are a great mother.
She's wearing me out.
Someday she'll see you
for all that you are.
-[dramatic music playing]
-[thunder crashing]
-[quiet chatter]
-[electronic bell dings]
[Joanna] Britain will
pull France with them.
If they want to remain allies,
they have to fall in line.
But you can't bully them into it.
When did you start pulling punches?
[scoffs]
I seem to remember an attack ad
during the primary calling me a warmonger.
Well, Danny, then I came across as
looking like I was jealous of a war hero
and kissed the nomination goodbye.
But then we became friends again.
[chuckles]
Jo, we never stopped being friends.
Right?
But being strong is what got us here.
About 100 years ago,
neither of us could vote.
But here we are, you and I,
on the way to G20 on Air Force One.
[knock on door]
Madam, the vice president
and CIA Director Mikkelson are standing by
for your security briefing,
if you're ready.
Yeah.
-Mikkelson, Harold.
-[door closes]
-Madam President.
Walk me through it.
Who wants to kill me today?
Well, there has been
a major uptick in violent rhetoric
around the digital currency element
of your agenda.
-How's the threat level?
-This hotel is a fortress.
But with the less experienced host nation,
we brought in Pax Worldwide Security
for additional support.
You know how I feel
about private contractors.
Danny, it is the best way.
We vetted the Pax team
over the last six months.
Between them, Secret Service and
our Special Forces Counter Assault Team...
We got them the honeymoon suite.
-...you're in good hands, Madam President.
-Good luck out there.
[dramatic music playing]
Thanks, mate.
[Paxton] Corporal Rutledge!
Jesus Christ, mate.
Last time I saw you, we were pinned down,
out of ammo, sand up our cracks.
Brother, good to see you, mate.
-You look good. Huh?
-[chuckles]
I was damned surprised you wanted
to come and work logistics for us.
Ah, no, no, no, no.
Thanks for sending the company bird.
Well, you know most of these boys.
Uh, most of them served under you.
Those you don't know know you.
Christ, that was a lifetime ago,
wasn't it?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
[chuckles]
Now here we are babysitting
the same bastards
that put us in
their dirty little war, right?
-Well, let me show you about.
-[pats chest]
Yeah, right.
Hotel is nearly impenetrable.
Is it?
♪ ♪
-[♪ Miriam Makeba sings "Pata Pata"]
-[seabirds calling]
[song continues in Xhosa]
♪ ♪
[busy chatter]
[indistinct police radio chatter]
[song ends]
Madam President.
Good morning.
Park The Beast downstairs.
The rest stay above.
[man over radio] Copy that.
Welcome, Sutton family.
I am Melokuhle Koale of the Grand Diamont.
We are incredibly honored
to have you here.
Thank you for having us.
Please come this way.
You will wear these.
They give you access to your rooms
and all other areas of the hotel.
[lock beeps]
-Please come on in. Welcome.
-[chatter and cameras clicking outside]
You use RFID?
RFID allows us to monitor movement
around the property, Miss Sutton.
Mm.
So what if I just ditched the card
and scaled down the perimeter wall?
Then you'll miss our delightful brunch.
[laughs]
[choir singing lively song
in native language]
♪ ♪
[Derek laughing]
[dramatic music playing]
[busy chatter]
Security Central.
Paxton checking in from the ballroom.
Advance team is still inside.
I got Secret Service sniffing wallpaper.
-We should be clear in 20.
-Thanks, mate.
[R&amp;B music playing quietly]
[Derek] Come on, Madam President.
I can't wait to see Kelly's handiwork.
It can't be that bad.
Well, damn.
A red rose gown
with a superhero cape and...
some super comfy medieval torture devices.
[laughing]
You can take them off, baby.
I won't tell anyone.
-I'll live.
-Yeah, you better.
-Because you are my heart and my purpose.
-Mm-hmm.
I knew that the moment
you landed on my gurney.
Aw.
[gentle music playing]
I was a hot mess, and you saved me.
Mm.
Yeah.
-Now I got to go save the world.
-[chuckles]
[rousing music playing]
-[reporters murmuring]
-[cameras clicking]
Only close security inside. Stay alert.
[scanner beeps, chimes]
-[lively chatter]
-[upbeat music playing]
[laughter]
[reporters murmuring "Madam President"]
Madam President.
Madam President, excuse me.
Madam-Madam President,
some say your Together Plan
is an attempt to back the failing dollar.
Don't try to hijack my narrative.
The dollar is not failing.
How much money will you hand out
to these farmers, and who pays for it?
[Derek] Now you're hijacking my date.
[reporters murmuring "Madam President"]
Oh, you waste no time.
That's why I love you.
-[Joanna laughs]
-Oh.
Our most glorious human triumphs
have been achieved through cooperation,
and here we are at the height of it.
-[Derek] Hmm.
-Plenty to celebrate.
-And, Derek...
-Hmm?
...the great tragedy of my middle age is
that you don't have an older brother
who likes divorcées.
-[laughs]
-Maybe we can find you
a handsome sheikh this weekend.
-All right.
-[chuckles]
Let's go over the hard targets.
Yes, back to work.
Be right back.
So, Saudi Arabia and Russia
remain their charitable selves.
Even if they do choose to support,
they won't contribute.
And that cold wind you feel
is Elena Romano.
She is the new head
of the International Monetary Fund.
Only the second most powerful woman
in the world, after you.
She's proposed to cut our plan in half,
and I believe that she leaked
the details of it to the press.
Look, I will deal with Elena,
one soulless capitalist to another,
-but you have the harder job.
-[glasses clink]
[whispers] Good luck.
Prime Minister Everett.
[Derek] Win him over, babe.
-I'm gonna say good night to the kids.
-Yeah.
Then I got your six at dinner.
[tense music playing]
[Rutledge] Press have had their window.
Get them out of the ballroom.
Bring it up.
All right, thank you,
ladies and gentlemen.
Press time is now over.
If you would kindly make your way
outside the door.
This is Parry.
I got Angel heading upstairs.
Taking the press out to the woodshed.
[Parry] Looks like it, sir.
Only security teams allowed
in the foyer tonight.
[elevator bell chimes]
[upbeat music playing]
Madam President. [chuckles]
A vision in red.
Thank you, Prime Minister.
You're too kind.
Now, the subtle art here is to let
our colleagues get a drink in their belly
before you ask for the moon.
Drink up.
I won't let this be another summit
that's all talk and no action.
A lone wolf and her Together Plan.
I must say, I-I admire your tenacity,
but, you know, nobody likes a bulldozer.
If you get the merest consideration
of your proposal,
it'd be a victory.
Now let's get you a drink.
[contemplative music playing]
[indistinct security radio chatter]
Green light from
the Pax team on the ground.
Good.
Okay. Too right.
[exhales slowly]
-Sixty seconds out.
-Right.
[Titos] This is a great moment.
Smile, please.
We are making history here.
It's fantastic.
[camera clicking]
Great. Great.
One more shot.
I've recoded the door locks
to respond to our card keys only.
[applause]
[Titos] Thank you very much.
Cape Town cell towers and Wi-Fi
going dark in three, two, one.
[computer chiming]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Darden] Room service has arrived
outside the ballroom.
[Rutledge over earpiece] Thanks, mate.
Copy that.
Looks like the POTUS's
"break glass in case of emergency" squad
is back in their holding suite.
Please confirm.
[man] Confirmed, sir.
U.S. Special Forces CAT team
is in their room.
Great.
[lively chatter]
Madam President.
Thirty seconds.
[elevator bell chimes]
[gas hissing]
♪ ♪
[man] Perimeter gate secured.
And away we go.
-[busy chatter]
-[guns clicking]
What is this?
[quiet, steady beeping]
[people screaming, clamoring]
[bell rings]
-What was that?
-[frantic murmuring]
-An explosion?
-[people coughing]
-Open up the door!
-[alarm blaring]
-[panicked chatter]
-[lock buzzes]
[coughing continues]
My kids, my husband.
I need you to stay here, ma'am.
Stay with me.
What's happening?!
We need to go down, sir. We have to--
-Not without my kids.
-They have their own detail--
Stand down!
Keep away from the windows.
I have Avid and A-Student.
Sweeping the hallway before evacuating.
[whispers] Stay here.
-[alarm continues blaring]
-[urgent chatter over radio]
Beautiful, isn't it?
-What was it? Are-are we under attack?
-[panicked murmuring]
What in God's name is happening?
I know as much as you do, sir.
So, for now, we all huddle in place.
[quietly] They look like
they're guarding the doors more than us.
Oh, ridiculous. Just ridiculous.
Our men should be
banging down those doors by now.
What about the CAT team?
That first explosion came from
the east wing and that honeymoon suite.
If I was taking down this party,
that CAT team would be my primary target.
[dramatic music playing]
[alarm continues blaring]
Explosions along the east wing.
Evacuation Plan Delta.
-Move! Move!
-[urgent chatter]
Eddie. Eddie. Come on, mate.
We have a breach.
Yeah.
We do.
[pained grunting]
Need you to let go.
Just let go.
[blade stabs]
[gunfire outside door]
[lock beeps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[door creaking]
Get up. Get up!
[dramatic music playing]
Requesting status on Avid and A-Student.
[radio static crackles]
What countries' security teams made it in?
Same four that always demand it.
U.S.,
China, Russia
and Turkey.
[Sutton] That's four for four.
-Should we--
-No, we're safe here until we aren't.
[people murmuring]
Thank goodness.
Now, if you'll kindly escort us all out.
Somebody better start talking.
I'm taking my president out.
You cannot hold us here.
[panicked shouting, screaming]
Get the hostages!
Separate the leaders from the spouses!
Get in the corner now!
[gunfire continues]
Stay down! Down!
Jo!
Broken arrow! Broken arrow!
Get going! All the way back!
[gunfire continues]
Oliver!
-Madam!
-Down. Come on.
-[fabric rips]
-[grunts] Shit!
-Get up!
-[grunts]
-[man shouts]
-Come on.
[whimpers, speaks Italian]
We need to move. Stay low.
-Danielle!
-Joanna!
[Manny] Come on. Let's go.
[gunfire continues]
-[man] Back up! Back up!
-[man 2] Watch the doors!
This is suicide. Where are we going?
[Manny] There's a door behind the bar.
-Madam.
-[Sutton] We need cover.
Come on.
[Elena hyperventilating]
Until I give the signal,
I need you to stay, okay?
Okay.
She's having panic attack.
[Sutton speaking indistinctly]
-Look at me.
-[gasping]
I'm gonna get you out of here.
[Elena] Okay.
[gunfire continues]
[Sutton grunting]
-Go.
-Okay.
Come on.
-Let's go. Go.
-[Elena whimpers]
[Everett] Oh, God!
Come on. Gotcha.
[panting]
[hushed] Take off our conference bands.
They have a chip that can track us.
We need to keep moving, Madam President.
How'd you find this?
Saw the blueprints.
I found the door in my advance work.
[Sutton] Well, you might have
saved all of us.
[pots clanking]
Stay down!
[door creaks]
-Dad!
-[grunting]
[Derek yelling]
[punches landing]
[panting]
You guys okay?
Let me say this again so you can get it
through your thick skull.
How many others are hiding in here?
Tell me or I'm going to shoot you.
[hushed] Okay.
[pots clatter]
Two tangos with weapons
right outside those doors.
-Right.
-Maybe if I surprise them...
Okay, give me your secondary.
Two against two, we eliminate the maybe.
Ma'am, zero chance
-that you're going in there.
-What do you think this is?
It's not the ideal,
but I've handled weapons before,
and I've seen my share of combat.
-I know. I was there.
-Where do you think this goes?
With all due respect,
that was two decades ago, ma'am.
-Well, that's more than you can say
about any of those.
-[overlapping hushed chatter]
I'm not worried about the others
because they aren't
the president of the United States.
Agent Ruiz, do you know
that rank has its privileges?
We're doing it, and that's an order.
Where'd she go?
[whimpers, screams]
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[applause]
Eighteen out of 20.
The American president and British gone.
How?
I don't know, boss,
but I found where they escaped.
[murmuring]
I told you that
she was gonna be a problem.
Yeah, your problem.
She's the linchpin to all of this.
That's why I gave her to you.
'Cause I trusted you.
You take two men right now,
and you bring me the American president.
Do not let me down.
-Agent Parry saved our lives, okay?
-Mm-hmm.
It wasn't your fault.
That was his job.
Hey, son, come help me.
-We need to block the door.
-[Demetrius] That's the only way out.
[straining] Come on. Pull it.
Okay, go, go.
[suspenseful music playing]
[man] Clear the east entrance.
Copy.
[chatter fades]
This is much better.
Yeah, if you don't mind soiled sheets.
[sighs] Thank you for our much-improved
situation, Madam First Lady.
Please, Han Min-Seo.
Han Min-Seo.
[Elena] I'm Elena.
-Elena Romano.
-Elena.
I'm grateful for your quick action,
Madam President.
Special Agent Manny Ruiz.
-And you know the prime minister.
-[Everett] Yes, splendid.
Yes, we're all, we're all good friends.
Manny, you have the evacuation routes,
contingency plans?
So do they.
This has to be an inside job.
Well, you Americans never leave home
without your Special Forces.
Where are they?
We believe that
after the first explosions,
our entire team was eliminated.
[stammers] Y-You have troops
around the globe.
Send up a bloody flare.
-[shushing]
-Oliver, there is
no U.S. base in South Africa.
Any QRF is hours out.
And... I'm not sure how effective
they would be with high-value hostages.
So what do we do?
We have to breach the perimeter.
[mutters]
And that's a good mile away,
so we'll need cover.
Any ideas?
What about The Beast?
Is it underground?
It is.
Which kind of animal is this beast?
Oh, no, that's my ride.
It's a military vehicle
disguised as a luxury sedan.
But, uh, h-how do we get to it?
Need to get to the ground floor.
Cross the service entrance.
That elevator's our way out,
but we tossed our security keys.
Even if we hadn't,
I'm sure they changed the codes by now.
What? It's a little short.
We're not going down.
[knock on door]
-[Karl] Housekeeping!
-[knock]
Open up!
[fabric ripping]
[knocking on door]
[Karl] Open up!
Wait.
-Come on.
-What are you doing?
[Serena] Follow me.
Serena, no.
[knocking]
[Karl] I said open up!
-[Serena] Let's go, Dee.
-Son, go.
-Open!
-[gunshot]
-[Derek] Come on, Dee.
Go.
[whimpers]
[panting]
[radio beeps]
Corporal Rutledge.
The kids escaped to the first floor.
We'll canvass the ground level.
I am the leader of the organization
that has taken the G20 by force.
They are gonna say we're terrorists.
We are not.
What we are is a group of individuals
who refuse to stand by
and let world leaders strip away
the rights and wealth of their citizens.
Who is he? We need to know now.
-[urgent chatter]
-We will be releasing
recorded evidence of their deceit,
evidence that America and her allies
intend to steal weaker nations' resources
to bolster their own failing currencies
and completely reset the monetary system.
[phones ringing]
This currency
that President Sutton is proposing
would allow them to dictate when, where
and how you spend your hard-earned money.
-[man] We have a match.
-Thank you.
Edward Rutledge, former Special Forces,
Australian military.
FBI has a file on him.
How the hell did he get past our checks?
[Mikkelson] He came with Pax Worldwide.
His background was clean.
[Rutledge] ...protect yourself,
your family, your loved ones
is to pull your money
from their banks and stock markets,
and you invest in crypto
because it is the only currency
that they do not and cannot control.
To the governments watching,
if you try and stop me,
I'll execute your precious leaders.
To the citizens watching...
...if we act now, together,
then tomorrow
we will awaken
to a brand-new world.
We got to keep going.
But how are we gonna find Mom?
We don't.
-What?
-Your mom and I had
a long talk when she got elected that
if anything like this were to ever happen,
it was my job to get you two out.
That no matter what happens to her...
...I would look out for you.
Let's go.
[Everett] Then, I say we bar the door
and we wait for the cavalry.
[Sutton] The cavalry took over the summit.
If you want to live,
you'll follow my lead.
Back to giving orders.
I don't recall us putting you in charge.
If they want to stay, let them.
It's not safe here, and you know it.
I won't leave them.
The men will canvass the hotel
and find you.
-You don't know that.
-Well, you know what?
I've seen enough to know
what we're up against here.
You carried a child
from a blown-up building,
and someone snapped a photo,
and now you're Captain America?
Know what?
You stay here, then.
Ladies?
I'd rather go and be led by you
than stay and be annoyed by him.
Yes. How do we go to the garage?
Ladies and gentlemen,
as you can see, the format
for the evening's event has changed,
but as long as you follow my instructions,
we're all gonna get on
like a house on fire.
Now, one by one, you're gonna come up,
you're gonna look straight down the lens,
and you're gonna read the words
exactly as written.
Let's start with, uh, South Korea.
President Lee Young-Ho, please.
-[Young-Ho grunts]
-[people murmuring]
In your own time, read the words.
Are you needing a translator?
'Cause I don't think
any of my boys speak Asian.
I speak English.
-[chuckles] Oh, good.
-But I will not say that.
This is a pangram, a sentence
using every sound in a language.
If he records us saying this,
he can use his AI server to make
a deepfake that would make it seem like
we are saying anything he wants.
Even AI won't be able
to identify it as fake.
A tech-savvy South Korean.
[chuckles] What are the odds?
I will not help you.
Uh, okay, fine.
We'll, uh, we'll start with someone else.
Come here.
-[screams]
-[people screaming, murmuring]
[groaning]
[Young-Ho] My ear!
You're an animal!
Yeah, I am an animal.
I'm your animal. You created me.
You created all of this with
your corrupt wars and your profiteering.
You people have created nothing
but animosity and division.
If we were as guilty as you claim,
you would not need deepfakes.
Well, yeah,
but politics is theater, isn't it?
You guys are gonna be rock stars. [laughs]
[tense music playing]
"That quick beige fox jumped in the air
over each thin dog."
-"That quick..."
-"...beige fox..."
-"...jumped in the air..."
-"...over each thin dog."
[voices overlapping] "'Look out,' I shout,
'for he's foiled you again,
creating chaos.'"
"'...creating chaos.'"
[echoing] "'...creating chaos.'"
[Paulson] Whoever has done this
appears to have control of the firewall.
All surveillance is gone.
We have no eyes or ears inside.
This is a coup.
A global coup.
And do we have POTUS's status?
No, we don't, sir.
And with world leaders being held inside,
any unilateral attempt to rescue anybody
that results in the death of a hostage,
that could be considered an act of war.
Then let's get these other 19 countries
on the phone and come up with a plan.
A video was just uploaded
from inside the summit.
One world digital currency
will allow us to monitor
every movement our citizens make.
We will agree to President Sutton's plan.
How could they film this?
-It's got to be a deepfake.
-Doesn't matter.
It will create enough chaos
to devastate the currency markets.
[Jennifer] They uploaded another one.
We can use it to strengthen
our positions at the polls
or, uh, enrich ourselves in the process
and, uh, stay in power maybe indefinitely.
[Moseley] In a world where disinformation
is more powerful than information,
this will look very damning.
[distorted voice] That quick beige fox
jumped in the air over the thin dog.
-"Look out," I shouted...
-You were right.
The press are losing their heads.
[overlapping news chatter]
Your plan is working.
The crypto is multiplying.
[newswoman] ...cryptocurrency
what looks like tripling every 15 minutes.
[Rutledge] Yeah, making us billionaires.
Now all we need is the American president
to blow the doors off.
But where, oh, where can she be?
[tense music playing]
[Manny] Ma'am, it won't work
without a key card.
We could climb up here
and wait for someone to use it.
Min-Seo.
I'm just old woman.
-I'll only slow you down.
-Let's go.
-[clatter in distance]
-[gasps]
-[heavy footsteps]
-[men chattering]
-[man shouts]
-[woman screams]
-Let's go.
-Go. Go.
-Come on. Up, up.
-Here we go.
-Boost me up.
[Manny] One, two, three.
[grunting, straining]
[panting]
One, two, three.
[grunting]
[fabric ripping]
[dramatic music playing]
[Manny] Come on.
♪ ♪
[quiet chatter]
[elevator button beeps]
[elevator clanking]
[elevator whirring]
[pained grunt]
Bloody hell! Sorry.
-[elevator bell dings]
-[elevator clanking]
[whirring stops]
[Sutton shouts]
[grunting]
[screams]
Madam!
[straining]
-[straining]
-[Sutton shouts]
-[man choking]
-[grunting]
[gasping]
-Manny.
-[Everett groans]
[choking]
-Leave her!
-[man choking]
[Elena shouting in Italian]
[Manny choking]
[panting]
Good shot.
[grunts]
Thank you.
Madam, are you hurt?
Only my feelings.
[groans]
That was quite, uh...
...well done.
[elevator bell dings]
Thank you.
Okay, go.
We've got a key card.
Now we move.
Ma'am...
you should probably have this.
[picks up gun]
[gun racks]
[dramatic music playing]
Why aren't the police
storming in to save us?
It doesn't work like that.
Too many high-value hostages.
They just can't storm the gates.
All right, we just have to hang tight.
This is how your mom
would want us to play it.
Well, Mom would not just hang tight.
Mom would be doing something.
Yeah. Let's hope she is.
[watch chimes]
[Serena] Every network is down.
They must have jammed them.
There must be something, or the terrorists
wouldn't be able to get their message out.
I mean, they have to have
a hidden Wi-Fi network.
I mean, they have to.
The TVs were still working.
I can pull components
from the TV satellites,
and maybe we can hook a remote network.
You're gonna hook it?
Serena, wait.
[grunting]
[hushed] Hey, where are you going?
Serena.
Be careful.
Are you sure we're related?
♪ ♪
There's a shortcut
to the service entrance.
Okay.
[Elena] Hey, hey.
Wait a minute.
These shoes.
My stylist tried to put me
in a pair of those.
Had to veto it.
But I'm not as tall
and as confident as you.
I have to wear them.
All right. Two in the hallway.
I go first. You bring up the rear.
Okay.
Go.
[newsman] Continuing this hour with
our breaking news coverage of
the G20 summit takeover in South Africa.
Reports of chaos amongst the G20 nations
as they struggle to gather
the intel necessary
for a coordinated rescue mission
of world leaders.
[TV chatter continues indistinctly
in distance]
Though little is known about
the terrorists or the cells...
Hey. Since when did Suidlanders
take orders from an Aussie?
[man] Yeah, but it's working, bro.
Currency's crashing.
[newsman] ...Edward Rutledge, former
corporal in the Australian Defence Force.
[Rutledge] ...that America and her allies
intend to steal weaker nations' resources
and completely reset the monetary system.
This currency
that President Sutton is proposing,
it would mean the end of personal freedom.
But there is something we can do.
[gasps softly]
Pull your money from their banks,
and you invest in crypto
because it is the only currency
that they do not control.
[Sutton] They've got at least
five hostages in the kitchen.
They're working for
an Aussie named Rutledge.
He's telling people
to pull their money out of banks.
It'll crash the markets.
He may have shorted the currencies.
I'm-I'm sorry.
I'm a humanitarian, not a banker.
What does this mean?
It means we're being robbed.
If people pull their money out,
the value of the currencies will drop.
The more it drops, the more he makes.
We have to keep moving, madam.
I will not leave these people behind.
We have to help them.
The people in that kitchen
are not my job, madam.
Your survival is what matters most.
Okay? We can't save everyone.
But we can save the people in the kitchen.
I will not leave them.
And as president,
I do not need your permission, Manny.
But I do need your cooperation.
[tense music playing]
[mouth full] Ah, this is good, dude.
[timer bell ringing in distance]
What the hell is that?
Let's check it out, bro.
[gun racks]
What was that?
Huh? [speaks foreign language]
Huh?
[ringing continues]
You better tell me or I will shoot you
one by one.
-[ringing continues]
-[water boiling]
[man shouting angrily in distance]
[timer bell dings]
[water flowing]
[grunts] Enough of this!
Drop it!
[laughs]
Brilliant.
They're all out there looking for you.
But I get to bring you in myself.
You take your hands off the weapon.
Not a bloody chance.
[screams]
-[pained grunt]
-I said drop it.
[angry grunt]
[grunting]
[man groans]
[both grunting]
-[electricity crackling]
-[screaming]
[panting]
Where are you?
[pained grunting]
[water boiling]
[object clatters]
-[sizzling]
-[man screaming]
[Melokuhle] Quick, untie me.
[Lesedi] Here you go.
It's going to be okay.
[Melokuhle] Help me out here.
[hostages murmuring]
Madam!
[Sutton] Manny!
-Oh! Manny!
-[Manny] I'm hit.
-He's hit!
-[groaning]
-[Elena whimpers]
-He's hit. We got to move him.
Come on. Come on.
[Serena] Dad, it works like
an old-fashioned antenna.
[Derek] All right, but where did you learn
how to do this?
She got it from Mr. Robot.
Did not.
[Demetrius] He used a Pringles can.
Same thing.
Perfect.
Now, if this old-school antenna allows me
to connect to that old satellite dish,
I should be able to send
an outgoing message.
[Darden] They are out there,
and we will find them.
It's Darden.
[shushes]
[hushed] All right. Stay put.
-[Darden] You, check over there.
-[Derek] Something's not right.
Stay there.
[men chattering in distance]
Hey.
If anything, go up. Go up.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Darden] Look underneath it, too.
Come on.
Check behind the HVAC.
What was that?
I'm unarmed!
Step all the way out, Derek.
-All the way.
-[typing]
Slow.
How could you betray us like this?
My oath was not to you or to your wife.
-You betrayed your country.
-No.
Your wife betrayed my country
when she decided farmers in Africa
were more important
-than Americans!
-[computer beeps]
Where's Demetrius and Serena?
I don't know.
[tense music playing]
Move!
Move.
Where are they?
[Derek] I said I don't know.
But I do know she's real good
at escaping from you.
♪ ♪
[Darden] Where is the president, Derek?
[Derek] No idea.
[Darden] Fine. We'll do it the hard way.
Let's get him out of here.
[dramatic music playing]
-[Moseley] My God, it's chaos out there.
-[crowd clamoring over TV]
-How far out is our response?
-[Paulson] The CENTCOM USS carrier group
is approaching target, three hours out.
But even once they get there,
there's a problem.
Coordination with member nations
is lagging.
We got an email from
an unsecure network in Cape Town.
Someone claiming to be Serena Sutton.
-What's it say?
-Says her father's been apprehended,
but her mother is still on the loose.
-[cheering, murmuring]
-How do we know it's her?
She, uh...
She says "Agent Asshole Darden"
is behind all this.
Our agent?
[newswoman over TV] This just in.
The G20 member nations
and the South African government
have agreed on a coordinated response
to the terrorist attack,
which will ensure the safety of the world
leaders held there.
Sources tell us that elements
from the USS carrier group
are about three hours away,
off the coast of South Africa.
Time to cut off some bacon
from our little piggies over there.
[people murmuring, crying]
That'll bring her in.
[Manny breathing heavily]
[Sutton] It's still inside.
There's no exit wound.
So, gonna leave it in there.
Can you dress the wound?
Of course.
[Sutton] Hang in there, jarhead.
Okay. Okay.
[Elena] Hold still, okay?
You two are far too composed
for your job descriptions.
One might say the same for you, madam.
The South African government thought
well-placed operatives
among the staff made sense.
We're grateful to the both of you.
The honor is ours.
My husband and kids are missing.
I'd like to know that they're safe.
We'll find your family, madam.
[Melokuhle] Okay, take this.
Isn't this risky, using a radio?
The terrorists have not been
using the upper channels,
so we'll reach you on eight.
Okay.
Find them and take these people
someplace safe.
-Await my instructions.
-Yes, ma'am.
[people crying]
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
Australian Prime Minister Lowe.
Good news, mate.
You're getting out of here.
[people screaming, sobbing]
[groaning]
Look at what you made me do.
[Elena] Don't move. Don't move.
[water running]
How you holding up?
Um...
As well as can be expected.
[grunts]
You've been through
this kind of thing before.
[stammers]
Does it get any easier?
It was quiet at the beginning,
so I didn't see much combat.
But when I finally did...
...it was intense.
I was wounded,
carried a boy to safety,
and that was a photo that wound up
on the cover of Time magazine.
[gentle music playing]
Mm.
But what they didn't capture is...
...I had to pry...
...that child from his mom,
who was blown apart.
I was so scared.
I ran.
I just ran.
I walk around like I fought in a war.
[scoffs softly]
I was only there for a few minutes.
[stammers]
My country had a...
a war correspondent
who escaped from a POW camp
here in South Africa during the Boer Wars.
He, um...
yeah, he jumped a fence,
took a long walk, and then rose to fame
on his retelling of his escape.
Winston Churchill.
We get here how we can.
It's what we do here that matters.
[dramatic music playing]
-[Sutton grunting]
-[Manny] There it is.
Straight ahead.
-You drive.
-Okay.
[grunting]
Better than 007.
-[groans]
-[Sutton] Hurry. Let's go.
-[radio static crackles]
[Derek over radio] Danny.
Danny, can you hear me?
Derek.
Babe, a-are you hurt?
[panting] Oh, my God.
Derek.
No. No, I'm not.
Where are the kids?
[Derek] Baby, the kids are fine.
The kids are safe.
-[radio beeps]
-Okay...
[radio beeps]
President Danielle Sutton.
-Rutledge.
-Hey, you know my name.
Dead Russians in the elevator.
Dead Suidlanders in the kitchen.
You get around, don't you, girl?
I'll get around to you, too.
Good. Great. Come join me.
I'm in the ballroom.
I'll tell you where I am when you release
my husband and kids from the hotel.
No, no, no, my dear.
I've got two dead world leaders here,
and there'll be more
the longer you make me wait for you.
You'll tell me exactly where you are right
now or I'm gonna thumb Derek's eyes out.
And you can listen over the walkie.
Why would a mercenary take on the G20?
What?
Wait. You...
You call me a mercenary?
Lady, you fought a war over gasoline.
I served my country
just as I serve it now.
Yeah, blindly. You serve it blindly.
You were used by them then,
and they're using you now.
So you feel used?
That's why you terrorize the world
and crash markets?
We want to switch to cryptocurrency
so that you--
Bullshit.
This isn't about crypto.
You want to crash currencies and get rich.
This seems like something personal.
What... what are you after?
I'm after you.
[man] Come in, Karl.
Sutton's kids. Hallway six. Go, go, go.
But if you won't talk face-to-face, I'll
have the conversation with your children.
You don't have my children.
[Rutledge] Not yet.
But I'm looking at 'em
on-screen right now.
Derek, time to make yourself useful.
Tell the missus what you're looking at.
Darden is one of them.
-[grunts]
-[people gasping]
No! Stop!
-Leave him alone!
-[blow lands]
[people crying]
Again.
-[blows landing]
-[Derek grunting]
Derek, I love you.
Tell the children I love them.
Tell Dee he's my joy.
-Tell Serena I'm sorry.
-Oh.
I'm proud of who she is.
-[blows landing]
-[Derek grunting]
I'm in the underground garage.
-[radio beeps]
-[Derek groaning]
[pensive music playing]
They're coming for me.
[tires squealing]
♪ ♪
[inhales sharply]
[pained groaning]
What are you doing?
Where's the president?
Where's the president?!
[Everett] I'm just doing what I'm told.
-[Elena screams]
-[Manny grunts]
[Serena] Look, there's a door.
Maybe we can get out this way.
[radio beeps]
[Karl] It's Karl.
Heading to the pool. Over.
[playfully] Hello, kids.
Chilling by the pool, yeah?
Schvitzing in the sauna.
Yeah. Cool.
I can see you.
My little Schatzi.
[gunfire]
[grunting]
[Demetrius] Holy shit.
You're from Wakanda.
Your mother sent us.
[pensive music playing]
♪ ♪
[gun racks]
[vehicle door closes]
Agent Darden.
Madam President.
I'm unarmed.
All right. Let's move.
Who helped you?
I know you couldn't
pull this off on your own.
[tires squealing]
[stammers]
[choking]
Backstabbing piece of shit.
[tires squealing]
[panting]
You doing my job for me now? Huh?
Manny--
Don't play me like that!
All right?
Your back's against the wall, you tell me
so I can stand next to you, madam!
[vehicle door opens]
-The steering wheel's on the wrong--
-Nothing from you, Oliver!
You're in time-out!
[stammers, sighs]
[groaning]
[Sutton] I'm sorry.
You good, jarhead?
[panting]
-[radio static crackles]
-[Serena over radio] Mom?
Mom?
Serena?
Serena, are you okay? Is Dee okay?
Yes, yes. We're fine. We're fine.
-We're with Melokuhle.
-Don't say where.
They could be listening.
[panting]
I am so sorry.
No, Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything,
and I did not mean what I said.
[Sutton] I know. We'll get through this.
Okay?
Mom, but they took Dad.
What are we gonna do?
You're not gonna do anything.
I need you
and Dee to get out.
What if I can help?
I wish you could,
but I think we're way past that.
I need you--
For once, I need you to trust me.
To do what?
Maybe I can do that thing
you told me to never ever do again.
-S-Serena, I--
-But instead of going to the party,
I can bring the party to us.
She's talking about the key card reader.
The one she used to hack into our system.
What do you need to do that thing?
I need one of those machines.
The one that I have at home,
the one that you found.
That'd be in the lobby.
I think I can get one of those.
You hold tight, okay?
I love you, Mom.
I love you, too, baby girl.
[radio beeps]
Elena, you, Oliver, Min-Seo,
you're getting out of here.
Yes.
I'm sorry, I won't leave my husband.
I can't.
I understand. Okay.
Elena, you, Oliver,
that leaves you on the front lines.
-Yes.
-We've followed you this far.
We will do what's necessary.
But I'm driving.
[uplifting music playing]
All right.
Here's what we need to do.
What the...?
[indistinct radio chatter]
-[button clicks]
-[computer chimes]
A hostage is loose.
A small Asian lady.
Back lobby.
Now.
[Sutton] You think
my stylist would approve?
Kevlar goes with everything.
I'm talking about the pants.
Like I said,
camo goes with everything, madam.
[gentle music playing over speakers]
[whistles]
How many of these
do you have planted in the hotel?
[speaks Zulu]
That means "a lot" in Zulu.
[Lesedi] This is the second part
of your mother's plan.
We need to take out
the strategic defenses.
[Serena sighs]
We need to keep moving.
-Love you, Dee.
-Love you, too, sis.
[suspenseful music playing]
What the hell?
The president's limo
is headed for the gate.
[engine revving]
-Hey! Fire! Drop 'em!
-[gunfire]
[Everett and Elena grunting]
-[Everett] Oh, God!
-[Elena whimpers]
-We did it! We did it!
-Yes! Yes!
Yes! [exclaims]
-[panting]
-We made it.
We made it.
[Bousquet over radio] The U.S. president
is trying to breach the perimeter.
The missile launcher.
That's what it's for.
Target locked, sir.
[Rutledge] Fire!
-Eyes on!
-[agents murmuring]
We got movement.
Hold your fire!
That's one of ours.
[Elena screams]
-[men shouting]
-[rapid gunfire]
-[Bousquet] Missile off target.
-[Rutledge] That's why we have more.
Fire, goddamn it!
Fire!
-Oh, Christ.
-[bullets ricocheting]
Oh, my God.
[Everett] Oh, sweet Christ.
[man shouts]
Oh, Christ! Oh, Christ!
-Shut up, Oliver!
-Oh, Christ!
Hold your shit!
[screaming]
[Everett screams]
-[fire crackling]
-[agents murmuring]
[panting]
Ciao bello.
Ciao.
[laughing]
Any intel they pass on
is gonna quicken a reaction.
-We don't have much time.
-[Titos] Maybe it is time to lift off.
I need Sutton.
Barricade the garage
and disable all vehicles.
I need a 45 on the perimeter now.
Every country in the world's gonna be
planning a counteroffensive,
so I need you to move!
[tense music playing]
[Ledisi] Do you know
what "laduma" means in Zulu?
[Demetrius] What?
"Boom."
[grunting]
Let's go.
That came from inside.
They're inside!
Find the insurgents now!
[men shouting]
[quiet chatter]
That explosion was made
by our people on the inside
and part of the president's plan.
Now that we've disabled
the terrorists' main weapon,
we assemble a small strike force
to enter the hotel by the back entrance.
Serena will unlock those doors
in 12 minutes.
How do we know this'll work?
Look, we're on our bloody heels here,
but an evening spent following
your president has left me optimistic.
I urge you to follow her lead.
[both panting softly]
You know,
when I was running for office,
my campaign advisors...
...kept telling me to lean
into my military background.
I'm pretty sure
this is not what they meant.
-There it is.
-Okay.
[pained grunting]
Got it.
I hope this works.
Lobby. Hallways.
Power's all here.
We have to give Serena a fighting chance.
[sighs]
You're a good mom.
You make me cry, I'll kill you.
I always knew you were a softy, madam.
[chuckles]
[hopeful music playing]
I'll see you on the other side.
[Manny sighs]
You'll see me on this side, Danielle.
[Min-Seo sobbing, speaking Korean]
-[door opens]
-[Rutledge] Titos, come here.
-[door closes]
-[Titos] Rutledge, we have to go.
-[Rutledge] No, no. No, no, no.
-We have to get out of here.
-Shh. Shut up.
-[Titos] Listen--
[Rutledge] Shut up.
Shut up. Let me think.
You two, get up.
-Get up. Get 'em up!
-[Titos] Come! Move!
Get up!
-Get up. Come on.
-[Rutledge] Nobody gets in here!
Nobody gets out!
You stay in the fight no matter what!
This is not over.
[tense music playing]
[hushed] Manny, lights out.
[quiet murmuring]
We have lost power to the east wing.
[suspenseful music playing]
[panting softly]
What was that?
Look over there.
[panting]
[dramatic music playing]
[Serena gasps]
[murmurs softly]
[whispers] Go.
[man] Here!
[men grunting]
[man groans]
♪ ♪
[elevator whirring]
[elevator clanks]
[elevator bell chimes]
[Sutton gasping]
Let's dance, Madam President.
[gun clicking]
[♪ ZVRI &amp; Kususa featuring DJ Tira
play "Danger Zone"]
[grunting]
[urgent knocking on door]
[straining, grunting]
[yelling]
And where have you been? Something is--
-[grunting]
-[bone cracks]
[grunting continues]
[Serena] Restoring all cellular
and data communications.
♪ ♪
-[silenced gunshot]
-[man grunts]
[song continues in foreign language]
[yelling]
[screams, groans]
[choking]
[guttural groaning]
[Sutton panting]
[song ends]
[pensive music playing]
Manny, lights.
Manny.
Manny, wake up.
That's my boy.
[wheezing]
[dramatic music playing]
We're outside the service entrance.
And... rear doors.
[lock beeps]
[typing]
Hey.
Mom, watch out!
You realize she could have done that
the whole time, right?
Lucky you only got grounded.
She's kind of a badass, huh?
-[Rutledge] Danielle.
-Oh, my God.
[chuckles] Come get hubby.
Mom?
Mom, can you hear me?
[Sutton] What is it, my baby?
He has Dad in this big conference room.
He has a knife to his throat.
I'm on my way.
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunts]
[Rutledge] That'll do.
I'm here, okay?
You can let them go now.
-[Rutledge laughs] No, no.
-[muffled pleading]
I don't think so.
Oh, you're so much
less formidable in person.
I was gonna say the same about you.
Yeah, but look. [sniffs]
-I am glad we're all here together.
-[muffled whimper]
Sit.
I mean, that was your plan, wasn't it?
Get your gang of 20 together.
[sets gun on table]
Rob the world.
-Hmm?
-You're the thief.
You know nothing about me.
Less than nothing.
Corporal Edward Rutledge, I know you.
You're the soldier who never came home.
You left your blood, sweat
and heart on the field,
and you came back a shell of a man.
You want to control,
you want to have power,
but that's not gonna make you a leader.
I don't need to be a leader.
I don't want to be a leader.
What I want is a voice.
But when you have the actions of a tyrant,
no one's gonna hear your voice.
That's why I need to borrow yours.
So why don't you quit squawking at me
and read that.
They'll never believe it.
Read this right now.
-You read it or he's dead.
-[muffled grunt]
Read it!
[Derek] Mm-mm.
Mm-mm.
"That quick beige fox jumped in the air
-over each thin dog."
-[sighs]
-[video replaying quietly]
-[Rutledge] Good.
"'Look out,' I shout,
'for he's foiled you again...'"
"'...creating chaos.'"
You're broken.
I don't know what you saw,
I don't know how you suffered,
but your damage is gonna
swallow the world.
Don't do this.
[computer trilling]
[hushed] On me. Go.
[garbled radio chatter]
[gasps]
Masks off.
They're in. It worked.
[Adwi] Preparing to breach the ballroom
in three, two, one.
[lock beeps]
[people screaming]
Three, two, go!
Everybody, down!
Down!
[dramatic music playing]
Get down!
Move!
[men shouting]
-Clear!
-Are you okay, madam?
-Yeah, yeah.
Clear!
[people sobbing]
[Adwi] Ballroom's secure.
Assessing casualties.
[Moseley] Do we know POTUS's status?
Two world leaders,
Australia and South Korea,
killed in action.
The American president missing.
They don't know where she is.
She's in the conference room!
Go!
I'll go.
What? No.
-Block the doors.
-No.
I'll-I'll lead them to her.
-Serena, no! You can't!
-I got it!
[Rutledge laughing]
Hey, Danielle.
It's happening. [laughing]
[newsman over tablet] If you're just
joining us this hour,
we have breaking news.
[Rutledge] Our worlds are flipping.
[newsman] Despite the White House's claim
that this viral video is a deepfake,
its effects on the market
have been immediate,
causing a financial bloodbath.
[Sutton over video] Our digital
currency...
[Titos] 150 billion.
Soldiers of a goddamn fortune.
[Sutton over video] ...and get
foreign citizens in their countries...
[Titos] We did it.
Start the bird, all right?
Grab anyone still vertical.
We're wheels up in five.
Go. Go, go.
[Sutton over video] We will,
in a very real sense,
own the world.
People will never believe this.
[laughing]
Oh, yeah, they'll believe it.
They'll believe it just like they believed
the big lie that got you elected.
See, Danielle...
...I know you.
Yeah.
I was there.
Fallujah.
I was in the caravan ahead of you...
...clearing IEDs off the road,
and a bomb made just for you Americans
killed two of my brothers.
My best mates.
You know what's worse than
losing your mates in a war zone?
It's knowing that you never should've
been there in the first place.
I stood in the same dark place as you,
and I came back.
-And I chose a life.
-[scoffs]
I chose service.
You chose destruction and death.
You made the most of it, didn't you?
You plucked a kid
out of the rubble that you'd created.
You got a photo taken,
and you came home to a hero's welcome.
But you're no hero.
I see you for what you are.
You're a fake. You're a fraud.
You're a fake president.
I see you for what you are, too,
and you're never gonna make it
out of here alive.
Oh, I'm gonna change the world,
and the world is gonna see you
for the liar and cheat that you are.
I am who I say I am!
And you're not gonna change anything
because I won't let you!
-[yelling]
-[grunting]
[groaning]
I win.
No!
[muffled screaming]
[both grunting]
Hey, Danny, changed my mind.
I mean this.
-Thank you for your serv--
-[shouts]
-[screams, groans]
-[speaks Korean]
[speaks Korean]
-[Rutledge groaning]
-[speaks Korean]
[sniffles]
[somber music playing]
[sobbing softly]
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
[gasps]
-Just give me a minute, babe.
-[sighs]
Oh, my God. Don't move.
[Sutton gasps]
-[sighs, laughs]
-I'm okay.
-Oh. I love you.
-[grunts]
Danielle!
He's gone! He's gone!
-[Derek] Oh, yeah.
-[Min-Seo] I'll stay with him.
Thank you.
[Min-Seo speaking quietly]
[grunts]
[Joanna panting]
[Joanna] Danielle.
Thank God.
[panting]
You sure you don't want to join him, Jo?
What?
You were their inside man.
[chuckles] What are you saying?
You chose the location, Pax Security.
[chuckles] No.
I just saw you hide his wallet.
You did it all.
I can't believe it took me this long
to put it all together.
How dare you judge me?
I played the cards I was dealt.
You sold us out.
My family. My children.
And you stole my destiny.
I didn't steal anything.
I worked my entire life
for the job you took.
It was mine, and I was forced to sit
and watch you walk into it
as if it belonged to you!
[slap]
[shouts]
[sobbing]
I was elected...
coward.
[door opens]
Mom!
[Demetrius sobbing]
H-He took her. H-He took Serena.
She went looking for you.
I saw him on the camera.
-He dragged her off.
-Stay here.
[dramatic music playing]
[Rutledge] Come on.
[angry muttering]
[mutters]
In.
Get in!
Watch it.
[panting]
[grunts]
Oh, quit it, you little shit.
[engine powering up]
-You're not getting away with this.
-Shut up.
[hopeful music playing]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[laughing]
You're too late, darling.
You still need this?
You can't access the money
without it, can you?
[Rutledge] No, no. No, no.
No! No!
[dramatic music playing]
Give me the wallet now or I'm gonna
blow your little girl's head off.
-Give it!
-Take me!
Let her go!
They won't shoot me out of the sky.
All right.
Wallet first.
Put the gun on the deck now.
That's it.
Now you come to me.
Don't you pull any shit
or I'll put a bullet straight between
your eyes, I swear to God.
You want change, you start with yourself,
not with a crypto wallet.
Yeah, let's just start with the wallet
and see where I end up, eh?
-[Sutton grunts]
-No!
[shouts, groans]
[shouts]
[yells]
-Got to get you out.
-[pained grunt]
-Mom! Behind you!
-[grunts]
Just go!
-All right. Get down. Get down.
-[Serena screams]
-[Serena] Come on!
-[Sutton] I'm trying.
Lift off the ground!
You know I'm not a pilot!
[gunshot]
[Serena] Oh, my God! Come on!
-All right! Try to break free! Serena!
-I'm trying!
-[Rutledge grunts]
-[Serena screams]
[Serena and Rutledge screaming]
[people gasping, murmuring]
Team! Move!
[panting]
[grunting]
Mom!
[people gasping, murmuring]
[Serena] Get him! Come on!
[Serena screaming]
No! No!
No!
[grunts]
[metal creaking]
[Sutton grunts]
-[Serena shouts]
-[Rutledge grunts]
-[Sutton] No!
-Mom!
[wind whistling]
[panting]
[somber music playing]
[uplifting music playing]
Grab my hand.
[both grunting]
[Sutton] We got to climb out.
We can't move! It won't hold!
-[Serena] It's okay, Mom.
-Come here.
[sobs softly]
Mom, you are really something special.
[metal clanking, creaking]
You, too, baby girl. You, too.
[men shouting]
[Adwi] Pull up!
One, two, three!
Pull!
[men straining]
[Adwi] Everyone, pull!
It's working!
[men straining]
[uplifting music playing]
[men speaking urgently, straining]
[Derek] Serena.
Let's go.
[people cheering, applauding]
Danny.
Your hand, Madam President.
[cheering and applause continue]
[cheering wildly]
[choir singing uplifting music
in foreign language]
-[♪ Asiahn sings "Higher"]
-♪ Hold your head up,
don't you back down now ♪
♪ You know you'll make it out somehow ♪
♪ Soak it all in,
let the pressure move you ♪
♪ Been through worse, so get out my way ♪
-Congratulations, Madam President.
-♪ Standing strong ♪
-[applause]
-♪ Don't care what they say ♪
♪ Drown it all out,
let the voices build your strength ♪
♪ Let's go higher, higher ♪
♪ than we've ever gone before ♪
♪ Let's get higher, higher ♪
♪ What are you waiting for? ♪
♪ There's no way they can stop us now ♪
♪ We've already left the ground ♪
♪ Let your wings soar now ♪
♪ Higher, higher ♪
♪ 'Cause there's no way
they can stop us now ♪
♪ We've already left the ground ♪
♪ Let your wings soar now ♪
♪ Feel the pain, let it drive your grind ♪
♪ No ill words, keep 'em out your mind ♪
♪ Just go hard,
let the moment pull you in ♪
That's a good look.
♪ You are way stronger than you know ♪
♪ Don't look back, you can let it go ♪
♪ Victory's close,
so don't you give up now ♪
♪ Let's go higher, higher ♪
♪ than we've ever gone before ♪
♪ Let's get higher, higher ♪
♪ What are you waiting for? ♪
♪ There's no way they can stop us now ♪
♪ We've already left the ground ♪
♪ Let your wings soar now ♪
♪ Higher, higher ♪
♪ 'Cause there's no way
they can stop us now ♪
♪ We've already left the ground ♪
♪ Let your wings soar now ♪
♪ Higher, higher ♪
♪ 'Cause there's no way
they can stop us now ♪
♪ We've already left the ground ♪
♪ Let your wings soar now ♪♪
[dramatic music playing]
♪ ♪
[gentle music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
♪ ♪
[gentle music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
♪ ♪
[music ends]