Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[Chrissy humming]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
Yeah! [giggles]
It's me, Chrissy. [honks]
Vroom, vroom, vroom!
[giggles]
-Is the tub full of water?
-Yep.
-Got the bubbles?
-Extra towels?
-Extra extra.
Let's do it.
Chrissy! It's time for your…
-Huh?
-[both] Chrissy?
[Chrissy] No bath time!
[giggles]
Can't catch me!
Get back here, you little hubcap! It's…
[Chrissy reading text]
[Mama] All right,
you've got nowhere to go!
Let's all just go home
and take a nice, warm bath.
No!
[tires screeching]
Whee!
[both] Uh-oh.
Ready for that bath?
No, thank you.
[Chrissy giggling]
[both] Huh?
[Papa] Go, go, go!
Stay on her tail.
I'll cut her off at the pass!
Huh? Why aren't you in school?
Why aren't you at work?
Touché.
Come back here!
-[chuckling]
-Huh?
I'm gonna get you!
[gasps] No, no, no!
I got ya! I got ya! I…
don't got ya.
You fall for that every time.
Just catch that toddler.
Get back here, Chrissy!
[inhales, exhales]
Another peaceful day in Bumperton Hills.
Chrissy!
Hey, slow down!
[siren wailing]
[upbeat jingle playing]
Hey! Slow down.
[Chrissy giggling]
Hey, get back here!
Hi, Wilder!
Hi, Chrissy!
Bath time?
Bath time.
Good luck!
You too. Call me later!
She's getting away, Mrs. C.
Not helpful, Halle.
[Chrissy] Whee!
Can't catch me!
Ah-ha!
[exclaims, giggles]
[Chrissy] Yeah!
[Chrissy, slowed-down] Whee!
Huh? Aw.
-Get her, honey!
-[gasps]
[Mama exclaims]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-[splash]
-[Papa winces]
-[Mama] Gotcha!
-[Chrissy] Aw!
Tub's almost full.
All right, Chrissy.
You ready?
No.
Come on. It's your turn to take a bath.
Then me next!
[chuckles] What? I love baths.
Maybe you could teach Chrissy
to love baths too.
What do you think?
Huh?
Whoa. She's good.
-Chrissy!
[giggling]
[Chrissy reading on-screen text]
[Papa humming]
-[giggles]
-Hmm?
Whoa! Amazing!
-Amazing?
-Look!
A box?
Huh? No!
Pretend.
See?
Box… with drawing?
Box? No!
House. Come inside.
Uh, it's dark. Can't see.
[Chrissy] Hold on.
Better?
[gasps]
Wow!
[Chrissy] Come here.
What's this?
TV! Use the remote.
What?
Pretend!
Oh.
[imitates static]
Time to go downstairs.
-[Chrissy hums]
-[laugh track]
[gasps, laughs]
Now, Chrissy with the weather.
Up next, tornado!
[laughing]
[beeping]
I am a robot. Ah!
[laughing]
Ah, beep! Robot!
Tornado!
Now what?
Hmm…
Oh! [giggles]
It's just a hole.
Not a hole. Mirror!
Huh?
[giggles]
[gasps]
[both blubbering]
-Boo!
[yelping]
-Ah!
-[thud]
[grunts] What now?
Hmm. Uh-oh.
What?
What is it?
Volcano!
[sizzling]
Hot!
-Huh?
-Pretend.
Oh.
We're trapped.
Hmm.
[Chrissy] Way out!
Let's jump. Ready?
[Chrissy grunting]
[Chrissy] Whoo!
Aw, broken.
Hmm.
[gasps] I know!
[whimsical music]
Pirate ship! Ahoy, matey.
Arr, matey!
We sail!
Choppy water, choppy water, choppy water.
Huh? Whoa!
[giggles] What's next?
Hmm. Oh!
[gasps] No more marker!
No…
All done.
Aw.
[gasps] I know!
Close your eyes and pretend real hard.
[both straining]
[gasps] Look!
[gasps] Yay! Pretend!
-Let's go!
-Hold on.
[both giggling] Whee!
Yeah!
[Chrissy giggling]
Hi, Carley!
Hey, Chrissy. You look so cute
bouncing on that trampoline.
[gasps]
Really?
Of course. Chrissy.
You are just the cutest thing ever!
[gasps]
I'll see you later.
[giggles]
I'm so cute!
-[Carley] Hey, Bobby.
-Huh?
What you doin'?
Blowin' dandelions? Makin' wishes?
[spluttering]
You are just the cutest thing ever!
What?
[giggles] Thank you.
-Aw! [chuckles]
-[Bobby giggles]
-[dramatic music]
-[chuckles]
[gasps]
[Chrissy reading text]
-[Bobby blowing]
-Keep trying, little guy. You can do it.
Oh, hello.
Whoa, whoa!
So cute!
Hmm.
-[Bobby pretending to cry]
-Aw!
Did someone fall down?
Looks like someone needs some holdin'.
-[Chrissy] Woof! Woof! Woof!
-Oh!
Aw! You're a little puppy!
[Bobby sulks]
-Meow, meow, meow.
-Huh?
-Aw!
So cute.
Woof! Woof! Woof!
-Meow.
-[grumbles]
Cute!
[Chrissy] Carley!
Yes, cutie?
[sneezes]
Oh, gesundheit.
[hiccuping]
Oh! [laughs] Excuse you.
[sneezes]
Gesundheit.
Gesundheit. I mean, excuse you!
So cute. All so cute!
Yes, cutie?
-You're giving me candy?
-[Chrissy clears throat]
Oh, you're giving me money?
Thank you?
[Bobby blows noisemaker]
So cute!
[drumming, humming]
Oh, I love it!
[overlapping drumming]
Yeah!
Oh, I-- I don't know that song.
-[techno music]
-Cute!
-[techno music playing]
-Um…
[playing classical music]
Oh, is that Beethoven?
Uh, this is all so very cute.
-[Bobby] Ahem.
-Huh?
-What is it, Bobby?
-I lo-lo-love…
What do you love, Bobby?
Don't you dare.
I love you, Carley.
-[gasps]
[chuckling]
[grumbling]
[Carley] That is the cutest thing ever!
[both] Huh?
What is it?
Well, you see, my dad
was gonna throw it out, but I saved it.
Because it reminded me of you.
Timeless.
Oh, Brett!
You are the cutest!
-[gasping]
-Thanks, Carley.
Wanna go help me
add it to my gallery space?
[laughs] Okay.
-Teenagers.
[Chrissy reading text]
Snacky snack!
Here you go, Chrissy.
I got you a special treat.
Yay!
Raisins!
Huh? Raisins?
Yuck. [groans]
Nice try, but raisins are good for you,
and makes Mommy feel better
about that milkshake I gave you yesterday.
[gasps] Cookie!
[giggles]
[gasps]
Hmm.
Yay!
[exclaims]
[gasps] Whoa!
Come back, cookie!
[whistling]
-Ah!
-Bye, Papa.
Bye! [sighs]
-Hi, Papa.
-Ah!
[horn blowing]
Hi!
Oh, hello there, Chrissy.
Chasing a cookie in a jar, I see.
I remember the first time
I chased a sugary snack.
Fastest crumb cake I ever--
Don't mean to be rude,
but I'm going left. Bye!
Bye, Mr. Coaltrain!
Hope you catch your cookie!
Come back!
[Chrissy panting]
Hey, wait up.
Whoa! Whoa!
Wait for me!
Gotcha!
Huh?
-[kids clamoring]
-[horn honks]
Hey, kids. Who wants a healthy snack?
Huh?
Ooh!
-Cookies!
[all] Cookies!
[chuckles] What? Cookies?
No. I brought oranges.
[kids clamoring] Cookies! Cookies!
I, uh…
I-- I don't have any cookies!
-[wailing]
-[honking horns]
Cookies!
[yelling]
[panting]
[exhales]
[Chrissy babbling]
[yells]
Please don't eat me!
I'm not as sweet as I look!
-Ah-ha!
-[gasps]
Oh no!
[exclaiming]
[slowed down] Oh no!
Aw.
[Mama gasps]
You ate all your raisins!
Good job, Chrissy.
I think you deserve a cookie.
[gasps] Cookie!
Here you go.
-Huh?
-The last oatmeal raisin cookie.
Raisins?
What?
♪ Baby Unicar! Colors so bright! ♪
♪ Travels the universe… ♪
[gasps]
♪ Baby Unicar! Colors so bright!
Travels the uni-- ♪
[Papa] Chrissy!
Now, you know we don't draw on the wall…
Huh?Is that me?
Aw. Wait.
[blubbers] No. No drawing on the wall.
[gasps] Put the chalk down.
That is not what I meant!
Chrissy, I'm warning you.
That's it! Time out!
No!
[Chrissy reading text]
Okay, you need to stay
on the couch until time out is over.
I'm setting this timer for five minutes.
You can get up
when the face goes from sad to happy.
I'll be just in the other room.
[timer ticking]
[scoffs]
♪ Baby Unicar! Colors so bright! ♪
Hmm?
[scoffs] Whatever.
♪ Travels the universe
Making wrongs right ♪
[groans]
Hmm.
[gasps] Ooh.
No, no.
[gasps] Yay, ball!
[giggles]
Ow!
Hmm…
-[Papa] Uh-uh-uh.
-Ah!
[Chrissy] Eek!
Stay on the couch until time out is over.
But, Papa--
No more talking, please.
[wails]
Yeah!
♪ Baby Unicar! Colors so bright! ♪
Yes! Baby Unicar!
♪ Travels the universe making-- ♪
[gasps] Oh no!
No TV during time outs.
Aw…
[ticking grows louder]
[groans]
Well, at least it comes off easy.
My trunk's not that big.
Hmm.
[Chrissy whimpering]
[ticking echoes]
[exclaiming]
[ringing]
All done!
♪ Baby Unicar! Colors so-- ♪
[gasps] Papa?
Oh! Uh…
I was just fixing it.
-No, you see, Chrissy, I was just--
-That's it! Time out!
No!
[sighs] Fair is fair.
Okay, Papa.
Don't leave couch until sad to happy.
Uh, Chrissy, you set it for an hour.
Uh-uh-uh!
No more talking, please. Bye-bye.
Oh boy.
-[Mama] Where to next, everybody?
-Last one to the ball pit's a rusty car!
-Woo-hoo!
-[Chrissy] Huh?
Ooh!
Chrissy want!
-Wow!
-[gasps]
Bobby Mini Van.
Chrissy Carson. Hmm.
Are you two eyeing
that big Baby Unicar toy?
One hundred tickets is a lot,
but it's worth it
'cause it's our last one.
-[gasps]
-It's on!
[Chrissy reading text]
[video game] Three, two, one, go!
Oh, yay!
Oh no!
Banana peel.
[groans]
Energy boost!
Yay, boost!
You got fourth place!
Yay, tickets!
Aww.
Only one ticket?
-[chiming]
-Huh?
New high score!
Tickets, tickets, tickets.
[gasps]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hmm.
Huh?
Whee!
[chuckling]
-Yay, tickets!
-[chiming]
-[Bobby chuckles]
-Huh?
Baby Unicar, here I come!
[attendant over PA] Hey, Mike's Carcaders.
Last chance to bring your tickets in
to exchange them for a prize!
[Chrissy chuckles]
Baby Unicar is mine!
-No. Mine.
-[video game] Get ready!
Three, two, one, go!
[exciting rock music plays]
Best banana I've ever had.
-Whoops!
-[exclaiming]
Oh, banana peel!
Enjoy your banana, Chrissy!
Oh no!
Hey!
-Hey!
-Energy boost!
Finished!
Hey, you two.
What prizes can I get you today?
[both] Baby Unicar!
Whoa! Okay. I'm gonna go count these up.
-Yeah!
Okay, here come your prizes.
Yes!
-What?
-Pencils?
Sorry, guys.
You both only have 50 tickets each.
Pencils are all you can get.
[both] Aw.
Maybe if you put your tickets together,
you could share the Baby Unicar toy?
-Share?
[growls]
[fumes]
Hmm.
[both] Whee!
[Chrissy reading text]
Hmm.
-[gasps] Found you!
-Aw.
[Chrissy giggles]
Found you!
-Found you!
-Whoa!
How'd you do that?
Chrissy best hide and seeker.
-She is pretty good.
-Mm-hmm.
Well, we'll see who's the best.
Now it's my turn to seek
and I'm gonna find you all in no time.
Not Chrissy!
Chrissy, if I can't find you,
you can have cookies for dinner.
-Cookies!
-Papa!
Oh! Uh, I mean… Uh…
-One, two…
-Quick!
-Three, four, five…
-Let's hide in here!
Oh, I know!
[Papa] …eight, nine, ten.
Ready or not, here I come!
Ah-ha!
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
Hmm.
Found you!
-Aw!
-Huh?
-I thought you'd never find me here.
-[Papa chuckles]
-Let's find the others.
-Okay.
-If we split up, we can cover more ground.
-Good idea.
Whew.
Huh? Eh.
[Chrissy panting]
Papa! Did you find anything?
Nothing so far.
[Cory humming]
[Chrissy] Uh…
Any luck?
Nothing downstairs.
All right. Let's keep looking.
[giggles]
-Huh?
-Ah!
[clattering]
-Chrissy!
-[Papa] What?
-[Cory] It came from the closet!
-Chrissy, they're coming!
-Found you.
-[chuckles]
[scoffs] Looks like
they found us, Chrissy.
Huh?
Chrissy? She was just here.
Looks like Chrissy's
better than you thought.
What? She just got lucky! We'll find her.
Chrissy?
Hmm, Chrissy?
-Chrissy!
[both] Huh?
[both giggle]
-[Cory, Papa] Ah-ha!
-Ah!
-What?
-Freddie, why are you in my house?
I'm playing hide and seek with Kimmy
and Timmy. They'll never find me here.
Well, good luck!
Chrissy!
-Chrissy!
Oh, she's not here!
She's nowhere!
-What should we do?
-I don't know where else to look.
[light squeaks]
-What?
-Was that her?
[Chrissy giggles]
-[loud clattering]
-[all] Huh?!
How is she doing this?
[Papa whimpers]
Just give up, Papa!
Okay, you win!
Chrissy, you're the best at hide and seek!
Chrissy best!
Cookie, please.
Chrissy scares me sometimes.
-Yeah.
-Me too.
[giggling]
[Chrissy reading text]
Whoa!
[Chrissy] Yay!
Cannonball!
-[giggling]
-Huh?
Chrissy?
Boo!
Splashy!
Cannonball!
Whoa, you keep jumping like that
and there won't be any water left!
Time to head home, Chrissy.
Say goodbye to Catalina.
-[Catalina pouts]
-One more!
Okay, just one more.
I'm gonna say goodbye to Cat's mom.
Okay!
[chanting] Cannonball! Cannonball!
-Cannonball!
-Huh?
Cannonball! Cannonball!
No wheel.
No cannonball.
Huh? No cannonball?
Need…
wheels!
Those kids just love being in the water.
They sure do.
-[wind rushing]
-Huh?
[giggles]
Whoa!
Cannonball!
-[Catalina] Whoa!
-Huh?
Too slow.
Hmm… Oh!
Huh?
[Catalina] Uh…
[Chrissy chuckling]
[Chrissy] Ooh!
Uh, Chrissy?
-Huh?
-I…
[Catalina] Whoa!
[Catalina] Whee!
Whoa!
[Catalina] Hello!
Oh, hello there, little boat.
Wait, a boat?
[Chrissy panting] Uh…
[Coaltrain] She went that way!
What?
[yelling]
Hi.
Chrissy!
[laughing]
-Nice circle!
-How are we gonna make this triangle?
[both] Perfect!
[both] Huh?
[both] Whoa!
-Can't stop.
-Oh no!
[Chrissy gasps, strains]
Huh?
[straining]
-Huh?
-[Chrissy and Catalina laughing]
What the…
A boat?! But…
my boat!
Oh no! My masterpiece! Ah!
[Chrissy] Whee!
Wait! Wait! No, no, no!
-Huh?
-Hi, Cory.
Uh…
-[Chrissy, Catalina] Whoa!
-Whew.
[Cory] No!
[both chanting] Cannonball! Cannonball!
Huh? Uh-oh.
Can we please have crumpets for dinner?
[laughs] Maybe when boats fly.
Huh?
Hello.
Woo-hoo!
[both laughing]
-Cannonball!
-All right, see you next week.
-See you then.
Chrissy?
-Cannonball!
[both giggling]
[Mama] Sweet dreams, Chrissy.
[Chrissy reading text]
[Chrissy murmuring]
[laughing]
Ooh, it's me!
Ahh!
[babbling]
[giggling]
-[imitates car engine]
-Hi! I'm Honkin' Henry!
[clattering]
[Mama] Chrissy, is that you?
[Chrissy gasps] Uh-oh!
[Chrissy] Shh!
[Mama] Huh? What was that?
Hmm, oh well.
[Chrissy giggles]
-Whoa!
-[Mama humming]
[Chrissy humming]
[Chrissy giggles]
Float?
[laughs] No float.
[toilet flushing]
[Papa] Hmm, now it just needs
a really funny joke.
Let's see what's on the internet.
[Papa scatting]
[Chrissy] Ooh, popcorn!
[Papa] ♪ A great idea will come to me ♪
[Chrissy chewing happily]
Ooh, someone commented
on my new profile pic!
[Chrissy gasps] Uh-oh!
Out of popcorn already? Hmm.
I should probably take
a power nap before lunch.
[Chrissy giggles]
[Chrissy panting]
Whee!
Whoa!
"You're late again, Chrissy?"
Get off my bumper, Bobby.
Are we doing it or not?
[Mama] …additional concrete
to support the new structure.
Oh, hold on, Julia,
I need to take this call.
Hi, hon, it's me, Papa.
Have you seen my snuggle socks?
Top drawer.
Wait, are you about to take a nap?
Uh--
[laptop chimes]
I'm back. Let's open the blueprints
and take a look at the foundation.
[Chrissy giggles]
-Hi, Chrissy.
-Hi, Wilder.
Chrissy.
Bobby Mini Van.
One and a two and a three, four, five.
[playing rock song]
[Chrissy vocalizing]
[repeating] ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah! ♪
[alarm rings]
Huh? [gasps]
Nap time is over!
Time to roll!
Bye, Wilder!
Bye, Chrissy.
Chrissy.
Bobby Mini Van.
[Chrissy] Whoa!
[Chrissy grunts]
[gasps] Uh-oh!
Okay.
[Mama] Hi, sleepyhead.
[Chrissy yawns]
-Did you have a good nap?
-Yep!
Come sit with Mama.
[grunts] You're getting so big.
Don't you grow up too fast, okay?
[giggles]
-Wait. Did you just wink at yourself?
-Yep.
[Chrissy reading text]
[humming]
[hiccups]
[hiccups] Uh-oh!
Almost finished.
I just need to draw
a perfectly straight line.
Yes. Almost there.
-Yes.
-[Chrissy hiccups]
Ah! Oh, Chrissy. You scared me.
-[hiccups]
-Aw.
Do you have a case of the hiccups?
I have just the thing. Drink some water.
[gasps, hiccups]
-Aw.
-Hmm…
Oh, I know. Let's try this.
Now take a drink of water.
Uh, what's going on?
Oh. [chuckles]
I'm just helping Chrissy cure her hiccups.
[hiccups]
Oh. Well, I have an idea.
My mom always gave me
a spoonful of sugar to cure my hiccups.
Sugar!
I don't know if that'll work.
Papa, let's try.
-I guess--
-Sugar! [slurps]
[smacks lips]
[hiccups]
Hmm, maybe it wasn't sugar.
Salt? Maybe mustard? Not vinegar.
Pickle juice didn't work.
[groans, hiccups]
-Let's try ground pepper.
-[Cory] Oh no.
Did the fridge break again?
No, we're just trying
to get rid of Chrissy's hiccups.
Oh, my mom has a neat trick for that.
You just have to hold your breath
for ten seconds.
[inhales]
[hiccups, sneezes]
That was a neat trick.
-[hiccups]
-Oh, Chrissy! Do you have the hiccups?
Mm-hmm.
A good laugh
always gets rid of them for me.
What do you call a sick train?
A-choo-choo train!
-[Papa clears throat]
-[hiccups]
The best way to get rid of hiccups
is by scaring them away.
Boo!
Did it work?
[hiccups]
When I get the hiccups, I fly corkscrews
through the air. That always helps.
We have an idea!
[Chrissy] Whoa!
Spin 'em out!
[Chrissy murmuring woozily]
[gasps] They're gone!
[all cheer]
[hiccup]
[all] Aw.
Heat helps me.
[hiccups]
Cold gets rid of mine.
Swinging should get rid of 'em.
[yelling]
Still nothing?
[hiccups]
You'll just have to bounce them out.
Yeah! [hiccups]
Have you tried singing?
-My mom gave me a spoonful of sugar--
-Yeah, we tried that.
-[overlapping chatter]
-[hiccups] Aw.
[Frannie chuckling]
This mask will definitely
scare those hiccups out of Chrissy.
Now, where is she?
-Hmm? [hiccups]
-Ahh!
[all yelling]
[giggling]
Huh? [gasps]
Hiccups gone!
-Really?
-They're gone?
Ha!
I knew laughter would do the trick.
-[hiccups
-[all gasp]
[all hiccuping]
Uh-oh.
[Chrissy reading text]
Whoa! [Chrissy laughs]
Look at me! Look at me!
Oh!
Don't look at me.
-[laughs] Woo-hoo!
-Whee!
Hot chocolate.
Get your hot chocolate here!
What a nice day to go sledding.
Ooh, hot chocolate. Yummy!
Papa!
-Sorry!
-Sledding!
Whoa, slow down, Chrissy. Wait for me.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Okay! Okay!
[Chrissy gasps] Wow!
[Papa gasps] Yikes!
[chuckles]
Uh, uh-- [exclaiming]
Uh, Chrissy, people say the best part
of sledding is actually the view.
Why don't we just stay up here
and get some hot chocolate?
Huh? Hmm.
They've got marshmallows!
Yummy.
Thank you. Huh?
[Chrissy humming]
Wait! Chrissy!
Oh, no, no, no!
Yeah!
-[Chrissy laughing]
-[Papa spluttering]
Oh no!
[overlapping yelling]
[Chrissy] Whee!
-[Chrissy] Whee!
-[Papa yelps]
Yeah!
Chrissy!
Whee!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
[groaning woozily]
[coughing, spluttering]
Chrissy! Wait, wait, wait. No! No! No! No!
[Papa chortling]
[Papa] Oh, ho, ho!
Huh? Santa?
I think that's my dad.
Your dad is Santa?
[groaning]
Pretty!
[Papa chuckles] You know what?
The best part of sledding
really is the view.
My hot chocolate!
Whee!
-[Papa grunting]
-Whoo!
[Papa exclaiming]o
[sighs in satisfaction]
Finally. Open for business.
[Papa yelling]
[frustrated groan]
[Papa panting]
[gasps] Hot chocolate!
[Chrissy reading text]
-Uh, hmm…
-Play time!
Huh? Sorry, Chrissy, I can't.
I have a lot of work to do.
Oh, maybe you could go play
with Mama and Cory?
Aw.
-You get to draw two cards.
-Oh.
-Play time!
-Chrissy!
-We're actually in the middle of a game.
-Yeah, ages five and up.
-Maybe you can play with Papa?
-Papa no play time.
Hmm. Oh!
-Use this!
-Remote?
It's a super remote!
It lets you control someone
like you control the TV. Watch. Hey, Cory!
Oh, hey, is that super remote?
-We haven't played that game in--
-Pause!
-[gasps]
-It's just pretend.
But the rule  is that you have to
play along no matter what. Play!
…years.
I remember the fun we used to…
Hey! Who put this banana in my card pile?
[Chrissy, Mama laughing]
Have fun, kiddo.
[cackling]
Nice job distracting her.
You never do stuff like that to me,
do you?
-Uh, who wants nachos?
-Oh, me!
-Play time!
-Chrissy, I said I have--
-Super remote.
-What! Who told you about--
Pause!
[giggling]
-Play.
-…super remote?
Just don't use it on me, okay?
Huh? Where did my pencil go?
[Chrissy laughing]
Very funny,
but I need to get back to work.
This comic
is gonna take forever to finish.
Hmm. Huh!
Fast forward.
Done. Bye, Mr. Pencil! I'm hungry.
Time for a snack! See you later, Chrissy!
Wait! Play time!
Hi, whatcha doing? Making nachos?
None for me. Ketchup. Corn. Pan. No.
-Nothing like a cold glass of juice!
-Pause.
[Papa whimpering]
[Papa groans]
-Play.
-Oh, it's spilled everywhere!
-You two look like you're having fun.
-Mama, play time!
I can't. I gotta get back to my game.
Hmm!
Rewind.
Whoa! [Mama speaking in reverse]
[laughing] Huh?
Looking for this?
Hey!
Pause!
Looks like I'm in control now.
-Play. Pause. Play. Pause. Play.
-Mama, what are you doing?
We're still playing! Papa, do something!
Ha!
-Hey!
-[gasps]
[Cory] Come on, Chrissy.
You've had your fun.
-Hand over the remote.
-Volume down.
-[Cory mouthing]
-Uh… get her!
Pause!
Hmm. Oh!
Play.
Rewind.
[Chrissy yelps]
Time to get back to work.
[speaking in reverse]
[no audible dialogue]
[all grunting]
Well, I guess no more super remote.
And no more play time.
[all] Hmm.
Ah!
Look, everyone!
It's the saltshaker of madness!
If you get hit by the magic salt,
you turn into a monster!
Play time!
[Papa laughing]
I'm going to eat you!
[all laughing]
[Chrissy reading text]
Time for tea, friends.
Cheers!
Hmm? [sniffs]
Stinky.
Nope.
No.
Stay here.
Okay, so I think
we have all the resources we need.
-Chrissy!
-Stinky.
Hmm? [sniffs]
You're right. Something does stink.
I've got some work to do though.
Do you think you can take care of it?
Aye aye, Mama.
Whee!
All right, I'm back.
Let's raid this dungeon!
[sniffing]
Stinky.
[sniffs] Hmm…
Bye-bye, stinky!
Hmm? [sniffs]
Still stinky.
No stinky.
[whirring]
[Cory] A little bit more…
Perfect!
[both chuckle]
Freddie, look. Our first customer!
Put the cap on!
Okay! [Cory clears throat]
Presenting…
The Gary Garbage Truck Perfume.
Guaranteed to make you smell like
the greatest garbage truck in the world.
Well? What do you think?
[fog horn blows]
Is that a no?
No more stinky.
[sniffs] Still stinky.
I wouldn't go in there if I were you.
-What?
-It's a real stinker.
I don't know who used the bathroom last,
but might just be best to,
you know, let it air out.
-[takes deep breath]
-Chrissy, no!
Okay, okay, it was me!
-Stinky!
-Chrissy! Open up!
Yeah! We need to use the bathroom!
Uh, you wanna go first?
No more stinky.
Huh? [sniffs]
Still stinky.
No stinky.
Hmm?
Hmm.
[gasps]
Oh no!
Chrissy stinky.
Teatime!
[giggling]
Hey, Chrissy. I see you found the smell.
Mm-hmm.
I knew you could do it.
Wait. What the… Where's the toilet?
[giggles]
[Chrissy reading text]
Hi-yah!
-[machine buzzes]
-Ugh.
[gasps]
[machine] Sorry, you lose again!
Take one on the house.
Yes! Jackpot! Come to mama!
-[Franny laughing]
-Huh?
-[dance music]
-Welcome to the Lucky Lounge.
Here you go, boys.
Thank you, Miss Fenderson.
Enjoy yourself this evening.
This place is awesome!
[both] Whoa!
-Only big ticket winners allowed.
-Ticket.
You need more than that
if you wanna party with the high rollers.
[both] Better luck next time.
Aw!
[game] Sorry! Too bad! Sorry!
Almost! Too bad!
You lose!
[buzzing]
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
No! No! No!
Chrissy not lucky.
-[metallic clanging]
-Huh?
Crispy! Combo! Awesome!
Crispy! Combo! Perfect score!
Chrissy lucky?
You got a lucky penny.
Better hang onto it.
Lucky penny?
Hmm.
[electronic beeping]
Yeah!
Big ticket!
[laughing]
[gasps] Penny!
My tickets!
[Chrissy yells, pants]
Yeah!
Come back!
[Chrissy straining]
Mmm.
Aw!
Hey!
[murmuring indistinctly]
[Chrissy] Ahh! [grunts]
Thanks, Candace!
Wait!
What? [frustrated grunt]
Is somebody there?
Ahh!
-[exclaims] Penny!
-Huh?
[Chrissy] No!
Good luck fishing today, Squint.
Ha! Luck's got nothing to do with it.
Whoa!
[laughs]
I finally got the white whale!
[gasps] Lucky penny!
[grunts]
Get back here, you!
Huh?
Penny?
You won't get away!
[sighs]
Huh? Ticket?
Penny not lucky! Chrissy lucky!
Not enough.
Bro, look.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Right this way, Miss Carson.
[both] Welcome to the Lucky Lounge!
[Chrissy reading text]
[announcer] Welcome to the 65th
annual Bumper-Ball Championship!
It's game time.
But first, a quick word from our sponsor.
I'm gonna go upstairs and do some work.
-You're gonna take a nap, aren't you?
-What? No!
Morning, Mama.
Morning, Chrissy. We're babysitting
one of your friends today.
Yay!
Friend?
Hello, Chrissy Carson.
[gasps] Bobby Mini Van. [growls]
I left a snack for you two on the table!
Huh?
[both] Fruit gummies!
Only one?
We've got the match of the century
here today, folks!
It's the long-awaited showdown
between two fated rivals.
The Mean Green Machines
versus the Tin Can Vans!
Who will take the win?
Who will come out on top?
Chrissy, look, ice cream!
The Tin Can Vans
have snatched the ball from the offense.
They are headed downfield.
Look at that fancy wheel work.
Don't you dare!
They take aim.
And goal!
It's a goal for the Tin Can Vans!
The Mean Greens are left in shock.
But they don't leave them
a second to celebrate.
Both teams are scrambling.
I can barely see the ball, folks!
It's lost in the scuffle.
It's been found.
The Mean Greens have the ball.
We're off to the races!
What a beautiful maneuver.
Go, Mean Greens! Show 'em who's boss!
This kid's a regular twinkle-tires.
Ah-ha! And it's a goal for Green!
The Vans manage to break away!
It looks like a clean--
Oh!
Wait a minute. What just happened?
A fan has come onto the field.
He's stolen the ball!
-Huh?
-Can someone get stadium security, please?
[all yelling]
Can no one get their tires
on the slippery suspect?
Oh, they got him. The fan is down!
They're really giving him a walloping!
Yay!
On with the game!
[both growling]
The match is heating up.
There's no sign of it slowing down.
I'm working!
They're matching point for point.
And those victory dances
are nothing to sneeze at.
Oh yeah! Uh-huh! Oh yeah!
The walls are closing in.
There's nowhere left to turn.
But wait! A teammate is wide open.
Waiting in the wings like an angel.
Henry, catch!
A beautiful pass.
And beautifully received.
[toy] I'm Honkin' Henry!
Vamos, Mean Greens!
Vamos, Tin Cans!
[both growling]
[announcer] ¡Otro hermoso pase!
Thank you, Henry.
-Goal!
It's all come down to this.
One final goal will decide the match.
With seconds on the clock,
who will take the championship title?
It's another mad scramble.
The play goes haywire.
Cars are sent head over wheels.
The ball is in the air.
It's anyone's game.
[slowed down] Come on!
It's all over, folks! It's a tie!
A tie? Is that cherry?
Oh, look at you two
having so much fun together.
How about some juice?
Juice?
Oh, there's only one left.
I'll go get some cups so we can split it.
We wouldn't leave you hanging, folks!
The match moves into overtime.
Winner takes all!
[both exclaim]
[Chrissy reading text]
Okay. This goes in here. And this…
Found me!
[gasps] Aw!
-Now Mama hide.
-Sorry, Chrissy.
Hop on out of that box, please.
[Chrissy] Aw. [struggling]
Chrissy!
[sighs]
Mama, what this?
Oh!
We used to make home movies
of you and Cory with this all the time.
[gasp] Chrissy movies?
Probably.
Watch Chrissy movie!
Right now?
Please?
Well, we can watch one.
Yay!
Mmm, that one.
[Papa] Here we go!
Hi, Chrissy. Say hi to the camera!
Hi!
-[Papa] Whoa!
-[Chrissy giggling]
Okay, that was fun.
Now I need to get back to--
-More Chrissy movies!
-[winces]
I just have so much to do.
[Mama] Can you see the kids?
[Papa] Yeah. There's Cory,
walking down the hill.
Hi, Cory! Where's Chrissy?
[Chrissy] Whoa!
[Chrissy imitating ghost]
Now, when you're hunting a ghost,
you have to be very quiet.
Boo!
[both laughing]
[Mama] Oh, Chrissy's first restaurant!
And what would Madame like to order?
Uh…
-Potty.
-Pardon?
[Papa] That's the potty face!
-[Mama] We gotta go!
-[laughs]
-[rustling]
-Huh?
Mama!
Okay. Okay.
[laughing]
Ah--
[Mama] What do puppy cars say?
Bark, bark, bark!
[Mama laughs]
That's right! And what do puppy cars do?
Oh, no! Not that!
Now I wonder,
who could have made all of this mess?
Chrissy tornado!
[both laughing]
Yep, that's our Chrissy.
That's still our Chrissy.
Well, I think that was all of them.
[sighs] Back to work.
[Chrissy] Aw.
More movie!
Aw, you excited
for Mama and Papa to get home, Cory?
Baby!
Yep, I'm excited too.
Baby Cory?
Huh?
-Yeah!
-[older voice] Whoa!
Cory, let them through the door!
Here, let me grab your bags, dear.
Oh, thanks, Mom.
[Cory] I wanna see! Let me see!
[Papa] Slow down, bud.
Baby!
Gentle.
Cory, meet your new baby sister, Chrissy.
Hi, Chrissy.
[Chrissy coos]
I'm gonna show her my toys!
[Papa's mom]
These really are special times.
And they go by so fast.
[Mama sniffling]
Mama go back to work now?
How about I hide and you seek?
[gasps] I find you!
[upbeat closing theme music plays]