Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Raikan
Yosuke Kubozuka
Danbe
Kiyohiko Shibukawa
Prostitute
Haruka Imou
Benikichi / Kogoro
Danko Iida / Ryoichi Yuki
Cinematography
Kenji Maki
Art Direction
Takashi Sasaki
Costume Design
Masae Miyamoto
Sound Design
Masaya Kitada
Title Design
Danko Iida
Graphic Design
Osamu Ohashi
Still Photography
Keisuke Nagoshi
Written & Directed by
Toshiaki Toyoda
GO SEPPUKU YOURSELVES
How are you doing today?
Feverish?
Got money for medicine?
Guess not.
How about you?
Take the medicine and get well,
or leave it and kick the bucket.
You know what that means? Hell.
You hear?
Oh dear, you're getting
worse by day.
And you.
The epidemic got you, too?
What you need,
is money for medicine.
No money, tough luck.
You're still young.
Eat some fish, fart, and sleep.
That should sort you out.
Medicine...
Money first.
Money, money, money,
money is the enemy of the times.
Oh dear, Danbe, you're looking
a little worse for wear.
Be conscious about your looks
when you've passed forty, I say.
I'm bored of hearing
your usual balderdash.
What's wrong?
Is it about the epidemic palaver?
Since the well's been contaminated,
the magistrate's guards are eradicating
lawbreakers by beheading
or ordering them to do seppuku.
They'll come for you.
Me?
I'm just a medicine seller.
Who'd benefit from the epidemic.
I see... it's like that?
The culprit must be evil.
But I can see their motives.
Our avaricious magistrate
are paying for
their own wrongdoings at last.
Since when do you speak
like a wise man, huh?
I'm a pebble in a riverbed.
All edges get rounded over time.
The well nearby
is contaminated, too.
Any ideas?
A demon, I heard.
No one can be that savage unless
it's a demon or an evil spirit.
I'm looking for that demon.
An outsider, I wager.
I'm a samurai.
Killing people is what I do.
Raikan Kichiemon.
As the punishment for poisoning
the town's wells,
I order you to commit seppuku.
Like I said many times,
I know nothing about that poison.
Shame on you,
quibbleing until the end.
A woman said she saw you.
You spread the disease on purpose.
Did you not, Raikan?
You seem so eager to watch
me commit seppuku.
Exasperating I may,
yet I'd seppuku myself
if you insist.
The world today is
not worth living for.
Stop talking nonsense
and get on with it.
I must tell you
one thing before I die.
You are the ones
spreading the epidemic.
Each and every one of you
has been possessed
by an evil spirit.
Even now, as we speak...
you're letting it spread itself.
And the poor are dying from it.
Sucking the peasants dry with land tax
under the name of governance.
Shut up, outsider!
The one who poisoned the wells
was a demon.
Not a human.
Not that it matters to me.
Every single one of you should
go to hell!
After death,
you can be reborn and start over.
You cannot continue exploiting
the poor and making them suffer.
It's your turn
to go to hell.
God created the epidemic
out of fury.
And as a punishment
of your wrongdoings.
If my seppuku would clear out
the epidemic and save the poor,
I'll cut my stomach open with honor.
Then do it already!
There was a rogue samurai
in the red-light district,
and a young lad nearby laughed
at this samurai being smarmy.
The lad ended up
becoming a rogue himself.
They ran into each other one day,
and the samurai said to him
"Don't beat yourself up."
"A lost coin in deep snow
will be lost forever,"
"lost love under the bridge
will soon to be a telltale."
"Life is short,"
"too short to have your
questions answered."
"So you, who I met in the past,"
"whether you will be reborn
or you won't,"
"take a gamble and
see it for yourself."
I have lived my
whole life with sword.
One who has been following
the 'right' path all one's life,
is boring as fuck.
A path which is barely within the law,
there is pastime.
Life without pastime
is not worth living.
On a detour you take,
discover compassion.
I have killed many for money.
I have indulged myself with
good sake and fine women.
Yet I am enraged with intolerance.
Of your goddamn decision!
Have you ever said
anything like this?
Have you ever been allowed to do
anything you like?
Have I ever been a fawner?
Over my dead body!
Father, mother,
and brothers, I've been nothing
but the black sheep of the family.
Everybody dies.
Nobody can stand in my way.
I'll do whatever the hell
I want to do before I die.
But you lot, no matter
how hard you try,
your lives will never be
as good as mine.
Just deserts!
You bastards.
All kinds of disgrace and sins,
now purified, refreshed.
The end of the epidemic
at Mt. Resurrection-Wolf.
Funeral procession on its path.
I will be reborn as a beast.
Now all of you,
go seppuku yourselves!
Produced by:
Toshiaki Toyoda, Shinichiro Muraoka
Music by
Seppuku Pistols, Kodo,
Toshiyuki Terui, Tatsuya Nakamura,
Music by
Kazuhide Yamaji & Mars89
GO SEPPUKU YOURSELVES
English subtitle by Sayaka Rui