Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
A PRACTICE OF EVICTING
DEMONS AND GHOSTS
A LOST SOUL THAT REMAINS
IN THE AREA WHERE IT DIED
AN ANCIENT INDIAN DAGGER USED
BY TIBETAN SHAMANS DURING EXORCISM
GUIMOON: A PORTAL THAT CONNECTS
THE LIVING AND THE DEAD
ON OLD YEAR'S NIGHT
Damn it.
Gosh.
What's up?
That guy tries
to find any excuse not to work.
We gotta get this done today
to be on schedule!
Hey!
-Look.
-What is it?
A body?
A concealed body was discovered
while renovating
a derelict community center…
The unidentified body has found
without any decomposition,
and exact time of death, concealment time,
and other factors…
According to neighbors,
bodies without kin were found
at the community center,
and gruesome murders
took place here in the past.
More information is expected
after the investigation.
Damn it.
Stay away!
THE YEAR OF 1998
COMMUNITY CENTER
We got a nasty restligeist.
As if devouring people wasn't enough,
it took over the entire building.
A stubborn one…
GUEST LEDGER
1990, KIM SEOK-HO
NAME, AGE
FOUR YEARS LATER
FEBRUARY 11, 2002
Do-jin,
my frail body cannot handle this case.
Could you take over?
I can do nothing about my blood,
but I ain't no shaman.
Let's end the shaman heritage with you.
All right.
I'm sorry for passing on
such bad blood on to you.
Here is the traffic report
for February 11, 2002.
Due to the long holiday weekend,
highways are open.
Aside from southbound
Gyeongbu and Honam highways,
all national highways are breezy
without any congestion.
Due to a large accident
near Cheonan yesterday,
there was a traffic jam till evening,
but it has returned to normal overnight.
Yesterday…
TEMPORARILY CLOSED
It wasn't easy
obtaining evidence for an open case.
You know.
And? So what?
-Well, I'm just saying…
-Your wife's cheating, right?
She's about to take off with your seal.
Shouldn't you go?
My mom sure is stubborn.
You can't hold me back.
You know no one can stop me
when I put my mind to it.
So stop pestering and ascend, will you?
Whatever happened in there
that made you do that,
I'm going to find out.
NOTORIOUS SERIAL KILLERS
THERE WAS A SIGN OF DANGER
Do you have to go?
Stop with your tantrum.
I ain't going there to die.
Guimoon, the door connects
the living and the dead has appeared.
I have to get through that door
when it opens tonight.
Enough with your bullshit.
Mom…
Mom died like that. I can't lose you too.
I'm going there so I can live. All right?
I have to release all restligeists
who died by Kim Seok-ho's hands,
and once Kim is exorcised,
Mom's grudge will finally be released.
It'll be fine. Don't worry.
-Do-jin, please stop…
-I've been harassed for four years.
If I end up missing today's chance…
You won't have to worry.
THE YEAR OF 2002
FEB 11, 11:30 P.M.
"They are here.
It's all over. MPD ghost is here."
MAINTENANCE OFFICE
GUEST LEDGER
1990, KIM SEOK-HO
SEPTEMBER 9, 1990
"September 10, 1990."
Fuck.
Should I run? Hey, don't run.
Hey, don't run.
THE YEAR OF 1996
-Look, this thing moves.
-Stand in front of it.
-Take a picture of us.
-Here we go.
One, two…
I got a hold
of last year's contest winner film.
It's so bad that I almost puked.
Stop bullshitting me.
It's not bullshit.
Look at it.
Everything looks amazing to shoot.
No one will know
if someone gets killed here.
Holy shit!
Your face is hellish!
-You ignorant bastard.
-What?
Heavy makeup will scare away the ghosts.
My mom even puts on chicken blood
when performing a ritual.
Chicken blood? So nasty.
Tae-hun was here.
Write it bigger. Way bigger.
-In bloody red.
-Hey!
-What about it?
-That's bad luck!
Leaving a trace behind
is a tradition for a place like this.
But why leave my name?
-We're here because of you.
-Goddamnit.
Don't you dare swear at me again.
-What if we can never get out of here?
-Stop jinxing with that crap!
-Holy shit, stop shouting!
-Why? You scared?
That graffiti…
I think I saw it before.
-He's scared.
-So scared.
It rubs me the wrong way!
Why is he being a bitch?
I'll smack you with the shovel.
What should we do with this scaredy cat?
What was that?
Sorry! I'm sorry.
Why are you two so chickenshit?
-Do we really have to do this?
-Absolutely.
You're dropping out
because you can't pay the tuition.
The prize for this contest is huge.
Seeing and analyzing
all the past contest winners,
this will definitely work.
-But even so…
-Stop that.
Aren't you thankful of us?
If you are, then say so.
Yeah, man.
Hey! It's almost time. Let's get going!
Geez.
Wait for me!
-It's almost time. Four minutes left.
-Hey.
Geez.
I told you to wait for me.
Are you a child?
There's no time. Start shooting.
If we don't get this, we're so screwed.
Then Tae-hun will shave his head
and be drafted to the military.
All right. I'm feeling it. It's coming.
One, two, three.
Many years ago,
the custodian of this building…
Damn it. The community…
killed the owners and guests
on the third floor with a crowbar…
A shovel.
We're standing at that very crime scene.
The custodian's motive is still unknown.
Why?
Because he committed suicide afterwards.
Other mysterious and fatal incidents
continued to take place here.
Then a strange rumor started to spread.
On Old Year's Night,
the last day of lunar year!
The moon normally
does not shine at midnight,
but it's supposedly visible
only from this roof.
If a moon really does show up
at midnight tonight,
it's the moon of the afterlife,
not of the living.
The energy from it
is passed down the hallway
and opens the door.
Guimoon…
a boundary
between the dead and the living.
Forget it. That's enough.
Screw Guimoon. It's freezing here.
The shaman said it'd be here 100%…
Screw the afterlife moon.
-Maybe she lied.
-Let's just go get drunk.
I'm buying.
-Let's go. Come on.
-Hold on.
Wait, stop.
What is it?
Shit.
-It's up.
-What?
Don't mess around.
-I don't see anything.
-Let's just go.
-It's really up.
-Let me see.
Oh, my God. It was for real.
Tae-hun, come take a look.
This is batshit insane.
FEB 19, 1996, 12:02 A.M.
If you're lying, I'll kill you.
You see that?
What the hell?
It's locked.
-What?
-It won't open. Damn it!
Move aside.
Really?
Hang in there, Mom.
I'll cross over, exorcise those things,
and free your grudge.
FEBRUARY 12, 2002
JUNE 18, 2000
GUEST LEDGER
JULY 5, 1995
APRIL 2, 1993
JANUARY 5, 1991
SEPTEMBER 10, 1990
KILL
GUEST LEDGER
What the fuck?
Please don't kill me!
Get away from me!
Honey!
Help me!
Fuck.
SUPERNATURAL SPACE
BETWEEN THE LIVING AND THE DEAD
WHERE MURDERED VICTIMS
AT THE COMMUNITY CENTER ARE STUCK
Hey.
Do you see me?
Can you talk?
Talk to me.
You're Park Dae-hyeok, born 1968.
Right?
I have a particular skill,
so I want to help you,
but let me ask you one thing.
Before Kim went nuts
on that night in 1990,
what happened in this building--
I'll help you get out of here.
So hang in there.
Hwang Yeong-il, born 1968,
rest in peace.
Shit!
Sorry.
It's a piece of glass. Why is this here?
How could it only appear on the camcorder?
No one's gonna believe it, right?
This is the perfect time to spot a ghost.
What?
What is it?
There's…
What? Saw something?
-No, it's nothing.
-What is it?
Something's there?
Move out of the way.
Guys, it's ten past midnight.
-We're in the third-floor hallway.
-Hey.
-This is where Kim Seok-ho killed people.
-Let's just leave.
That's why most ghost sightings
happened here.
-Damn it!
-Gosh. What?
Stupid punk!
Did you breathe into my neck?
Are you nuts? You stink.
Someone definitely breathed into my neck!
What was that?
Hang on. We have to shoot something
to win the prize.
We definitely heard a strange noise.
Could it be Kim Seok-ho?
-Damn it.
-Holy crap.
-You startled me.
-Hey. This is crazy.
Something's definitely in there.
Guys.
If we get something,
we'll win grand prize for sure.
-Yeah, grand prize.
-You morons…
Hey, Hye-yeong! Hey!
-Damn it.
-Geez.
You idiot. What's with you?
I told you.
We shouldn't be here any longer.
My gosh.
Then you should've stopped us
from the beginning.
-Hey.
-Hye-yeong!
-You scared the crap out of me!
-Hey!
What? You nuts? What are you doing alone?
You chickenshits.
Hey. Take a look.
That was it?
You guys are so funny.
Didn't you just tease me
for getting scared?
But there's
no draft here.
What?
What is it?
Someone breathed down my neck again.
-I heard a laugh right beside me too.
-Geez.
-You heard it wrong.
-I didn't!
Let's get out of here!
Guys.
What?
-What's wrong?
-What is it?
Hye-yeong…
What the hell is it?
Fuck! What was that?
It was a ghost!
Shut the hell up!
Hye-yeong. It's us. Snap out of it!
Fuck.
You disloyal bastards.
Are you even my friends?
Hey. My camera…
Where's my camera?
Do you know how expensive that is?
You can't get it in Korea!
Screw your camera.
Let's just leave!
Hey! Dude!
My camera!
Seriously? Hey!
-Wait for me.
-Come on, man!
Get down here!
Won-jae, get down here!
-You heard it wrong.
-I didn't!
Let's get out of here!
What was it? Hold on.
You guys are so funny.
Didn't you just tease me
for getting scared?
Shit. What the hell?
We're stuck here,
just like what the graffiti said…
We ran down here,
but we're on the second floor again!
What the fuck is this?
It could be our delusion.
Or we didn't see the floor number…
We kept walking down.
What the hell?
What the shit?
You scared me!
Won-jae, why are you here?
I should be asking you that.
Shit, I'm sure we came down
from the second floor.
Guys.
There's something in here.
I heard voices. Ours!
Shit.
What's that?
Bastards…
I should have been careful.
Goddamn it. Now they know.
What was that?
Won-jae, come on! Get over here!
Damn it.
The dimensions are intertwined?
Come on, asshole!
Hey, Won-jae!
Who are you?
Answer me.
Where are you?
Who are you? How did you get in here?
We're college students…
Please help us!
We can't find the exit!
There are monsters! No, ghosts!
Find somewhere to hide!
You could die!
Room 304, Na Seon-hui and Na Hyeon-jeong.
Restligeist aren't supposed to leave
the place where they died.
Goddamnit!
Na Seon-hui, born 1965.
Right?
Or Na Hyeon-jeong?
Here.
I want to leave.
Na Hyeon-jeong.
I'm not Na Hyeon-jeong.
Then who are you?
Yun Mi-rin.
Yun Mi-rin?
All right.
I don't know who you are…
but a restligeist can't be here.
Yun Mi-rin!
Just run! What's that black thing?
Shut the hell up and run!
We have to get out of here!
Shit!
It's the same place! Same hallway!
We ran down here,
but we're on the second floor again!
Just go! Hurry!
Goddamn! Second floor again!
Won-jae, get the hell up!
Born 1976…
Yun Mi-rin.
MISSING CHILD
First floor.
What?
There's no door.
The damn door is gone!
-I heard my voice.
-There was one right here.
These glyphs weren't here when we came in.
I am sure it was my voice.
We will all die here.
Shut your damn mouth!
I told you we should leave!
You didn't listen to me then--
Hey! Stop it!
The roof.
Let's get to the roof.
Jump off or whatever. There will be a way.
You stupid idiot.
No.
Mom!
I'm sorry, Mom.
Son of a bitch.
You can't go.
If you go now, you'll die.
Come with me, please.
Hurry!
It's Kim Seok-ho!
It was definitely Kim Seok-ho.
Hey!
It'd be better to hide until sunrise.
Wherever we go, it's the same…
The door opened by itself.
Where is this voice coming from?
Mister.
Hurry.
Who is that?
Hye-yeong, what are you doing?
Hye-yeong!
Won-jae, what are you doing?
Won-jae!
Where am I?
Won-jae! Tae-hun!
Yun Mi-rin went missing in 1990.
That's you, right?
I didn't go missing.
What?
I was…
always here.
It wasn't me. It wasn't me!
Shut up!
Where did this crazy bitch come from?
It wasn't me! She did it!
It wasn't me!
Dad!
Please!
No!
Dad!
Dad! I'm sorry!
If you hit me again…
I'll kill you bastards first.
The missing case of Yun Mi-rin,
who went missing last August,
is at a standstill for several months.
The police are unable to rely on
testimonies of the parents,
and will expand the search nationwide.
Yun is said to suffer
from multiple personality disorder,
and she needs…
Free me at once!
I'll kill you all!
Let go of me!
Who are you?
"Multiple personality disorder."
MPD GHOST IS HERE
The one in control
of this place isn't Kim…
Kill...
It's another you.
The other you is controlling him to kill.
From that night in 1990 on…
You killed everyone who came here.
No.
It wasn't me!
No…
I can make this go away.
You want to flee from her, no?
No.
She shouldn't be messed with…
-No…
-It's okay, Mi-rin.
That girl hiding inside you.
What's her name?
This will be all over when she's gone.
Her name is Kim…
Kim…
Yu…
No.
-No.
-Tell me again. What did you say?
What's her name?
Tell me!
Get off me!
Something's wrong.
I have to block the door!
FEBRUARY 10, 1990
MAY 7, 1995
Name and date of birth.
Hong Hye-yeong…
born in 1975.
1975, Hong Hye-yeong.
What are you doing?
You okay?
What the hell.
-I'll kill you all!
-Wait! Stop!
Mister,
you're a human, aren't you?
Stupid punks.
It was you guys?
Mister!
Lower your voice.
How did you kids come in here?
Are you guys crazy?
I know, really.
You can help us, right?
Can't you help us find our friend?
What the hell for?
If they took him away, he's a goner.
"They"?
Would you even understand?
Instead of finding him,
worry about getting out of here.
Hold up.
Look in front of you.
They're all walls.
No way. I got out of Guimoon already.
No, that can't be.
There was a door when we came down here!
Goddamnit!
Something's messed up.
We have to hurry. Hurry!
I came back to the building,
but now the dimension has changed.
-We're here!
-Shit!
Please! Help us!
-Won-jae?
-Open this door!
What is it?
Won-jae! Lee Won-jae!
Do you want to die? That's a bait.
If you approach him,
you'll end up like him.
He's right.
Our lives come first.
Tae-hun, are you nuts?
He said Won-jae's dead!
Won-jae's dead.
There's nothing we can do.
Guys, I can't see.
Get me out of here.
She said so.
We can get out if we find the key.
Won-jae!
You there?
There you are.
Don't kid around.
If you do…
-Open the door!
-If you do, I'll kill you all!
Hey, Kang Tae-hun!
Let go! Damn it!
I'm gonna live.
-I'm going home!
-Wake up, you bastard!
We can go together.
Tae-hun.
Son of a bitch.
I want to live.
Fuck.
I want to go home.
IT'S ALL
Something's…
Something's wrong.
IT'S ALL OVER
Why is he spraying that message there?
What do you mean?
Also…
that's not the end of what I saw earlier.
There's one more line below.
"MPD…
ghost…
is here."
I certainly got out of there.
How did a restligeist…
What the hell's going on here?
How do you know about the graffiti,
and how does Tae-hun know about that too?
What's today's date?
February 19 of…
1996.
Here is the traffic report
for February 11, 2002.
What the hell's happening around here?
What's that for?
You'll do to us what you did to Won-jae?
You'll kill me too?
I'm not trying to kill you.
You are already dead.
No, I'm not.
You're so full of shit.
No! No way!
No.
I can live! I really can!
I can live if you die.
You'll regret this.
When I die, you'll be stuck here forever.
She said when she has your life,
she'll let me live!
-Kill him.
-She'll send me home!
Kill him.
But…
it might be different this time.
She told me that.
She said she'll let me live
if I kill you all.
Kill.
She'll let me go home.
Kill everyone! So you can live!
No, stop it!
You stupid bitch, do you want to die?
Please stop!
I need to kill you quick...
I'm the one who'll leave, not you!
Me!
The dead cannot walk out of that door.
I remember…
Son of a bitch.
You did it last time too.
You killed us all.
Help me!
Let me…
Let me go.
I don't want to rot here forever.
Please…
Born 1975…
Hong Hye-yeong.
Rest in peace.
No! Please let me go!
Please!
What the hell?
I just have to cross through the door,
Guimoon, and go back to 1990.
September 12, 1990.
From where did it repeat?
Shut your mouth!
You think you can take me on?
From where did it repeat?
Born 1964…
Seo Do…
THE DEAD CANNOT WALK
OUT OF THIS DOOR
Do-jin.
So where is that place?
Subtitle translation by: Mina Noh