Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Good morning!
Good morning, everybody.
Come on, y'all, let's get up,
wake up.
Breakfast and coffee is available
for those who want to grab it.
And those who've been here
for three days,
please grab your stuff
and check out.
We have to make room in the
shelter for others, okay?
All right, y'all, I hope y'all
have a blessed day.
Come on, come on.
Okay. All right.
It's July the 31st,
so hurry up and get your game on!
You know the rules, don't you?
The more you shop,
the more coupons you get.
The more coupons you get, the more chances
you have to win those million dollars.
Um, sir?
Hey!
Black man!
It's July the
31st, so hurry up!
How many fucking times
are you gonna do this to me?
How many? Who the fuck is Mike?
- I just...
- I'm sick of your sh...
- Why are you doing this to me?
- It's not what you think!
It's exactly what I'm
fucking saying right now!
I'm hitting you
in two seconds, for real.
I'm gonna hit you in one second!
I'm sick of your shit.
Stop talking so much.
- Get back in here, I'm not done talking to you.
- It's not... but...
- You don't understand!
- You are not going anywhere.
Get out of here,
get the fuck out.
Who is this guy? Why is he always around?
No, no!
No!