Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[lively trumpet music playing]
♪ Come on, melanin drip ♪
♪ Hourglass hips
Black girl privilege, black leadership ♪
♪ Godlike image matte brown finish ♪
♪ Born with the magic
that you just can't diminish oops ♪
♪ Your gimmicks a minute to read it
Thick locker space bitch… ♪
[female voice] Is happily ever after real?
Or just a ruse?
Wow! Yes. Ooh la la. Showstopper.
Like, I wanna make an entrance in this.
It's the one.
[female voice] Do we create it
ourselves or wait for it to find us?
Ooh! That looks beautiful.
That color is perfect.
-Next!
-[woman 1] Next.
[female voice] "Go to school," they said.
-"Don't let your body go," they said.
-[woman 2] I like that.
-[female voice] "Be sexy," they said.
-[indistinct chatter]
Try these. Let me see.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Complete.
[woman 1] Now this, my dear,
makes me feel like you're a princess.
-That is beautiful.
-My work here is done.
[woman 2] Yes!
[female voice] "And then
you'll find a perfect man
and live happily ever after," they said.
[laughing]
-[soothing music playing]
-[indistinct chatter]
[female voice] What if they lied?
Exactly what is happily ever after?
Maybe it's just
a perfect ending for Cinderella.
Nothing that deep for the rest of us.
Or the beginning
of our sleeping beauty stories.
[soothing music playing]
I'm Zimkhitha.
Welcome ladies. Um…
You can settle down
and um, roll off your mats.
[Zimkhitha] After three years
of committing to a relationship,
I came to Johannesburg to find my balance.
And let's just forget about
everything that's happened before.
Stay present, stay focused.
Holding our hands in to pray.
And deep breath in.
[audible inhale]
[Zimkhitha] And release. [audible exhale]
-[audible exhale]
-[soothing music playing]
[Zimkhitha] We order a soft life,
but instead, we found ourselves widowed.
Okay, take more.
Think we are pretty.
[hums softly]
Goodnight. [kisses]
I love you, miss Coco.
Okay.
Ah, don't run. You can see
I'm wearing heels, why you running?
[Zimkhitha] And forced into adulting.
[exhales]
[mellow music playing]
You look stunning.
Thank you.
[chuckles]
We don't want to show too much now, do we?
[nervous chuckle]
[lively music playing]
Oh, wow!
-You like?
-Oh, Zimkhitha, it is a definite "yes."
Ah, I'm so glad I actually added a little
-bit of an extra--
-This is exquisite. Wow!
Thank you, Zaza. Thank you.
Trust you to steal
the limelight from the artwork.
-I am art, darling.
-Yes, darling, you are.
All right. Ladies,
I think my work here is done.
I'll see you both in yoga, right? Monday.
-No!
-Stay.
Stay.
I'm not really dressed.
[both] Stay.
[laughs] Okay, um, it's not like
I'm really doing anything tonight, so…
[both] Good.
-Cool.
-[cork pops]
-[glasses clink]
-[lively music playing]
-[man] Yonda!
-Hey! Max, dude.
[Max] Glad you made it, bro.
Yeah. Man, this is great.
I mean, I might just consider art.
-Yeah?
-I know--
Uh, no, don't do that, bro.
Yeah, how about I become partner,
and then we make this whole thing digital?
Can you imagine that?
I can't, brah.
The thing about virtual exhibition is,
it robs us
of the complete experience of art.
Look around. Huh?
You've got to touch it, feel it.
Connect with your
artistic expression. The meaning.
-It's not a woman, it's art.
-Same difference, brah.
-Hey, ladies.
-Hey.
Hey, Princess, this is beautiful.
I mean, this is… This is mind-blowing.
Thank you, Yonda. Um,
this is my friend, Zaza.
Zaza, this is Yonda.
-Nice to meet you.
-Lovely to meet you.
Uh, Yonda here,
quit his previous project to make an app.
No, an app…
An app that will build my empire.
Yeah, uh…[clears throat]…
I thought you were
-becoming an artist, brah?
-[sarcastic chuckle]
Yeah, how about a toast?
[Max] Yeah, a toast.
-[Zaza] Cheers.
-[Princess] Cheers.
[Max] To you.
[Zimkhitha] But for some of us,
the search for true love never ends.
[sensuous music playing]
[Zimkhitha] Ladies and gentlemen,
press "play."
[Max] Now, for the real reason
why we are all gathered here tonight.
Please put your hands together
for the beautiful Princess.
[applause]
[loud sigh]
This year's theme for
the self-portraiture series exhibition,
is "Breathe."
Some moments carry messages,
signals, clues.
But we miss them.
We miss these moments
because we never stop to just breathe.
Take it all in.
The practice of yoga
teaches us the art of breathing.
Allowing us to reach deep
and draw strength from within.
May we all remember
to take the time to breathe.
And truly listen
to those signals and messages.
-[intriguing music playing]
-Breathe. [giggles]
Thank you.
-[intriguing music playing]
-[applause fades]
Oh, hi. [chuckles]
-[Princess clears throat]
-So good. Guys.
[suspenseful music playing]
[man] Hey.
[exhales]
I, uh, I just wanted to see you and, uh…
our daughter.
Please, go.
I just think that we should talk.
[suspenseful music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
This is deep, alluring, yet calming.
Yeah, it's a bit
too abstract for me, you know.
-Oh?
-Yeah.
And what you kind of just said is…
-Bullshit. Yeah.
-[laughs] Yes.
You're beautiful.
[soothing music playing]
-And?
-No, nothing else. You're just--
Let me guess, I'm just deep,
alluring, and calming, yeah?
-Oh, it's like that? Okay. [laughs]
-Uh, it's like that.
-You gotta work on your game.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yes.
-[both laugh]
[softly] Honestly.
-Did… did you hear that?
-Hear what?
My stomach is grumbling.
Oh, thank God, I thought it was mine.
-Yours did that too?
-Yes.
-Oh, wow.
-[laughs]
Hey, what do you say
we get out of here and feed ourselves?
Yeah.
Yeah, um, I'd like that actually.
Just food, obviously, no funny business.
-Oh, no. Yeah.
-So.
Zimkhitha.
Yonda.
Pleased to meet you.
Lovely meeting you.
-And I get to choose where we eat.
-Okay.
-Pizza maybe?
-[Zimkhitha] I love vegan pizza.
[Zimkhitha] All right,
let's start off with an inhale,
open up the heart,
chin up, into seated cow.
And exhale,
relax the shoulders into seated cat.
And let's keep going, inhale.
[inhaling]
-And exhale, relax the shoulders into…
-[Zaza] Did you get Nandi's message?
[Princess] I did.
[Zimkhitha] And let's just keep going.
[Princess] I wish I could
just pack up and go.
Move to another country.
[Zaza] I know, right?
[Princess] Thomas is spoiling her rotten.
-[Zaza] I've missed that.
-[Zimkhitha huffs]
All right. Um.
Ladies, I think
we can do this another time.
-Thank you.
-[Zaza] Thanks.
Listen, Princess, um,
your exhibition was… was amazing.
-Aw.
-Honestly, from the artwork to…
to the people there, um.
-I'm glad I stayed.
-It was the people.
-Hmm, the people there.
-[Zimkhitha] Namaste, ladies.
-[chuckles]
-[Zaza] Namaste.
So shit has happened we need to dissect.
My life is not a science project, okay.
-There's nothing to dissect.
-You need to think about it.
The man you choose is actually
the one that's gonna define your future.
Hmm.
Beki took care of business.
I don't have to worry about anything.
So don't let this
Leo nonsense fool you. Please.
Why would I do that?
-Why would you do that?
-Oh ye of little faith.
-This was very useful.
-[chuckles]
[Yonda] See, we need
to be extremely accurate,
because these girls
are no match for the "single men."
If I may just say here, the basis of
this entire research is completely flawed.
We need to speak to real people
here and not some
scientific research or some stats now.
I got that.
I don't know. We-- We just need
to figure out what our users want
and that way, I can give it to them.
Wrong. That's not
how these things work, okay?
What they do is they give us the money,
and then we give them
a platform that they can explore.
Yonda, please,
it is scientifically proven that
lasting marriages
are founded on the basis--
That's not what we doing here.
We're in the business
of selling people a great time.
End of story.
[mellow music playing]
Boys.
Boys?
Hello, Fakazile.
It's been a year,
since my brother passed away.
-[dramatic music playing]
-Oh, I forgot.
You actually never mourned for him.
[Zaza] No one will tell me
how to mourn my husband.
Not even you.
[Fakazile scoffs]
When my brother
picked you from the gutters,
we all wondered what he saw in you.
What you gave him.
But that's all coming to an end.
The dignity of this family
shall be restored.
[dramatic music continues]
-[in Zulu] Hello, Ma.
-Hello, daughter-in-law.
-How are you?
-I'm well, Zaza.
[in English] Ma, I was just showing
Grandma my new PS5.
Yeah, go upstairs.
[in Zulu] Let's have some tea.
[dramatic music playing]
[man, in English]
Your late husband's will instructs us
to pay out half
once everything is rounded off.
[Zaza] And, um, the other 50%?
Well, he planted that
into the business as a loan.
You can withdraw from it, provided
it doesn't harm the business in any way.
Wow.
I'll make some copies of this for you.
[laptop pings]
[Max] Hey!
[Princess] Hey!
You're back early.
-Yep. Perks of being a lecturer.
-Hi.
A forever prepared one at that.
And there's my queen.
[playfully] Hey. [chuckles]
How are you?
Okay, let me grab these. [sighs]
And this.
Look what I got for you.
[playfully] Hey.
-Ah! look at that.
-Look.
-Do you like?
-Yeah.
-[phone ringing]
-Okay, let me show you how it works.
You won't believe who emailed me.
[Zaza] Who? Leo?
-Yes. Mm-hm.
-[Zaza groans]
You have no idea
what Beki left me and the kids.
Really?
I wish he was here though.
[Princess] My friend, I know.
Just remember he wanted
you to be taken care of, so…
[Zaza] I know, so I've decided to invest.
There's a penthouse that I saw
and I really love and I've made inquiries.
Property is always a very wise investment.
Plus, you know, if you ever need a…
private, quiet space for…
adult business.
-How are we friends again?
-I have to go.
Love you.
-[blender whirling]
-[phone beeps]
[phone beeps]
[tense music playing]
[panting]
[Yonda] Hey!
Hi.
-[panting] Hi, hey.
-Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
-Do you, like, need a lift?
-Nah, I'm all right.
-You can join me though.
-Yeah.
[Yonda] So, so tell me,
how come I never see you around here?
Ah, I usually jog
in the mornings, prefer it that way.
Ah. Ah.
Do you ever get that feeling,
like you know in the pit of your stomach
something bad is about to happen?
Mm-hm.
[Zimkhitha] Yeah, I had that today.
Yeah, I was doing my smoothie
and then my phone just…
Just kept going off.
All these messages
telling me my ex is getting married.
[somber music playing]
Um, yeah, sorry. [chuckles]
Kind of offloaded too much
there, but thanks for listening.
Yeah, no. It's okay, yeah.
Pleasure, pleasure.
[softly] Pleasure?
Did you just say pleasure?
Hey!
So is… is that how it ends?
I mean, that's rather…
shitty.
Yeah, it is. Pretty shitty.
Hey, I'm… I'm hungry.
Do you wanna grab something to eat?
Are you always hungry?
-No.
-Yeah.
No. Actually, no.
'Cause the last time…
No, not-- This is a recent thing.
Uh. Okay. [chuckles]
Honestly, I'm…
Yeah, I'm not really
in the right space to do that right now.
I just wanna head home,
you know, and just…
[sighs]… crawl into bed
and just let it all out.
Or we could eat together.
Again.
-[softly] Yeah.
-Yes?
-Yeah.
-Yes! Okay.
-Okay.
-I think I need it.
-But I'm cooking. Yes.
-Oh? You like dictating, huh?
Yeah. Do you have a problem?
No! Um, hey, I'm not complaining.
[oil sizzling]
Hey.
Listen to this.
"It is more difficult and more bitter
when a man fails alone."
[Princess] He's still one of my favorites.
[phone beeps]
-That's weird.
-Hmm?
Thandi's school says we settled
her fees, but we're over by 5,000 rand.
Hmm.
I didn't make that payment.
Must be a mistake.
Yeah.
Must be.
Hmm? What else you reading?
I love this guy.
-[chuckles]
-[phone beeps]
[Max sighs]
[Fakazile] How's school?
[Zaza's son] Auntie,
it's good. It's not bad.
[Fakazile] Look at your hair, you.
What is this?
-[Zaza's son] A style.
-[Fakazile laughs] It's a style.
-[Fakazile] Okay.
-Matt has the same thing, auntie, please.
[Fakazile] But you need to.
We could sort it out.
-[Zaza's son] For you I will.
-[Fakazile] Ah! Did you hear that?
"For you I will."
[in Zulu] Oh, my brother's child.
-[Fakazile laughs]
-[soothing music playing]
[Zimkhitha, in English]
Flowers are beautiful, right?
They're independent
and they just never stop growing.
Yeah, but they need someone to water them.
That's a problem.
Okay, firstly, how's that a problem?
And secondly, I actually
design self-sustaining flowers,
-thank you very much.
-What?
You know nothing about flowers.
Oh, actually I do.
I know about photosynthesis.
-Oh, photosynthesis.
-Yes, photosynthesis.
-I know about it.
-[laughing]
And I know that if you give them
too much love, they'll suffocate.
And, um, I think in this day and age
everything should be digital.
What are you talking about?
Well, I'm designing an app, an answer
to all the die-hard, unlucky romantics.
So you… you know
all about being unlucky in love?
Yeah.
I'm qualified.
So, what does-- Um, tell me
about this app of yours. What does it do?
Well…
it's, um…
It's more like this.
[romantic music playing]
-[Zaza] Cheers.
-[Princess] Cheers, friend.
The way she looked at me.
You know, it's as if
she knows something I don't.
Listen, let the estate run its course.
Okay? Beki loved you.
You know he's taken care of you.
[slams glass]
And then the drama with Leo, like…
-What's going on?
-Wait. Ooh, wait, I've got to tell you.
[clears throat]
"Princess, please,
I just want to meet her."
"Answer the phone."
"I'll keep trying you until you answer."
Shoot.
-Stalker.
-No, it sounds like a stalker.
Besides, that ship
sailed away four years ago.
-Four years.
-Yeah.
And he just walks into my gallery
-like nothing happened.
-That took me out.
[sucks teeth]
Princess, Maxwell's a good guy.
-I know.
-Maxwell loves you.
He's that perfect picture of stability.
Don't fuck it up.
I'm going to do
what is best for my daughter.
That's it.
[sighs]
["The Night" by Th&amp;o playing]
♪ Morning comes where I ♪
♪ Wake up to you and I'm not dreaming ♪
♪ Of the night ♪
♪ You call me to come around ♪
♪ Come around ♪
♪ I call the night ♪
-[Yonda] Hey.
-Morning.
Um, I… I have to run.
Oh. Okay, um, I'll see you later, right?
[sighs]
Look, I suck at relationships.
Oh, yeah, no,
don't worry about it, me too.
[Yonda] Oh.
Well, I guess you have yourself a friend.
[dramatic music playing]
Later.
[phone beeps]
[sighs]
[Leo] Clear instruction.
Who the hell gave you a clear instruction?
I'm here to see my daughter.
-[guard] I'm telling you you can't get in.
-[Leo] You're telling me--
Get out of my way.
I wanna see my daughter.
-Get out of my way!
-[Princess] Leo!
Please tell pork chops
to take it easy on me.
-What are you doing here?
-What am I doing here?
-Are you okay?
-[Leo] Yeah, she's cool.
Thanks, man, you can carry on jogging now.
And you are?
I'm Leo.
Leo.
Oh, Thandi's dad.
Yeah, that's right, Thandi's dad.
Right.
Well, we're fine, thanks for checking in.
[scoffs]
Babe, you're gonna be late for yoga.
Yoga?
[laughs] Princess, you do yoga?
Life must really be boring, huh?
Yeah, yoga beats any kind of high.
[softly] Go on.
What?
You need an Uber?
[scoffs]
-Get him out of here.
-[guard, in Zulu] Yes, sir.
[in English] Thank you.
Come back for the lamp, please.
[Zaza] What are you doing?
What the hell, Fakazile?
Your arrangements
are too hazardous for Coco.
What do you know about Coco?
Brian, I said wait.
Move!
How do you allow this?
This is nonsense, man.
This house
belongs to my niece and nephews.
And I'm here looking out
for my brother's best interests.
For the sake of his children.
I wouldn't want some undeserving bastard
to gain from my brother's blood and sweat.
Let me understand,
so you come from wherever you come from.
Come into my house
and you think you can threaten me?
-Zaza, a word, please.
-Ma?
Ma?
We just wanted to see the children.
The funeral was so rushed.
And Beki was supposed
to be buried with his father back home.
I know, Ma.
The thing is, Beki's life is here.
His children are here.
And why now? The funeral was a year ago.
Just to be here.
Where he spent his whole life.
It's part of grieving.
I need it.
I know you do, but…
The both of you make it seem
as if I didn't love my husband.
-[tuts]
-[Zaza] Ma, I loved Beki.
And living my life
every single day without him is difficult.
The only issue
I have right now is Fakazile.
[Grandma] Fakazile is also grieving
her brother. Just let her stay a bit.
Then we'll go.
Please.
[sighs]
[clicks tongue]
[softly] Okay.
Thank you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Max] I shouldn't have looked but I did.
So what, are you worried?
Nah, I'm not bothered by him.
He's not consistent.
What, she… she caving?
Look, we're building
something really special, so…
Whoa! Whoa! Max.
Just before you go down that road,
you know you don't have to
actually mark your territories, right?
-Uh-huh.
-No, no, I'm serious.
Don't do that, man, just take your time.
-Like you?
-Yeah, like me!
Yonda.
Having a territory
of your own is the goal here.
-Otherwise, what are you living for?
-[phone beeps]
Sorry, sorry, man. Just one second.
What? I'm looking for the phone.
[Max] New adventure?
Well, what you need to do, my friend,
is you need to invite me
to more exhibitions.
[laughing]
[Yonda] So, what you're looking at
is the prototype.
So the app has a function that simulates
the basic needs
that our clients look out for.
I'm also in talks
with the police department
regarding background checks.
-Our clients will be safe--
-Yonda.
This still feels detached.
Cold.
-It's--
-It's an app.
I can only fund this
from my private coffers.
And if return on investment
is not guaranteed,
I'm sorry, I can't help.
If you look at the file I sent you,
you'll see our figures are--
Based on random statistics. Hmm?
Where is proof of concept?
At least do proper research.
[monitor beeps]
[Zimkhitha sighs] Look what the sun
dragged out of the grave. What's up?
[Yonda] Well, I just presented
to my potential private investor.
Oh, wait, that was today? How'd it go?
-She wants a bloody focus group.
-That makes sense.
A bunch of random strangers
commenting on my idea,
that makes sense to you?
[Zimkhitha] It's not a bunch of randoms.
It can help you.
It's insightful, you get to understand
your target audience. So cheer up.
So does that mean you're gonna help me?
If you ask me nicely.
Well, I can do nice.
[dramatic music playing]
[Fakazile] Dubai was great and hot.
Fellas, we are in business.
We have been greenlit
to open an office over there.
I found a local construction guru
who will be our entry point.
Frank.
I need a very strong
admin team over there.
-Accounts? Where's accounts today?
-Peter's off sick, ma'am.
Why do I pay him,
if he's hardly ever at work?
Sorry, ma'am.
[Fakazile] Steven,
I'm relying on you to make sure
that all the legal documents are in order.
Everything must be above board.
Make sure that all the t's
are crossed and the i's are dotted.
-Is that clear?
-[Steven] I'm on it.
Brandon, talk to finance.
Tell them I need
a fraction from the business loan.
It is going to cost us.
But it will yield dividends.
Let's get moving, gentlemen.
[Zaza] Thato, how far are you
with the withdrawal from the loan account?
You have nothing to worry about.
I do. She has access to it and I don't.
Well, you have every right to that access.
I was minding my own business and
she scores a corner office here.
What's the worst she can do?
Send me home with no money. No children.
And the boutique
is not enough to keep me afloat.
Well, we can process a payment
to you from the loan in three days, but--
Two days.
[Yonda] I think…
the lady there in the pink.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Blond hair. Definitely "C."
[Zimkhitha] Uh-uh.
She's definitely an "A" type of girl.
[Zimkhitha] Boom!
[playfully] What did I say?
-Yeah, whatever, whatever.
-[laughs]
-[Yonda] There's a couple more to go.
-[Zimkhitha] Quite insightful, yeah?
-Really?
-Yeah, it's working.
Okay.
See? Told you.
People just wanna… play.
-Wow.
-Not all of them, Yonda.
I mean, some referenced friends
who found true love online, you realize--
Not our target market.
Come on! Such a great opportunity.
Right, just allow the market to dictate.
-Dictate?
-Yes.
It's not that deep though.
Wow.
What?
-Of course, it's never that deep with you.
-What?
[Yonda] He--
-Ah, come on.
-[footsteps fading]
[mockingly] And he chases after her,
fearlessly crossing roads
and dodging cars, or--
We need to compile the data
and look at the adjustments.
[tuts] So, you're just not gonna chase
after her?
Very well then.
[Princess] Leo, we really need to talk.
Here, come on, have a taste.
Come on, try it out.
Huh?
-It's not bad.
-Not bad? [scoffs] Not bad.
Not bad for someone who didn't forget
that you don't like onions
-and you don't like olives.
-Olives.
[chuckles]
I miss you, dude.
-How could you do that to me?
-Huh?
You heard me.
You made me all those promises.
And you just left me alone
to raise our child by myself.
-Princess.
-I trusted you.
[tense music playing]
How could you do that to me?
-I'm sorry.
-You weren't there.
You weren't there for any
of the things we spoke about.
You didn't give her
her bottle at 3:00 a.m. You…
You didn't let me
sleep in on Sundays. You--
You missed her first tooth.
You missed her first walk.
You didn't change a single nappy.
[agitated] I missed everything.
I know. Okay.
I know.
I was a mess.
I messed you up
and obviously that's unforgivable.
-Do you know that I came to the hospital?
-Oh, wow.
I was drunk out of my mind.
I couldn't meet Thandi like that.
I was an addict. A fucking drug addict!
Letting everyone down in my life.
I didn't know what the fuck I was doing!
Yeah, I didn't know
what the fuck I was doing!
But guess what?
I stayed.
[huffs] This was a bad idea. Please don't.
-[tensely] Please, please.
-Just don't.
Please don't go.
You hurt me.
I trusted you, Leo, and you hurt me.
[softly] Please don't.
-I'm so sorry.
-[exhales]
[exhales loudly]
I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
[Zimkhitha] What we actually need
is an Adulting 101 memo.
[nostalgic music playing]
[Zimkhitha] And some practicals
on how to slay our dragons.
[indistinct chatter from TV]
[phone ringing]
Hey.
[Zimkhitha] What they didn't tell us
is what lies on the road to ever after.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Zimkhitha] The traps, the truths,
and entanglements.
[music intensifies]
[Max] Hey, babe.
Hey, you're still up.
[Max] Yeah, it was your turn
to read her bedtime story.
[Princess] I know, I'm sorry, love. I, um…
I got carried away at the gallery.
I just completely lost track of time.
I'm just gonna jump in the shower quickly.
Can I join you?
[Princess] I won't be long.
Max!
-Maxwell.
-[phone ringing]
Wha-- [laughs] What is all of this?
-Just taking advantage of some alone time.
-Hmm.
[laughing]
[laughs] Max.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
We're great together.
Say yes.
Hmm.
Hey.
This is great for you, and Thandi.
[nervous chuckle]
[elated chuckle]
-[Princess laughs hesitantly]
-[laughs]
[Max] I love you so much.
We're going to be so happy.
[Max sighs]
Hey, we should invite Leon
for our engagement dinner.
-Um…
-[Max] He's family, right?
This is good.
[laughs softly]
[all] Namaste!
-Okay.
-I'm so proud of you.
-Thank you.
-Okay, there should be one good one.
-Hold on.
-Okay, wait. What? Princess!
This is amazing!
Thanks guys, it was…
Oh, it was just a…
[blows air]… small thing.
-"A small thing"?
-You know, at the house.
Listen, you ladies are killing it, eh?
I mean, new car, engaged.
Wow.
-[Princess clears throat]
-Let me get us ready for practice.
-[sighs]
-What, when, how?
More importantly, there is
a celebratory dinner at the house.
-[Zaza] Oh, that's nice.
-With Maxwell and his friends.
[Zaza] Mm-hm, okay.
And Leo.
What?
-Please come. Please, please.
-Uh, what?
And you want me there?
As an accessory to your--
What, are you crazy?
Thandi has to get to know her dad, okay.
We have to make it, like, normal.
[whispers] Please.
-[whispers] How many carats is this?
-It's a lot. It's nice.
-What will I wear?
-I know.
You should've told me
to book my salon appointment.
I know.
[Zimkhitha] All right, ladies, next
let's do a few rounds of downward dog.
Let's get our position alignment right.
Hands to the shoulders, knees with hips.
And, inhale, knees up.
Exhale, tummy to the thighs.
Inhale, straighten the legs. Exhale,
knee bend and let's just keep going.
[Zaza] Whoa, strelitzia.
Whoa, easy commander.
-Has she seen the car yet?
-Not yet.
What are they still doing here?
It beats me.
They're treating my house like a hotel.
You know how people are?
-After three days, they stink.
-[Princess laughs]
[Zimkhitha mutters]
[Princess] Okay, I can't do this.
-She's killing us today.
-[Princess] Zim.
-[Zaza] Seriously.
-Zim. Sorry.
[Princess] No, um, can we…
-[Princess] Zimkhitha.
-Yeah?
-[Princess] Can we try again next week?
-Yeah. Sure.
[loud exhale]
[Zimkhitha] Thanks, guys.
I needed that actually.
Listen, Princess, I um…
I really hope your wedding
actually happens, you know.
Some dudes propose and they go off
and marry someone else.
It's pretty fucked up.
-Huh.
-So, yeah. Namaste, ladies.
Namaste.
-Okay?
-[Zaza] That was deep.
Hmm.
Do you think that
the dinner is a good idea?
Yes.
Max is a good guy.
He's exactly what Thandi and I--
I'm not talking about Maxwell,
I'm talking about Leo.
Leo is getting
to know his daughter. That's it.
Say it to my face.
Leo is getting to know his daughter.
-[Zaza] All right.
-That's it.
-Okay.
-[phone beeps]
Who you texting?
Hmm?
-Let me see. [laughs]
-What are you? My mother?
[phone beeps]
[lighthearted music playing]
[clicks tongue] And we're hot again.
[phone rings]
Dan, hey.
No, um, let me just
check my emails. What awards?
No shit. Is… Is this real?
This is actually on my birthday, I--
[excitedly] Yes, of course
I'm coming. Yes. [giggles]
[softly] Thank you.
[tense music playing]
-[laughs] I had to go and sort it out.
-[laughs]
Why don't you eat at the table, boys?
'Cause they like it there,
Fakazile. [laughs]
There's just simply
no order in this house.
[Zaza] Why don't you go back
to your house and order?
And leave us alone.
-[Fakazile] Zandile? I'm not my brother.
-Hmm?
And I don't work hard every day
for you to just keep pillaging.
[dramatic music playing]
In a couple of days,
my brother's estate will be wound up.
And I'm here to make sure that
each and every single penny of his
does not land in the wrong hands.
Fakazile, don't you think
we should leave Zandile alone?
You're quite correct, Mummy,
we should leave her alone.
So she can go out there and live her life.
I'm sure she's already spotted
her next target.
-Next tar-- [chuckles] Fakazile.
How about you get yourself a life
and you get out of my house?
Now.
-You--
-[boy] G'night, Ma.
-Night, sweetheart.
-Night, boys.
Night, boys.
Night, Mummy.
[softly] I'm just getting started.
Goodnight.
[ominous music playing]
[Leo] Hey. So…
It's her birthday soon.
[Leo chuckles] This is from me to her.
Ta-da! [laughs]
It's her fourth birthday.
Trust me,
she doesn't need anything from you.
[Leo] Princess,
I'm just trying to make up.
-[scoffs]
-To you.
To her.
I'm getting married.
To Maxwell.
Are you happy?
-You don't get to ask me that, Leo.
-[Leo] Cool.
I mean, if he makes you happy then…
That is fine.
But no man is going to raise my daughter.
Yeah, it's too late for that.
[Max] Babe.
-Are you ready?
-Yeah. [clears throat]
You again?
-Uh, what's his name again?
-[Princess] Ah.
[Max] Leon! [scoffs].
-Hiya.
-Hi, baby.
Hi.
-Hello.
-Hi, my sweet.
[lively music playing]
[Zimkhitha] No, dude,
you have this song as well?
-This is my track.
-Don't lie--
I used to clean
the dance floor with this track.
-You? [laughs]
-Ha-ha! Yes.
-It was like, ah, eh, oh.
-Come on. Oh.
Oh!
[both] Eh! Oh!
[laughing]
Wait. I had a move. I had a move, right?
-What was your move?
-The sprinkler…
[makes sprinkler sounds]
Yeah! It's the sprinkler.
What? That move--
Why are you so extra?
Why are you like "ta ta"
-[laughing]
-[Zimkhitha] Can you just watch the road?
[thunder rumbles]
[Zimkhitha] Yeah. I mean,
I was happy, you know.
-[Yonda scoffs]
-[Zimkhitha] I was engaged.
And then he just comes to me one morning
all frantic 'cause
his Bitcoin investment went south,
and he needed some money.
[baffled chuckle] What?
Yeah. We were supposed to run
two successful businesses,
and his was in cryptocurrency.
I still don't get why
people call it a business.
Ah, I still don't understand
why I gave him my money.
And then, um…
He disappeared.
For a whole, whole year.
And then I…
I see his wedding on Instagram.
Hey! Look at you now, right? Look at you.
You're still here,
still winning without him.
You're still as beautiful as ever.
[chuckles]
[Yonda] Yeah?
["Black and White"
by Nasty C &amp; Ari Lennox playing]
♪ Let me in your temple
Show me what you're into ♪
♪ It could be so simple
Black and white yeah ♪
♪ You come first like rent due
I see our potential ♪
♪ It could be so simple like
Black and white yeah ♪
♪ I'll tell you some shit ♪
[birds chirping]
[moans]
Hey.
Hey! Hey. What's going on?
I, um, I just wanted to check--
Check up on you and…
Yonda, are you…
are you going cold on me again?
I had to come in early
because I have a meeting with Denelle.
Right.
Yeah.
Look, um, Yonda, I--
I don't really know
what's going on with you. I don't get you.
What do you mean?
Look, we're… we're great.
I mean, you know that.
You know things are so easy and…
You create a safe space
for me and things were amazing.
And then you do this.
You just completely pretend
like I'm nothing again.
Okay. Zimkhitha, um…
Look, you're great.
Right, I mean, you really are.
You, you're amazing.
[somber music playing]
But I can't be in a relationship.
I know, I know
that's what you want and last night…
Last night you--
You made me believe it was possible.
I'm so sorry.
I really am.
But I can't.
You won't even try.
Okay.
Have a good meeting.
[Fakazile]
Have we secured the office lease?
-[Frank] Yes.
-[Fakazile] Good.
-Get the contract signed.
-I'm on it.
[Fakazile] Peter, have we released
the money from the loan account?
Um, no, but someone else has.
[dramatic music playing]
Whose account is this?
Um, Mrs. Zulu.
The money was paid into her account
for a property in Sandton.
Who gave her access?
[shouts] Who gave her access?
My guess would be Legal.
They're the only ones that have access.
That Thato will be the death of us.
Thato.
You need to be honest with me.
Does FK have any right
to take over my house or just--
-Okay, hold on. What's going on?
-She's threatened me twice already.
She's threatened to put me
and my children in the street.
Talk to me, I need to know.
Okay, trust me.
You have nothing to worry about.
Promise me?
[suspenseful music playing]
Nothing is going to go wrong.
[buzzer rings]
[Leo] Coming!
[exhales loudly]
-Uh, hi.
-Hey.
-[Princess clears throat]
-[Leo] How are you?
Good.
Uh, Thandi.
This is, uh, Leo.
Your dad.
Hey.
He was very sick and so
he had to go away, but now he's, uh…
now he's much better and he's come back.
[softly] Yeah.
And you're a lucky girl, eh?
You have two dads.
Uh, it's great to finally meet you.
Princess, you want something to drink?
I've got wine,
I've got juice, I've got water.
Uh, water, thanks. Okay, let's go.
Upsy, there we go.
[Leo] I've got a lot of paint,
coloring books.
When I was young, I started out
really drawing all over the place.
Upsy, good girl. There you go.
I've got, like, some crayons,
that one's yours.
Yeah, oh, you like that one?
You can do whatever you want,
you know, um…
Remember to draw inside the lines, baby.
Inside the lines? What is that?
-I don't know!
-Exactly! Yeah, I also don't know.
You can draw wherever you wanna draw.
You can draw even on the carpet,
on the walls… [monster voice] …everywhere!
-[Princess] Leo.
-Yeah?
I'm trying to teach her something.
[scoffs] I'm trying
to free her imagination.
-Who said she's not free?
-Color between the lines?
Come on, Princess.
You draw wherever
you want. So what is that?
-[Thandi] Lines.
-Is that like a robot?
Uh, yes.
[laughing]
[Leo makes chomping sounds]
[Fakazile] Thanks for seeing me.
It's a pleasure.
[intriguing music playing]
Please show the lady around for me.
-Who is she?
-[Fakazile] An estate agent, Ma.
Zandile took money
out of the business account.
I'm simply doing my best to retrieve it.
[sighs] Fakazile, what about the children?
The children
will always be all right, Mama.
I mean, I'm ready to go home.
If you want to go home, Ma,
take the children with you.
Is that all right?
[in Zulu] Hey, Grandma.
[Fakazile, in English] Thank you.
[Leo] Yes, and what about here?
[Leo laughs]
It's a stills documentary series,
you know.
Work in progress.
Do you have a publisher?
I wouldn't waste a cent
on publishing fees.
I'm building her a legacy.
Hmm? Hmm.
What about this?
-Can I please--
-[Leo] Another one, another-- Okay.
-Leo.
-What about this one?
What about this one here?
[Princess] Leo.
You've met Thandi now. So…
Please,
don't come to the dinner.
I'm not the one you should be fighting.
-[Thandi] Done.
-Done?
Can I have a hug?
[Denelle] I have taken your proposal
under consultation and advisement.
-I will not be investing.
-Wha--
[Denelle] It lacks something.
But we did the focus groups, the research.
-And this is it?
-[Yonda] No, not all.
-We adjusted.
-Yonda.
Why are you doing this?
Hmm? What are you looking for?
You can't give what you don't have.
You have to find your fire.
-[laptop slams]
-[Yonda] Dammit.
[knocking on door]
[Yonda] Hey. So,
Denelle pulled out and now I'm stuck
and I don't know what to do.
Hey, are you okay?
Perfect.
[Yonda] Are you sure?
Yonda, what do you want?
Well, I just want
a friend to talk to right now.
-And where are your friends?
-What?
Look, I never consented
to being your friend, so where are they?
[Yonda grunts]
So, you know, she…
she asked me why I'm doing the app.
Why?
I wanna give people a break.
I wanna give people
a break from the pressure
of putting their hearts
into every relationship.
So you've decided for all of us
that relationships are pressure?
Look, it doesn't matter
what you do, these things don't work.
Okay? No matter how much
you work at it, it still flops.
Yonda, who hurt you? Hmm?
'Cause you're so bitter.
And you're cynical
and you're jaded and you're a coward.
And you're a fool.
If you think there's some fairy tale
love thing just waiting to happen,
then you're a fool.
You're not in control.
It doesn't matter
how you dictate the terms.
It doesn't change anything.
And you think everyone
wants to die lonely like you?
But at least I've accepted my fate.
Hi, Luella? Listen,
about this large order for Friday.
I… I actually, I'm done with it, so.
[Max] Hit him with the same.
-Yo, man, how you doing, bro?
-Hey.
Okay.
-I have an idea.
-[groans]
No, no, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Just hear me out.
Okay, okay. It's a reality TV show.
Dude, the madness has got to stop.
Oh, you laugh now. But you're
gonna be the first one queuing up
wanting to be a contestant on my show.
Only, I don't play games.
And frankly, at your age,
you shouldn't either.
-Your job is to support me.
-[Max] And I do.
But please, make it make sense.
Look, man.
My app bombed.
-Ah.
-Now I need another hustle.
No, what you need to do
is to make this one work.
-Oh, like you?
-Yeah. Like me.
What do you want, brah?
[sighs] Yeah, I'm leaving.
I've got a family waiting for me.
All right, man.
Give me another one.
[thunder rumbling]
[groans]
It's way past her bedtime.
You guys must have had a lot of fun.
Yeah, yeah. I know she had a lot of fun.
I don't think it's a good idea
to destabilize her routine.
I know, love, it was just--
It was just this one time.
[Max] Set up a system here.
She'll grow in it.
[melancholic music playing]
-Yeah.
-I think Leon must come see Thandi here.
[whispers] His name is Leo.
[phone beeps]
Hey.
[pants] What do you want?
Well, a lot of people
have been asking me that lately.
[nervous laugh]
Uh…
Maxwell is having an engagement dinner.
He's a really good friend of mine.
Can you be my date?
Wow.
Tell you what, why don't you
ask your app to accompany you?
Okay. Touché.
I need--
Please.
I need you.
[lively music playing]
-Oh, that's okay. Thank you.
-Okay. There you go.
[Max] Guys, you okay?
-Yeah, we good. Yeah.
-Okay, I'll just leave this here.
[buzzer rings]
[clock ticking]
-[Max] Hey!
-[phone beeps]
-[Max] Oh, good. Look at you!
-[woman] Hi!
-[woman] Princess! Hi! [squeals]
-Hi!
-Congratulations, girl.
-Oh, thank you. Oh, so good to see you.
You look stunning.
-Thank you. Please take a seat.
-[woman] Thank you!
-Hey!
-[Princess] Hi. How are you?
-Pretty good and yourself?
-Please.
-Drinks?
-Yes, please, man.
[clock ticking]
[Max] Okay. You guys
know each other, right?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Yeah.
-It's been a minute.
-I was traveling then.
Well, as you can see,
she's still blown away, guys.
[laughing]
You're a lucky girl, Princess.
[Zaza] Can I please get a drink?
-Hey.
-[laughing]
[Zaza] Hello, Maxwell.
-[Max] You look beautiful today.
-[Zaza] Thank you.
-[Zaza] Hello, sweetie. I love your hair.
-Hi!
-Hi. It's good to see you.
-[laughs]
Everyone, this is my friend, Zaza.
[all] Hi, Zaza.
Hello everyone.
[whispers] Stop.
[buzzer rings]
-Hey.
-[Yonda] Hey!
-Hi!
-[Zimkhitha] Friend, you look so stunning.
Welcome, hello. Good to see you.
-Yonda! I thought you weren't gonna come.
-[laughing]
[Zaza] Zim, let's see ya!
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] Princess.
I hear the wedding is in, like,
the next seven weeks or something.
-[chuckles] Yes.
-You know what they say.
"When you find what you're looking for,
there is no reason to wait."
[woman] A toast!
[Zimkhitha] To the couple!
[guests] Cheers!
-[lively music playing]
-[indistinct chatter]
[buzzer ringing]
-[Leo] Hey.
-Leon.
Hey. [clears throat]
Well, come on in.
Thanks.
I'll show you.
Guys. Guys.
Please welcome Leon.
[indistinct chatter]
-Leo. Hi. Hi, guys.
-Grab a seat.
[Leo] Thank you.
What is it, is it Leo or Leon?
Leo, Leon. I'll pour you a drink.
-Oh, uh…
-No, thanks.
-[Princess] That won't be necessary.
-[Max] Of course, uh…
Leon here is fighting demons.
Then aren't we all?
-[Leo] Yeah.
-Leon is Thandi's absent father.
-Maxwell!
-Oh!
But he is.
Yeah. You know what Prof.,
you're so right. I, uh, I've been absent.
But I plan to make up for all that now.
Is it?
[Leo] Yeah.
It is.
[woman] You know, Princess,
you've really struck gold
with Maxwell here.
-Babe.
-[Zaza] Oh, has she? Hmm?
-[Zim] Zaza.
-No, but she started it.
You know, everything that glitters
is not always gold.
-[dramatic music playing]
-[huffs]
-Yeah. Uh, guys, shall we?
-[indistinct chatter]
Thanks for the invite.
[Princess] Thank you so much
for tonight. It has been--
Before you thank us, who is that--
[woman] Sorry. Sorry.
Can I please use your bathroom?
Yes, of course.
It's just around the corner to your left.
Okay. It's Zozo?
-Za-za.
-"Lala," look.
If Mzwa tries to speak to you,
don't say anything.
I don't wanna have to put my hands on you.
-Oh.
-Okay?
-Princess, you… you found a real one.
-[Zaza] Huh.
Don't let him go. Okay? I'll be back.
You'll be back. [chuckles] Okay.
-It's okay. Zaza, Zaza.
-It's okay.
Okay guys, listen. You know what,
I think I'm gonna head.
-Please, don't. Please, please, please.
-No way, chill, chill, chill, chill.
So, wait.
-Yonda was the guy from yoga.
-[laughs]
-Why you laughing?
-Yonda was the guy from yoga.
-Okay, Miss Leo.
-Ooh.
-Let's talk about you.
-Let's don't.
Also, what was going
on with you at the table?
Don't put me in this thing
of yours, please, okay.
Yeah. Hey, tonight was crazy.
-[laughs]
-Like, actually, no?
Ha-ha-ha.
[Max] Bye.
[Max clears throat]
[Princess clears throat]
[Max] Well, the party's over.
It is, isn't it?
I wanna see her.
Yeah.
Yeah, um…
I'll call my mom
and find out how far they are.
-[Leo] Please.
-[softly] Yeah.
[Leo] Yeah?
Thandi's asleep, so…
She's gonna drop her off in the morning.
Just--
Please don't forget
to give her my present.
Yeah.
-I'll see you?
-[softly] Yeah.
You slept with him.
Is he what you want?
[sighs]
Maxwell.
You are what I want.
You're my peace.
You're my calm. You--
Max.
This is what I want.
[Max] No, that is what you want to want.
Princess, we are building
a solid family together.
I just wanted--
You know what?
You can go on living your lie.
My lie?
Yes, this lie that you deserve
to be with someone
that crushed you and left you.
Max!
This subservient wife shit, it's not me.
Yeah.
You know, if you don't know who you are,
everyone will tell you
who you're meant to be.
[somber music playing]
Don't blame me for your indecisiveness.
Max.
[Zaza] You know Princess,
if that basic, crass woman sells my house,
my kids and I are literally
on the streets. We're homeless.
Please just sell the penthouse
and pay back the money.
I don't want to.
So, uh, Maxwell, moved out.
Huh? What happened?
What did you do?
I mean, you know, I…
kind of slept with Leo. So…
Don't say it.
No, I won't. We know you, you're weak.
It just happened. I mean,
it's not like I planned it or anything.
Of course you didn't plan it,
you kinky cat.
-[sighs]
-And the ring?
I'm going to give
the ring back, don't worry.
-You're going. So it's still with you.
-[laughs]
Anyway, you never give back diamonds.
-I'm not you, I'll give it back.
-Slay queen.
-Stop.
-So.
-Did you-- Who--
-Oh, look. People.
-[Zaza] Slay queen.
-[laughing]
[groans]
What the hell, Fakazile?
-You're selling my house.
-[Fakazile] They've already put up a sign.
-That was quick.
-What did you do?
-Open this gate. Open this gate!
-Shush.
Mm-mm, sweetheart.
You're disturbing the peace.
This is my fucking house.
You're nothing but a liability.
And hell will freeze over
before I allow you to bring
Ben10's in my brother's house.
Excuse me?
You took the company's money
and bought a car!
A bloody car and a shag pad.
[in Zulu] Shame on you.
[in English] It was a loan, Fa--
[angrily] That loan was meant
for the Dubai Venture.
My brother was in the middle
of helping us build partnership there.
But you wouldn't know that, would you?
[in Zulu] Because you've
been gallivanting about town!
[in English] Gallivanting about town,
selling shoes nobody wants to buy
and spending money
you didn't earn, young lady.
[in English] If you paid
any attention, any attention at all,
you would know that this house
is under the company's name.
Hey! Why are you two
disgracing my son's memory
by shouting out here for everyone to hear?
My brother must be turning
in his grave watching you sleep around.
Sleep around?
[in Zulu] I caught her red-handed, Ma,
with another man!
Yes?
[in English] Yes.
We should write a letter to her family.
[in Zulu] And tell them that they
must come and collect their rubbish!
[Fakazile] Pack all your
belongings and get out of here!
Out!
[in English] You're bitter.
Why are you so bitter? Huh?
Is it jealousy?
That you've never had anyone
do what your brother did for me?
Fakazile, look around you.
All of this, the house,
the business, the car, the money.
It means nothing!
You can take it all, I will still rise.
You bully everybody that's in your life.
Your mother can't even
say anything anymore
because she's tired
of you and your nonsense!
[screams] And so am I!
[tense music playing]
[in Zulu] Go away!
[in English]
You both listen to me very well.
The noise, the bickering, the insults.
None of you is honoring my son.
And Beki never wanted this.
-[in Zulu] Daughter-in-law.
-[softly] Ma?
[Grandma, in English] Your husband
loved you very much.
His sister felt left out.
[in Zulu] And you, Fakazile.
[in English] Your brother
made his choice and he married her,
so live with it.
You both need each other
more than you realize.
You both loved my son.
Now, honor him.
Honor his memory.
[in Zulu] My children,
[in English] be nice to each other.
It won't cost you nothing.
Now that I spoke to both of you,
-I'm ready to go to my own house.
-[softly] Mama.
[Grandma] And I don't expect
to hear any of this, ever!
[in Zulu] My children. Ever!
[Thato] So, you'll be able
to put the pad on the market today.
Let's get it done.
Do you really need that car?
[Zaza] It's an SUV. Yes, I need that car.
[Thato] Well…
You might as well not sell the pad.
It's going to be your new home.
Fine.
-[man] Thank you very much.
-Thank you. Have a good day.
-All right, bye-bye.
-Thanks. Bye.
Hey.
Uh, I got a bigger paycheck
this month, so…
Listen, uh, I was thinking,
Can I have Thandi over for the weekend?
[chuckles]
Okay? That's cool.
Can I pick her up from school?
Oh?
From school to home. School to home.
Like, please?
Please, Princess.
-Fine, Leo.
-For real?
Mm-hm.
Thank you.
[Zimkhitha] You know, I'm over it.
I'm over all the nonsense,
the emotional roller-coaster ride
and… [tuts] …he just can't commit.
But anyway, on to
more exciting news, check your phones.
I'm sending you invite
and details to my awards dinner.
-Wow!
-[chuckles]
It would actually mean a lot
if you guys could come.
-Aw, well, congratulations.
-Congratulations.
And yes, we'll be there.
So excited!
[Zaza] Seeing that we're celebrating,
how about we take the car for a spin?
-Yes!
-For the last time.
-For old times' sake.
-Yes.
-[Princess] Cheers.
["Fly Away" by Bonj playing]
♪ Far away ♪
-♪ There isn't a storm ♪
-♪ Won't let you go ♪
-♪ We can't weather ♪
-♪ We'll fly away ♪
-♪ Won't let you go ♪
-♪ Far away ♪
-♪ And the harder it gets ♪
-♪ Won't let you go ♪
-♪ We're stronger together ♪
-♪ We'll fly away ♪
-♪ Won't let you go ♪
-♪ Away ♪
[Zaza moans] Harder.
Not hard, thank you, please.
You don't like it hard?
Oh, no babe, I start making noises
and it's not that type of fun.
[chuckles] No, seriously.
-[Zaza] Princess.
-Mm-mm, mm-mm.
Please my life is hard enough as it is.
[Zaza clicks tongue] Ah, babe.
[phone vibrates]
[Zimkhitha] What a perfect day.
-Thanks, friends. Cheers.
-Cheers.
-Cheers, cheers. Zaza, my cheers.
-[Zaza] Cheers.
-[Zimkhitha] You also.
-[chuckling]
-[phone rings]
-[Zimkhitha] Mm.
[Princess] Ooh.
Princess, hello.
Yes, speaking.
What?
No, there must be some kind of mistake.
Uh, thank you. Thank you
so much. I'll be right there. Thank you.
[Zimkhitha] What's wrong?
Princess?
Leo forgot to get Thandi.
She's been waiting at school
this whole afternoon.
[Princess] Hi. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Thank you so much, thank you.
[Leo] Girls!
Daddy's beautiful girls!
Guess who signed
on the dotted line? [laughs]
Are you okay?
Explain to me,
why it is that my four-year-old
was waiting outside school today for…
hours.
Oh, uh, shit.
So,
I was on my way
to the school, to go get her.
And then these guys,
they called me, Princess.
I had to go and sign the contract.
-[chuckles]
-I was gonna go get her afterwards.
Straight afterwards.
You know.
[sighs] I'm such an idiot.
-No, you're not.
-[chuckles]
I mean, you have not changed at all.
I warned you, Leo.
I begged you not to do this to her.
[Leo] I was gonna go get her
straight afterwards. I was on my way.
[breathing shakily]
Please leave.
[shouts] I said, "Get out!"
[door slams]
[Zaza] Fakazile.
Great news.
I have an offer,
which I will sign, naturally.
The children will move into my house,
Mama will always take care of them.
And as for you, dear, you can leave.
I'd like to stay longer.
I like my house.
Also, I could do so much
with this building.
Change its aesthetic.
Add a bit of color, just to make it pop.
[chuckles]
What do you think this is?
A shoe boutique?
Excuse me, ladies,
but I've got great news.
The money's been paid back.
[uplifting music playing]
[Peter] How about that?
[Zaza] This is how things will work,
you're going to teach me
everything you know.
Because we work together now.
I have skills.
Oh, Zandile, dear,
we both know the kind of skills you have.
A good for nothing, but the street corner.
And that's why I deserve the corner office
with a view of the street.
Tomorrow at 8:00 a.m.
[Zaza whistles]
♪ Take a bow look at me ♪
♪ Who the baddest baddie in this bitch ♪
♪ I'm certified bitch better recognize ♪
♪ I'm certified bitch ♪
♪ Who the baddest baddie in this bitch ♪
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Me too.
["Nothing New" by Sishii playing]
♪ Tonight I feel it more than ever ♪
♪ I feel like I'm on the peak ♪
♪ Purple haze and purple weather ♪
♪ These are heights I've never reached ♪
♪ Used to smoke and sip together ♪
♪ You didn't care that it was cheap ♪
♪ Now you're not around
Bottles I can't pronounce ♪
♪ Now that my money's loud
You ain't even down to check up on me ♪
♪ On me ♪
♪ New women all over me ♪
♪ Concealer on my skin ♪
♪ The scars that they leave ♪
♪ They don't see beyond the lights ♪
♪ I don't see beyond my mind ♪
♪ Got issues I'll be fine ♪
♪ Soon as you're back in my life ♪
-[Princess] Wow. [laughs]
-[Zaza] Wow. This is stunning.
-It's beautiful.
-[lively music playing]
[Zaza] There she is.
[Zaza] Maxine. Wow.
This exceeds my expectation.
Maxine, it is beautiful.
She didn't suspect anything?
When you placed the order for the flowers?
-No. No.
-No? Okay good.
Listen, she's here. I'd better go get her.
Okay.
I told her
the winners are doing press here.
-[Princess] Perfect.
-It is happening!
[Princess] Oh, I love the fairy lights.
[excitedly] Look at the cake.
No. No. I know you and cake.
[crowd] Surprise!
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Zimkhitha ♪
-Congratulations.
-[softly] Surprise.
-You did all of this for me?
-Mm-hm.
Thank you.
Come here.
I'd like to say a few words.
[exhales loudly]
Zaza.
Princess.
When I moved here, I…
I had no one.
No friends, no family, just…
really desperate for a fresh start.
But I found you two.
[sighs] Such strong,
resilient, amazing women
that I'm so proud to call my big sisters.
[whispers] You're welcome.
Thank you.
[sighs, sniffs]
Whoo! [laughs]
So, um… [clears throat]
…tonight is a true testament
that if you want something badly enough,
you need to go out and get it.
This was actually
my third attempt at a business,
believe it or not,
the first two failed dismally, but…
but I pushed through.
I failed forward and…
I committed right till the end.
So let's raise our glasses
for a toast. [chuckles]
To commitment.
-[all] To commitment.
-[Yonda] to commitment!
Wow. Um…
Hi.
Congratulations.
No, I should have, um…
I should've given us a chance.
I…
I shouldn't have just assumed that…
you were gonna walk out on me.
-Stop, please.
-Oh, just, just give me a second.
Just give me a second, okay.
[somber music playing]
You know I…
I loved once.
And then…
She walked out on me.
She, she left me at the altar.
I didn't wanna,
I didn't wanna pursue this.
Because,
I didn't want to fail. Again.
Yeah, but you failed
when you refused to try.
Yeah, but, that doesn't--
It doesn't matter anymore.
I'll try.
I'll try. It doesn't matter
how many times.
I'll try a thousand times,
it doesn't matter.
I'll try-- I'll fail a thousand times.
Even if it takes me a lifetime,
I'll do it.
Because I love you.
I tried not to love you, but I do.
[sighs]
[crowd cheering]
[whispers] I love you.
-Is everyone watching?
-Yeah.
["Tender Love" by Sha Sha playing]
♪ All this time I thought I was right ♪
♪ I thought I was better
I thought I was doing better ♪
Your mom is now a corporate woman.
-Wagwan. Wagwan. [laughs]
-Wagwan.
[Zimkhitha] What we're finding out
for ourselves
is that happily ever after does exist.
[laughs]
-[playful growling]
-Uh.
Okay. Okay. [laughs]
All right, so I will see you guys in…
-[Princess] Two hours.
-Two minutes!
Two hours.
-Yes. It's just lunch and ice cream.
-Okay.
Bye, Princess!
-Bye, princess bear!
-Goodbye, Princess!
Bye!
[Zimkhitha] But what we're discovering
is that ever after starts
when we choose ourselves.
To…
-New beginnings and happiness.
-New beginnings.
-Cheers.
[all] And… cheese!
[Yonda] Oh, no! No!
[Yonda] Of course, it's gotta be--
[Zimkhitha laughs]
["Tender Love" by Sha Sha playing]