Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Welcome, it's Billie,
and this is Happier Than Ever,
the first time I am doing my album
all in one, front to back.
So, enjoy.
Welcome to the Hollywood Bowl.
It's me, Billie.
I'm so excited for this,
and I couldn't be happier to be here
with Gustavo Dudamel right behind me
and the LA Phil.
I wanna thank Romero Lubambo
right over there
for playing guitar for me.
This is a dream come true.
[Billie] As you could see,
there's a choir out here.
And this was actually
the choir that I grew up in,
and, um, a song that we used to do,
that, like, beginning and ending section,
that you just heard
in the song we just did.
I just fell in love with it then and knew
that I wanted to put it in a song.
And I thought it would be really cool
to have them
actually come out and sing it here.
It's just a cute little
full-circle moment.
So, thank you to the choir.
I love you guys, and--
So the next song we have is "Lost Cause."
[whispers] So, let's do it.
It is such a thrill
to be able to do this in my hometown,
Los Angeles.
A place that really formed me
into who I am,
and I think that I took it for granted.
The older I've gotten,
the more I've come
to love Los Angeles so, so much
and be so grateful for my childhood
and my growth as a person.
LA really got me there.
[man 1] Billie! Billie!
-Yes! Billie!
-[clamoring]
-[security] Guys, don't get too excited.
-[fan] Yeah!
[woman 1] We love you, Billie!
[woman 2]
Billie, we have a present for you!
So here we are at our last song
of the whole night.
This has been a magical, beautiful,
um, amazing experience,
and I can't, uh, really believe
that this happened at all.
This is the Hollywood Bowl,
a place that has been the most
iconic venue in all of Los Angeles,
and it's a real dream come true.
It's been so beautiful and so, uh, surreal
to do this tonight,
and yeah.
We're gonna do "Male Fantasy,"
which is the last song on the album.
Thank you guys for listening,
and thank you to everyone who's involved.
I love you all to pieces,
and I will see you soon.