[♪♪♪♪♪]
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[♪♪♪♪♪]
‐Grandma?
‐Mm‐hmm?
What rhymes with "blue"?
Let's see.
Blue... "true."
"I love you."
[chuckling]
Look at all these Valentines.
We have quite a few.
Oh! [laughs]
That rhymes with "blue," too.
[both laughing]
I made a Valentine
for everyone in my class.
Oh. You take such good care
of your friends, Violet.
How many Valentines do you think
you'll get this year?
I don't know.
I didn't think about that.
You'll get one for certain.
How do you know that?
Because I have
a Valentine for you.
For me?
Mm‐hmm.
[gasps]
When I was a little girl,
I loved this music box
more than anything.
I used to wind it up
and listen to it every night
before I went to bed.
[music playing]
It's yours now.
♪ Sometimes
Inside a single moment ♪
♪ Your heartbeat
can be stolen ♪
♪ And then
your whole life can change ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[girls cheering]
And what are
the doctors saying?
Nothing?
I'll call you later,
Mary Anne.
Give him my love.
Last time I checked,
none of my grad students were
taking my undergrad classes.
What do you need, Violet?
‐I missed your office hours‐‐
‐Mm‐hmm.
...But I was hoping
to get your thoughts
on some exciting discoveries
I'm making around
the effects of music therapy
for patient rehabilitation.
Your seminar grad
is based on you writing a paper.
I know, but I picked up
some volunteer hours
at the clinic,
and it sort of
snowballed from there.
So... you didn't do a paper?
Uh, no. Not yet, but‐‐
Again.
Yes. But‐‐
Your clinical hours
are through the roof.
Thank you.
But you consistently ignore
the mandatory
written assignments
that constitute your grade.
I know it looks bad,
but I am doing the assignments‐‐
just in real life.
You applied for
the music therapist position
at the university hospital,
correct?
Of course.
It's my dream job.
[chuckles]
Well, Miss McKay...
your dedication is inspiring,
but I'm afraid
there isn't gonna be a job,
because you're not gonna be able
to graduate this semester.
What?
No, no, no, Professor Carver‐‐
I'm sorry.
I can't pass you.
Please. Please,
there has to be a way.
The university hospital
has the finest music therapy
center in the country.
They have an acoustics lab
and everything.
Well, we only have
two weeks left
and my hands are tied.
You helped this patient
regain mobility in her hands?
Yeah, I did.
What about speech?
Do you think your methods
could help a patient
regain his ability to speak?
I don't see why not.
Music has a very powerful
capacity to heal.
I have a proposition for you.
There is one...
outside‐the‐box option
that the university hospital
offers
to students
in your predicament.
You would be required to do
in‐person patient sessions
and a paper.
Absolutely.
You'd have until the end
of this semester‐‐
February 15th.
If you pass,
I will personally recommend you
to the university hospital.
If you fail,
well...
I'll see you here next fall.
I won't let you down.
Who is the patient?
My brother.
Two dozen red roses.
So, are these for your mother?
‐No, they're for my...
‐Sister?
[chuckles] No, for my‐‐
Real estate agent
who just landed you
the perfect beach house
in Cape Cod?
[laughs]
They're actually
for my girlfriend.
Great.
Okay, well, I will get those
for ya... right there.
Well, I got that.
Thank you.
I come bearing gifts.
Yes!
People did not appreciate
me tying their bouquets
with dental floss last year.
What would I do without you?
Well, you're gonna find out,
because I'm going out of town
for two weeks.
Oh...
romantic getaway for one?
Not exactly.
I have a patient
out in Stockbridge.
Wait, does this mean
you can't be my plus‐one
for the Under the Sea party
on the 13th?
Have I ever missed one of your
"O‐fish‐ally Single" mixers?
Good. Because I am going
all out this year.
Even Donna's flying in.
Wait, Donna?
‐From design school?
‐Mm‐hmm.
I thought you said‐‐
quote, unquote‐‐
she's "too perfect."
I did not say that.
It was "way too perfect."
'Kay?
[laughs]
"Way too perfect."
But it turns out
she's not so perfect after all.
She just got divorced
from her
Silicon Valley zillionaire
and told me that
she's looking to mingle again.
I'm sure she is.
Who knows? Maybe you'll meet
an eligible Stockbridge suitor
while you're out there.
[laughs]
Honestly, I think
this is the year, V.
That you finally get
your chocolate fountain
for your mixer?
The year
you finally fall in love.
Yeah, I'd probably put my money
on the chocolate fountain.
Come on.
When's the last time
you experienced
any kind of romance?
What do you mean?
I watched the entire season
of The Single Man with you,
did I not?
Well, first of all, turns out
the winner wasn't there
for the right reason.
You know.
And, second of all...
I'm talking about you, V.
You're always looking out
for everyone else.
When are you gonna
open up your heart chakra
and let someone take care of you
for a change?
Wait.
Did you just say "heart chakra"?
All I'm saying is,
it's time you
put yourself out there, V.
Let me just take care
of my patient,
get the job of my dreams,
find you a chocolate fountain,
and then...
we can talk all about aligning
my heart... chakra.
‐"Chakra."
‐Chakra.
[laughs]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[indistinct P. A. announcements]
Do these hearts
look straight to you?
[chuckles]
A little higher on the right.
Thanks.
I'm here to meet
my new patient, Charles Carver?
Let's see here.
Charles Carver
was discharged this morning.
He's under home care now.
Can I help you?
I'm his doctor.
Uh, I'm Violet.
I'm his new music therapist.
His what?
I'm gonna be treating him
for the next two weeks,
to help him regain his speech.
With music?
Music therapy has shown
to have so many positive
healing effects on patients‐‐
from lowered blood pressure
to improved memory.
Well...
so has traditional medicine.
Yeah, which, clearly, has
not been working for Charles.
Is that right?
And music's gonna make
all the difference?
‐Absolutely.
‐I'll believe it when I see it.
You mean, when you "hear it."
Ah, music puns.
Cute.
[announcement]
Dr. Williams to O. R.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I have a patient to attend to.
Uh, no. No, no,
if you'll excuse me,
I also have a patient
to attend to‐‐
a patient that is gonna regain
his speech by Valentine's Day.
He thinks
he is so important.
Dr. Williams is performing
open‐heart surgery.
He's pretty important.
Uh, can I get Charles Carver's
home address, please?
Sure.
Word of advice.
Mrs. Carver's hard to impress.
Bring a gift.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Hey. Welcome
to Max's Chocolate Shop.
I'm Max.
Hi.
Hey, if you are looking
for a Valentine's Day box,
I just made a fresh batch.
I'm actually looking
for something not romantic.
Oh. Okay, okay.
Well, hey,
we got plenty of that.
What kind of chocolate
do they like?
You know, I don't know.
And, apparently,
she is really hard to impress.
Hey. I mean, come on.
Everybody loves
a mixed assortment.
[chuckles] Perfect.
‐Yeah?
‐Mm‐hmm.
Okay.
By the way, I know
someone who's in the market
to rent one of
those chocolate fountains.
Really? Sweet.
Send 'em my way.
Expect a call from Desiree.
Desiree?
Okay, yeah, yeah.
No, I'll take good care of her.
Um, you want this personalized,
right?
Yes, please.
To Mary Anne Carver.
Mary Anne... [chuckles]
That's my grandma.
Wait, really?
Yeah.
Wait. Wait a second.
You're the music therapist.
That's me. I'm Violet.
Oh, wait. Oh, no.
She's not gonna like these.
Oh‐‐
What you're gonna want‐‐
trust me on this...
...are these‐‐
white chocolate.
White chocolate, okay.
Thank you for the tip.
It is my pleasure. Enjoy.
Here.
Thank you.
[beeping]
All right.
Your change is...
$11 and...
[drawer thumps shut]
...11 cents.
[chuckles]
Well, thank you. Again.
Yeah.
Next time, I have to come back
and get something for myself.
Okay. Can't wait.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Come in, come in.
Wow, your house
is so beautiful.
Mm. You'll be staying
in the guest house.
Oh, you must be Mrs. Carver.
Mm‐hmm.
I brought you these.
Oh. Thank you.
You shouldn't have.
He's upstairs.
This way.
It's so nice
to meet you, Charles.
I'm Violet. I'm gonna be
your music therapist
for the next two weeks.
I see that you are
a very big music fan.
You used to play?
That's great.
Music appreciation helps.
I don't think we're gonna have
any problem making progress.
Well, we're counting on it.
I'm just gonna stay in
for this first session,
if you don't mind.
Yeah. No. Not at all.
Okay, Charles.
So why don't we start
with some basic scales?
That should be a piece of cake
for a seasoned musician
like you.
Sing after me.
♪ Do, re, mi, fa, so... ♪
No problem.
Let's... hum along instead?
[Violet hums scales]
Try it with me.
Your turn.
You know what?
Why don't we back it up
and take it slow?
And we can do
some simple rhythm exercises.
You good with that?
Five, six, seven, eight...
[she claps]
Let's just forget the clapping.
Let's imagine moving our fingers
and playing
our favorite instrument.
Yeah. Just like that.
Okay, um, you know what,
I think that's‐‐
that's enough for now.
Oh, we're just getting started.
This is an assessment
and it's tricky‐‐
Violet, I'd just like
to speak to you for a minute.
I... yeah.
Look, I want this to work,
I really do,
but I'm having a hard time
believing that it will.
Just give me a couple days
with him,
and you'll start to see
some real progress.
It's been a difficult year.
[sighs sadly]
We were married
on Valentine's Day.
It'll be
our 50th anniversary this year.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You know, he's the same man
I've always loved.
And I love him
just the way he is.
I just wish I could hear him
say "I love you"
on our anniversary.
You have my word.
Okay.
Your sessions with Charles
will be every day at 9:00 a. m.
Don't be late.
Oh, and my grandson
has volunteered
to supervise his sessions.
The chocolate maker?
What? Oh, no, no.
No, the other one. The doctor.
No, he has rearranged
his surgery schedule
for the next two weeks.
Oh! Violet.
Meet my grandson,
Dr. Blake Williams.
‐We met.
Well, great, because you two
are gonna be working together
for the next two weeks.
Just what the doctor ordered.
Music to my ears.
Hey, I'll take a beer.
Whatever you got on tap.
Is that...
Hot chocolate.
Don't you get
enough chocolate at work?
Clearly,
you've never been in love.
You are projecting
because you can't find a date
for Valentine's Day.
See, you spend too much time
in that chocolate shop, buddy.
What's this?
Rose petal‐infused truffles.
[host] And the last carnation
after a word from our sponsors.
[Desiree] Oh, come on!
They always cut right before
the last carnation.
Okay, catch me up
on your new patient.
I mean, I don't
usually get nervous
about these sorts of things,
but between Professor Carver
and Mary Anne,
it's a lot of pressure.
I basically promised them
a miracle by Valentine's Day.
I hope I'm not in over my head.
No way. You're brilliant.
Dr. Blake Williams
doesn't think so.
Who's Dr. Blake Williams?
He sounds handsome.
He's just this guy who thinks
that he's better than me
because he knows
how to use a scalpel
instead of a piano.
Hey, did you hear that Grandpa
is doing music therapy?
Mm. Don't remind me.
All right? This "therapist"
is overly‐idealistic,
and she's gonna make Grandpa's
recovery ten times harder.
It sounds like
this music therapist
has really gotten
under your skin, huh?
Not really.
He is arrogant and difficult,
and he is making my job
twice as hard.
Sounds like you really care what
this Dr. Blake thinks.
No, I don't care
what he thinks.
I care that he ruined my day.
And my pedicure.
Well, if he's got
a cute brother,
just let me know.
Anyway, it's like
what my grandma said,
you know,
tomorrow is a new day.
Hey. You got plans next week?
Working with
the music therapist
in the mornings.
Only a couple of surgeries
on deck. Why?
I need you to come by the shop
and help me out.
I'm drowning in orders.
Why do people get so crazy
about Valentine's Day?
You're only saying that
because you've had your heart
broken too many times.
You can't stay Stockbridge's
most‐eligible bachelor forever.
No, I believe that title
belongs to you.
[laughs] Yeah.
And I think this is gonna
this is your year‐‐
this is gonna be the year
that you find
your soulmate, Maxey.
Really?
Oh, absolutely.
Oh, my gosh, it's back on.
[host] ... who are you going
to promise forever?
Lauren A
is definitely going home.
[engine rumbles off]
Hello.
Morning.
So, uh, I got to get back
to the hospital
for surgery
in a couple hours, so.
Sounds serious.
Are you sure you shouldn't
get going right now?
You know, as much as I would
love to miss music class,
I love my grandfather too much
to leave him
in questionable hands.
"Questionable hands."
Do you know
the steadiness of hand
that it takes
to play Stravinsky?
Let's just get
this over with.
Let's.
I spoke to Mary Anne
and I thought we would
change up the environment.
Hi, Grandpa.
How are you feeling today?
So, I thought, instead of
just jumping into making music,
I thought that maybe we could
listen to some music.
Huh?
Music memory has the power
to unlock muscle memory.
Okay. Breathe in, Grandpa.
[deep breath]
Breathe out.
[exhales deeply]
You're a little congested.
I'll ask Grandma
to make you some hot tea.
Earl Grey, right?
Musical vibrations
can also boost immunity.
The tea should do the trick.
[zips bag up]
Wow...
Look at all the records.
Is this you?
Grandpa was pretty famous
in the local scene.
He would have made it big
if the label hadn't gone under.
But his instrument business
did pretty well, huh, Gramps?
[jazz music playing]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Today was good.
He didn't seem to hate it.
A doctor with a motorcycle?
Is there a problem?
No. Just doesn't seem
like the best idea
for someone
who works at a hospital.
All right.
See you tomorrow.
Unfortunately.
[engine revs]
Good morning, Lucille.
Looks like we made it
just on time.
Is the physio room ready?
‐It sure is.
‐Okay, Grandpa.
Morning, Charles. Blake.
What can we do for you, Violet?
Nothing. I just heard
from Mrs. Carver
that you changed Charles'
physical‐therapy appointment
to this morning.
Yeah, there was
a last‐minute opening.
Yeah, but it's my time
with him,
so maybe you'd like some music
to accompany your physio?
No, I'm sorry,
but this is a doctor‐and‐patient
only session.
Come on, Grandpa.
Let's go.
It's just down here.
You all right?
[doorbell chimes]
Oh. Flowers and chocolate.
Yup.
[gasps]
‐Grandma. These are for you.
‐What?
Oh, thank you!
Sweet. Mm.
Come on in.
Ahh.
So thoughtful.
[whispers] If you really
want to win her over,
she's a huge Emily Bronte fan.
Ahh.
What‐‐
What are you doing here?
My grandmother told me
you were buying records
for Grandpa Charlie.
I'm here to vet them.
You're joking.
Grandma wanted me
to invite you to dinner
with the family tonight.
Really?
Well, unless, of course,
you're busy.
No. I mean,
that's really nice of her.
‐Ah.
‐I'll be there.
Do you even like music?
My grandpa
was a jazz musician.
I love music.
I just don't believe
in music as medicine.
Okay.
So who's your favorite band?
I don't have
a favorite band.
Because you don't really
like music.
No, because
I like solo artists.
Hendrix. Janice Joplin.
Paul Simon.
Paul Simon was half of a duo
before he became a solo artist.
Everyone knows
Simon was better on his own.
I disagree!
All of his best songs
were with Garfunkel.
"Bridge Over Troubled Water,"
"Sound of Silence,"
"Mrs. Robinson."
Well, I am buying Grandpa
a Paul Simon record.
Or, I mean, we could compromise
and get him a collection
of greatest‐‐
...love songs?
Wow, Mary Anne,
this looks delicious.
Oh, it's actually
my mother's recipe.
She always said the fastest way
to a man's heart
was through his stomach.
Medically untrue.
But that was interesting,
because, as it turned out,
I was hopeless in the kitchen.
I clearly did not inherit
the cooking gene,
like our Max did.
That's right!
[laughing]
But, luckily enough,
Charles didn't seem to mind.
He was happy just to go out
for dinner,
especially if
there was live music.
Our very first date
was at this quaint
little jazz club
in Stockbridge.
Wow. Living on the edge,
Grandma.
Hey. Hey!
And right
in the middle of dinner,
he was invited up
onto the stage‐‐
to...
to play the saxophone.
‐[laughing]
‐I mean...
I didn't know what...
it turned out
it was his band!
[laughing]
It was all a set‐up.
It was so sweet.
Oh, I was so...
enamored.
Ah.
What song were they playing?
Um...
It... "It Had to Be You."
Yeah. "It Had to Be You."
Aw, Blake.
Is that why you used to sing
that song with your band?
Wait! You had a band?
No, no.
It wasn't a serious band.
It was just a group of us
from Doctors Without Borders
doing covers
for the locals in Belarus.
Did this band have a name?
It was the, uh...
[mutters] ...it was
"the Heartmenders."
‐What?
‐Come again?
"The Heartmenders."
‐[laughing]
‐That's what it was!
‐Heartmenders.
‐It was!
He was wonderful.
Wow. Is there a solo career
in your future, Mr. Simon?
No. No. I'm retired.
So what about you, Violet? Huh?
You have a‐‐ a musical family?
I do, yeah.
As a little girl,
I was raised by my grandmother,
and there was always music
through the house.
She had
the most beautiful voice.
I still feel like
she's watching over me.
[Mary Anne] Oh, that's so sweet.
Uh... I would like
to make a toast.
Oh.
To...
‐...The Heartmenders.
‐Of course.
‐[laughing]
‐To The Heartmenders.
[indistinct exchange]
Here's your coat.
Thanks.
You know, that was nice,
what you said‐‐
about your grandmother?
I was raised
by my grandparents, too.
So, do The Heartmenders
have an upcoming show?
[laughs] Very funny.
‐I know the lead singer‐‐
‐All right, all right.
...so I don't want them
to sell out of tickets.
You know?
Maybe a backstage pass.
If you play your cards right.
[cell phone chiming]
Des. What's up?
I have a flower emergency!
An order just came in
for a wedding‐‐
their florist fell through.
I am already up to my neck
in baby's breath
with everything
I have to prepare
for Valentine's Day,
and I just‐‐ I do not
have enough hands
to assemble
the wedding flowers in time.
Okay. All right. Don't panic.
I will be there in...
Two hours?
Oh, my...
I'll be there soon.
Ah, you're the best.
Really soon. Okay. Bye.
You know, there's a game
tonight, Violet.
You'll get there
a lot faster on a bike.
Yeah. No.
[laughs] What, are you scared?
No, I'm not scared.
[Blake]
You're pretty good at this.
Ah. Weddings. So romantic.
Hey, this reminds me of
that episode of The Single Man,
when he surprised Lauren G
on a date on a hot‐air balloon
filled with flowers
and, oh!
Poor Lauren A did not
appreciate that gesture.
That show is such a racket.
I mean, they know each other
for what, two weeks?
All of a sudden, they're
supposed to fall in love?
That doesn't happen
in real life.
Dr. Williams here
is a realist.
That's right.
He doesn't believe
in what he can't see.
Love... musical therapy.
I believe in love,
all right?
I just don't believe
in Valentine's Day.
You know, the flowers,
the chocolates,
the flying baby
with a bow and arrow
he menacingly points
at unsuspecting singles.
Okay.
Leave Cupid out of this.
I personally
love Valentine's Day.
It's the one day a year
you get to unapologetically show
people how much you love them,
with flowers and...
[sighs dreamily]
...oh, chocolate.
Maybe I should start
loading these in the truck.
Mm‐hmm.
Excuse me.
Side bar‐‐
I approve.
What do you mean?
Oh, you two
are perfect for each other.
What?
No! No.
Yeah, you
with your big heart,
him with his cool exterior,
just waiting to be loved.
Yeah, you know what?
Actually, it's perfect.
Except for the fact that
we cannot stand each other.
Hey, he drove you
all the way from Stockbridge
and he stuck around to help.
I think you're just
a hopeless romantic.
Oh. "Hopeful romantic."
Hopeful.
Who knows? Maybe
I should start planning
your floral arrangement
for your wedding.
So?
We all set?
Yep. Yep, yep.
I think we've accomplished
everything we needed to tonight.
Yeah. And you know what?
Here you go.
"O Fish Ally Single Mixer."
Valentine's Day Eve?
That's a thing?
Oh, I'm making it a thing.
Now you've been
cordially invited.
Who knows?
Maybe Cupid will... tch...
strike ya...
with his arrow.
Luckily, I'm a surgeon.
[laughs]
That's good.
Oh, I definitely approve.
We're here.
[chuckles awkwardly]
‐You okay?
‐Yeah.
Thanks for that.
I probably...
would have still
been sitting in traffic.
It was nothing.
You know, I'd do the same
for any, uh, colleague.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah. Thanks, Doc.
[engine revs]
[cell phone ringing]
Professor Carver. Hi.
This is
your midpoint check‐in,
Miss McKay.
How's it going?
Great. Wonderful.
Oh. Your enthusiasm suggests
you've made progress.
Yep.
Uh, well, I don't‐‐
I don't know if I would say...
There's definitely been‐‐
So, Charles hasn't spoken
a single word yet?
No.
But‐‐
You are less than a week
from your deadline.
Are you sure you can do this?
Yeah. We are right on track.
Then I won't keep you.
♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ Wake unto me ♪
♪ Starlight and dewdrops
are waiting for thee ♪
♪ Sounds of the rude world
heard in the day ♪
♪ Lulled by the moonlight ♪
♪ Have all passed away ♪
That was beautiful.
Imagine...
we're taking a trip
down memory lane.
It's the night of
your first date with Mary Anne.
Can you picture
what she's wearing?
I'm wearing a red dress.
So, now, you're holding
the door open for her.
And what do you say?
Um...
maybe visualization
doesn't work on Charles.
I think we should take
a little break.
11:11.
You know...
whenever my grandmother had
a day that wasn't going her way,
she would stop
whatever she was doing,
and she would
sing her favorite song.
Just to get things
back on track
and to switch things up.
What do you think?
One more?
I think you're gonna
like this one.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ It had to be you... ♪
♪ I wandered around ♪
♪ And I finally found ♪
♪ Somebody who... ♪
♪ Could make me be true ♪
♪ And could make me be blue ♪
♪ And even be glad ♪
♪ Just to be sad ♪
♪ Thinking of you ♪
♪ Some others I've seen ♪
♪ Might never be mean ♪
♪ Might never be cross ♪
♪ Or try to be boss ♪
♪ But they wouldn't do ♪
♪ For nobody else
gave me a thrill ♪
♪ With all your faults ♪
♪ I love you still ♪
♪ It had to be you ♪
♪ Wonderful you ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
Charles.
[laughs]
Heard you singing.
Your voice, it's, uh...
it's something.
Thank you?
Yeah.
I heard you used to sing.
I'm sure your voice
is something, too.
Are you okay?
You know, it didn't sound
like you and Grandpa
really needed me in there...
as far as
the music therapy is concerned.
[crack]
He hummed along, you know.
Yeah, well, not exactly
clinically significant,
but not bad.
You are unbelievable.
Someone's got to be
a realist, right?
Yeah, more like
an impossible pessimist.
Well, better than
a blind optimist.
Gah, you're so... so...
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
What happened?
‐Nothing.
‐You all right?
‐Yeah. I just got a splinter.
‐Let me. Let me see.
No, I'm good!
‐I can do it on my own.
‐Let me see.
Trust me. Trust me.
‐I can do it on my own.
Trust me.
Let me see.
Ouch. Ouch, ouch, ouch.
‐There.
‐Ouch!
Got it. It's out.
That wasn't so bad, now,
was it?
Thank you, Doctor.
Might not be able
to play Stravinsky,
but I'm pretty good
with my hands.
Cute.
[chuckles]
Wow. Black coffee?
Even your drink is pessimistic.
I resent that.
I value the taste
of real coffee.
That looks like
it's gonna give you a cavity.
[chuckles]
You, uh,
you have beautiful eyes.
And some whipped cream
on your lip.
Ah.
Is that...
Hey, Jimmy!
He played trumpet
in my grandpa's jazz band.
How're you doing?
Well, well, well,
if it isn't the Carver boy.
‐Miss.
‐Hi.
How's your grandpa holding up?
Me and the boys wanted
to come by
and pay a visit,
but we didn't want
to disturb Mary Anne‐‐
she's one tough cookie.
You should try bringing her
some white chocolate.
She's not wrong.
I'll keep that in mind.
Well, I don't want
to disturb your date.
Well‐‐
no, it's not a...
‐It's not a...
He plays a mean trumpet.
Wait, so, the whole band
still lives in town?
Yup. I guess local celebrities
don't like to leave.
I cannot believe
that the Heartmenders
left Belarus behind.
What can I say?
My patients needed me.
We still get the occasional
piece of fan mail.
[laughs]
Your grandpa's proud of you.
I can tell.
Thanks.
I just wish there was more
I could do for him.
So do I...
but I think
you've been good for him.
I mean, don't get me wrong‐‐
I'm still a skeptic,
but I'd be lying
if I said
he didn't look happier
this past week
than he has in a long time.
So...
um, you have any plans tonight?
Uh, Desiree got me
this rose oil face mask, so...
Wow! Busy schedule.
Are you...
...Asking you to help out
at my brother's chocolate shop?
Guilty.
[laughs] Are you kidding?
You helped tie, what,
a hundred bouquets for Desiree?
So I'd say
it's the least I could do.
Awesome. Max will be thrilled
to have another helping hand.
You, uh...
have a little more
whipped cream.
I can feel
the cavities forming.
[both chuckling]
‐Maxey.
‐Hey! There you guys are.
Okay. Yeah. Oh!
I'm up to my eyeballs
in fondant.
Are you guys ready?
Huh? Yeah, okay,
'cause I need you here.
All right.
Is he gonna be okay?
Oh, yeah, 100% normal
pre‐Valentine's Day behavior.
I do 12‐hour surgeries‐‐
nothing compared to this.
Okay, what do I need?
What do I need?
Come on, come on,
let's go, let's go.
Um, yeah. That's good.
So... what're we making?
It's almost Valentine's Day.
We're making everything‐‐
starting with
my world‐famous chocolate‐
covered Graham crackers.
The secret is‐‐
[brothers]
...Two layers of chocolate!
Yeah! [laughing]
You look like
you know what you're doing.
Yeah.
Blake helps me every year.
Whether I want to or not.
Come on, man.
[laughs] Oh, wait.
You know what?
I need some maple syrup,
because that is
the second secret ingredient.
This might be a good time
to tell you
that I am a terrible cook.
Well, luckily,
we're baking, not cooking.
It's more science than art.
Oh. So that's why you like it.
Bingo. Can you stir this?
Yeah.
Thanks, Doc.
So why did you
become a doctor, anyway?
Well, there's a lot of reasons
I became a doctor.
It's, uh, methodical, orderly.
There's generally a reliable way
of doing things
in order to achieve
a certain outcome.
That's very practical.
And you know
the other reason.
Can you crumble these?
Uh... sure.
What is "the other reason"?
Ah, it's, uh...
it's kind of mushy.
They're Graham crackers.
Aren't they supposed
to be mushy?
No, I mean, the other reason
I wanted to become a surgeon.
It's a...
It's a little mushy.
Well, your secret
is safe with me.
Chocolate makers' code.
[chuckles]
Okay.
I lost my parents
in a car accident when I was 11.
I'm sorry.
Max and I moved in
with our grandparents
not long after.
I asked for a stethoscope
that Christmas.
So you knew you wanted
to be a doctor
since you were a kid?
I don't know, I guess.
And what I really wanted
was to do everything I could
to help people
never experience
the heartache
that I went through.
You know, I thought
if I studied hard enough,
I could...
change the outcome...
for other people.
Gives new meaning
to being a heart doctor, huh?
Told you it was mushy.
No.
It's sweet.
What about you?
Why'd you decide
to go into music therapy?
I also lost my mom,
and my grandma raised me.
I used to sing to her
and she always told me
it made her feel better.
So right before she passed away,
I made her this promise that...
...no matter what,
I would try to use my voice
to heal people.
Wow.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
So, who's the special person
in Violet McKay's life?
[chuckles]
There is no special person.
Why not?
Because.
I don't know.
My last relationship ended
with him moving away to Denver.
You didn't want to go with him?
He didn't ask me.
Which is fine,
because it allowed me
to pour my time and energy
into my career.
Huh.
Well, I'd say
that was a colossal
error in judgment on his part.
Thank you.
So what about you?
When...
When was your last relationship?
Ended about two years ago.
Found out she cheated on me...
one week before
I was gonna propose.
Perfect timing.
Well...
I'd say
that was a colossal error
in judgment on her part.
[footsteps approaching]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You gotta keep stirring
or else it's gonna get too hot.
Sorry. Right.
Maxey.
Yeah. Okay.
You're doing great.
Like this.
‐Okay. All right.
‐And keep going.
Ooh, look at that.
Wow.
We did it.
You can come back next year,
Violet,
because your baking was superb.
What about me?
Yeah, you were okay.
[chuckling]
For your information,
music therapy has been around
since the days
of Plato and Aristotle.
[Blake laughs]
They believed
that it contributed positively
towards public health.
Well, who am I to argue
with the greats?
Have you ever listened
to ABBA's "Dancing Queen"
and not smiled?
Or how about,
every time I hear
Adele's "Someone Like You,"
I bawl my eyes out
like a baby.
Celine Dion‐‐
"My Heart Will Go On."
I mean, there's a tearjerker.
[laughs] See?
You're starting to get it.
Music can tap into
our emotional systems.
I'll be driving my car
and a song will come
on the radio,
and, instantly,
I am just transported back
to that certain time in my life.
A song can stimulate our memory
in powerful ways.
It can make us feel things
we haven't felt in a long time.
Well, uh,
speaking of nostalgia...
I have a little surprise for you
back at the house.
Come on.
You've got a whole rotisserie.
That's right.
[Violet laughs]
So, when do I get to hear
this famous singing voice
of yours?
Right about never.
That is not fair!
You heard me sing.
You basically have
the voice of an angel,
you know,
so I'm a little intimidated.
What's your favorite song
to sing
when you're not
seeing to patients?
That's a tough one.
♪ Sometimes ♪
♪ Inside a single moment ♪
♪ Your heartbeat
can be stolen ♪
♪ Suddenly, your life
can change ♪
You make me blush.
♪ I've been a little scared
of wondering ♪
♪ If maybe there is something ♪
♪ That keeps
pulling me your way ♪
Wow.
You're incredible.
Thank you.
It's my grandmother's song.
Here you go.
This looks great.
I'm gonna take this to go.
It's getting late.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow?
Yeah. Yeah.
Goodnight, Violet.
Goodnight, Dr. Williams.
This was fun.
This looks good.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[Blake]
So what do you think, Grandpa?
You wanna take it out
for a spin?
Let's see those fingers
we've been practicing.
Outstanding!
Let's improvise.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[accompanying on piano]
[playing notes expertly]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Bravo. Bravo!
Well done, Grandpa.
That was amazing.
[Blake] Wow.
So good.
Are you sure you don't want
any hot cocoa?
I think I've had
enough chocolate‐‐
for the year.
[laughs] For the year?
Let me guess.
You're not a big V‐Day fan?
‐Eh.
‐That's a shocker.
I like that it means something
to my grandparents‐‐
50 years together,
that's quite an accomplishment.
It certainly means something
to Desiree and Max.
Ooh...
I've just never really had
a reason to celebrate it,
personally.
Well, now you do.
Your grandfather is the reason.
Right.
So, I take it
you're a big V‐Day fan?
[chuckles]
Well, I love me a love song‐‐
that's for sure‐‐
but I guess I was more into it
when I was a kid.
Every year, my grandma and I
would make Valentines
for everyone in my class.
And this one year,
she gave me this music box.
I still have it.
I can't fall asleep at night
unless I hear that song.
Your grandma sounds like
she was a pretty amazing lady.
Music has always been a way
for me to feel close to her.
Well, I'm sure she would've
been proud of you, too.
I'd like to think so.
I know this might sound
a little weird,
but every time I see "11:11,"
I know she's with me.
It was just our special number.
Can't believe I only have
a few more days left
with your grandpa.
Why the deadline to get Grandpa
to speak by Valentine's Day?
Because, if I don't,
I have to retake the class,
which means a whole new
trimester at school,
and I don't think my dream job
at the university hospital
will still be waiting for me.
You know, my cousin, Charlie,
works there.
Might be able to put in
a good word for you?
I didn't realize you were under
so much pressure.
[chuckles]
Would you have been easier
on me if you did?
Not a chance.
Didn't think so.
Looks like Cupid threw up
in your basket.
Wow. You really despise Cupid.
How could I despise a baby?
I just think he should
put some clothes on.
I'll have you know
I am starting to warm up
to this whole
Valentine's Day thing.
Wow. One trip to the market
and you're like a brand‐new man.
[chuckles]
Hi.
Okay, we got streamers...
napkins...
candles, plates...
And every kind of heart
the market has to offer.
What's with
all the decorations?
I don't know,
I was feeling kind of festive.
I thought maybe I'd go decorate
the guest house, you know?
Romantic Valentine's Day
for one.
You are adorable.
Just don't
let my grandmother see.
Wait a second.
What if we decorate
their living room?
I'm confused.
I just told you my grandma
doesn't do decorations.
No. No, no. No, no.
Listen. Hear me out.
What if we decorate it
and surprise them
for their 50th?
It's not every day
that they get to celebrate
a milestone like this.
Okay. I'm in.
Here you go.
Wait. Did you just say
you were in?
Yeah.
[cash drawer rumbles]
Huh. 11.11.
Weird.
Thanks.
Are you spotting me?
Yes, I'm spotting you.
What are you doing up there?
You got it?
I think that looks pretty good.
Hey! I think
I hear them coming.
Oh, okay.
[both] Surprise!
What do you think, Grandma?
I think...
I think it's wonderful.
Thank you.
‐I'm glad you like it.
‐Yeah.
And this is perfect
for our 50th, too.
[chuckles] Oh, you.
Thank you.
Ohh.
Oh, this is so lovely.
[giggles]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Brussels sprouts?
Mm‐hmm.
Oh, that's bad,
but it's the only one
you've missed so far.
Ah, this is
such a romantic movie.
Right?
[chuckles]
I love black‐and‐white films.
What do you say
we give these two lovebirds
some time alone?
You want to go get some snacks?
Yeah, snacks sound good.
[blurts]
Hey, did you say "snacks"?
[lowers voice] Sorry.
Buttered popcorn, please.
You got it, Grams.
[actor] Well, she's pretty...
I can't remember
the last time
Grandma and Grandpa
went on a proper date.
I can't believe that
they've been together 50 years.
Most of the contestants
on The Single Man
they don't even last six weeks.
You really like that show?
I support Desiree.
Would you ever
go on The Single Man?
What? No. No.
I would totally lose.
I would become best friends
with all the women.
I'm not very competitive.
[laughs]
You could've fooled me.
You are the exception.
Good luck.
Oh. So it's my fault?
I hope Desiree finds love
at her singles mixer.
You going to that thing?
Yeah, of course,
I go every year.
It's her big night.
Can we get two orders of wings
with fries and two sodas,
please?
Plus, there's gonna be
a chocolate fountain there.
Oh. Again with the chocolate!
Are you going?
Who do you think's
getting suckered into carrying
that chocolate fountain?
You know, I think
it would be kind of cool
if two people fell in love
at the mixer, you know?
Like, love at first sight?
Well, it happened
to my grandma and grandpa,
so I think it's possible.
Number 11!
What about Mr. Denver?
Was that love at first sight?
Ha! Uh, not really.
It wasn't that "Cupid's arrow
hitting you in the chest"
head‐over‐heels
kind of love.
Poetic.
What can I say?
I dabble in poetry.
‐Oh, yeah?
‐Yeah.
Let's hear one.
Roses are red.
Violets are blue.
So far, so good.
I don't remember the rest.
Oh, come on.
Sorry.
Okay, my turn.
Let's hear it, Shakespeare.
Roses are red.
Violets...
are blue.
Okay.
I don't know
about music therapy...
No, you don't.
But I think
I'm coming around on you.
How'd I do?
I think that was
too many syllables.
I'm pretty sure
that was iambic pentameter.
[chuckles]
Oh, I think
I remember my poem now.
Oh, yeah?
‐Mm‐hmm.
‐It's never gonna top mine.
Just wait.
See? Competitive.
[chuckles]
Okay, roses are red.
‐Okay.
‐Violets are blue.
Doctors can be arrogant...
Hey!
But their hearts can be true.
All right. Not bad.
Not bad?
That was spectacular.
"Spectacular"
might be a bit much.
Okay, well, it was marvelous,
at the very least.
Satisfactory.
"Satisfactory"?
[woman] Hey!
You're blocking the movie!
Sorry!
We forgot the popcorn.
The popcorn! Right!
Hey, Grams, be right back.
‐Just getting some popcorn.
‐Free popcorn.
[music playing]
[knocking]
[giggling]
Surprise!
What are you doing here?
I started to make
Valentine's Day cookies,
but the idea of making
V‐Day cookies all by myself
felt too depressing.
What's wrong? You look off.
What? Nothing.
Mm‐hmm.
I guess
I'm feeling a little...
confused.
Oh. Is this about
Dr. McHandsome?
N‐No.
No.
What's there
to be confused about?
I guess I just‐‐
I wasn't expecting to...
I wasn't looking for...
Love?
What? No.
Nobody said
anything about love.
I just...
you know what I think it is?
I think that it's all this
Valentine's Day stuff.
It's just getting to my head.
That's it.
Okay, well,
forget about all this.
Because we...
we have to break some hearts.
‐Okay.
‐Shh.
It's okay, it's okay.
Shh. Des, no.
This is a terrible idea.
No, it's totally fine, okay?
We'll be super‐quiet.
No one will never know
we were here.
‐[crashing]
‐Oh!
‐[frantic whispering]
‐Stop. Where'd it go?
Excuse me?
[shrieking]
[chuckles awkwardly]
Cookies?
My issue is
I've got plenty of matches
on Love‐Link,
but the minute
I get passionate
and start talking about how much
I love flowers and romance,
they disappear.
Do you think
I'm scaring away
my soulmate?
We didn't have
all this crazy technology
when I was dating,
and I certainly had
my fair share of, um...
..."love links,"
I think it was.
But this is what I learned,
Desiree‐‐
you cannot scare away
your soulmate.
You just can't.
The right one will love you
just the way you are.
Wow. You're so intuitive,
Mary Anne.
[laughs]
[gasps softly]
Maybe you could help Violet
with...
her love life.
What's up, Violet?
Let's hear it.
Violet
has this...
‐Friend.
‐Mm‐hmm. ...Friend.
A friend...
that you want
to be more than a friend?
Well, up until recently,
I really disliked him.
Mm‐hmm. What changed?
It's like he has this tough
outer‐shell around him.
Like a candy?
But on the inside,
he's...
Sweet and wonderful?
Something like that.
Mm.
It's just the more
that I learn,
the more I seem...
[to not dislike him
as much as I thought I did.
Oh.
So what are you waiting for?
[whispers]
I think she's scared.
You know
I'm sitting right here?
I'm just saying!
Okay, so. So, you are the girl
who takes care of everyone else,
but won't allow
her own soulmate in?
Is that it?
Oh! She is so wise.
My advice?
Listen to your heart.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[indistinct P. A. announcements]
Did you make these?
You know, I can't believe
I'm actually saying this,
but yes.
I baked cookies.
Do you want one?
Yes!
Dr. Williams,
you've gotta try these.
Did I just hear that correctly?
You're baking now?
I learned from the best.
Let's see here.
Um... anatomically incorrect.
Mm.
Almost good enough to make me
a Valentine's Day believer.
So what brings you in?
Trying to make some new friends?
Well. I just finished
a double session with Charles
since the deadline
is around the corner.
Did you need me to come back?
I could get someone
to cover my shift.
No, no, no.
Your patients need you.
And Charles is actually
doing really great.
Mm.
I actually stopped by tonight
because...
Why don't we, uh,
step over here for a minute?
What's up?
I was thinking‐‐
Mm? Yeah, well,
that's a good start.
Maybe we could go
to the O Fish Ally
Singles Mixer.
Yeah. We already
talked about that.
Together.
Oh.
As colleagues.
‐Yeah.
‐Colleagues.
As colleagues.
You know,
we could drive together.
Save some gas.
‐Mm.
‐What do you think?
Okay. Sure.
Great.
Great. Well,
I'll pick you up tonight.
Perfect.
Well, enjoy the cookies.
Thank you. I will.
[awkward chuckles]
[overlapping] Bye.
[under her breath]
"Save some gas"?
Just for the‐‐
Hi! Hi. Yeah.
The fountain's not here yet.
Wait, what do you mean?
And I already tried calling
the chocolate shop,
and no one answered
and I have
the perfect spot for it,
but, uh, it's not here,
so...
Your chocolate fountain
is on its way.
It better be.
Oh, hey.
Hi.
Max is heading
in the same direction,
so I figured we could just
all drive together.
You know.
Save on gas.
[forced chuckle]
Sure.
[Max whistling off‐key,
drumming on knees]
Hey, you got any tunes?
Uh, yeah.
Here you go.
[soft rock playing]
Really?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Yeah... why?
Nothing.
I just didn't expect that.
I like it.
Can't we just enjoy the ride...
quietly?
What? No. No, no, no.
We gotta get pumped up
for this party, man. Come on.
To this?
Okay, fine. Here.
Is this better?
[DJ] Coming up next,
one of my personal favorites.
Oh, yeah! Yeah‐yeah‐yeah‐yeah!
I love this song.
Turn it up.
Okay, here.
♪ Just take that old record
off the shelf ♪
♪ I sit and listen to 'em
by myself ♪
♪ Today's music
ain't got the same soul ♪
♪ I like that old‐time
rock‐and‐roll ♪
[Blake joins] ♪ Don't try
To take me to a disco ♪
♪ You'll never even
get me out on the floor ♪
♪ In ten minutes
I'll be late for the door ♪
♪ I like
that old‐time rock‐and‐roll ♪
♪ Said I like
That old‐time rock‐and‐roll ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]
So you made
most of this yourself?
‐Is that cardboard?
‐No, that's not cardboard.
"O Fish Ally Single Mixer."
I love that name.
You do?
Yeah!
Des!
You made it.
Happy Valentine's Day Eve.
You remember Donna,
my old classmate?
‐She flew in just for the party.
‐Hi.
I wouldn't miss it.
[gasps] Ah! Your dress!
[Donna laughs]
So, Des, tell me‐‐
uh...
Don't tell me.
Excuse me.
Happy Valentine's Day Eve.
Your fountain...
has arrived.
‐Oh...
‐Yeah.
Oh, my God.
He looks amazing.
Who, Blake?
No. Him.
Max?
That's Max?
Yeah, that's Blake's brother.
[whispers]
Blake has a brother?
So, where do you
want this thing?
‐[mouths words]
‐Uh...
I think you can
just put it over there.
Cool.
‐[giggles]
‐Hello?
Hello.
‐[laughs]
‐Hi.
Uh, w‐who is that?
Who, Desiree?
Excuse me.
Well, if you didn't believe
in love at first sight before...
Yeah, no kidding.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[Violet]
Look at them‐‐
not a worry in the world.
You say that like you've got
something on your mind.
I have one day left to get
your grandfather to speak.
Listen, you have made
excellent progress with him.
I'm sure my grandmother
and great‐aunt
will be happy regardless.
I hope so.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[laughs]
Uh... you wanna‐‐
‐Yeah.
‐Yeah?
‐Okay.
Is this okay?
‐Yeah.
‐Yeah?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
So, um...
tell me how you got to be
so incredible.
[quickly adds]
...At‐at‐at all this.
Honestly,
it started
at the farmer's market,
and I met this cute
married couple with a farm
who had to throw away
their extra flowers every week,
so I volunteered
to deliver the extras
to the local hospital,
which is where I met Violet,
and then I realized,
I could support
local farmers' work
if I opened up my own shop
and only sourced local flowers,
and, yeah,
and then the business
ended up taking off,
and now everybody's winning,
and I basically get to do
what I love every day,
which is work with flowers
and support romance,
and do you possibly just want
to run away right now?
Oh, no. No way.
I mean, that‐that is incredible.
I mean it, seriously.
You're doing
what you're passionate about,
while you're helping
the community.
Exactly. You get it.
Oh! Man down.
It's a little more complicated
than I thought.
Tell me about it.
At least love
is in the air tonight.
Really?
For some.
I think
Desiree can start planning
the flower arrangements now.
Ah. Right.
I don't think I've ever seen
Max like anything that much.
Well, except chocolate.
Do you believe two people
are meant to be together,
like your grandpa and grandma?
What?
You mean, like, soulmates?
Yeah.
Two people destined
to find each other,
and no matter how hard
they try to mess it up,
inevitably, they end up together
in the end,
because it's written
in the stars, or something.
Doesn't sound very logical.
What do you mean?
What if one person
lives in Boston,
and the other person
lives in...
Stockbridge?
I was gonna say London
or Tahiti.
[chuckles] But sure.
I mean, how are they
supposed to meet,
let alone fall in love?
Well, I think that's where
the destiny part comes in.
Hmm.
So you don't believe in
the romantic notion
of soulmates?
I don't know, maybe.
But I don't believe in destiny
like you're describing it.
I like to believe
that there's free will,
and that one of these people
from Boston or London or...
Stockbridge.
One of these people will
make a choice at some point.
Take action.
Tell the other person
how they feel.
But what do I know?
You know,
I only operate on hearts.
I don't claim to know
their secret wants and desires.
Hmm.
Will you excuse me
a second?
Yeah.
I bought a frog desk,
and I named it "Bubble"...
Hi, Violet.
What's up?
I'm sorry.
Can we talk?
Oh, yeah, of course.
I will be right back.
Okay.
I know I said that this was
the year that you fall in love,
but I think
it might be my year.
I think it might be
both of our years.
What? Dr. Blake
finally admitted
he's in love with you?
Well, no. Not exactly.
But I think
I'm gonna do it tonight.
I'm gonna tell him
how I feel.
Oh!
Violet, you're finally
opening up your heart.
Yeah,
and it's really uncomfortable.
Well, that's how you know
you're growing.
Thanks.
Or at least that's what
Mary Anne says, anyways.
We're friends now.
We text.
‐Yeah?
‐Mm‐hmm.
Okay.
‐Deep breath.
‐Okay.
You're doing the right thing.
Mm‐hmm.
I know you better than
anybody else on this planet.
You deserve to be loved.
‐Okay.
‐Okay?
Okay.
Now, you're gonna
march over there‐‐
Mm‐hmm.
And you're gonna say,
"Dr. Blake"‐‐
I don't call him that.
It doesn't matter.
I like how it sounds.
‐Okay. Okay.
‐All right? Okay.
"Dr. Blake, I am
falling in love with you."
I am falling‐‐
[words catch]
"...In love..."
‐...In love.
‐"...With you."
...With you.
"I'm falling in love with you."
Exactly. See?
There's nothing to it.
You can do this.
I can do this!
Yes!
What if he doesn't
feel the same?
Are you kidding me?
I've seen the way
he looks at you.
How?
Like you're the only woman
in the world.
[chuckles]
Are you ready...
to give
your final carnation?
[chuckles]
I am.
That's my girl.
Okay. I'm doing it.
‐Okay, you got this. Go, team!
‐Go, team.
‐[smack]
‐Thanks for the pep talk.
‐Oh, I love you.
‐Love you.
[Des squeals]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Uh, Donna, hi‐‐
Oh, Violet‐‐
there are so many men
at this party.
How is a girl to choose?
[giggles]
Uh, speaking of men‐‐
did you see where the man
that was standing here went?
Was he tall?
Yeah.
Handsome,
like he could be in a movie?
Yeah. That's him.
Yeah.
He's over there
with that blonde woman.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Oh! She is gorgeous.
[Donna laughs]
Should've made your move sooner.
I mean, she's the definition
of perfection.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[phone chimes]
[phone rings]
Violet?
I'm at my brother's house.
Oh, Professor. Hi.
Listen, I know that I said
he would be speaking
by Valentine's Day,
but I have a whole day
with him still,
and I think that‐‐
Uh, no.
I'm calling
to congratulate you.
You are?
I know the assignment
was to get him to speak again,
but... look at him!
I haven't seen my brother
this happy in a year.
And he's playing again.
You did
an outstanding job, Violet.
In fact,
I've already placed a call
to the university hospital.
You're graduating.
You've got the job.
[stammers]
I don't know what to say.
Say yes.
That's your dream, isn't it?
And take tomorrow off‐‐
Mary Anne can get
your things together.
I'm sure you have someone
who would love to spend
Valentine's Day with you.
‐Melinda!
‐I have to go.
We're about to play
Valentine's Day‐themed Scrabble.
I get very competitive when
I'm playing against my brother.
Take care.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[Max] Let me get that.
Thanks.
Uh, hey, buddy.
Just keep it running.
I'll be right back.
Violet?
What are you doing here?
You okay?
Yeah.
You know what? I'll just...
I'll see you tomorrow.
Sure. Thanks for the fun night.
That was‐‐
that was the best.
[chuckles]
I'll call you?
‐Yeah.
‐Yeah?
[giggles]
Okay.
‐Bye!
‐Bye.
‐Hey.
‐Hi.
What happened?
I don't want to talk about it.
Yes, you do.
He doesn't feel the same.
Oh.
You know what they say?
A carton of ice cream a day
keeps the doctor away.
‐Too soon?
‐Mm‐hmm.
‐[chuckles]
‐Too soon.
Thanks for this.
I really wanted to, Des.
I did. I...
tried to open up my heart,
like you said.
Now it's too late.
[knocking]
That'll be the pizza.
What are you doing here?
Can I talk to Violet?
Violet doesn't want
to talk to you right now.
Des?
It's okay.
I assume Max told you
where you could find me?
When I realized you left,
I caught a ride back
to my grandparents' house,
but you weren't there.
My grandmother
must have missed this
when she was packing up
your things.
I know how much it means to you.
Thank you.
Can we talk?
Sure.
So why'd you leave
the mixer like that?
I don't know.
I was tired.
Violet.
I saw you.
With that beautiful blonde.
You had your arm around her.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What‐‐ what blonde?
You mean Charlotte?
I don't need to know her name.
We call her "Charlie."
After Grandpa Charlie.
She's my cousin.
...Who works at
the university hospital?
I was talking to her about
putting in a good word for you.
I mean, did you think
that she and I were...?
No. No.
‐Because that‐‐
‐I mean, even if you were,
why would I care?
Right.
Right!
So it was just
a huge misunderstanding?
Yeah, I‐‐
I think it is.
Ah.
Well, congratulations.
Heard about your job.
Oh, gosh, I almost... forgot.
Yeah, no, it's really exciting.
Their music‐therapy center
is second to none.
I know you still don't
believe in what I do‐‐
Violet.
I still don't know
if I believe in music therapy...
but I believe in you.
I don't even know if
I believe in myself right now.
What?
What are you talking about?
I‐‐ Look at all the good
you've done.
I gave your grandmother
my word‐‐
that I would have him
speaking by tomorrow.
And I'm gonna keep my word.
Okay. What can I do to help?
Do you happen to have
your grandpa's old friend
Jimmy Golightly's number?
No.
But I know where he hangs out.
Him and the boys still play
at the old jazz club in town.
[chuckles] Huh!
Perfect.
Do you like it?
I love it.
Hey! Hi.
Hey, this was such a great idea.
Thanks.
Have you seen your brother?
Yeah, he texted me‐‐
he's stuck at the hospital.
Okay. Uh...
I guess I'll go stall them.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
‐Hi.
‐You want to go sit?
‐Yeah.
'Kay.
Hi, everyone!
Thank you for coming
to Mr. and Mrs. Carver's
Valentine's Day 50th
Wedding Anniversary celebration.
‐Whoo!
‐[cheering and applauding]
Sing something!
[Max] Yeah! Sing something!
Um...
uh, well, I guess I could,
but only because the main act
is running a little bit late.
Have you ever heard her
sing before?
No. Never. Why?
You're in for a treat.
This is an original song
and it was actually
written by my grandmother
and it's called "11:11."
Tonight,
I want to dedicate this
to that beautiful couple
sitting in the front row.
They just celebrated
their 50th wedding anniversary.
I think I speak on behalf
of everybody in this room
when I say
that theirs is a really special
and inspirational relationship.
[cheering]
Whoo!
I hope you like this.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ Sometimes ♪
♪ Inside a single moment ♪
♪ Your heartbeat can be stolen ♪
♪ Suddenly
your life can change ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ I've been ♪
♪ A little scared
of wondering ♪
♪ If maybe there is something ♪
♪ That keeps pulling me away ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ How could life
ever be the same? ♪
♪ Wish I could tell you
what I'm thinking ♪
♪ Wish I could say
what's on my mind ♪
♪ Wish I could find
the words to tell you ♪
♪ All of the things
I feel tonight ♪
♪ Wish I could show you
what I've been through ♪
♪ How I wished for you
every day ♪
♪ All that I know
is something's different ♪
♪ I know I've never
felt this way ♪
♪ Felt this way ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ Missin'... ♪
♪ What have I been missin'? ♪
♪ So many years not listening ♪
♪ To what my heart would say ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ I've been a little scared
of trying ♪
♪ But now there's no denying ♪
♪ That the future's on its way ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ How could life
ever be the same? ♪
♪ Wish I could tell you
what I'm thinking ♪
♪ Wish I could say
what's on my mind ♪
♪ Wish I could find
the words to tell you ♪
♪ All of the things
I feel tonight ♪
♪ Wish I could show you
what I've been through ♪
♪ How I wished for you
every day ♪
♪ All that I know
is something's different ♪
♪ I know I've never
felt this way ♪
♪ Felt this way... ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ Felt this way ♪
[cheering]
[applauding]
Whoo!
And now I'd like to invite
everyone's favorite doctor
to the stage.
Yeah!
Whoo‐hoo!
[applause]
[whispers]
That... was spectacular.
Everyone, please put
your hands together
for Stockbridge's very own
Dr. Blake Williams!
[cheering and applauding]
Grandma, Grandpa...
Happy Anniversary.
There's no place
I would rather be
on the most romantic day
of the year
than the place
you had your first date.
We love you.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ It had to be you... ♪
♪ It had to be you ♪
♪ I wandered around ♪
♪ And I finally found ♪
♪ The somebody who ♪
♪ Could make me be true ♪
♪ Could make me be blue ♪
♪ And even be glad ♪
♪ Just to be sad
thinking of you ♪
♪ Some others I've seen... ♪
♪ Some others I've seen ♪
♪ Might never be mean... ♪
♪ Might never be mean ♪
♪ Might never be cross ♪
♪ Or try to be boss ♪
♪ But they wouldn't do ♪
♪ For nobody else
gave me a thrill ♪
♪ With all your faults
I love you still ♪
♪ It had to be you ♪
♪ Wonderful you ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[shakily]
♪ I love you still ♪
♪ It had to be you ♪
[applauding and cheering]
Boy, your voice is something.
Thanks, Garfunkel.
You, uh, happen
to see the time?
Guess Grandma Louise
got a ticket to tonight's show.
Hey, there's something‐‐
something I've been meaning
to tell you.
It might sound crazy,
because I know we've only known
each other for two weeks.
I know I said I don't believe
in any of that Cupid stuff,
and I'm pretty sure
The Single Man
is all scripted, anyway, so...
What I'm trying to say
is, uh...
You're falling in love with me?
[chuckles nervously]
Yeah.
[♪♪♪♪♪]