Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Maybe.
It depends if they get
another cash offer.
Sorry.
Hey, I just found this in the lot.
Thanks.
Sam.
Last chance for you to come with us.
I'm good.
And you're sure you're gonna be okay?
I'll be at college in five months.
I know. I know.
Go to the meet. I'll be fine.
And you promise,
you're not gonna have anyone over?
Yes.
Including Nikki.
I think that's dumb, but, yes.
If her mom is around, her place is fine.
She's still not out to her mom yet.
-Please, let that go.
-Okay.
-Mom, hurry up.
-I'm not gonna fight about it.
Right.
Hey.
I love when you wear this jacket.
Thanks. I like your whole outfit.
Thanks.
I'm worried someone's gonna see
and tell your mom.
We're not doing anything bad, okay?
We're just… being together.
For two whole days.
-Okay.
-Okay?
You ready? You ready?
I'm ready.
-Oh my God. What?
Oh my goodness.
You're literally like the coolest person
I've ever met.
How would your senior year have been
different if you didn't move here?
A lot more boring.
I hated my old town.
Why?
I had to pretend to be
someone I'm not, you know?
Hmm.
I do.
How would your senior year be different?
Also pretty boring.
There are no queer girls at school.
I've noticed.
But that's not the only reason.
Oh, yeah. No. Me either.
You gotta keep stirring.
Did your mom teach you this?
We were all taught the basic stuff,
but this I learned on YouTube
so I can make it for you,
which means it might be very bad.
High stakes.
When you said, "We all,"
you mean your older sisters?
Yeah.
You don't talk about them much.
We're not close.
Do, um…
any of them know about us?
Not yet.
Here.
Okay, I'm actually mad
at how good this is.
-Really?
-Yes.
I wanna eat this and kiss you
at the same time. Come here.
-Gross.
-Come here!
Hey, honey, you live here?
Yeah.
Great, um, do you know
which way to Mountain View?
Up on the left.
Perfect. Thanks so much.
This feels different today.
Different how?
Almost like we're living together?
I hope this doesn't sound crazy, but
I think you should come
to Nashville with me.
I know you don't wanna do college,
but you could get a job.
We can get an apartment near campus.
I've always wanted to adopt a cat
with a really weird face.
Like a scrunched up one
that gets grumpy all the time.
Well, maybe we should wait
a few more months to decide
just in case you change your mind.
What?
Which would be really understandable.
I love you.
Do you not feel the same?
Oh, no, no. I…
I'm just worried
you don't know me well enough.
We've spent every moment
that we can together for months.
I know.
I try not to lie,
but there are things about me
and my family I haven't told you.
What does that mean?
When I was younger,
my sisters and I would do these races,
like, to see who's the strongest
or the fastest.
And this one time, I was in second place.
I really wanted to win.
So,
I threw a rock at my sister's head.
Was she okay?
She needed 18 stitches.
What did your mom say?
She was happy I won the race.
How did you feel when you did it?
Proud of myself.
That's bad, right?
I've had issues… with my dad.
So, I know how hard family can be.
I love you.
Sam…
I want you to have that cat.
But it can't be with me.
I'm sorry that I can't explain more.
But I promise, one day, if I can ever
make things different, I'll come back.
I'll find you wherever you are,
and I'll tell you the truth.
Show me your hands.
Please. Please don't hurt me.
-Let me see your hands!
No, please.
I don't understand.
Hands!
Now!
-What--
-Don't say anything.
I'm here. You can untie her.
I liked your hair shorter.
She doesn't know anything. I promise.
But I'm curious what she does know.
Who do you think this is?
Nikki, my girlfriend.
Wow. What do you tell her?
Your parents just work a lot?
That's why she's never seen them?
I assume she's never seen
that shithole you sleep in.
You're so selfish.
Fine! I'll go back!
I'll do whatever Mom wants.
Mom wants punishment.
What do you think that looks like?
You can't take her.
I am taking her.
Don't worry. Mom said not to kill you.
Just to beat the fucking shit out of you.
Ty, please, you're my sister.
You're too weak to be my sister.
Stop! Stop, don't!
Please stop! Stop!
You are killing her!
Stop! Please don't do this!
No, please don't do this!
Don't hurt her! Stop! Nikki!
Nikki! Nikki! Nikki!
Nikki, please! Nikki!
Nikki, hey!
Nikki!
I promise, one day,
if I can ever make things different,
I'll come back.
I'll find you wherever you are,
and I'll tell you the truth.
I love you too.