["AMAZED" BY LONESTAR PLAYING]
Every time our eyes meet
This feeling inside me
- [BIRD CALLING]
- Is almost more than
I can take
Baby, when you touch me...
Patrick.
Adeline.
This is going to be the best
Valentine's Day ever.
This place...
it's just so gorge.
PATRICK: Of course it is, babe.
- You picked it!
- I picked it!
- [BOTH LAUGHING]
- [SLOW, HEAVY BREATHING]
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [SONG CONTINUES OVER SPEAKERS]
Oh.
Mmm. Mmm.
Mmm.
[GROANS]
What the hell?
I told you
not to put it in my food.
- Oh, shit. I'm sorry. Sorry, I--
- It's fine. Keep going.
Uh...
Adeline Delilah Garrett.
You're smart.
- You're beautiful.
- [MOUTHING ALONG]
And perhaps
most important of all,
you make me think.
You're my person and I can't
imagine my life without you.
- Will you marry me?
- [MOUTHING ALONG]
Yes. A million times, yes!
I don't know how
you do what you do
I'm so in love with you
- It just keeps getting...
- [SONG STOPS]
[RINGTONE PLAYING "PONY"]
[RINGTONE STOPS]
Why are you
calling me right now?
NICO: I didn't get it.
PATRICK: What the fuck
do you mean you didn't get it?
Yeah, I'm sorry, dude.
There was a couple
of sun flares and, like...
Um, could you maybe
do it again or...
Why, yes. Let me re-propose
to my fucking girlfriend
so you can do your job right.
- Technically she's your fiancée.
- Don't get cute with me.
Do it right this time
or I'll fucking end you...
- on Yelp.
- Okay, cool, thanks.
I'll talk to you later.
I'm not even on Yelp, dick.
[GROANS]
Uh, speech, speech, speech.
Lovey, lovey-dovey.
Uh, and, uh...
Will you marry me?
Yes. A million times, yes.
[OVER SPEAKER]
I'm so in love with you...
Just one second.
- [LINE RINGING]
- [SIGHS]
Give me that. Hello?
NICO: Nico the Photo Guy.
Leave a message.
- [SHARP THUD]
- ADELINE: Are you fucking
kidding... me?
[PATRICK CHOKING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]
[ARROW WHIZZING]
[OVER SPEAKER] I'm so in love...
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHIMPERING]
- [ARROW WHIZZES]
- [SCREAMING]
[HYPERVENTILATING]
[SOBBING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[ARROW WHIZZES]
[SCREAMING]
[CRYING] Oh, no!
[WHIMPERING]
[PANTING]
[SCREAMING]
[RINGTONE PLAYING
ROMANTIC CLASSICAL MUSIC]
[PHONE VIBRATING]
- [RINGTONE AND VIBRATING STOP]
- [BREATH TREMBLING]
Hello?
[HEAVY BREATHING AND CHUCKLING
OVER PHONE]
You listen here, asshole.
[SNIFFLES]
I have been planning this day
my whole life...
and you fucking killed him!
You messed with the wrong bride.
[PANTING]
You hear me?
You messed with the wrong fu--
[SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHIMPERING]
- [SCREAMS]
- GUARD: Whoa.
Ma'am, you can't be here.
- What are you doing?
- He's trying to kill me!
[SCREAMING]
GUARD: Hey, buddy, you wanna
tell me what's going on?
Wait. Stop!
Drop the knife, asshole!
[SCREAMING]
ADELINE: Somebody! Please!
[WHIMPERING]
[SOBS LOUDLY]
[BLADE RINGS SOFTLY]
[HEAVY BREATHING THROUGH MASK]
[MUFFLED HEAVY BREATHING]
[GASPING QUIETLY]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [WHISPERING] Oh, shoot.
[BREATH TREMBLING]
[PANTING SOFTLY]
[CHOKING]
- [YELPING]
- [KILLER GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Take that, you motherfucker!
Go away!
[MUFFLED] You go away!
You go away!
- You go away!
- [BEEPING]
[ALARM BUZZING]
[MECHANICAL CLANK]
No.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no. Please!
Hey! Hey!
[MECHANICAL RUMBLING]
[SCREAMS] No!
[SCREAMS]
[GASPING]
[SCREAMING]
No!
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
["HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY"
BY OUTKAST PLAYING]
Happy Valentine's Day
Every day the 14th
I don't think y'all heard me
I just wanna say
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Happy Valentine's Day
Every day the 14th...
REPORTER ON TV:
It's Valentine's Day
and the nation
is once again on high alert.
For the past two years,
a masked maniac
known as
the Heart Eyes Killer...
...or HEK, as authorities
call him for short,
has emerged on a day
meant for romance
to target, hunt
and brutally kill couples.
HEK seems to target cities
at random.
From a blood-soaked rampage in
the Boston area two years ago...
...as well as a second
killing spree,
which left several dead
in Philadelphia just last year.
Even though he's after
couples in love,
let me be perfectly
clear about this...
He will kill anyone
who gets in his way.
...leaving Americans
once again plagued with anxiety
on Cupid's holiday
asking the question...
Where will the Heart Eyes Killer
strike next?
Happy Valentine's Day...
FEMALE REPORTER: Do you expect
the Heart Eyes Killer
to kill your
Valentine's Day plans?
Who the hell
makes Valentine's Day plans?
Yeah, this holiday sucks ass,
dude.
- Literally.
- [BLEEP] Valentine...
I ain't even low-key scared.
The HEK ain't got nothin' on me.
You know...
Oh, shut up, Dylan.
You're afraid of the dark.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
No, I don't.
Happy Valentine's...
MAN 1: The Heart Eyes Killer--
WOMAN 1: So glad I'm single.
MAN 2: I'm gonna
celebrate inside.
WOMAN 2: That dude hunts you.
MAN 3: ...rubbing your shitty
PDA all up in our faces.
MAN 4: He only kills
straight people, I think.
REPORTER: Whether you're with
a partner or looking for love,
stay vigilant
this Valentine's Day.
["I NO LONGER BELIEVE IN
MIRACLES" BY ADA RAY PLAYING]
'Cause the one
Who says
He loves you
Has found
Someone new...
Shit!
[ALL LAUGHING]
- [CHUCKLES] Nice one, dipshits.
- BARISTA: Got a cappuccino here.
Hope Cupid
shoots you in the dick.
Caramel soy latte for Monica!
- MONICA: Oh, that's me.
- Okay, yeah. There.
Why do you look so stressed?
Is it 'cause you're single again
on Valentine's Day?
No, I'm... [SIGHS]
No, I'm stressed
because Crystal just called
an all-hands meeting
and the subject of her email
literally says
"Ally's Campaign."
- Mm, I saw that.
- So I'm fucked.
Okay, worst-case scenario,
you get fired and you never work
another day in your life. Hmm?
Worst-case scenario, Crystal
wears my skin as a pantsuit.
Best-case scenario,
you got nice skin though.
Boop. You know what? Whatever.
If you go down,
I'll go down with you, okay?
We'll Thelma and Louise
this shit.
BARISTA: Large iced
blended Americano
with oat milk,
two honey, one sugar.
- Mm.
- JAY: Oh.
Sorry, are you sure
that's yours?
Yes, that is definitely mine.
No one else would order...
ALL: ...a large iced
blended Americano
with oat milk,
two honey, one sugar.
Sugar. Yeah. Look at that. Wow.
Guess we're coffee mates.
- [LAUGHS] Nice dad joke.
- Thanks.
I thought I was the only one
in the world with
- the obnoxious coffee order.
- [LAUGHS]
It's a pretty
common order actually.
Can you guys move? We're busy.
Yes.
[WHISPERS] He's hot!
Hey, can I interest you
in one of these guys?
Oh, no, I'm okay. Thanks.
I carry my own.
- Oh. Metal straw.
- I hate paper straws.
They just turn into mush
in, like, three seconds.
Yeah, no. I totally get
what you're saying.
Let's put all the coffee
in a plastic cup,
but, hey, as long as the straw
is paper, planet saved.
- Planet saved.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Oh, sugar though. Want one?
- Yeah.
A little slow poison
for the pancreas.
- Oh. Oh!
- Oh. Ooh!
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
- I'm sorry. No, I'm--
- [LAUGHS]
- Sorry.
- I got it. It's okay.
- No, it's totally--
- Oh! Fucking Jesus Murphy!
- Shit! Oh, my God. Are you okay?
- Yeah. Am I?
- Oh, my God. You're bleeding!
- Uh, here. Shit.
- Oh-- Uh, thank you for that.
Bye. Um, I'm gonna go.
I'll see you at work, Mon.
Sorry.
She's getting fired today.
REPORTER ON TV: Exactly one year
after a Valentine's Day massacre
left three couples dead
in Boston
and four couples dead
in Philadelphia,
the Heart Eyes Killer
has come to Seattle.
Four victims have
now been claimed at a winery,
ending one dream engagement
in a nightmare.
Chief Hartley, is this the work
of the Heart Eyes Killer?
That's not confirmed
at this point,
but given the pattern
of targeting couples
on Valentine's Day,
we suspect it's the work of HEK.
What do you have to say
to all those couples out there
planning to celebrate
Valentine's Day?
- Stay home.
- [TV BEEPS]
[CRYSTAL SIGHS] Well.
[SMACKS LIPS]
This is quite a pickle.
[SUCKS TEETH]
Why didn't a single one of you
tell me that there is a maniac
running around
slaughtering people
on Valentine's Day
these last couple years?
Tommy?
Not a single one of you.
This campaign
is certainly ill-timed.
Wouldn't you say so, missy?
Uh... Um...
- [CLEARS THROAT] I mean--
- You know, Crystal, um,
how you always tell us
that relevance is really
important in our pitches?
Well, I personally believe that
Ally's campaign is very "now."
Monica, thank you so much.
If you could do me a huge favor.
Shut the fuck up.
Tommy?
["THAT'S WHY I CRY" BY
MARGARET LEWIS PLAYING OVER TV]
My baby's gone
[GASPS]
[SOBBING]
He's gone away
He won't be back
[THUNDER CRASHES]
That's why I cry, cry, cry
Cry, cry, cry
All the time
- All the time
- [GUNSHOTS]
He said, "Bye-bye..."
[SONG STOPS]
[WOMAN COUGHS]
"Wow. Profiting off the death
of couples to sell rings."
"Speechless."
- "This is disgusting."
- I'll say.
TOMMY: "What did I just watch?"
"Straight-up tacky."
"Someone find out who made this
and dox their ignorant ass."
- I mean, it just-- it goes on.
- CRYSTAL: I'm sure it does.
Ally, I'm worried
about your safety.
Gee, thanks, Tommy.
How many people has this
heart-shaped asshole killed?
I think, like, a lot.
CRYSTAL: A lot? [SCOFFS]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- You built a nationwide campaign
around romance ending in death?
Well, you approved it.
Because I trusted you.
I'm gonna need a new campaign.
- Okay. Um, no problem. I'll--
- Jay, get in here.
Jay? Who's Jay?
JAY: Thank you very much.
BOTH: No way.
That's the guy whose nose you
smashed in at the coffee shop.
Mon, sit down.
CRYSTAL: Jay Simmonds,
everybody.
This is Jay Simmonds.
Who's Jay Simmonds?
Well, I'll tell you.
Jay Simmonds is the former
CCD of BMY New York.
He is the youngest freelancer
to win a Clio Award
for his viral
romantic campaigns.
Everything from fancy cars
to luxury chocolates. [LAUGHS]
And, he has then earned himself
a nice little moniker
of "Consumer Cupid."
- That is Jay Simmonds...
- [GASPS] That's him?
...and I'll tell you what.
When I realized how far up
shit's creek
Ally here had paddled us,
I knew I needed
some reinforcements.
And thank Baby Jesus.
Now, he's got to leave
and push off tomorrow
and skedaddle,
so he's on the clock.
Jay. Everybody, Jay!
Thank you for the lovely
flattery, Crystal.
I appreciate it. Um...
Listen, as I understand it,
we've experienced
some turbulence as of late,
but it's about how you land
the plane that matters, so...
we will get through this...
together.
[SIREN WAILING]
[ELECTRONIC WOLF WHISTLE]
OFFICER: What the hell was that?
FEMALE OFFICER: I got a match.
OFFICER: Oh, for fuck sakes.
We're gonna get married.
I can feel it. [SIGHS]
[SIGHS] That's your boyfriend?
Yeah, he will be.
He's an actual firefighter
who loves puppies.
[GASPS]
[SMACKS LIPS] You see?
That's why you're still single.
- [SIGHS]
- You know what you need, Shaw?
You need a real man.
One that's willing to make
the first move.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
HARTLEY: Come on, detectives.
You're gonna love this.
Check it out.
OFFICER: What is that,
a wedding band?
Could it be one of the victim's?
Unlikely. [SIGHS]
The initials engraved
on the inside... JS.
Doesn't match
either of the deceased.
Huh.
[FLIES BUZZING]
What kind
of an animal would do this?
Probably some incel virgin troll
living in his mommy's basement.
Assuming it's a man.
What about the girl
who never got asked to prom?
The love-scorned woman who got
cheated on one too many times
- and just snapped.
- [ELECTRONIC WOLF WHISTLE]
OFFICER: Oh, fuck.
Oh. Yes. He replied. [LAUGHS]
OFFICER: The gay fireman?
No, no. This guy works in tech.
- Shaw's got a fetish for betas.
- I don't have a fetish.
BOTH: Everybody's got a fetish.
Gentlemen, this is more
than just a simple murder.
It's a...
...kink.
That's the understatement
of the fucking year.
How do you know for sure
it's HEK?
FORENSIC WORKER:
Here you go, Detective.
'Cause this is the last thing
the wedding photographer
ever saw.
Heart Eyes
has come to our city, boys.
And they've got
another ten hours
of Valentine's Day left to kill.
[CAMERA CLICKING]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Excuse me.
What in hell are you doing?
What do you mean? You just fired
me in front of the whole team.
Fired you? I got six more months
on your contract.
I intend to squeeze every single
last drop out of you. [CHUCKLES]
Okay. Great. So what
am I supposed to do?
Get him coffee
while he lands the plane?
No. You're gonna
turn in a sizzling,
sexy, seductive, blockbuster
Crystal Cane campaign.
And if you don't, I'll kill you.
I'm kidding. I won't.
I'll blacklist you, though.
I won't kill you.
I mean, maybe.
But no.
But would I?
ALLY: "Whoever made this,
I hope you get
"murdered and canceled.
Not in that order."
"Hashtag do better."
"As someone who may die someday,
"I find this commercial
"to be tone-deaf
and borderline ableist."
Wow, people are fucking dumb.
"The only thing deader
than the couples in this ad
"is the brain cell of the person
who created it."
"The level of cringe
in this video is off the charts.
"Hashtag just stop."
- [DOOR OPENS]
- JAY: Hey, Ally?
- Yeah?
- JAY: Howdy.
Jay? Wha--
This is the women's bathroom,
dude. You can't be in here.
Technically, it is a unisex
bathroom, but...
can we talk?
- Hi.
I'm... [SIGHS]
I am really sorry about earlier.
Oh, no, it's totally fine.
Sorry to stalk and run,
but I'm trying
to make this yoga class
that starts in, like, an hour.
You serious? Yoga?
Mm-hmm.
Aren't we supposed
to be saving the company?
Yes, and we will.
Just after yoga.
I booked us a table at L'oie.
We get inspired,
talk about the campaign.
You realize that
it's Valentine's Day, right?
Oh, that's right.
You probably got plans,
don't you?
- No.
- Well, great!
It'll be a great place
for some field research.
- Romance, flowers, candles--
- [SMACKS LIPS]
Uh, do you think that maybe
we could just do this tomorrow?
Uh, see, I would love
to do tomorrow,
I just have to take
the first flight
out in the morning
for my best friend's wedding.
So, how about this?
We'll call it 08:00 sharp
and I'll see you there.
- Yeah? I'm excited.
- Uh--
- No, no, I-- [SIGHS]
- It's gonna be great!
It looks like the rain...
MONICA: Oh, thank you so much.
Uh, no, Mon. Let me get this.
You're, like, $100,000 in debt.
[CHUCKLES] Not anymore.
Arthur paid it off.
And I get to keep the card.
- Are you serious?
- Mm-hmm.
Damn. Someone likes a little
sugar with their daddy.
Aha. Excuse me, Ally.
I do not have a sugar daddy.
That term is very problematic.
I have a sponsor.
And do you love your sponsor,
or is he just erasing your debt?
Yes, I love him. And I love
that he's erasing my debt.
So, when am I gonna meet this
secret Hugh Hefner?
Shall we all get dinner soon?
What do you say, like, 4:30?
- Soup?
- Ha ha.
Real clever, Miss Judgy Judy,
while you're literally
stalking your ex online.
I'm not stalking him.
The algorithm
is stalking me, okay?
- It's the algorithm?
- Hey, is Arthur Heart Eyes?
Is that why
I haven't met him yet?
That's not fucking funny.
[LAUGHS] Of course
Arthur's not Heart Eyes.
That guy has so much arthritis,
he can't run.
- Honestly, I bet it's Crystal.
- Mm.
You know when she does
that, like, thing...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...when her Botox doesn't
sit right and it gets stuck?
[NEWS THEME PLAYS ON TV]
REPORTER: Breaking news.
Our Channel 7 affiliate
is reporting that two more
couples have been found murdered
at a downtown spa.
We go live
to the scene in Seattle.
- [PHONE DINGS]
- Can't watch this.
REPORTER: Thanks, Mike...
MONICA: Ally.
- Ally, hello? Hey, ho.
- Monica!
Oh, my God.
Why are you torturing yourself?
You're the one who ended things.
I know.
He just moved on so fast.
I mean, what even is her job?
Look at her feed.
It's all vacation pics.
And she doesn't even have
rich parents. I checked.
You need to stop hate-fucking
yourself and get out there
and find someone to actually
fuck-fuck yourself, you know?
- No.
- Oh, what about that guy?
He's so cute. The-the...
The bathroom boy, you know?
Your little stalker?
You mean the guy
trying to take my job?
Oh, my fuck.
He is so hot,
I could literally throw up.
My basement just flooded.
[GASPS SOFTLY]
He's okay.
Wait, what are you
wearing on this date?
It's not a date.
We're working. And what's wrong
with my clothes?
You look like a before picture.
[CHUCKLES] Monica!
That is so mean!
Okay, this place, what's
the vibe? Is it, what, fancy?
- Yeah, it's fancy. Why?
- Come on.
Where are we going?
We're gonna go fuck up
a credit card.
Pretty girls don't do drama
'less we wanna
It'll be depending
on the day
Pretty girls packed
in a Defender
Know I'm-a defend her
never let her catch no stray
This that pretty-girl mantra
She's that stunna
make you wanna swing both...
- It's gorgeous.
- So much skin.
- Hike it up a little bit.
- It's so much skin.
- It can go shorter.
- Monica, no! It's not a date.
- Love what it feel like
- Feel like
To be off of the grid
like, all night
- Oh, with my bih like
- Bitch, like
We ain't even trying to talk
to no one
Swerve off all the creeps
no weird vibes
We ain't never let it ruin
a good time
Ain't nobody gon' dim
our good light
This them words
we're living by
No.
This that pretty-girl mantra
This that flaunt you
- Just touched down in L.A.
- Ah
Pretty girls don't do drama
no new drama
- We already got a full day
- Ah, ah
Pretty girls
that you gon' remember...
Hi. Uh, reservation
for Simmonds.
MAÎTRE D': Of course. AJ?
- BOUNCER: Arms out, please.
- Pretty...
- [SONG STOPS]
- [METAL DETECTOR SQUEALING]
- What gives?
- Heart Eyes.
Can't be too careful.
[HIGH-PITCHED SQUEALING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
I'm environmentally conscious.
- [GENTLE PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
- [QUIET CHATTER]
[SIGHS]
[SCOFFS]
Sharp, my ass.
MAN: You look so beautiful
tonight, darling.
Happy Valentine's. I mean that.
Aw. [CHUCKLES]
Good evening, miss.
Will anyone be joining you?
Uh, yes. Um, a friend.
A colleague.
It's a... It's a work dinner.
Well, I'll be back with the
specials once your date arrives.
Oh, no, no, no.
He's not my date.
["MAY I" BY BROOK BENTON
PLAYING]
May I tell you
that you're lovely...
JAY: I am so sorry that
I am late. I tried to get a car.
And for what it's worth,
I had no idea this place
was gonna be this nice,
but, um...
- You look amazing.
- Thank you.
WAITER: Welcome to L'oie.
May I offer you a beverage?
- Um, I'm good. Thank you.
- JAY: Yeah, please. How about
a bottle of champagne,
maybe two glasses?
Oh, uh, no, no, no. I'm sorry.
- No offense, but we're working.
- None taken.
WAITER: I'll be right back.
So, where you from?
Uh, Phoenix.
Do you have siblings?
[SMACKS LIPS] No.
Are your parents still together?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, that's nice.
Yeah, I'd love to grow old
with somebody.
Change their Depends?
You know,
I don't immediately go to poop
when I think about love,
but yeah. I would change
an adult diaper
if it was in the name of love.
The perfect romance...
- [CORK POPS]
- [GASPS, SIGHS]
WAITER: Here we are.
- JAY: Thank you.
- Thank you.
- WAITER: Miss?
- Yeah.
Didn't want any, but thank you.
And for you, sir?
JAY: Thank you very much.
WAITER: Enjoy.
What do you say?
- To love?
- Mm.
Okay.
- Listen, this is all very cute.
- Mm-hmm.
- And you're smooth.
- Oh, thanks.
But I'm just trying
to salvage whatever's left of
my career here, so can we skip
whatever this is and get
to cracking this campaign?
- By all means.
- Okay.
I have a couple ideas in here.
Some probably suck,
but I'm sure there's a--
You've had
your heart broken recently.
- I'm sorry, what?
- No, I just like to think
I'm intuitive
with these things and...
Ew. Yeah, no.
I did not get my heart broken...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...recently.
And it's really
none of your business.
Oh, you're totally right,
it's not.
Definitely not. Okay. Um, is...
It's just your campaign.
Doomed lovers? I mean, it hardly
screams romance to me.
The most romantic stories
of all time are doomed.
You got husbands, wives,
partners, twin flames,
soulmates.
Whatever you wanna call it,
it's all gonna end.
It's just a matter
of time before
someone cheats, bails, or dies.
What about butterflies
in your stomach?
A lightning bolt to the heart?
- Cozy Sundays in bed?
- [CHUCKLES]
What's next, birth charts
and long walks on the beach?
I like those things,
but I get it, not for everyone.
You wanna know how I feel
about romance?
Yeah.
It's a farce.
A lie.
Not to everyone, I know that.
Some people get... [SMACKS LIPS]
...really lucky and stumble
into something real and forever.
But the other 99% of us
are just bouncing from one
failed experiment to the next,
chasing the same regurgitated
fairy-tale bullshit
that's been stuffed into our
brains since we were kids.
Prince Charming? [SCOFFS]
Till you catch him
fucking your sister.
I thought you were
an only child.
- It's a metaphor. Jesus.
- Right.
My point is, it's not real.
And somehow, I landed a job
that forces me to propagate
a fantasy in order to sell
blood diamonds
harvested from third-world
slave labor,
so please forgive me
if I'm not swept away
by your magical notions
of romance, Jay.
Wow.
That's really...
What?
...sad.
Why are you single?
- Excuse me?
- No, really, Mr. Romantic...
doe-eyed, first love,
Esther Perel mama's boy
know-it-all. Why are you single?
- Well...
- Are you really looking for love
or are you just another
fake-ass, ho-hunting,
- ankle-cuff prick in a suit?
- Oh, my God.
You know, you don't know me.
And you don't get
to cast judgment
just because I don't think
like you, okay?
Yeah, um...
I think you were right.
Tonight's a bad night.
Should've just
let you clear your head.
Um, don't worry about
the champagne. It's on Crystal.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Jay! Jay, hey--
I'm sorry, okay? You win.
Listen, I told you it was fine
and I meant it. It's all good.
No, I had
a really rough day and...
and I took it out on you
and that was shitty
and-and wrong and...
Jay, please,
I can't lose this job.
Ally, I am not
gonna take your job.
Although it does seem like
you don't really want
this job, but...
- This is me, so...
- [PEOPLE LAUGHING NEARBY]
I'm gonna go back to the hotel,
brainstorm some creative,
see what we can
salvage from the-- Oh.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
COLLIN: [IN BRITISH ACCENT]
Ally?
ALLY: Collin! [CHUCKLES]
What are you doing here?
Um, well, Sienna and I are on
a little dinner date, actually.
- I've heard so much about you.
- Really?
Why?
And, uh, you are?
Oh, Jay. I'm Ally's...
- He's my friend-- Boyfriend.
- ...Boyfriend.
Friend. Boyfriend.
I didn't know
you had a boyfriend.
- Yeah! [LAUGHS]
- Yeah. [LAUGHS]
Yeah. I mean, why would you?
It's not like I publicize it
on social media or anything.
[FORCED LAUGHTER]
Uh, well, it's nice
to meet you, Jay.
Pleasure. So, um, dinner, huh?
Yeah. It was supposed
to be a double date,
uh, but unfortunately...
- Ooh.
- What does that mean?
Well, you know the couple that
got murdered up at the winery?
- What, you know them?
- We worked together.
- Played racquetball.
- Racquetball.
It's tragic, really.
- You still kept the reservation?
- And you still came to dinner?
- Of course. In their honor.
- JAY: Oh.
- ALLY: Wow.
- Well, a lot to
eat in there and it's good.
We should go.
See you, Ally, as well, and...
You have such a sexy suit.
- Oh, that's a sexy dress.
- Yeah. Oh, yeah.
- [LAUGHS]
- You guys have a good dinner.
Happy Valentine's Day!
Happy V-Day!
Don't get killed,
all right? [LAUGHS]
- [FORCED LAUGH] What was--
- Why would he say that?
That was weird.
Oh, you're coming with me.
- ALLY: That was so embarrassing.
- [MUFFLED HEAVY BREATHING]
Are you in love
with somebody
And just a little afraid
to say who?
Are you in love
with somebody
Thank you.
Who doesn't know you're
in love with 'em, too?
Not a... not a problem.
[CHUCKLES]
Being in love with somebody
Is something
that everybody should be...
So is it the accent?
Is that what it is?
Women love that fucking accent.
[SIGHS] God,
I can't stand it now.
Brits are so unemotional.
Mm.
Well, that would explain
the dead friends' resy.
DRIVER: Love
is a beautiful thing, no?
- Oh, we-we just work together.
- No, we're not a couple.
- But you just kissed, no?
- Oh. See, no,
that was a performance
to seem maybe more desirable
and perhaps less pathetic
- in front of her ex.
- Oh. You love Spotify?
I have Ultimate Sexies
playlist and--
- I love Spotify.
- Yeah, we're-- No, we're okay.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Can we add a stop?
Again, I'm really sorry
about tonight.
I swear I'm not a lunatic.
That's exactly what I think
a lunatic would say.
Okay.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Have fun
at your best friend's wedding.
Thank you.
Afraid of being
left alone...
[SIGHS]
- DRIVER: Okey dokey.
- Yeah.
What the...
ALLY: No!
Next stop,
2640 Westlake Avenue South, sir?
[ALLY GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION]
Hey, can you hold off a second?
I think she locked herself out.
You know what you should do?
You should go to her,
tell her you love her,
then never let her go.
It's never too late
for true love...
Right. Right. Yeah, you just
keep that meter running.
Howdy. Everything okay?
No. [CHUCKLES]
No, I think I left my keys
in a dressing room somewhere.
Oh.
[CHUCKLES] Oh, my God. This
night could not get any worse.
You have a spare hidden?
[SIGHS] Yeah,
under a mat upstairs.
It's okay.
I'll just break the window.
No. What are you talking about,
breaking windows? No.
No, it's fine.
My landlord loves me.
Well, if you're serious, maybe
just, you know, let me do it.
- I can break a window.
- No, I know you can
break a window, but if you
cut yourself--
I'm not gonna cut myself.
Knock yourself out.
Just know I don't condone this.
I'm worried for your safety.
And you're punching with your
thumb inside your hand,
- which is not a good thing.
- Okay, yeah. You're gonna do it.
Yeah. Why don't you hold that?
Came prepared.
Ah, not so bad.
That's bad.
I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
No, no, I'm sorry I'm bleeding
all over your floor.
Here. Okay.
Let's run it under some water.
- Mm.
- [WATER RUNNING]
- Thanks.
- Okay, you're just gonna wash up
in here for a sec.
[WHISPERS] Oh, God.
Um, sorry it's so messy.
I had a house cleaner,
but she won the lottery
last week and fired me.
JAY: Really?
How much did she win?
Uh, like, a million dollars.
[CHUCKLES]
JAY: Damn. Well, I hope you find
a replacement soon.
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- [SIGHS]
Aw. Cute.
[ALLY SIGHS]
I was Pikachu for Halloween too.
Oh, yeah. [LAUGHS]
That wasn't Halloween.
Well, what was it?
It was Tuesday.
Yeah, I was pretty obsessed.
Wore that shit everywhere.
- I'll take that.
- It was on your shelf.
No, I really
wasn't expecting company.
Ever?
Why don't you just take a seat
while I look for
the first aid kit?
[RUMMAGING]
Huh.
[SIGHS]
Found it!
Jay?
[GROANS]
Excuse you.
I'm sorry. I didn't wanna sit
on your nice clothes.
- [ALLY SIGHS]
- Oh.
Would you relax?
It's just
a very expensive jacket.
Let's see your hand.
- [SIGHS]
- [GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- Ooh.
- Careful now.
Does it hurt?
No, actually.
- You're really good at this.
- [CHUCKLES]
Did you go to med school
or something?
I dropped out actually.
[CHUCKLES]
I really can't do blood.
- No way.
- Way.
Hmm.
Well, I think you're doing
a pretty good job right now,
if I do say so myself.
- ALLY: Uh...
- Oh.
This is why we dropped out
of med school
and pivoted to advertising.
[JAY CHUCKLES]
You're funny.
- Am I?
- I think so, yeah.
Would you mind?
My hair, falling in my face.
- Oh, of course.
- [CHUCKLES] Thank you.
- Okay. There we go.
- Oh, wow. [CHUCKLES]
So, you mind my asking
what kind of medicine
you were planning on going into?
[SMACKS LIPS] Uh, nephrology.
That's the liver.
Kidneys.
- Nailed it. Damn.
- Yeah.
Well, why that?
I had a family member
that was pretty sick.
Mm-hmm.
Guess I, I don't know,
thought I could fix people.
Anyway, now
I'm considered hemophobic.
Oh.
- I didn't take you for a bigot.
- [LAUGHING] Okay, wow.
Between that and coffee mates,
your dad jokes are top-notch.
I'm being facetious obviously.
Your jokes are cheesy as--
[SCREAMS] Fuck!
- Ally! Ally!
- [GRUNTS]
- Oh, shit!
- [ALLY SCREAMS]
[JAY YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
Fuck you!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
- Run!
- [VIBRATING]
Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
- [GROANS] What are you doing?
- [POUNDING ON DOOR]
Get your mind out of the gutter!
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Come on. Come on, come on!
Come on, come on! [GROANS]
Come on, come on, come on!
- You got it?
- Yes!
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
Good job.
Thanks.
Hey, you good?
Yeah. [SCREAMS]
- Help! He's trying to kill us!
- Oh, here's lovebirds. [GRUNTS]
- [ALLY SCREAMS]
- [JAY GRUNTING]
No! No, no, no.
You've got the wrong people.
- Hey. What are you doing?
- He only kills couples, right?
We're not a couple!
We barely know each other.
So back the fuck off!
OPERATOR OVER PHONE:
911, what's your emergency?
[ALLY SCREAMS] Run!
Help! Help!
Help us!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
JAY: Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
What?
Did you hear that?
I don't hear anything.
- [SCREAMING]
- Oh, shit!
- Ally!
- [GRUNTING]
Get off of her!
Hey, hey!
[GROANS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS, SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATH TREMBLING]
[SLOW, RHYTHMIC CREAKING]
[CREAKING CONTINUES]
[BREATH TREMBLING]
[CREAKING STOPS]
[WHIMPERS SOFTLY]
[MECHANICAL CLANK]
[MECHANICAL WHIRRING]
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MECHANICAL CLANK]
- [GRUNTS]
[WHIRRING CONTINUES FASTER]
[GROANING]
[BLADE RINGS]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[SCREAMING]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
No!
No! No! No!
[SIREN WAILING]
Help! He's right behind...
[CAR DOORS OPENING]
OFFICER 1: Here!
- ...me.
- [CAR DOORS CLOSING]
He was-- He was right here.
OFFICER 2: I'll go check it out.
Oh, my God. Jay.
- Jay, is he okay?
- I don't know who
- you're talking about.
- Jay Simmonds.
We were with each other all
night and-and we got attacked
and we got separated
back there. I...
- You just left him?
- No, I didn't leave him!
OFFICER OVER RADIO: All units.
All units, stand down.
We have Heart Eyes.
- I repeat, we have Heart Eyes.
- Yes! We got that motherfucker!
Seattle PD, baby! Fuck, yeah!
OFFICER OVER RADIO: On behalf of
Seattle PD, I just wanna say...
OFFICER 1: Yeah,
congratulations.
OFFICER OVER RADIO:
Incredible teamwork, huh?
Hey! Hey, you need to back up!
- Fucking weirdos.
- BOY: What did I do?
Detectives.
Here she is.
Detective Zeke Hobbs.
This is my partner,
Detective Jeanine Shaw.
Hobbs and Shaw?
Like the movie?
- Haven't heard of it.
- Haven't seen it.
- We're here to ID a murderer.
- Oh, my God. Jay?
Jay!
- Jay, are you okay?
- Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
- Jay!
- Nope.
Jay, are you okay?
Uh, no, Ally, I'm not okay.
Thank you for asking.
You ditched me.
What? I did not ditch you!
Oh, yes, you did! You absolutely
ditched me. We were a team.
I was being chased
by a fucking serial killer!
I know! I also was
being chased by a serial killer.
- What the fuck does that mean?
- Jay, you're tall and ripped
and perfectly capable
of defending yourself.
Ally, I really appreciate
the compliments,
especially coming from you,
but right now
is not the time, okay?
These muscles were not made
for violence!
They're for cuddling!
- Okay.
- JAY: Hey, we're talking here!
Guys, this was not him.
We were together all night.
Heart Eyes was after both of us.
Ma'am... We found this man
in the park wearing this
and in possession of this.
JAY: Come on!
No, that's--
That's not possible.
Jay didn't do this.
Maybe.
Maybe Jay wasn't acting alone.
- What?
- JAY: What?
We're gonna have to take your
tall, ripped friend in
for questioning.
Oh! [CHUCKLES]
- Hey, good going. Really great.
- [ENGINE STARTS]
See you at the station, I guess.
[SIREN WHOOPS]
[WHISPERS] Fuck.
JAY: What is this?
That's a ring.
[HOBBS SIGHS]
- Read it.
- Read what?
Let me help you out.
It says, "JS."
- As in "Jay Simmonds."
- "Jay Simmonds."
You are really good.
You're really good
at detective work.
That was really--
It's impressive.
[WHISPERS] That sarcasm?
A, I am not married.
B, why would I leave a wedding
band at the scene of the crime?
And C,
who gets their own initials
engraved in their
own fucking wedding band?
Also, D,
yes, that was sarcasm.
- Hey, hey, hey! Hobbs.
- Hey, relax. Relax!
Take five. Go. Go.
Cool down.
Come on.
[SHAW SIGHS]
I'm sorry. He can get
a little hot under the collar.
Yeah. No kidding.
Do you need anything?
Water, coffee?
- I am fine, thank you very much.
- Okay.
Just you and me.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I want you to look me
in the eyes
and tell me the truth.
All right.
How long have you known Ally?
[CHUCKLES] Fourteen hours.
You seem to care about her.
Yeah. Maybe I do.
But that ring. That's...
It's not yours, correct?
No. Again, I am not married.
You're not married.
I mean, it's not, like,
by choice or anything.
I just haven't met
the right person.
You're telling me.
- You're--
- Single. Shocker.
Kind of.
No-- You really, um...
[CHUCKLING]
Okay. Um... [CLEARS THROAT]
Lady, I have been waiting here
for over an hour.
- First of all, it's "officer."
- [TALK RADIO PLAYING QUIETLY]
Second, I already told you
they're interrogating
the suspect.
And I already told you they're
interrogating the wrong guy.
Can you please
just go back there
and give me some sort
of information?
DAVID: Sorry, Fran. The ethernet
cable was all frayed.
- Should be working now.
- Thanks, David.
What's a five-letter word
for a dog ending in H?
Bitch?
Excuse me?
Female dog.
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
Can you please go back there now
and give me some sort of update?
- Fine.
- Thank you.
Hey. Do we know each other?
No, I don't think so.
Bumble.
Yeah, no. I'm...
I'm not on the apps.
Oh. It's a waste of time anyway.
Hmm.
Just shooting my shot here.
Um...
Could I take you out to coffee
sometime? I'll pay for it.
[SIGHS] I almost
got murdered tonight.
- I am so sorry. Um...
- Yeah.
Stay safe. Have a good night.
Thank you.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- Where the hell is everybody?
DAVID: Celebrating.
They caught Heart Eyes.
SHAW: So, what else
do you want to tell me?
- I'm not a serial killer.
- [SHAW CHUCKLES]
So there's that.
Were you in Boston
in February of '23
and Philadelphia
in February of '24?
I...
Let me rephrase.
You were in Boston and Philly.
Same dates and locations
as HEK's
two prior killing sprees.
Jay, I got to admit...
that doesn't look very good.
I don't know
what you want me to say.
I'm a freelancer, so yeah,
I travel for, like, work.
Do you ever get lonely
on the road?
I like to think
that I can keep myself busy.
Yeah? How?
How do you blow off steam
when you're alone
with your thoughts, Jay?
Do you go to a vineyard?
Maybe a spa?
[TALK RADIO CONTINUES QUIETLY]
- Holy... Who--
- [CLANKS]
[GASPS]
MAN OVER RADIO: So, for HEK
to come out of the blue
and denounce Valentine's Day
and all it stands for...
Hello?
...by cutting these couples
down to size.
In my professional opinion,
what we have here...
- Detective.
- [SIGHS]
We got an HWW out front.
What do you want me to do
with her?
An HWW?
BOTH: "Hysterical white woman."
I'll handle her.
You sit tight.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- We're not done yet.
I'll be here.
He just snapped.
And he made it a point
to kill again and again
until the very concept
of an entire day dedicated
to couples and romance
is eradicated.
He sneaks into your house
and waits in the dark.
Cunning and quiet as a corpse.
And then,
when you least expect it...
he pulls out
one of the many, many, many toys
from his tools.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
FRAN: What the hell
are you doing?
God...
bless the USA.
- Told ya.
- Yeah.
I'm so sorry.
- Are you letting him go?
- Not yet.
Why the hell not?
- He's innocent.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, then tell me something.
Why is the Heart Eyes Killer
after him?
- You're not a couple.
- I don't know.
I assume he saw us
and thought we were together.
Why?
We...
kissed.
[STUTTERS] We had--
We had to kiss.
We had to kiss because...
because my ex...
he was there, and I was jealous.
- It's really stupid, I know.
- Okay.
I get it.
I do.
So you're not interested
in him romantically?
[COIN CLINKS]
Why is that relevant?
Just girl talk.
I mean, he's cute, he has a...
really good job.
Perfect candidate
for a little girl like yourself.
A little girl like myself?
- [LIGHTS CLANK]
- [ALLY SCREAMS]
- [SHAW SIGHS]
- [ALLY WHIMPERS]
SHAW: Oh, relax.
- Probably just the breaker.
- [FLASHLIGHT CLICKS]
ALLY: That's what people say
before they get stabbed
to death.
How would you know?
Watch her.
ALLY: No, no, no, no, no.
She said to watch me.
FRAN: Calm down,
I'm just getting a flashlight.
Little space? Any closer,
you'd be inside me.
ALLY: I'm sorry.
I'm just scared.
No, no, no, no. Careful.
He hides in closets.
No killers in here.
- [ALLY SCREAMING]
- [FRAN CHOKING]
[FRAN GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMS]
- [FRAN GROANS]
- [SHARP THUD]
- [BLOOD SPLASHES]
- [SLOW, HEAVY BREATHING]
- [SOFT BEEP]
[MUFFLED HEAVY BREATHING]
[YELLS]
[BLADE RINGS]
ALLY: Help!
- Hey! Hey! What's happening?
- [SCREAMS]
- He's here.
- Who?
Go! Get back! Get back!
[PANTING]
[GUNSHOTS IN DISTANCE]
- [SHAW SCREAMS IN DISTANCE]
- Hey. Hey. Hey, hey. Hey!
Where are you going? Uncuff me.
Don't worry, lover boy.
I'll protect you. [KISSES]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- No. No. No.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
JAY: [MUFFLED] God! Damn it!
Shaw?
[JAY GROANS]
Shaw!
[GASPS SOFTLY]
- [BLADE STABS]
- [GRUNTING WEAKLY]
[SCREAMING]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [SCREAM ECHOES IN DISTANCE]
[PANTING, GRUNTING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SHARP THUMPING]
- [GASPS]
[JAY GRUNTING OVER SPEAKERS]
- ALLY: Jay?
- [THUMPING]
- Jay!
- [GRUNTING]
ALLY: Jay, can you hear me?
OVER SPEAKER:
Uh, yes, yes, Ally.
Ally, you've gotta
find the keys.
Uh, Hobbs has the keys, okay?
You have to find Hobbs
'cause he locked me in here
like a fucking asshole.
Ally?
[GRUNTS] She ditched me.
That's okay.
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [SIGHS]
Ally?
- [LOCK BEEPS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[METALLIC SCRAPING]
[BREATH TREMBLING]
Hey.
Come on.
Hey, come on.
This is not fair!
Shit!
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GLASS CRACKLING]
[GUNSHOT]
Die. [YELLS]
JAY: Ally! Ally!
Goddamn! I'm right here!
Jay! [GRUNTS]
Careful! Careful.
[ALLY GROANS, GRUNTS]
- Hi.
- Hi. [GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[CHUCKLING] Are you okay?
You're a terrible shot,
by the way.
- Don't fucking push it, Romeo.
- Ooh.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- No! Hey!
- Ally!
- ALLY: Stop! [SCREAMS]
- No, no, no! Ally!
- [TIRES SQUEAL]
- [HORN BLARES]
DRIVER: Fucking assholes!
You saved my life.
You saved mine.
I owed you one.
[GLASS CLATTERING]
ALLY: We're not together!
- Go kill somebody else!
- Get up. Get up. Get up.
- He's coming. He's coming.
- [MOVIE PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
- [LIVELY CHATTER]
Oh, fuck.
Do you know what we just did?
Yeah. We led a couples-killing
maniac to a, uh...
- To an all-you-can-kill buffet.
- Come on.
HILDY: A big fat lummox like you
hiring an aeroplane to write,
"Hildy, don't be hasty.
Remember my dimple. Walter."
Delayed our divorce 20 minutes
while the judge
went out to watch it.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
WOMAN: Are you kidding me?
MAN: Oh, shit!
[CHATTER CONTINUES]
[LAUGHTER]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
MAN 1: Yo, that costume is dope.
MAN 2: I don't like that.
WOMAN 1: That's not him, right?
MAN 3: What the fuck?
WOMAN 2: It is him!
WALTER: Was it my fault?
Did I know that coal mine
was gonna have another cave-in?
I intended to be with you
on our honeymoon, Hildy.
- MAN 4: 'Sup, man?
- [BLADE STABS]
[CHOKING]
HILDY: I spent two weeks in
a coal mine with John Kruptzky.
You don't deny that,
do you, Walter?
WALTER: Deny it?
I'm proud of it.
We beat the whole country
on that story.
HILDY: Suppose we did. That
isn't what I got married for!
Excuse us.
WOMAN 3: What a creep.
Left. Left.
No. Right. Go. Go, go, go.
Turn.
In here.
[BOTH PANTING]
- [QUIET THUMPING]
- [GASPS]
Hmm?
[WHISPERS] Put a fucking shirt
on. There's a killer after us.
- WOMAN: Mm. Oh, what is it?
- [BOTTLES CLINK]
- [CHUCKLES]
- JAY: The Heart Eyes Killer.
He's out there right now.
We need to be quiet.
Oh! Dude, that's so hot.
[CHUCKLES] Fuck.
- We love role-play. [LAUGHS]
- Yeah.
- WOMAN: Oh, my God. He's coming.
- We're so dead.
WOMAN: Oh,
he's so scary and big.
- [SIGHS] We can't stay here.
- No.
[BOTH LAUGHING, MOANING]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [MOVIE CONTINUES PLAYING]
- ...without shuddering.
- Walter...
I made a great reporter
out of you, Hildy.
You won't be half as good
on another paper. You know it.
We're a team.
You need me, I need you,
the paper needs us!
Sold, American!
[SIGHS]
It just didn't work out, Walter.
- MAN: Oh, fuck.
- [WOMAN MOANS]
[SUCKS TEETH]
Maybe we lay low
for a little bit.
Yeah.
HILDY: I wasn't satisfied.
I suppose I proposed to you?
You practically did.
Making goo-goo eyes at me
for two years.
"Oh, Walter." And I still...
I actually kind of
like this movie.
- MAN: Yeah, you like that?
- [WOMAN MOANS]
- Yeah.
- Really?
- [MAN MOANING]
- [OBJECTS CLATTERING]
Yeah. Are you surprised?
Little bit, yeah.
[BOTH MOANING]
I did ditch you.
N-No. Ditch me?
[SCOFFS] It's what I'm best at.
- Ditching people?
- Running.
Hey, I was holding my own.
You didn't see me?
He was shaking
in his little leather boots.
- [BOTH MOANING]
- [THUMPING]
Jay, I wasn't entirely honest
at dinner.
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
My parents had this, like...
storybook romance.
They were literally
perfect together.
And then my dad died.
- [BOTTLES CLATTERING]
- [WOMAN GIGGLES]
I don't think
my mom ever fully recovered.
[SOFT, RHYTHMIC SLAPPING]
I'm sorry.
[WOMAN GRUNTING]
You know, when I was a kid,
my parents just...
hated each other.
I mean, they fought...
all the time.
[MAN SIGHS IN PLEASURE]
JAY: I think that...
is why I'm just this...
hapless romantic.
Just putting every girl
I fall for on a pedestal,
only to have
my heart broken over...
- WOMAN: More.
- and over...
WOMAN: More?
...and over.
WOMAN: Keep going.
- All because they...
- [MAN MOANS]
- They just can't... breathe...
- [WOMAN SQUEALS]
...my suffocating attempt
to prove Mom and Dad wrong.
[BOTH MOANING]
You know, I think...
I think tonight
should've been, like,
the worst night of my life.
[KISSING]
But it isn't.
[SOFT, RHYTHMIC SLAPPING]
Ditto.
MAN: Baby, you're so wet.
WOMAN: Mm-hmm.
[MOANING LOUDLY]
- [MAN GRUNTING]
- [WOMAN LAUGHING]
- God, you're so hard!
- [SHARP SLAP]
- WOMAN: Ow!
- [ALLY AND JAY LAUGHING]
[BOTH MOANING]
At least they're having fun.
- WOMAN: Oh, shit!
- [FABRIC RIPS]
- [CONTINUES MOANING]
- [CHUCKLES] It's kinda loud.
[BOTH MOANING LOUDLY]
- Yeah, it's too loud.
- [CREAKING]
- Hey! Shh!
- Shut the fuck up! Shh!
- Shut up! Shut the fuck up.
- Quiet down!
- MAN: Samm! I'm coming!
- [EXCLAIMS] Oh, God!
- MAN: Oh, I'm coming!
- JAY: Guys!
Shut up! Shut up!
- [MAN MOANING]
- [EXCLAIMS, SCREAMS]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[CHOKING]
[SCREAMING]
Holy shit. Someone call 911!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
Fuck!
- [SHARP THUMP]
- [GRUNTS]
Please, no!
[ALL CLAMORING, SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[SCREAMS]
[BOTH CRYING AND WHIMPERING]
[CLAMORING]
What are you-- Hey, Ally.
- What are you doing?
- Wait.
Wait for what?
He's gonna kill us.
And if he doesn't kill us,
he's gonna keep killing people.
We brought him here,
we end it here.
- We-- [BREATH TREMBLING]
- Come on.
I thought we were a team.
["PLEASE DON'T GO" BY KC
AND THE SUNSHINE BAND PLAYING]
Babe, I love you so
I want you to know
That I'm gonna miss
your love
The minute
you walk out that door
So please don't...
- [SONG STOPS]
- [WOMEN SCREAMING, WHIMPERING]
ALLY: Hey, Fuck Eyes!
Wait, wait, wait.
We need a weapon.
I have this.
That is not a weapon.
That could work.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- I don't think I can do that.
- What? Hey...
Yes, you can.
Come on.
[ALLY GROANS]
[BOTH GROANING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMS]
Run!
- Ally!
- [SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
[EARS RING]
[GRUNTS WEAKLY]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
- [BLADE CLATTERS]
- [PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
Oh, shit!
[YELLS]
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
[SIGHING]
Thanks a lot, Jay.
What?
[BREATH TREMBLES]
You got it in my mouth.
I just saved your life.
Oh, my God.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
- No. Hey.
- [STOMACH GURGLING]
Oh, no, no, no.
[ALLY RETCHING]
[COUGHING]
[GROANS]
I told you
I was not good with blood.
Yeah, no kidding.
[ALLY SIGHS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, who the fuck is that?
I have no idea.
WOMAN: He's lost
a lot of blood here.
[URGENT CHATTER]
MAN: Do you have
an ID on the victim?
You two, you're gonna be famous.
The couple
that stopped Heart Eyes. I...
[SIGHS]
It's very cute.
[STUTTERS] Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
I'm gonna leave you alone now.
Shot in the dark here.
Wanna come back to my hotel
and try and crack this campaign
before my flight?
Just actually eat some dinner.
Order a whole bunch
of room service.
Um...
Jay, I can't.
[SIGHS]
[SIREN WHOOPS]
Hey, you two.
Just wanted to make sure
you both got home safe.
Either of you need a lift?
JAY: Um... actually...
I don't suppose
you have a phone,
just so I can call a cab?
No, don't be silly.
I'll give you a ride home.
Least I can do.
- Your chariot awaits.
- [JAY CHUCKLES]
- [CHUCKLES]
- Okay.
Work call later?
Sounds like a plan.
Hey, uh, does anyone have a pen?
- PARAMEDIC: I got you, dude.
- Okay.
Can I see that?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
That's me.
[HORN HONKS]
ALLY: Your chariot awaits.
[SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[CHUCKLES]
She's not my type.
[ENGINE STARTS]
["THIS YEAR'S LOVE"
BY DAVID GRAY PLAYING]
PARAMEDIC: Hey, um,
I got another call,
so I'm just gonna
have to take that
- and that too.
- Uh...
- This year's love
- [DOORS CLOSE]
- Had better last
- [ENGINE STARTS]
Heaven knows
- It's high time
- [SIREN WHOOPS]
- I've been waiting
- [SIREN WAILING]
On my own
WOMAN: Hey, do you need a ride?
Too long
And when you hold me
like you do
It feels so right, oh, now
I start to forget
How my heart gets torn
When that hurt gets thrown
Feeling like you can't go on
[PHONE VIBRATING]
[PHONE CLICKS]
Hey.
MONICA OVER PHONE:
Um, do you have
something you wanna tell me?
Oh, you're never gonna believe
what happened.
Hello? Heart Eyes?
Are you kidding me?
But wait, are you okay?
Tell me the truth.
Do you need to come over?
You can sleep
in Arthur's panic room.
No, I hate this feeling.
What feeling?
Liking someone.
God, I fucked up.
I fucked up, Mon.
I met a really,
really great guy,
and now he's gone.
Where is he?
At the airport.
Oh. Okay, great.
He's at the airport. Go get him.
Mon, I--
- [SIGHS]
- Hey, Ally. Ally, listen to me.
You deserve to be happy.
You deserve
to have someone love you
for the beautiful,
neurotic mess that you are.
I mean, you can be
so clueless sometimes.
It's one of the ten things
I hate about you, honestly.
You can't let Jay go off
to his best friend's wedding
and hook up with
a bunch of bridesmaids
and move to Notting Hill. No.
This is love, mama.
Some kind of wonderful,
crazy, stupid love, actually.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Go get him. Go get
that beautiful, melanin man.
- Okay!
- He's gorgeous!
- Oh, my God. Okay,
- Ally, go get him right now!
- I'm going.
- I love you! You're beautiful!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
WOMAN OVER PA: This is your
final call for all passengers
on flight 403 to Boston.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
- ALLY: Thank you.
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Jay?
WOMAN OVER PA: Please have
your boarding pass...
- Jay!
- ...and identification ready.
Thank you.
Jay?
[INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
OVER PA]
- Jay!
- MAN: Fuck!
Sorry.
Jay!
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
I thought
you were somebody else.
WOMAN OVER PA: Paging passengers
Mr. and Mrs. Jones
flying to Denver...
- Sorry.
- ...on flight 273.
Your flight is boarded
and ready for departure.
- Please make your way...
- [PHONE VIBRATING]
...to gate lounge 11
immediately.
- Hello?
- DISTORTED VOICE: Roses are red,
violets are black.
Guess who's with me
and not coming back?
Who is this?
We've met before.
Forget me not.
JAY OVER PHONE: Ally! Ally! No!
Don't-- Do not-- [GRUNTS]
DISTORTED VOICE:
St. Valentine's Chapel.
Come alone or he dies.
Okay.
Call for help, he dies.
Okay. Just please
don't hurt him.
DISTORTED VOICE: [LAUGHS]
That's up to you, sweetheart.
- [LINE CLICKS]
- [PANTING SOFTLY]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[DOORS CREAKING]
[WIND WHISTLING SOFTLY]
- [BREATH TREMBLING]
- [DOORS CREAKING]
[DOORS CLOSE]
DISTORTED VOICE:
They say love is blind
and lovers cannot see,
the pretty follies
that they themselves commit.
But love isn't blind...
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[SIGHS]
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Is it?
Wait, you're--
It's me.
David.
The IT guy.
Wait, who the fuck
did we kill then?
[LAUGHS] Eli.
Poor, stupid Eli.
You guys were a couple?
Couple? No. No. [SIGHS]
Throuple.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Love looks with eyes wide open.
Seeking what the heart desires
the most.
A partner.
Its true companion.
I found mine ten years ago
in a chat room.
[GRUNTS]
David saw me.
He understood me
and I understood him.
[DAVID GASPS, MOANS]
[SIGHS] We got married here.
You know, I didn't really take
you for the religious type.
[BOTH LAUGH]
No. We just like the story.
Saint Valentine...
[WHISPERS] ...was beheaded.
[SHAW LAUGHS]
You murdered innocent people.
- Share what you love.
- Mm.
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
DAVID: And we love
hunting, killing...
SHAW: Deceit.
Taking turns on our victims.
Murdering couples.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
DAVID: It's our kink.
SHAW: It's our kink.
Everybody's got a fetish.
- [BREATH TREMBLING]
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
Well, too bad we wasted
your boyfriend at the drive-in.
- DAVID: Oh, God.
- [SHAW LAUGHS]
He wasn't our boyfriend.
No, Eli was just
a stupid fanboy.
He was obsessed with us.
He was obsessed with me.
Yeah. Learned a lot from me.
It just got messy.
- [JAY SHOUTS]
- [SCREAMS] Fuck!
SHAW: I almost got you at home.
- JAY: [YELLS] Go, go, go, go!
- [SCREAMS]
- I killed your driver.
- ...lovebirds.
ALLY: [SCREAMS] No, no, no,
you've got the wrong people!
JAY: Hey, what are you doing?
And I had a blast wasting those
vile dickheads at the winery.
- [CHOKES]
- [SCREAMS]
Ooh, that reminds me.
- Oh.
- Found this.
- God, you're the fucking best.
- [CHUCKLING]
Isn't she the fucking best?
SHAW: Yeah, I know.
And as luck would have it,
[CLICKS TONGUE]
your initials match.
J. Shaw.
Jeanine Shaw, bitch.
Why us? We're not even a couple.
Just let him go! Let him go!
[SIGHS] Truth be told,
we were gonna kill the other
couple at the restaurant.
[LAUGHING]
But then...
- we saw that kiss.
- Oh, that kiss! God!
[CHUCKLES]
Your chemistry is undeniable.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, I didn't know that murder
was a love language.
SHAW: Try it.
Maybe you'll like it.
[THUNDER BREAKING]
Pick it up.
There's a single bullet
in that chamber
with one single choice,
him or you.
We may have
mistaken you for lovers
at the beginning of the night,
but can you prove us right?
Could you save
his life with yours,
thus proving that love
really does conquer all?
If you don't love him, kill him.
DAVID: And you're free to go.
Wow.
You know,
your dedication is impressive.
It's twisted as fuck, but--
[PANTING]
Jay.
I've spent so long
running from love.
Convinced it would destroy me.
[SOFT EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't wanna be
that person anymore.
I want the storybook thing.
It was just one single night...
but I fell hard for you, Jay.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC SWELLS]
JAY: No, no, no.
- No, no, no. Don't do that.
- [SHAW AND DAVID LAUGHING]
No! No, hey.
Hey. Hey, no.
- No, no! Ally!
- Forgive me.
- [DAVID LAUGHING]
- [SHAW GASPING]
[SHAW GROANING, GASPING]
- [DAVID CONTINUES LAUGHING]
- Huh?
Baby, no!
- Come on.
- JAY: [GROANS] Oh, you shot me.
ALLY: Sorry, I overcorrected.
- That's a lucky fucking shot.
- [DAVID GRUNTING ANGRILY]
[SCREAMING]
- [GUN CLICKS]
- [SHOUTS]
- Ally?
- [COUGHING]
Did you mean what you said?
[GRUNTS] Come on.
SHAW: [IN SINGSONG] Pookie.
Chop that pretty boy up.
I'm gonna have fun
with this one.
- ALLY: No. No.
- Oh, yes, Mommy.
- No! No!
- [GRUNTS]
Don't you fucking touch him! No!
[WHIMPERS] No!
No!
[PANTING]
You shouldn't
have shot me, bitch.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[ALLY AND SHAW GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
DAVID: Hey, hey, come on.
Look at her go.
[GROANS]
[SHAW LAUGHING]
DAVID: Oh, you don't wanna
miss this, do you?
Isn't she perfect?
You talk too much.
[SCREAMING]
- [WAX SIZZLING]
- [SCREAMING CONTINUES]
I'm gonna fucking kill you both.
[ALLY YELLING]
[YELPS]
[YELLING]
[COUGHING]
You watching, Jay?
I want you to see her die.
- [GRUNTS]
- [GASPS]
Love hurts, bitch. [GRUNTS]
[CHOKING, WHEEZING]
- [THUNDER BREAKING]
- [TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING, CHOKING]
[SCREAMING]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[THUNDER BREAKING]
[CHOKING, WHEEZING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDER BREAKING]
Your day fucking sucks.
Jay.
Jay. Hey.
Hey.
JAY: Hi, you.
ALLY: Hey.
[BREATH TREMBLING]
I think you got over
your fear of blood.
[CHUCKLES]
[GROWLING] I'm gonna kill you.
I'll fucking kill you.
- I'm gonna fucking kill you.
- [GRUNTS]
[CHUCKLES]
[PANTING]
Planet saved.
[OMINOUS MUSIC FADING]
[THUNDER BREAKING]
[APPLAUSE]
[CORKS POP]
[RINGS CLINKING ON GLASS]
Now, if you told me that,
a year ago,
I'd be drinking [LAUGHS]
to the highest recorded sales
in Crystal Cane history,
I'd say,
"Y'all just a lying sack
of hot trash."
- [LAUGHTER]
- But... here we are.
WOMAN: Whoo!
And it's all thanks
to these two marketing mavens.
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
Right here. These two.
Now, Ally. I am,
believe it or not,
mildly devastated
that this is your last day.
But I am proud of you for going,
pursuing your dreams,
going back to doctor school.
All told, I hope
that you're better with a needle
than you are with a pitch deck!
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHTER]
To success!
- ALL: To success!
- To success.
Wait.
To love.
[SOFT EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, baby.
Hi.
[GRUNTS] What did I miss?
Hey, do you think it's weird
having a date here
after everything that happened?
Nope. Not to me.
This is where I realized
I was in love with you.
So, feels symbolic.
[LAUGHS] Okay. Symbolic?
You think it's symb--
Listen, don't freak out.
Don't freak out.
I know stuff like this
can freak you out, but...
Ally, this has been
the best year of my life.
[SOFT EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
So...
will you move in with me?
Jay, I--
I don't know what to say.
Yeah, no. I know
where that's going.
- It's okay.
- No, I--
- I don't want a key.
- [CHUCKLES]
I don't want a key.
I want you.
[LAUGHS]
Jay Simmonds...
will you marry me?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC SWELLS]
Yes.
- Yes?
- Yes. Yes.
A million fucking times, yes.
["YOU CAN'T HURRY LOVE"
BY THE SUPREMES PLAYING]
[HORNS HONKING]
I need love, love
to ease my mind
I need to find, find
Someone to call mine
But Mama said
you can't hurry love
No, you just have to wait
She said
love don't come easy
It's a game of give and take
You can't hurry love
No, you just have to wait
You gotta trust
give it time
No matter how long it takes
But how many heartaches
must I stand
Before I find a love
To let me live again?
Right now the only thing
That keeps me hanging on
When I feel my strength
Yeah, it's almost gone
- I remember Mama said
- You can't hurry love
No, you just have to wait
She said
love don't come easy
It's a game of give and take
How long must I wait?
How much more can I take
Before loneliness
Will cause my heart
heart to break?
No, I can't bear
To live my life alone
I grow impatient for a love
To call my own
But when I feel that I
I can't go on
These precious words
Keeps me hanging on
- I remember Mama said
- You can't hurry love
No, you just have to wait
She said
love don't come easy
It's a game of give and take
You can't hurry love...
- [SONG CONTINUES QUIETLY]
- [PHONE VIBRATING]
Hello?
[DISTORTED VOICE OVER PHONE]
Roses are red,
violets are blue.
Guess who just took
a picture of you?
Who is this?
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Relax, bitch.
Too soon?
Monica, that's not funny!
[LAUGHS] Where even are you?
Did you get it?
Of course I got it.
Are you kidding me?
You look super cute. I mean,
I would have gotten a manicure,
but I told you that,
and you're fine with that.
You're a natural gal.
You look great.
Okay, enjoy the movie, fiancés.
Love you.
- [KISSING]
- [LINE CLICKS, BEEPS]
Ally? Hello?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SLOW, HEAVY BREATHING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]