Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
-Hilda!
Stay away from me!
-I won't hurt you.
-Wait!
-Leave me alone!
Please. I can explain.
You can talk now?
I could always talk.
It's just that you understand me,
now that you're a troll.
I am not a troll.
I didn't mean…
Hilda, wait!
I'm going home!
Please, don't go out there!
Baba, baba, baba!
Huh?
Baba, baba!
Ba!
Baba!
-Hey! Can you--
-Baba, baba!
It was really quite hard
to stack all that.
She was in Hilda's bed?
-Baba!
Yes. Just like I said.
I made breakfast, went in,
and she was just there, and Hilda wasn't.
Unless…
Baba. Ba?
You couldn't be Hilda, could you, somehow?
Baba.
Baba!
In light of your recent
escapades with trolls,
I'd say this is a changeling.
-A what?
-A swap!
A troll child in human form
who's taken Hilda's place.
Hang on.
You're the little troll
from inside the mountain.
I do recognize you.
But if you're here and you're like this,
then that means Hilda must be…
I don't understand.
This is the place, isn't it, Twig?
Where we escaped.
Then, shouldn't there be a cave somewhere?
We won't find it just by standing here.
Let's look around and keep an eye on…
Baba.
Oh, there's so many of them.
Do you think one of these could be--
Right. How many is that now?
-That's 11 or 12.
-Right, so that's a good job.
Oh. Safety Patrol.
I wonder what they're up to.
Good morning! Good morning.
Looking good. Ooh! Good to see you.
We've all seen the fires in the hills.
You've no doubt heard rumors
about sudden increases
in troll numbers and so on.
And I want you to know
I hear your concerns.
That is why I am here to announce a curfew
on all beyond-wall activity after sundown.
In addition, I pledge today
to once more put a man, or woman,
in every tower along our historic wall.
Applications for volunteer bell ringers
are now open.
Yes, you there.
Are the rumors true?
Is there a danger of an attack?
Well, of course!
But that is why I am here.
My people are out there,
belling troll rocks even as we speak.
And not only that,
we've been preparing for an eventuality
like this for quite some time.
Our technology
is more effective than ever.
I present to you our state-of-the-art,
troll-buster mobile light cannon.
Imagine for a moment
a dedicated fleet of these babies
guarding every corner of our fair city.
A fleet, sir?
You are aware we have
just one troll-buster vehicle?
They don't need to know that.
Good citizens, please be reassured.
Your safety is safe with me.
Now, there's a man
who's got the right idea.
I do feel safer
with an Ahlberg protecting us.
I didn't, when I was stuck
on a mountain with him.
Of course you didn't.
You were surrounded by trolls!
We were so worried, sweetie!
He did get you back safely,
though, didn't he?
Where are you off to?
We said you don't have to go
to school today, remember?
I'd rather do something
than sit here all day watching trash TV.
Hey! You're here!
No thanks to my parents.
Yours too?
I just want things to get back to normal
as quickly as possible.
How's your leg?
Mmm, it's still a bit sore,
but it feels much better.
No sign of Hilda?
She and her mum went through a lot.
We might not need the time off,
but I'm not surprised that she does.
Come on, let's get to class.
Now, children.
I'm sorry to say
our regularly-scheduled lesson
is canceled today.
Instead, we have a visitor.
Officer Selby
from the Trolberg Safety Patrol.
-Hello.
-He's brought a video.
-Trolls.
Fearsome.
Blood-thirsty.
With a taste for human flesh.
But are they really so dangerous?
Yes! That's why we must make sure…
Um, Ms. Hallgrim.
-Ms. Hallgrim?
-Huh?
Frida.
This isn't true.
They don't have a taste for human flesh.
They like vegetables as much as anything.
And Jorts.
If you could save your thoughts
until after the video.
Trolls and humans
may be natural enemies…
We are not natural enemies.
Frida, please.
…the heroic endeavors
of Safety Patrol have kept the peace
for the citizens of Trolberg
for generations,
by remaining vigilant
and staying one step ahead of the threat
at every turn.
But it wasn't always so easy.
When man first came to this valley,
savage attacks by trolls
were tragically common.
Our ancestors may not have survived
if it wasn't for one thing.
The symbol of Trolberg,
the humble bell.
Now, under the leadership of Erik Ahlberg,
Head Officer of Safety Patr--
Huh? Hey! You can't--
Ms. Hallgrim! With all due respect,
I can say with first-hand experience
that none of that is true.
Trolls aren't just mindless people-eaters.
-My grandfather was eaten by a troll!
-No way!
-They're evil.
-They are not!
My great-grandmother raised a troll
that she found in her garden.
Yeah, it probably grew up
to eat my grandfather.
-It didn't!
-Children!
My parents say they steal children.
That's not true!
Are you calling my parents liars?
I'm calling you stupid.
Listen!
Most of you have spent
your whole lives in Trolberg.
Have you ever heard of anyone
actually being eaten by a troll?
-Uh, no.
-No, not really.
You shouldn't have to sit here
and be taught lies, and I won't.
I can't believe
algebra was canceled for this.
Hilda!
We've been searching all day.
Are we walking in circles?
I don't think so.
How have
we not found a single cave?
She's in there, I know it.
But if we can't get in--
Ow!
Um, excuse me. Excuse me, Miss.
Is everything okay here?
Fine! Everything's fine.
It's not safe for you to be
outside the walls
so late in the day, ma'am.
Much less your, uh…
children.
May I ask what you're doing out here?
You haven't heard about the curfew?
Curfew?
Oh! Oh, we're looking for…
Berries. You know? To make jam.
Please! Do no such thing.
Those berries
are intensely poisonous, ma'am.
-Oh, I knew that.
No! I didn't mean
these berries.
Sir?
They're stirring.
I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
Please don't make me insist.
Right. Well, then, let's go, children.
This way.
Why did you lie to him?
Because they're looking for
the same thing we are, Tontu.
But I'm not sure we're on the same side.
Right. I was going home.
Huh?
The sound of them.
That little one was one thing.
The ones on the wall are going to kill me.
-Hey, in here.
Whoa!
What are you hiding from?
A troll.
Are you not a troll?
No.
Are you sure about that?
I'm sorry.
You're hiding from a troll,
and you found a troll.
That must be quite annoying.
I'm Trundle, by the way,
if you're interested.
Hilda.
You're a lot bigger
than the troll I'm hiding from.
Yes, it's a shame.
If I wasn't,
then maybe I could get out of here
as easily as you got in.
The bells. You're trapped in here.
Ah, don't worry yourself about it.
I guess neither of us
are where we want to be.
I didn't know it was like this.
How am I ever going to get home
with these things in the way?
Home?
Yes, home. Trolberg.
What would you do once you were there?
You're a troll. They built a big wall
to keep you out, you know.
You're welcome to stay here
as long as you want.
I know it's not much.
Is…
Is it permanent?
It depends.
The other trolls won't tell you this,
but there is a way to change you back.
There is?
It's an old magic, rarely practiced.
In theory, I could do it,
but not in my present state.
I would need you
to do a few things for me.
What?
Anything. Name it, and I'll do it.
And this would have to remain
between you and me.
No one else can know.
Whatever. Just tell me.
Well,
first, I could really use a drink.
Some troll mead would be nice.
Hilda! Hilda!
It's that troll. She won't give up.
You should go to her.
Hilda!
Are you crazy?
She's the one that did this to me.
You may find this hard to understand,
but there was a kindness in her magic.
She won't allow any harm to come to you.
In fact, she will take care of you
as though you were her own child.
Yeah, well, I'm definitely not.
Nevertheless…
Hilda!
…as long as you're out here,
that troll is your mother.
And a mother's love
should not be taken for granted.
I should still be looking for her.
We should never have come home.
No, you need rest.
Besides, it's no good
if you get yourself eaten.
She really is quite resourceful,
that daughter of yours.
I'm sure she's made some arrangements.
-She shouldn't have to make-- Ow!
-Baba, baba, baba!
Please, can you just…
Ugh! You stupid, stupid--
Hey, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to shout, I--
Hey, hey, it's gonna be okay.
I've got you.
Shh.
-Come on.
-Baba.
I still don't really understand why.
Why you did it.
My daughter is a gentle soul.
You've seen what it can be like out here.
Turning to stone. The bells.
This is no place for her
at the best of times,
and there's trouble brewing.
Even so,
you can't just swap people like that.
It's kidnapping!
What is that?
It's like a sound. But more of a feeling.
I can't hear it, but I know it's there.
We all feel it.
I don't know what it is,
but it's always been there.
Calling us towards the city.
Have you ever wondered why we stay here
among these particular mountains
when we are so clearly unwelcome?
I always thought it was pretty obvious.
You were here long before Trolberg was.
I don't think I ever realized
there were this many of you out here.
The calling has become stronger lately.
It's bringing more and more of us
out of the mountains each night.
The humans have noticed.
I'm sure they imagine
there's some kind of plan
to storm the city.
There isn't, though, right?
Of course not, but that's not the point.
There are some that want to lash out,
to answer the call the only way they can.
But, could they really do anything?
With the wall, and those bells?
Maybe not.
It'll be sunrise soon.
We should rest. Big day tomorrow.
What are we doing?
Showing you how to be a troll.
-Oh!
Huh!
Perhaps we could erect
some kind of large net,
to catch anything
thrown over and prevent--
No, no, no, no. That doesn't capture
the imagination enough.
They need something to look towards,
not practical solutions.
But, sir, given the--
-What's this?
-That is a gun, sir.
It utilizes a compact version
of the technology
from the troll-buster cannon, but--
Yes! This could be just the thing.
But sir, that is a one-of-a-kind,
untested prototype.
I am not sure it even works.
Come, Gerda. The people await!
Boulders are just big stones,
and thrown stones are no match
for the latest
in state-of-the-art troll deterrence.
This baby will turn a full-size troll
into a harmless pile of gravel.
If Hilda is how we think she is, Tontu,
we need to find her before they do.
-We should be out there looking.
-Baba.
Baba, shoes on.
-Baba. Baba-baba.
Why don't I stay here and look after her?
We'll only slow you down anyway.
You'll cover more ground.
If you're sure.
Between Alfur and I,
I think we can handle her.
-Actually, uh…
Cedric here and I
are going to help out with the search.
-Oh, I see.
Beep.
Baba, baba.
-Baba.
-Oh.
Don't tell Johanna, but you're actually
a lot less trouble than the regular kid.
Ooh.
Baba, baba!
Hey, Baba.
What's a five-letter word
meaning "hairy thief?"
Baba?
Oh!
No, no, no, no, no!
Baba!
-Baba, baba, baba!
Baba, baba!
-Baba.
-Baba!
Baba.
Excuse me. Sorry!
-Baba!
Sloppy work. Make a note of this, Deputy.
We'll need
another bell team out here sharpish.
Sir, forgive my pointing it out.
But you know the effects these bells have.
Should we not be looking
at ways to calm the situation
rather than stir it up?
You see this?
This is what we're up against!
Cowards.
They turn to stone rather than face me.
And the rest slink off
and disappear once the sun is up.
It strikes me
that they are keeping to themselves, sir.
It strikes me that
they are denying us victory.
-And if they--
What is that?
It appears to be a pigeon, sir.
Cedric!
We need to get inside the mountain.
-Sir?
-Take them by surprise.
Secure the advantage.
But nobody has ever found a way
into troll country.
Nobody yet.
But if we can do this, Deputy Gerda,
my name will go down
in the annals of Trolberg history.
Come, we have plans to make.
Silence the bells! Silence the bells!
Silence the bells!
-Ahlberg smells! Silence the bells!
Silence the bells?
Exactly whose side are you on?
We're on the side
of peace and communication.
The enemies of misinformation and fear.
Really? Well, I'd love to hear
what your teachers have to say about that.
Their teacher is very proud of them
and would ask you to move along.
Hmm!
Silence the bells! Silence the--
David, what's this about?
It's my mum.
She's only gone and volunteered
to be one of Ahlberg's
emergency bell-ringers.
And I'm guessing
she wouldn't approve of all this.
I can't face the conversation.
Huh. Still got it.
-Tontu!
Oh, you got her.
Thanks, guys.
-Who's this?
You think you can help me
get her back home?
I'll explain on the way.
Hilda's a troll?
Yes, it's not ideal.
Oh, boy!
The question is,
what are we going to do about it?
Well, you're a witch. Is there a spell
or something that could turn her back?
There has to be.
Come on, let's ask Kaisa.
-What did I do with my jumper?
Baba!
Ugh!
Body swapping. I think
this is the book you're looking for.
-Thanks.
-Wait.
-Whose bodies are we swapping?
-Hilda's!
She's been swapped
with a troll changeling child,
and we need to change her back.
Ah. That's not going to work, I'm afraid.
What? Why?
Troll magic. It's just, uh…
Works differently.
You can't counter
a troll spell with witch magic.
They don't combine.
-At all.
-But--
On top of that, witches do not like
to get involved in troll affairs.
It's kind of a protocol thing
that the council
would love to explain to you in detail.
But this is Hilda we're talking about.
You know her.
I do. And so I know
she'll find her own way out of this.
You seriously can't help?
Whoa.
Yes!
Hmm.
Did you sleep well?
As well as can be expected.
Where are we going?
-To have breakfast.
-Huh?
Humans have breakfast, don't they?
Do you think there's anything vegetarian?
Oh! Thank you.
Oh!
It's okay
if you want to nibble on my leaf.
Uh…
A drink for you.
Mmm, thank you.
Mmm. Ah!
Oh, I love this stuff. What is it?
That's troll mead.
Powerful stuff.
Just a sip will keep
a thing like you running for days.
You know, I think I'm gonna go
stretch my legs if that's okay.
-I won't be long.
-Okay.
Hmm. Too much troll mead.
Say, who's got it anyway?
Ah! That's the stuff.
I feel like I could pull
the horns off a forest giant.
Is that a good thing?
It's something.
So, what's next?
Next?
Yes, next.
What's the next thing I need to do
for you to turn me back?
Oh!
No time to chat?
Uh…
No, no, you're in a hurry.
Who'd want to be a troll
longer than they have to be?
I'm sorry, I didn't--
The next thing I would ask of you
is that you remove
those dreadful bells from my front door.
What? How am I supposed to do that?
If I knew, I would have done it myself.
Humph.
Tell me. Why are there so many bells here?
Someone obviously
didn't want you to leave.
They were worried enough about you
to put a bell on your nose.
What do you think they make of me?
Mmm.
If it's too much trouble…
No.
I'll figure it out.
-What is it, Twig? Do you smell something?
Trolls!
I don't see her with them.
But look, the cave.
I knew it was around here.
It looks like they're on the move.
Hey, you! Wait! Don't walk away from me.
Wha… What?
What? No, no!
No! Open up! Give her back to me!
Just give me a minute. Okay, Twig?
-Uh, Johanna?
Oh.
-Okay, um…
Don't panic.
There's no reason to believe
they aren't friendly.
Hello. I… I don't mean any harm.
I'm looking for my daughter.
You see, I think
she might have been-- Ahh!
-No! Please, I don't--
Ow!
Evasive maneuvers!
Cedric!
No!
-Start, start, start!
Sorry for wandering off before.
Why would someone apologize for wandering?
-Well, I--
-You didn't miss anything.
We caught the scent of some trolls
looking to steal our food. So we left.
Why would they do that?
-Shouldn't you all be friends?
-You mean how all humans are friends?
There are all kinds of trolls here,
all with different ideas and priorities.
Good, bad, stupid,
it can be hard to find common ground.
It's a shame you can't work together more.
You need, like, some laws
or a leader or something.
Come. I should show you something.
What is that place?
That was once the home of a troll
that called himself the Mountain King.
Mountain King?
He was the only one
that ever managed to unite
any real number of us
around a single idea.
That's the sort of thing
I'm talking about. What idea?
To lead an army of trolls
to attack the city.
Oh. Mmm. And what… What happened to him?
Whoa.
The idea proved to be quite popular.
But not everyone agreed with it.
There was a battle.
In the end, he was defeated
before his goal could be achieved.
No troll has tried
to crown themselves king or queen since.
Maybe you don't need a leader, then.
-All right.
The spell says we need organic matter.
Luckily, I found some of Hilda's hair
tangled in this random stick
she left here for some reason.
But the troll kid--
Oh! I've got just the thing!
Perfect.
Okay, then that should be it.
Ew.
I hope this works.
Me too.
Gifr syn, gifr syn, gifr syn…
Uh, maybe you should check the footnotes?
This place is really something.
You think so?
Apart from breakfast
and not getting robbed,
what do we do all day?
Well, the same as humans, I suppose.
-Whatever we want.
-We don't do whatever we want.
We have to go to school
and have jobs and schedules.
You don't want to do those things?
Not really.
That might just be you.
And the sort of thing
that made me think you'd like it here.
Hmm.
What do we do? Hmm.
We drink. Eat.
Think. Wander.
Throw each other.
Throw each other?
-Yes. You know?
-Wait!
It's like a game!
See? You're getting
the hang of it already.
What are the piles of junk all about?
We gather it.
Things the humans have dumped
or don't seem to need anymore.
Hmm? Hmm?
-What does she want with that?
-It's probably for her hoard.
Hoards! I've read
about troll-treasure hoards.
I'm sure that you have. Let me show you.
The treasure you're probably thinking of
is quite hard to come by these days.
Modern trolls tend to focus
on a more modest and curated collection.
Like what?
Car parts.
Barrels, buckets, and pine cones.
Bones!
What do you collect?
Soft furnishings.
Whoa-ho!
Mmm, this is more like it.
Gifr syn, gifr syn…
I'm sick of saying, "Gifr syn"!
Look! There's the troll kid.
And there's Hilda!
Is that meant to be happening?
I don't think so. Um…
I guess that's what Kaisa meant
by, "Doesn't combine well."
-Yeah.
-Don't worry.
We'll find some
other non-bucket-related way to help.
You know, when we saw her,
it kind of looked like--
She was enjoying herself.
Whoo-hoo!
You're having fun?
Are you kidding? With this troll body,
I feel like I could run a hundred miles.
Whoo-hoo!
Or lift up an entire mountain!
There's so much space out here.
No roads, cars,
fences and walls.
I'd forgotten.
Race you to the top of the mountain?
What do you think?
It beats the view from my bedroom window.
So, weird question.
Do I have a troll dad anywhere?
No, why?
No reason.
Trolls aren't usually born
in the sense that you are.
You mean you don't have a mum?
There was a troll once,
a mother to all of us.
But she died a long time ago.
My daughter came to me.
But we are all the children
of the stones in the Earth.
You miss her already, don't you?
Your daughter.
Do you have a hoard?
You must collect something.
I don't need much to feel content.
But I do have this.
-Oh!
-I know it's not much.
I think it's wonderful.
Well, they're yours now.
I've had a nice time today.
But don't you see how wrong this all is?
Maybe this place
isn't perfect for your daughter,
but you've made things
really nice for her.
There's nothing
on the other side of that wall
that's better for her than this.
This is a home.
Her home. And she should be here with you.
Hmm. Maybe I have made a mistake.
So make it right!
Change us back. I know you can do it.
I can't. What's done is done.
I don't know a way.
It's been a long day.
We should sleep.
Are you telling me the truth?
You're not just saying that
to keep me here?
I'm sorry.
Very good. Very good.
I knew your human trickery
would get the job done.
Right, what next?
You sleep?
No. Did you hear
the trolls roaring last night?
It's like they were taunting me.
How's your scratch?
It's not too bad.
You could have been eaten.
I know.
Today has got to be the day.
We have got to get her back!
I don't think
we can do it on our own.
We know all about Hilda,
and we want to help.
So what's the plan?
Well, first,
we just have to make a quick stop.
Baba.
Wait. This is my house.
-What are you doing?
I'm so grateful that you want to help.
I really am.
You are the best friends Hilda could have.
But it's not right
to drag you kids into this. I'm sorry.
Hey!
Wait!
Didn't see that coming.
-Captain?
Ah!
Is it good news, officer? A new lead?
It's someone to see you, sir.
They say it's urgent.
Transformed into a troll.
I know it sounds strange.
Nothing entirely surprises me anymore.
Now, how do you think we can help you?
You're Safety Patrol, aren't you?
It's too dangerous out there,
but not for someone who has one of those.
You want an armed escort?
For my safety.
That's quite a request.
You're welcome to file a report.
But unfortunately--
Help me, and I'll show you
how to get inside the mountain.
I will escort you personally.
-Yes, sir. Understood, sir.
-Do you understand?
-I hope I can count on you.
-You can count on me, sir. Goodbye.
Ahlberg has just put me
in temporary command
of all of Safety Patrol.
So you can't help us.
I'm sorry, children.
I suddenly have quite a lot to do.
This is ridiculous.
Everyone we've turned to
either can't help,
won't help, or won't let us help.
Flipping grown-ups.
Did you hear the news?
Apparently, there were
so many troll rocks outside the town gate,
no cars could get through.
I'm telling you,
there's gonna be an attack or something.
Mark my words.
Oh. I don't know who else to turn to.
What would Hilda do?
She'd probably go and ask a troll.
David, that's it.
We should talk to the trolls.
But, Frida, trolls can't talk.
I know, but perhaps they don't need to.
-Do you remember the Kraken?
The giant tentacle monster-island thing?
Yep. Never, ever gonna forget that.
I was able to tap into its thoughts
and kind of speak to it.
Mind to mind.
If I can do that with a troll--
Then maybe it can help us find Hilda!
It'll be hard getting out there,
though, with the curfew.
My mum! She's gonna be
on bell duty at one of the gates tonight.
You could distract her.
I could.
But it means
you'll be out there on your own.
I don't think we've got much choice.
The final thing I ask of you…
is to bring me something very special.
It lies in the home of the Mountain King.
His hoard is well hidden.
But I can tell you how to find it.
The object I require
is blood red,
and extremely precious.
You will know it when you see it.
This must be it.
Bring it to me,
and I will make you human once more.
Hmm.
Huh?
Wait.
I'm me again!
What is this place?
Whoa!
Hilda!
Mum?
Hilda! Hilda!
Mum! I hear you.
I'm coming!
-Hilda, where are you?
-Mum! I… I don't…
No! Let me through!
Oh.
Uh, hello there. I'm Hilda.
Help!
Help me!
Hilda.
Mum?
What the heck was that?
Still a troll.
Come on then, orb.
Let's get out of here.
Oh.
I'm glad this place is abandoned.
If that Mountain King guy was still here,
this whole thing would have been a lot…
harder.
Baba, you ready?
Easy.
It works.
Uh, should it not?
He'll wake up in a couple of hours
with a splitting headache.
Ugh. This is the place.
Here? But, where's the cave?
I'll remind you, I've gone
well out of my way to be here personally.
If this turns out to be
a waste of my time…
Baba.
Ba.
There. That's the way in.
Now help me find my daughter.
"Ba-ba"?
Wait!
Mum.
-Troll!
Stay back, you beast!
Oh, I can't believe I found you!
I didn't know what to do. I was losing my…
I am so sorry.
Mum! It's okay.
We found each other.
That's all that matters.
Twig!
Tontu! Alfur! You're all here.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
And you. It's nice to see you again.
You've been looking after
my mum, I take it?
Ba!
Hilda. Look at you.
You're… You're--
Oh! Ah, you're strong!
I know. Hop on, Baba.
There's no time to lose.
Where are we going?
To put everything right.
There she is.
Looks
like the other tower is empty.
Use your eyes, try not to fall asleep,
and that's all there is to it.
Psst!
-Hey! Mum!
Who's that?
It's my son!
I have it! I found the thing!
Now you can change me back!
Trundle!
Trundle?
Weird.
He's always been here before.
Hilda.
You! Stay back.
No, Mum. It's okay.
I just found my daughter,
and I won't let you
take her from… me… again.
The bells. They're…
Hilda, what have you done?
Baba?
Baba!
Ba! Ba! Ba! Ba! Ba!
Got you!
Take one more step towards this child,
beast, and I'll turn you to rubble.
Ahlberg? What's he doing here?
Oh! Another one!
-Put that thing away!
That's my daughter.
Is it?
Are you sure? Perhaps she was once.
But how can we be certain she's anything
but the blood-thirsty monster
she appears to be.
Ready to turn on us at any moment.
I'm telling you. Put that thing down,
or I'll take it off you.
And render me defenseless?
Good Lord, they've bewitched you
with their troll magic.
-I'll take that.
Baba!
Oh!
I'm warning you--
I'm warning you.
Mum!
Um, hi!
-Hilda, you're--
-Yep. I'm me again.
And I, uh… I don't have any clothes.
Oh.
Well, perhaps Baba
won't need hers anymore, so…
Oh.
Well, isn't it a good job
Tontu came along?
I brought spares.
How has this all happened?
Returning them to their true mothers
must have brought the spell full circle.
Effectively rendering
the changeling contract null and void.
If this was the way to break the spell,
then doing all that stuff
was just a waste of time.
I don't even need this freaky orb.
Hmm. It was right here.
Orb?
Where are the bells
that used to hang here?
I took them down.
Trundle said if I did,
it'd help him change me back.
Those bells were put there
a long time ago, for a very good reason.
This cave is a prison cell.
The prison cell of the Mountain King.
What? That doesn't make any sense.
Oh, hey. There's my orb.
At last!
Trundle?
Thank you for all your help, Hilda.
It looks like we both got what we wanted.
You… You liar! You tricked me!
He's…
…enormous!
He's heading straight for Trolberg!
We have to stop him.
Baba!
Okay, here we go.
Hello.
Can I help you with that?
There. That's better, isn't it?
All right. If it's okay with you,
I just want to try something.
Huh! You're just as nervous as me.
You know, a lot of people think
there's an army of you
ready to attack Trolberg.
Oh, cruddlesticks.
What are they doing?
He's going to attack the city.
-Attack the city?
-What?
Ha! I don't know
what you're all so concerned about.
He's a big chap, I'll give him that,
but he'll turn around like all the others
once those bells start ringing.
David, what's all this about?
I know something's bothering you,
but I can't help or change anything
if you won't talk to me.
I'm doing this for you, you know.
-For me? You're the one who--
What's going on?
Okay. We're leaving.
Frida!
Oh!
Mum?
Frida, quick! Inside.
Huh?
What?
I can't let you do this, brother.
And what is it you think
that I'm doing, exactly?
We both know what's happening here.
There's a reason I kept that eye from you.
I won't fight you, brother.
I'm not here to fight anyone.
Phew.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Take positions!
All eyes on that gate.
We're too late.
Please.
That wall has kept the people
of Trolberg safe for hundreds of years.
Eyes on the gate.
And mark my words…
Don't say it.
…it will continue to do so.
Oh, my!
Should we fire?
No, don't do anything.
One of them's breaking away.
-I can't let this happen.
-Hilda, wait.
This is my fault. I can speak to them.
Please, let me try.
Go.
Stop!
Hilda!
David!
Mum, I have to.
Don't go any further!
I know it looks like
you might win this fight,
but there'll be more men coming.
You'll be fighting forever.
Everybody loses.
Please!
Listen to me!
Frida!
Are you okay?
Yeah. What are you doing here?
Looking for you,
hoping to avert disaster. The usual.
I came out and made
a mind connection with a troll
to find out what happened to you,
but, well, here you are.
Here I am.
And I feel like I've been here before.
Except that was me!
Frida, when you did your mind connection,
did you learn anything?
It was confusing.
But I did get something to do
with their mother.
Of course!
That's what's been calling them
to the city. A mother's love.
Hilda!
Oh, no. This is what he wants.
Come any closer, and we will open fire.
What's that?
I don't know. But it doesn't feel good.
Hey, where did Ahlberg go?
Deputy!
Sir?
It is very good to see you.
Prepare this weapon to fire.
Yes, sir.
Target acquired. Cannon is charged.
-Open fire.
-Stop!
Whatever you do, don't fire that thing.
Are you blind, child?
That monster
is about to trample the whole city.
This is going to sound crazy,
but I think there's
a giant troll underneath Trolberg.
Hundreds of times bigger than that one,
and she's worried about her children.
That's why he's here, to provoke you.
Because if you react,
if you harm them,
she won't just lie there.
She's going to defend them.
She's going to sit up,
destroying the entire city.
Fire at will, Deputy.
No.
You put me in charge, Erik,
and I am not following that order.
Then you're relieved. Move over.
No!
Please, don't!
Thanks for that.
Ba!
At the ready, people,
prepare to defend your city.
Please, let me talk to them.
We can stop this.
I don't think talking is going to cut it.
This is war!
It doesn't have to be.
Let's get out of here!
Listen to me.
Trolberg is about to be destroyed,
and if you don't take me seriously,
then it's going to be your fault.
That is enough of your nonsense.
Go back to your mother
and stay out of my way.
Hilda!
Throw me!
What?
Mmm.
Get that cannon recharged.
Uh, sir.
What the…
Where am I?
Oh, that kid
is really starting to get on my…
Erik.
Mother.
What do we do?
We have to get out of here.
Agreed.
Baba!
Baba.
Baba, no!
Troll advancing.
-Open fire!
-Stand down!
Sir?
Uh… What do we do?
Nothing.
We do nothing.
Baba.
Keep a close watch.
But just let them in.
They've stopped.
Why have they stopped here?
We're right above her.
I can feel it too.
But I'm not sure
if I can make sense of it on my own.
Help me?
Her name is Amma.
The mother and grandmother to all trolls.
She built these mountains a long time ago
as a home for her children.
She would lie down to sleep between them,
surrounded by those she loved.
One time, after a long rest,
she woke up
to find a village had appeared.
But she didn't want to disturb the people,
so she decided
to remain there until they left.
But the village grew and grew.
It wasn't so bad at first.
Her children could still be close to her.
She could speak to them.
But the people drove them further
and further away from her.
Then they built the wall.
Nothing was ever stopping her
from getting up.
But she didn't do it.
She stayed there,
cut off from her children.
For us. For our sakes.
Do you feel that?
What's happening to them?
She's speaking.
It's hard to directly translate
the trolls' language.
But her words
were along the lines of this.
"My children, I am proud of you."
"You may not remember me,
but I have never,
and will never, forget you."
"Take care of one another."
"Be strong, be good,
and know that I am never far away."
Erik Ahlberg was presented with a medal
for the "unshakable bravery
and quick diplomatic instincts,"
which prevented a catastrophic troll war.
At the same event,
he announced his immediate retirement
from public service.
Chief Officer Gerda Gustav's first act
was to declare
an annual Night of the Trolls.
Every year, the gates are to be opened,
the bells are to be silenced,
and the people of the mountain
allowed to walk peacefully into Trolberg.
It's not perfect.
Many people will still fear the trolls,
and they'll still fear us.
But it's a start.
And perhaps one day,
we'll live truly peacefully, side by side.
There are, however, a few other nights
you might find a troll in Trolberg.
Baba!
-A-ha!
Baba, baba!
And once in a while,
I go out on the mountainside.
-Baba, ba!
And I get to be a troll.
Whoo-hoo!
Baba, ba!