Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Where am I?
Whoa, what?
What's going on?
Let's move him over. Ready?
Turn on the monitor. Get his vitals.
Secure vascular access!
Makoto! Can you hear me?
-Prepare to draw blood.
-Makoto!
Makoto!
His blood pressure looks low.
Get the IV ready!
-Makoto?
-Mom, please calm down.
We're checking his status.
-He's cold. Get him a blanket.
-Okay.
Congratulations,
you are the winner!
How does it feel to be back
in this world, Blank?
Blank?
Yup.
A soul like you who is here to train
for enlightenment is called "Blank."
Look.
Who?
Ow!
What's going on?
So Blank, starting today,
you will homestay
in Makoto Kobayashi's body,
and begin your training.
Hold on.
You're saying that "Blank" is a soul?
Does that mean...
I'm dead?
That's right.
You don't remember.
But you've done pretty bad things
in your previous life.
Bad things?
But,
once in a while, we have lottery
to give souls like you a second chance.
If you answer my quiz correctly,
you will be given the chance to be reborn!
So, it's quiz time.
Quiz?
What was Makoto Kobayashi's
cause of death?
Begin!
Wait, this guy's dead too?
Yeah, dead as a door-nail.
Otherwise, you couldn't enter his body.
How would I know?
And I don't know how I di...
You have 100 days to answer correctly.
Three strikes and you're out.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Nobody can know that you're Blank.
If someone finds out or I can't
get it in 100 days?
Are you the devil?
I'm flattered.
How do I put it...
I'm just a "Guardian" that guides
souls who go on homestays.
If you answer correctly,
this hourglass will stop.
Makoto?
-Makoto?
Please wait outside.
Um...
-Ready to draw blood?
-Yes.
Yes?
Will you do it now?
-You hear me, right?
-Let me check.
-Nothing...
-Can you talk?
Can you recognize where you are?
MAKOTO KOBAYASHI
-Makoto... Kobayashi...
-I'm impressed with his vitality.
It's the first time
a patient has come back to life
a day after being pronounced dead.
I'm guessing she's the mom?
Doctor...
Will Makoto's memory come back?
CIVIL LAW
ADMINISTRATIVE LAW
He has no memory from before
-and after he collapsed...
-And...
-who is...
-His test results appear normal.
...this guy?
But he may or may not have brain damage.
We know of are cases where memory comes
back in a few days...
Some bedside manner!
...amnesia remains permanently...
What was Makoto Kobayashi's
cause of death?
How should I know?
Well,
might as well start by asking his mom.
How did I die?
You had a nasty cold
that turned into pneumonia.
Besides, you're not dead.
What?
Again?
So, you've figured out the quiz already?
Did Makoto die from a cold? Pneumonia-ish?
Sir, you can't be serious.
I told you you're a trainee.
You think reincarnation is that easy?
But the mother said it was a cold...
Yeah, I heard her...
So?
Will you make your first guess
by telling me "he died from a cold"?
Yes?
No.
Makoto?
Hey, what do you want to eat tonight?
Shoot.
Something like beef stew?
Why did she react like that?
All right, beef stew it is.
Beef stew...
Thank you.
We're home.
Here.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'll get dinner ready.
Yeah.
Excuse me...
Hey, nice place.
The brother... the mom...
and he must be the dad.
KEIEI UNIV ENTRANCE CEREMONY
Wait...
Where's Dad?
He's on a business trip to Shanghai.
Business trip?
But he rushed to the hospital to see you.
He had to leave before you woke up though.
What kind of father figure...
Also,
I want you to sleep
in Mitsuru's room for a while.
Huh?
You're still not in tip-top condition,
so I don't want you to be alone.
Mitsuru, look after him, okay?
Can I help?
What?
Do I peel this?
Just... This is the first time
we're cooking together.
Seriously?
Uh, I thought... why not, once in a while?
Okay, thanks.
Sure.
Close one!
Good.
Here you are.
The cold shoulder again.
Beef stew again?
What?
It's what Makoto requested.
I know it's your favorite.
Wow! That was lucky guess!
Yeah.
Okay, let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
I wish Dad was here.
You're right.
What's with this vibe?
Mitsuru?
He's probably tired from studying.
Yeah.
Let's eat.
I survived Day One
without being found out.
You can't tap out.
You have to find out
why Makoto Kobayashi died.
The time limit is 100 days.
So he didn't die... from a cold...
Was it an accident?
Maybe killed?
No way...
But...
What?
Hey, Makoto isn't in any of these photos.
Seems like a normal room.
MODERN LITERATURE
2ND GRADE CLASS C
MAKOTO KOBAYASHI
Cause of death...
That's where you collapsed.
But... if it was just a cold,
what's all this...
It was just a cold.
What's going on?
Go back to sleep.
Wait, Mitsuru!
Mom,
I'd rather sleep in this room.
No, you may not.
I just told you.
It's for when you feel sick again.
I'll feel more comfortable in my room.
Okay?
This family is so weird...
Why did you die?
Good morning.
Thanks for coming by.
No, I wanted to.
It's been a while,
so I'm happy to see you.
How's your grandma?
She's into tai chi now.
-Wow, sounds like she's doing well.
-Who is this?
His girlfriend?
Morning.
What was that?
You're smirking.
Besides getting a cold,
you must've hit your head.
Akira came because
she was worried about you.
Really?
Actually,
I was just worried about the prep work
for the School Foundation Day.
You seem fine, so I'm going.
Then, I'll go with you.
Makoto, were you really just sick?
Why do you say that?
The last time I saw you,
you were acting strange.
In what way?
Gloomy,
zero energy, gaze lowered...
Oh, that's...
But I guess that's the usual you, huh?
The "usual" me?
But today, you're acting way more strange.
Strange?
What's so strange about me?
I'm all better and full of energy.
Talkative. We're having
a decent conversation.
Because I was absent for ten days, so
I hadn't spoken to anyone but my family.
Hurry up and finish your mass game design.
I'm on the committee.
I'm the one who gets blamed.
The mass game design?
Don't tell me you forgot about it.
Sorry... I forgot.
Come to the multipurpose room later.
I will.
Also, Mitsuki was asking me
about what you were up to.
Mitsuki?
Are you happy?
I guess...
I may be happy.
Oh.
Tell me,
Akira, are we just friends, or...
We're just childhood friends!
Wait.
CELEBRATION - SHUYU GAKUIN HIGH SCHOOL
100TH ANNIVERSARY
SHUYU GAKUIN HIGH SCHOOL
Makoto... Kobayashi...
Found it.
Oh, gosh...
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks.
Oh my favorite pen... My textbooks, too...
Hey.
-Eh?
-What?
Your classroom is over there.
Oh, sorry.
Makoto.
Hang in there.
Huh? "Hang in there"?
Morning.
Oh, morning...
Something wrong with me?
Which is Makoto's desk?
-Hey!
Morning.
So sleepy.
Move it!
So, that's why she said "Hang in there."
He's here!
Leave it to me.
I know!
Don't lose, okay?
On your marks...
-Go get 'em!
-Get 'em!
-It's gonna start.
-Okay.
-Get set.
-Okay, I got this now.
Go, go! Keep going!
What the hell's wrong with this body?
-Move it, dork.
-Out of the way.
I have no chance with this guy's body...
Thank you for this meal.
At least, Mom is a really good cook.
You're so polite.
But you're so heartless.
You ignore my DMs,
you won't answer my calls...
I modeled for your painting
and this is what I get?
She modeled for him?
I'm... sorry?
You look so troubled.
Is this...
Mitsuki?
Are you mad?
I'm sorry, I was just messing with you.
She's really cute!
Have you recovered?
Yes.
Then,
you can help me go look for it.
Go look?
Remember my friend's present?
I asked you to help me choose one.
Makoto was going to go shopping with her?
Oh, that's right.
You know a lot about
painting and photography.
I know nothing about art.
Whenever is convenient for you.
Seriously?
Eh? Did I say something wrong?
No, not at all.
But I'm sorry.
I have a practice exam soon.
Can we reschedule it to next month?
Sure.
Looks like I have a chance here!
You're like a different person today.
Huh?
Maybe you...
still have a fever?
So close!
You should know the work excuse isn't
going to cut it this time.
You don't understand
how much we need you at home
as a father figure.
Besides since then Makoto is...
Oh nothing more.
Okay.
Understand that.
Bye now.
Was that Dad?
Yes, his return to Japan got postponed.
It's a shame.
He must be busy.
He's just working hard for our family.
Makoto, go tell Mitsuru.
Okay.
Let's have dinner.
Yup.
Hey, Mom says dinner's ready.
Don't open the door before I answer.
Sorry...
Brother is always so difficult.
Dad never shows up.
See you.
Mom is...
Kobayashi.
Yes?
Here.
Thank you very much.
Oh...
How is Mitsuru doing?
Law classes must be tough
at his university.
Yes.
So, have you talked to your parents?
What?
I always thought
you'd go to the same university
as Mitsuru.
Your parents must have been shocked.
And what did I decide on?
Your parents value education,
so you need courage to tell them.
But it's about your future.
If you're serious about art school,
you have to talk to them.
Art school?
We have less than 100 days
until the event.
Some students have been
working on it since January.
Here.
This?
Hey...
I can't do this.
What? I asked you to help
because I know you can do it.
Yeah, but...
-Akira.
-Coming.
-I'm looking forward to a masterpiece.
-What?
A masterpiece...
93 DAYS TO 100TH ANNIVERSARY
NINETY THREE
Makoto...
Why did you take this...
So annoying...
Mitsuki!
Sorry.
Ready?
Say cheese!
-One more!
-Okay.
Found it!
ENTER PASSWORD
STUDENT ID
MAKOTO KOBAYASHI
DOB SEP 8, 2004
Let's give it a try.
2004...
September... 8th...
Ever heard of security?
PEACE
RIKO'S NEW WORK!
ALL OF US OUT AGAIN!
MITSUKI
Hello?
Look outside. Iridescent clouds!
Iridescent clouds?
Wow...
We'll be filled with happiness, right?
Huh?
You told me, iridescent clouds are
a sign that happiness will come.
But the one we saw from the rooftop
together was too small,
so it had no effect.
But this one... I know it will be amazing.
Right.
Okay, bye.
Wait, Mitsuki!
Where is the painting that I did of you?
I don't know.
Maybe you took it to the Art Room.
MAKOTO KOBAYASHI
Wow!
Makoto, you're pretty good!
Hey, Kobayashi?
Yes, it's Kobayashi.
How's the mass game design going?
Any progress?
Yes, thank you.
What? You're here to gather materials?
Yes, something like that.
What?
Kobayashi, draw something for me.
I love your paintings.
-But I can't...
-What?
You can't do me a favor?
You have...
five minutes.
-Five minutes?
-Ready.
Start.
What's wrong?
You don't want to be released?
Teacher, you're getting too close...
What's going on? This is just impossible.
What? Huh?
Wait.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one,
time up.
I did it...
Wow!
See? You can do it.
Makoto's drawing skill is mine now?
But I prefer something more colorful.
Is it...
Oh, it's coming...
Will you knock it off?
Huh?
You're so funny. I couldn't help it.
Don't do that.
So tell me.
Do you have the answer to my quiz?
I know it wasn't because of a cold.
What?
That's it?
-Yes.
-You're kidding.
-What?
-Come on.
I'll give you one clue, Blank.
What color is this?
Purple.
Are you sure?
This is the clue.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Never mind.
Anyways, start by learning about Makoto.
Okay...
Hey, wait...
Kobayashi?
What? What's wrong?
Sorry, it's nothing.
-Clean this up before you leave, okay?
-Yes!
100TH ANNIVERSARY MASS GAME DESIGN
Start by learning about Makoto.
Easier said than done.
NEW MESSAGE FROM MITSUKI
Yeah!
WHEN ARE YOU FREE TO LOOK FOR THE PRESENT?
First phase of my mission is
to get to know Makoto.
WHERE WE GOING?
Let's ask Mitsuki all about Makoto!
I'LL FIND A SPOT!
I'M COUNTING ON YOU!
A date with Mitsuki!
Makoto! That looks too lame, dude.
Makoto's stuff is my stuff, yeah?
Wait, is that me?
Yes.
I'm still working on it.
I'm flattered.
Thanks.
You like it?
Yeah.
But...
I'm not that pretty.
You got a haircut.
Yeah.
You look good.
Oh, thanks.
DATE SPOT ART
DATE SPOTS FOR ART LOVERS
ART AQUARIUM
There's a play too.
67 DAYS TO 100TH ANNIVERSARY
Is this okay?
A little higher.
-More up?
-Right there.
Okay.
Hey.
Are you going on a date?
What?
With Mitsuki?
Oh...
Just going shopping with her.
How did you know?
You were searching online
while pretending to draw.
You knew?
It was so obvious.
Akira?
Makoto!
Sorry. Didn't see ya.
Don't act like it was our fault!
Shut up, ugly.
Ugly...
So annoying...
Hey! You should apologize to Akira.
Guys, did you just hear something?
Nope.
Apologize to her!
Makoto...
Okay, then. We apologize.
Nice.
That's enough!
Are you mad?
Leave her alone!
Sorry.
I couldn't see you.
-You're so bony.
-Let's go.
-Oh, I'm so hungry.
-Me too.
Are you mad at me?
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
I'm not mad.
I'm just...
wondering why you did that.
What do you mean "why"?
I get it that you were pissed,
but why did you talk back?
It's not funny.
Just...
It's kind of funny because
most girls would get mad
if I didn't talk back.
Even if you talk back,
you end up getting beat up.
Okay.
I was scared.
Makoto,
you didn't seem like the Makoto I know.
And your hair and attitude
are all different.
And...
You don't...
look away now.
But...
Thanks.
Yeah.
But...
You have to finish the design.
Sure.
67 DAYS TO 100TH ANNIVERSARY
51 DAYS TO 100TH ANNIVERSARY
Akira is kind.
And I can draw like a painter.
And Mitsuki's fabulous.
Your life is not so bad, Makoto!
HEY, HEY!
Mitsuki.
Makoto.
-I'm sorry to make you wait.
-No, it's fine.
Hey, you look different
out of school uniform.
Do I... look weird?
It looks good on you.
Let's go.
Wow! This place is awesome.
-You looked it up just for me?
-Huh?
I happened to see it on TV.
"Happened to"?
I... happened... to...
Okay.
But I'm still flattered.
Why do you even pay attention to me?
Because you're cool, Makoto.
Cool?
Me?
The first time I saw you on the rooftop,
you were sitting alone quietly and drawing
not caring what anybody else thought.
That only means...
I'm a loner without friends.
It means you have your own world
that nobody can invade.
That's why I thought you were strong.
But through my eyes,
you're the stronger one, Mitsuki.
You think so? Thanks...
ART AQUARIUM
-Welcome.
-For two, please.
One moment, please.
Do you want a bite?
Uh, no...
Um...
Yeah?
About the present...
Yeah.
That's...
for your "friend..."
Do you mean...
It's for her.
Riko, my classmate.
Oh, for a girl friend.
Yeah.
You're such a good friend.
Yeah, she's my best friend.
Excuse me.
This is on the house.
What? On the house?
Your mother is such a great help here.
What?
Your mother?
Why didn't you tell me?
So embarrassing?
Thanks for the dessert.
We should do this together!
Besides, I was able to buy
a beautiful present.
Thanks to you, Makoto.
No problem.
I hope your friend Riko likes it.
My house is that way.
Say hi to your mom for me.
I will.
Bye.
-Bye.
-Let's weave a peaceful
and beautiful country!
Let's weave it, let's weave it.
To do that, time is very limited.
That's right. My time to get a
girlfriend is close!
Hey, Blank!
And isn't that the same for you, too?
WE ONLY LIVE ONCE
I understand that Mitsuki is pretty.
I do understand that,
Her beauty is like no other,
the transience veiled by her sexiness,
her friendliness that goes against that.
There's not one aspect about her
that is unattractive.
-Right?
-I totally agree, Guardian.
However!
Huh?
It is preposterous if you have forgotten
your main mission!
You seem to be enjoying
your time living someone else's life,
but at this very moment,
the sand in the hourglass
continues to flow,
grain after grain, even as we speak.
Thank you.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you very much.
OSAMU KOBAYASHI
I'LL BE HOME NEXT WEEK
Bye!
See you tomorrow.
Thank you for your kind gesture earlier.
Oh, that's nothing...
I know exactly
how a man feels when he's in love.
Whoops!
Are you alright?
I'm fine, don't worry.
Morning.
Thank you.
Your father is coming home next week.
So, let's all eat dinner together.
What shall I make?
Mitsuru, something you like this time?
Why together?
What do you mean?
I want to eat together.
We're family, right?
And pretend that we're happy?
So...
How was it?
Huh?
You two went on a date, right?
Oh...
Yeah.
It was fun.
Are you two dating?
No,
we're not there yet.
Yet?
So it might happen?
Who knows?
So,
about the Fireworks Show.
How does 5 p.m. sound?
Huh?
We've promised each other
to go together every year.
You forgot?
Of course not.
Makoto,
whatever you do,
please don't catch a cold that day.
I'm home.
Dad?
You're home.
Yeah, hey.
How are you feeling?
I feel fine.
I'm sorry... I couldn't be there for you.
It's okay, you had work to do.
So, you love to paint that much?
I probably...
like it.
I still don't think...
what I did was wrong
for the sake of your future.
What do you mean?
Dad,
did you do something to me?
You really lost your memory, huh?
What the hell was that?
What if his memory comes back...
You don't have to worry about anything.
Where's Mitsuru?
He already left.
He has a bar exam lecture class.
I see. He's studying hard
even on weekends, huh?
He's serious-minded just like you.
I hear he can probably pass the exam
on his first try.
We don't have to worry
about Mitsuru, then.
I don't know about that.
You know very well things don't always go
the way parents want them to, right?
What's that supposed to mean?
Do you hate Makoto's paintings?
I'm just worried about him.
I asked if you like them or not.
You regret breaking his paintbrushes,
don't you?
Makoto and Mitsuru are different.
Just take a closer look at him.
That's your job.
You're just running away from it.
And what about you?
Huh?
You think I don't know anything?
I'll be back in two weeks.
Look after those two for me.
You really lost your memory, huh?
You had a nasty cold
that turned into pneumonia.
Don't open the door before I answer.
Makoto,
I'm going to work, okay?
Okay. See you.
Oh, this is for you, from the library.
When you borrow something
you have to return it.
Yeah.
Makoto,
I...
I love your paintings.
Thanks.
Bye.
Why?
MAKOTO KOBAYASHI
Today, I decided to die.
How many people in this world are
happy with my existence?
What are you doing in my room?
Give me that!
That's my sketchbook.
Why are you hiding it?
You can't let Mom and Dad see this!
You're better off forgetting everything!
You... What did you do to Makoto?
What?
There must be something in there
you don't want people to see!
Hey! What the hell!
Hey!
No! Don't!
Looking for something?
Did you see a sketchbook falling down?
Oh, that thing.
Seriously?
Blank, do you have the answer to my quiz?
Makoto committed suicide.
Listen.
That's merely "how he died."
You have to tell me what the cause was.
The cause was his brother.
Mitsuru drove Makoto to suicide.
Nice try.
Close, but no cigar.
Strike one.
So, two more chances left.
Aoi!
Coming!
Today, I decided to die.
How many people in this world...
What do you want?
Huh?
But...
It's already 5:00 p.m.
So?
The Fireworks Festival...
Sorry, I'll have to pass.
Hey. Wait.
Hey,
Makoto...
What happened?
Nothing.
It's none of your business, Akira.
Is it about school?
Home?
Or...
Is it Mitsuki?
What if it was?
I just want you to tell me
if something's bothering you.
What's up with your hair and clothes?
This is...
To go to the festival with me?
So you got all dressed up?
What if I said "Yes"?
You love Makoto, don't you?
Makoto wasn't in the hospital
because of a cold.
He committed suicide!
What?
He got sick of living a crappy life
surrounded with rotten people,
and popped a bunch of pills.
His will...
didn't mention you at all.
I get it.
You're the same as Makoto.
Nobody notices you.
You poor thing.
"Today,
"I decided to die.
"How many people
"in this world are happy
with my existence?"
I hate myself, too.
If I was near me,
I wouldn't want myself to come into sight
because my darkness might be contagious.
I feel sorry for Mitsuru
for being connected to me
by blood.
I love...
to paint.
Only when I paint,
can I be myself.
Beyond the canvas...
is a world, that exists just for me.
But Dad...
couldn't allow me to live in that world.
-Osamu!
-That's why, that moment...
COLLEGE APPLICATION
...I truly became a person
that has nothing else left.
An empty shell.
But I still had...
the rooftop.
Whenever I went there,
Mitsuki would always be there.
Mitsuki is the only person...
that knew I existed.
Mitsuki!
You were modeling for a picture?
We didn't know that.
MAKOTO KOBAYASHI
Who's Makoto Kobayashi?
A freshman?
You know him?
No, never heard of him.
Fifty... two points!
This for the mass game? Such a turnoff.
It's a "my dearest goddess" kind of thing?
Talk about delusional.
It's so serious, it's lame.
-Doesn't this look like you, Mitsuki?
-Huh?
No... Cut it out, that's creepy.
But look at her face!
This doesn't look like me at all.
-You think?
-Yeah.
What did you just say?
-You should've told me you didn't like it.
-That's not it...
What's "not it"?
You called me "cool"
and said you counted on me.
Were you just lying and making fun of me?
-I really meant it.
-Then that makes it even worse.
Makoto...
Mitsuki is the only person...
100TH ANNIVERSARY MASS GAME DESIGN
...that knew I existed.
But that too was...
just an illusion.
Mitsuki, are you dating him?
What?
You should go after him.
We can talk later. Okay?
Bye.
We're not dating.
But I just saw...
Because you're the one I love.
Huh?
Riko, I love you...
Your birthday present...
You don't have to accept it
if you don't want to.
I have been a void
to all others since the very beginning.
Not even my own mother.
What shall we eat?
Broccoli!
I'm sorry I brought Anna along.
It's fine.
Because this is the last time.
Come on, hurry!
Okay.
I'm not being pessimistic.
I'm only being realistic.
Even if I'm gone,
there's no need to fill that void.
Even now...
Because I have always been a void to them,
CONTRADICTION
...since the very beginning.
People are laughing,
crying,
being angry,
being happy...
Even while I'm doing this,
they're going on with their lives.
This may sound like a contradiction,
but all I ask for now,
is that through my death,
somebody will be...
aware of my existence...
Are you thinking of jumping?
That sounds like a good idea.
But you have to answer correctly first,
since Blank is still doing a homestay.
Everybody killed Makoto.
Mitsuru,
Mom,
Dad,
Mitsuki...
Everybody who didn't
take notice of Makoto,
they all drove Makoto to suicide.
In there.
EIGHT
Strike two.
You have eight days left.
Makoto hasn't come home yet.
What? What about school?
I already called.
They said he left a while ago.
Stop.
No! I don't want to relive
that moment ever again!
Mitsuru...
I have to find him...
I must find him...
Or just like that... Makoto...
It'll be alright!
Calm down!
I'll go look for him, so you stay home.
You need to be here
in case Makoto comes home.
Okay?
CALLING
MAKOTO...
Makoto...
CALLING
MAKOTO...
Makoto...
Hurry, get in the car.
No wonder he killed himself.
You say you love Makoto's paintings?
You pretend to be a loving mother,
but you're playing make-believe
with someone else's family!
Bringing along that cute little girl...
Did you have fun?
That's not...
No!
Today is the last day I'll see him.
So you expect to be forgiven?
It was so easy for you.
You just ran away
to someone else's family.
But Makoto, he had nowhere to run to...
Death was the only way out for him!
You didn't need to put up his paintings.
You needed to meet him face-to-face!
Makoto's already dead.
Makoto!
You were sound asleep.
You were lucky. Just minor injuries.
You can go home tomorrow.
"You were"?
I was afraid to admit...
that I was wrong.
Come on honey,
give me a chance to talk to you again...
They said she hit her head hard.
She's still unconscious.
That painting...
You got really hurt that time
and spoiled our family camping trip,
but it might've been our best memory.
What's the point...
of bringing some old painting...
Isn't there something
you finally realized?
You still don't get it?
Don't be a baby and expect people
to read your emotions.
If you want to go to art college,
you gotta face Dad.
Nobody will understand you...
until you say it out loud.
-Look who's talking, you're...
-Exactly!
That's why I'm telling you!
You don't stand out,
and you lack confidence and social skills.
Day in and day out,
you followed me around,
you'd fall down and cry.
I can't keep my eyes off you.
I have a little brother
who needs so much attention.
And suddenly, he's gone.
Do you think I can live with that?
Do you think I was okay
seeing you die in front of my eyes?
"Nobody sees me"?
Then, what were your eyes seeing?
Cut the crap!
There you are!
COMMITTEE MEMBER
We can't find your design.
Do you know where it could be?
Uh...
It's not in the multipurpose room.
Sorry...
Actually, I lost it.
You what?
Come on! What will you do about this?
First Akira,
now you...
What happened to Akira?
She said she wants to quit.
We're so busy as it is. We need her.
Without her...
Hey, look at this.
Isn't this Mitsuki?
Oh, gosh.
-Oh, no...
-Really?
What the hell...
I don't believe it...
Good morning.
Mitsuki.
Any comment on this?
Huh? How...
Okay, then.
Miss Riko, care to comment on this?
It's not my business.
Mitsuki initiated without asking.
Honestly, I'm really annoyed.
Harsh.
Mitsuki?
I'm sorry.
This is...
how you must've felt that time, huh?
I was horrible to you.
Don't worry about it.
You're really a strong person, Makoto.
But I'm not...
I was afraid to be alone...
so I went along with my friends...
All the while, I was hiding my true self,
and I betrayed you.
But you know what?
I'm in so much pain now,
but part of me feels relieved
they found out about Riko.
I wonder why?
I want to run away,
but all I can remember are
our happy memories.
I want to disappear this very moment...
but I don't even know
which me is the real me.
There's...
nothing wrong with that.
I don't know who the real me is, either.
But you know,
red,
blue,
purple...
We all have multiple colors
within ourselves.
The "you" that feels relieved
and the "you" that wants to run away,
all these different colors
overlap with each other
and make you, Mitsuki.
They're all...
your true self, Mitsuki.
And...
It can be quite a pain in the butt
if you die.
That's funny...
You sound like you have experience.
I'm home.
FROM DAD
Sorry,
I forgot something.
Guardian?
Guardian!
Hi everyone.
What's wrong?
Makoto said he lost his design.
What?
We're never going to make the deadline.
What should we do?
We'll use someone else's design instead.
Hey, Guardian!
I know you're watching me!
Come down here!
Guardian...
Hey, Guardian!
After I answer correctly,
what will happen to this body?
If you like it, you can keep it.
Once you rejoin the cycle of rebirth,
you can be reincarnated
as Makoto Kobayashi.
I don't want it.
I don't need it.
I...
I want to return this body to Makoto.
Not just to Makoto.
I want to return Makoto to his family
and everybody around him!
Please.
Bring Makoto's soul back!
Alright.
I'll bring it back.
On one condition.
I'm gonna add another question.
By the end of tomorrow,
you have to remember the mistake that you
yourself made in your previous life.
Then, Makoto can have his body back.
My?
If you can't answer correctly,
both of your souls will evaporate.
Makoto will be gone, too?
There's no backing out.
I suggest you open your eyes wide.
You have to remember the mistake that you
yourself made in your previous life.
WAR
MISTAKES
STUDENT DEAD BY SUICIDE
You've done pretty bad things
in your previous life.
MY MISTAKES
That's merely "how he died."
BURGLARY
ABUSE
You have to answer what the cause was.
You seem to be enjoying
your time living someone else's life.
Start by learning about Makoto.
CAR CRASH KILLS HIGH SCHOOLER
Where is it?
You're a trainee.
You think reincarnation is that easy?
Blank is still doing a homestay.
JAPAN DAILY NUMBER OF DEATHS
AVERAGE 3,780 PEOPLE
I love your paintings.
You love to paint that much?
Do you think I was okay
seeing you die in front of my eyes?
MY LAST WISHES
MAKOTO
"Dear Makoto."
I wanted to...
MAKOTO IS BORN!
...return this body to you.
FIREWORKS SHOW
But...
FIRST TIME FISHING
I've run out of time...
OUR FIRST FAMILY CAMPING TRIP!
MAKOTO IS HAPPY TO BE WITH HIS BIG BROTHER
ARTIST MAKOTO'S MASTERPIECE
Makoto,
I'm sorry I couldn't return this body...
to you...
FISHING!
EXCITED FOR FIREWORKS
FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL
MAKOTO GRADUATION
GRADUATION
FIRST DAY OF HIGH SCHOOL
Akira...
SHUYU GAKUIN HIGH SCHOOL
I asked you to help
because I know you can do it, Makoto.
100TH ANNIVERSARY MASS GAME DESIGN
ONE DAY TO 100TH ANNIVERSARY
LET'S DO OUR BEST IN THE REHEARSAL
AS WELL AS THE PERFORMANCE TOMORROW!
You're in charge of filming?
We need to check the whole procedure.
I see.
Akira...
I'm sorry...
You really hurt me.
Enough hurt to last a lifetime.
Yeah...
But,
let's call it even.
What?
I didn't realize...
how much you were struggling and in pain.
So...
I'm sorry, too.
What an idiot...
What?
It's just that,
I think I'm really an idiot...
You've always been there for me.
Thank you.
You're... being too honest. It's creepy.
This...
I know it's too late, but...
What is it?
I wanted to give that to you, Akira.
This...
I couldn't go to the fireworks show
with you, so...
That's awesome.
Yeah.
We can see this just once in a lifetime.
What? Once?
It's the 100th anniversary.
We won't be around for the 200th, will we?
I'm so glad...
I got to see this.
Tomorrow's the big day, not today.
Oh...
Makoto, your painting is next.
Huh?
I borrowed a painting of yours
from the Art Club and made it.
If I can't pick a painting,
what's the use of being on the Committee?
It's... the same...
I chose my favorite painting.
Makoto,
you've changed a little bit,
but you're still the same you.
Makoto?
It's nothing.
-I have to go now.
-Okay.
I know what mistake I made...
I am responsible for Makoto's death.
I killed myself.
I...
I am Makoto.
Congratulations, Blank.
You did a wonderful job!
Aren't you the nurse?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm just as surprised as you are.
This person is working two jobs.
He must be living a tough life.
Yeah, but...
what's gonna happen to me?
Of course,
you're gonna die.
A few decades from now
as Makoto Kobayashi.
What?
What? Aren't you happy?
Um...
Happy? It's more like...
mixed emotions...
Anxiousness?
Come on, don't worry.
You completed your homestay.
-I thought it was someone else's life.
-So what?
You're tapping out?
Huh?
Can I?
Of course you can't!
I know that.
After all,
life is merely a long-term homestay.
Will I see you again?
Makoto,
hold on to your life, okay?
Dear Makoto.
I wanted to
return this body to you.
You were wrong to think
that nobody was aware of you.
You were the one who wasn't aware
that everybody was there for you.
NO RESEMBLANCE - MAKOTO
BY AKIRA
That's why I wanted to return
this body to you
and return Makoto...
OVERDUE
...to your family.
But...
I've run out of time.
I'm sorry for the late return.
Makoto.
I'm sorry I couldn't return
this body to you.
But,
there's something I had to tell you.
Dear Makoto, I wanted to
return this body to you. You were...
"You were...
"loved all along."
Makoto!
Here.
I told you to bring this to your mom.
Oh, sorry, I forgot.
Yeah.
You're the same old Makoto...
What do you mean?
I'm not telling.
That's why, I've decided
to love this life a little longer.
I'm going to hold on to my life.
After all, life is merely
a long-term homestay.