(crickets chirping)
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
(birds chirping)
(motor revving)
(dog barking)
(uplifting rhythmic music)
(speaking Spanish)
(electronic music)
(Spanish music)
(lively music)
(singing in Spanish)
Every single day I grind
my way up different levels
Different levels
(singing in Spanish)
Can't nobody tell me nothing
-Eagles on one!
-One! Eagles!
This is KIHR,
Hood Rover sports radio
and this is the moment
you've been waiting for.
The start of boys soccer season.
-Yes!
-Here we go Eagles!
Wow.
Goal!
It's a windy one out there.
Player's jerseys are billowing.
(crowd cheering)
-Goal!
-Here we go!
Eagles feature a dynamic group
of stars up and down the lineup.
With the conference
championship and a spot
in the state playoffs looming
as a very real possibility.
No!
Oh.
Here's our chance.
Goal!
Angel Sonato.
And goal!
Woo!
(singing in Spanish)
(indistinct team chatter)
One, two, three we are Eagles!
(wind rustling)
(bus humming)
(fanfare)
Coming in as MVP.
(crowd cheering)
I really feel like
the senior class
has just a ton
and ton of spirit.
(cheering)
So let's show these guys
what it means
to have the Eagle beat.
Here we go!
Who's got the beat?
The mighty Eagle beat,
it goes...
(clapping in unison)
Who's got the beat.
The mighty eagle beat,
it goes...
(clapping in unison)
(cheering)
Hey guys, we got a real quick
rundown of our fall sports
today for you.
So right now, I'd like
our boys varsity soccer players
to stand up real quick,
boys varsity soccer.
(cheering)
They're ranked number one
in the state.
Nice job boys soccer.
(cheering)
(indistinct chatter)
Three, two and time.
So now we've got two attackers
on the sides.
Depending where the forward is
maybe he turns and shoots.
Or maybe he plays the ball out
and we get across.
Hood River Valley
high school boys soccer
is a big part of our community.
(speaking Spanish)
It's probably the most popular
sport in Hood River.
There's a lot of talent
on this team.
We have a shot at winning
our division
and then maybe
even making some noise
-in the state playoffs.
-Goal scored over here.
You have two goals
to score on, guys.
Play, play, play.
The team is sort of
broken up right now.
Some of the Anglo kids certainly
tend to stick to one group
and then there's like another
group of Mexican kids
who maybe don't speak
as good of English.
(speaking Spanish)
We gotta finish!
Keep it crispy, guys.
When I first went
to kindergarten,
I like saw this divide
where like all right,
Mexicans versus the white kids.
(kicking soccer ball)
At the time, we didn't really
think it was like bad, you know.
But like you still see it
in high school too.
There's another goal,
there's another goal.
Monday through Friday we're all
on the soccer field together
and it's my job to get those two
groups to work together
on the same team.
Yes! I like that.
Yes, yes.
I dream about that last night.
I'm serious.
(machine beeping)
We came back to here from Mexico
cause we have
a lot of family here.
My mom came with refugee visa.
And my dad,
he came under the border.
(speaking Spanish)
(heavy breathing)
I have some plans for the future
but I don't like school.
The biggest reason
that I'm still going
is cause I love soccer.
(guitar music)
I kind of started making
my meals in the mornings
two months ago.
As soon as I started
tracking what I was eating
I realized that it could help me
play soccer
a lot better than I was.
And I felt
so much better lately.
-Hi Dad.
-Hey, bud, so how long
does this whole meal prep
thing now usually take?
It was a train wreck
the first time.
The first time was pretty bad,
now I like--I'm probably
20 minutes out, 30 minutes out.
So.
Where did you get
the recipe again?
Some video,
YouTube or something?
Some bodybuilder, yeah.
But I had changed it
a little bit.
Okay.
Sometimes I get frustrated
with my teammates.
It seems pretty obvious to me,
like yeah,
you guys ate Twinkies
before the game.
And you got two hours of sleep
last night.
Like, no shit
we don't play well.
But a lot of these kids, like
that's all they've ever known.
They don't have the money
to pay for really good food.
They don't have parents
who preach to them
how important sleep is.
Domingo!
Push up, push up!
Let's go! Get up.
Make it work Mingo.
Stop walking, let's go.
Push up! Push up!
One more, one more.
It's so important for me
to be able to have an impact
on those guys.
But if they show up late,
they don't wear the right gear,
they don't care,
it's really discouraging.
Hey, Saul, come on.
You're literally walking, dude.
Don't ever catch
yourself walking.
It's really fucking tiring
when you're the only one
-that's running.
-I know it does, dude.
I'm in that position
every single practice.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
(dogs barking)
My mom works
at the juice factory.
She's amazing.
I love my mom.
My dad, he doesn't have
like education.
He doesn't have
a high school diploma
but he's my inspiration.
(school bus humming)
(uplifting music)
-Eyy!
-Yo, actually put that beat
back on I like that.
Just went from overlooked
to overbooked
My (indistinct lyrics)
is overcooked
Only spit verses,
ain't got no hook
Said it couldn't be done
so I undertook
(inaudible rapping)
Yeah!
Bro, I can't come up with--
(laughing)
Dude.
Ugh.
Who's next?
Fuck yeah.
Number 21, a junior, Robbie
(inaudible).
This is not a time to just come
out here and score eight goals
-and then we leave.
-Saul Chavarria.
We've got better dribbling,
we've got better skills.
But we've got to make
combination play, you guys.
All right? We have to get
ready for Woodburn, dudes.
A senior, Erik Siekkinen.
That is your Hood River Valley
Eagles.
-Eagles on one.
-One!
Eagles!
KIHR Hood River sports radio.
-Home of the Eagles.
-Let's go guys.
Move the ball around guys,
move the ball around.
Move the ball around,
just like practice, guys.
(crowd cheering)
Shoot. Move the ball!
If we just continue to dribble
we're gonna draw more defenders,
right.
Hustling for the goal,
Erik Quintones takes a hard
fall.
Referees calling a foul.
(cheering)
Goal!
Nice. Good, good.
(indistinct chatter)
Robbie, Quintones!
(intense music)
Get the ball, look inside!
Who's the 45?
He needs a better 45 than that.
Saul Chavarria with the passing
and the (rapid game commentary)
Goal!
Erik Siekkinen.
Yes Wesley!
Wesley Carter with a blast,
he scores!
That's a goal.
Sub, can we get a sub?
Domingo. Let's finish it off
for Fabian.
Hustle, dude.
Sal Chavarria
(rapid play calling)
Here we go!
Goal!
Another great pass
and Saul and Barragan
won't miss many of those.
(cheering)
(buzzer)
The Eagles systematically
dismantle
the Pendleton Buckaroos to
remain on top of the division.
Still undefeated
but largely untested.
Oh, 11!
Dude, these shoes are like--
I got you beat, brother.
Check my touch.
Dude, I've hit like what? 300.
Hood River,
it's either one or two ways.
Count for me I'm with 21.
You just work hard worrying
about the next bill.
Worrying about the next payment
or you live in Hood River
and then you're worrying about
the next biking trip
or the next like, ski trip.
It's a good place to live
if you have money.
Most of the white kids
all just be like,
"Oh, where are you going
for like, Thanksgiving break?"
It's like,
"I'm staying here, man."
Like, we're not going anywhere.
And like, all of them
go to like freaking,
Park City or like Whistler
and all that stuff.
And it's cool and then they all
go to the mountains and stuff
but we just hang around here
and just play footie.
Oh my god.
If you don't know anyone here
in Hood River
and you don't have money
then you're kind of like...
just here.
(indistinct chatter)
All right, Erik, Travis, you
have three minutes prep time.
Three minutes starting now.
Freaky, this is about
to get freaky.
Yeah, Robbie's gonna win this.
That was five minutes.
I'm gonna have to wing it.
I have one bar.
-I'll start, I'll start.
-We need a group name.
Wait, one minute
to create of group name.
-Red--
-White Rice!
White Rice!
-Ready?
-Okay.
Coming real hot
come and seeky
Yeah, I'm doing this weekly
It's about to get freaky
You say you got the sauce
But I just say you're leaky
(laughing)
All right, everybody be quiet,
everybody be quiet.
Everybody be quiet.
Be quiet, be quiet, be quiet.
Get out of there.
My name is Robby
Rapping's just a hobby
Erik isn't even
in my freaking lobby
Yo, we're White Rice
We're pretty nice
I got a lot of ice
(laughing)
You guys just lost.
Yeah Kiki,
you're looking like a boy
You need to eat some more
You need to eat
some more soy
Oh! Woah.
His name is Erik and he...
Soccer ball
but little does he know
His starting position's
about to fall
Oh!
Woah! She just said you'll
be on the bench, Erik!
Cover your ears.
Erik, you are pretty lazy
Those muscles
don't get ladies
Just ask Katie
Oh!
(laughing)
Erik, you are the bitch
of the squad
And just like these chords
they're slim as his quad
You already know that
your starting game is week
Player of the year
You know Angel's
got you beat
Oh!
(laughing)
(indistinct chatter)
Yo, what was crazy dude.
I've been thinking about making
a fitness account for a while
cause I've been working
pretty hard at the gym.
Pretty much everyday
I go to soccer practice
and then I go to the gym
and then my dad helps me
with my--my, uh, homework.
(lively music)
Erik, you can't beat him
Oh my god!
When I moved here
I was nine years old.
It was super tough, I didn't
really have any friends.
In the fourth grade
my mom was like,
"You're too smart for
these people around here, so
I was homeschooled."
My mom homeschooled me cause she
didn't like my teacher.
So when I got into middle school
from a social standpoint
I was terrified.
(heavy breathing)
I had friends but I didn't have
like a really,
really good friend.
It didn't take long for me
to lose my confidence.
I was just basically afraid.
I remember praying about it.
Like, I was lost, you know.
(crows cawing)
(thunder rumbling)
(rain pattering)
(dramatic music)
My dad, he didn't
make a stop correctly
and got arrested.
They took him
to an immigration jail.
Now he's fighting
to not get deported.
(coughing)
(solemn music)
(car starting)
That's it, he got deported.
(thunder rumbling)
(water running)
(water splashing)
All right, 15 second sprint, go!
Let's go, boys.
(clapping)
Let's go, let's go,
come on, let's go boys.
Come on, anybody can sprint
for 15 seconds.
Let's go, Mingo.
(heavy breathing)
One minute break.
Ugh.
How's this warmup for you,
Galvez.
This is what we do
after our 1Ks.
(coughing)
(indistinct chatter)
(guitar music)
(drumming music)
KIHR Hood River sports radio.
Home of the Eagles.
Coach Jamie Rivera called
into our AM Morning Show
to talk about what this game
means for the team
and for the season.
At this point in our season,
every game is a championship.
Because if you don't win
then you go home.
(indistinct conversation)
And if someone's lagging
behind yell at him.
If it's me, yell at me.
People make sure I'm on the guy.
If I'm late...
(chanting)
-Eagles on one!
-One!
Eagles!
Let's play some
Hood River soccer.
Keep tight, nice and tight.
Win this!
No turn, Robbie!
One and two touch.
The Eagles moving the ball
to the Hermiston territory
for the first time this game.
(cheering)
Keep them there!
Go Erik!
Siekkinen goes to clear
and he misses and the ball rolls
dangerously through the crease.
Win it back! Win it back! Erik!
Erik back on defense
but he trips and falls
and they score.
(indistinct chatter)
Some smart, aggressive gameplay
on the part of Hermiston
seems to have confused
the Eagles.
There's a lot of effort
but not a lot of team work.
Hey, keep it buzzing all right?
Keep it buzzing.
-One nothing Hermiston.
-Watch your body language,
-watch your body language.
-I'm pissed off
at how I'm playing,
I want to yell at our team
because I'm mad
about our intensity.
I need every single one
of you guys to give 100 percent
of your effort every single time
you're in the game.
Can you guys do that for me?
Yeah?
Yeah.
Play resumes with 22:30
left on the clock.
(cheering)
Plenty of time, plenty of time.
(intense music)
One and two touch guys!
Siekkinen goes go clear
and he misses and the ball rolls
dangerously through the crease.
Win it back!
Hey, that's a quarter!
Yeah, let's get it,
let's go boys.
6:53 left in the game
and the Eagles are going to
start running out of options.
(indistinct chatter)
Erik!
Goal!
(cheering)
(indistinct cheering)
Eagles scramming
for a quick follow up goal
to salvage the game.
And Erik Siekkinen
in the final seconds
is just a few steps behind.
(clapping)
(whistle blowing)
(solemn music)
(rain pattering)
(dog barking)
Nobody likes me right now, man.
Erik!
Good.
Go threes.
Mingo didn't get the message
that it was at four here.
So that's why he's late.
You know about his father,
right?
Yeah, it's hard.
And last one, here we go,
here we go, here we go.
Give it away.
Guys we're moving right
into another activity.
Here we go, we're going to go
one V ones in these lanes here.
We're working on
defending the player
that's attacking at speed.
You win the ball
you counter all the way
to the end of the lane here.
Don't just win the ball
and then walk off.
That's not the game.
Let's see Erik, let's see, Erik.
Erik, what'd I just say?
Erik, 50 burpees
for not doing
what I just asked you to do.
(heavy breathing)
You guys gotta listen
to the instructions, guys.
On the whistle.
Erik.
That's shit defending, man.
If you got him like this there's
no way he's cutting behind.
He's just going to hit it long
and you got him there.
Erik?
Erik.
(thunder rumbling)
Just go now.
Just leave.
(rain pattering)
(thunder rumbling)
(crickets chirping)
(guitar music)
(indistinct plane announcement)
Papa.
(sobbing)
(crying)
(solemn guitar music)
(upbeat live music)
(banging)
(guitar music)
(singing in Spanish)
And I
Haven't lost my mind
Thinking about you
Manny's with us today right?
Lesley's not playing.
Lodi can't play.
Domingo's out.
-Why isn't he on the bus?
-What's that?
Why is he not on the bus?
You know about his father right?
-I don't.
-His father was deported
to Mexico.
He just doesn't say
a whole lot, you know.
Like, sometimes I feel like
he just comes
and he doesn't feel like
he's part of the team sometimes.
I'm not putting that on him
but I think sometimes
we don't accept him as like...
Even though Domingo doesn't
speak the best English
some words of encouragement
to him would go a long ways
-right now because...
-A lot of people on this team
that would help him out but he's
gotta actually want it.
I think that's where
the team comes in right?
That's where you guys need to...
I mean, imagine how he feels.
We should be doing what
we can to help him
stay eligible and motivated,
right?
Yeah.
Oh my god, I feel like I'm
somewhere in like East Coast
Wait, this is a high school?
KIHR Hood River sports radio
coming to you today from
the Atkinson Community Stadium
in Franklin, Oregon.
Where the Franklin Quakers
will host
the Hood River Valley Eagles
later today.
With the season winding down
the statistics
become increasingly important.
A tie or worse, a loss,
could shuffle the rankings.
And either force
a division playoff
or eliminate
the Eagles completely.
Tails it is.
Kick-off or end?
Let's go Eagles!
Franklin looking to extend
a four-game winning streak.
Eagles remain undefeated
with one tie.
Two much space between
the back line and Robby.
Roc be the middle guy.
Hey, hey, hey!
(indistinct instructions)
Keep moving the ball.
Refs call a penalty number 18,
Angel Sonato.
Shit.
Hey, let's go, let's go.
How is that a balanced call?
Let's go Eagles.
Come on, bring it Alex.
And here comes the kick.
(cheering)
Alex Rodriguez
has a beautiful save.
Two in a row
and the Eagles recover.
(cheering)
Team Caption, Saul Chavarria
countering up the field
and comes crashing down.
Are you kidding me?
Incredibly aggressive gameplay
on the part of both teams.
Still no score.
And he's like that's not a foul.
I was like what the--
and then the next play
I went like this to him
and he called a foul on me.
Fucking stupid as hell.
Our rhythm is totally
screwed up.
Stop dribbling so dang much
and show you guys
want this win. Okay?
Let's make them look
like children boys.
-Eagles on one!
-One!
Eagles.
Both teams trying anxiously
to avoid a tie,
or worse, a loss.
Go, get on that,
come on, come on.
(indistinct remarks)
Get set up!
Flying into counter attack,
the ball's in the box,
and goal!
Saul Chavarria gets
a head on it.
Eagles on the board with
under two minutes remaining.
Franklin incoming
for what could be
the last play of the game.
And it's a handball,
a handball call
against the Eagles.
Come on, dude, they've gotten
two penalties already.
Two.
Scoop it.
(whistle blowing)
Here comes the shot.
Franklin has tied the game
with seconds on the clock.
(whistle blowing)
Saul Chavarria with
a last desperate attempt.
(buzzing)
The clock runs out
on an intense second half.
(grunting)
(cheering)
(indistinct remarks)
Let's go, let's go.
Heads up, boys, heads up,
forget about it.
Poor communication
and a little bit of bad luck
on the part of the Eagles
have the division championship
slipping through their fingers.
(buzzing)
You know what, guys, come here,
all of you guys, come here.
Yeah.
You guys realize that
if there would to be
another tie,
or a potential loss,
the conference championship
is not secure?
You guys understand that, right?
Angel, come on,
this is not funny, dude.
I'm--I'm being serious.
If you don't wanna
take this seriously,
you can just excuse yourself
from the meeting here.
We gotta pick it up, boys.
Let's go, let's go.
Get your 11 on each side,
let's go.
So, are you--are you hurt?
Just step off, you can turn
if you want them to.
Well, if you're really hurt,
then get off the fucking field.
-Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
-If you're going to play,
-then play.
-All right, that's what I'm--
That's what
I'm telling you, dude.
-It's fine, dude.
-If you're hurt, then leave--
-Why are you telling me that?
-Because I didn't play.
Just fucking chill, dude,
Jesus Christ.
-Yeah, bro, if you can't, then--
-I'm telling him
I'm gonna try it.
Yeah.
As a--as a team, like--
We can't really play
with each other this year.
That's one, yep.
It's like--it's like chemistry,
and right now we're, like,
at 45 percent chemistry
-out of 100.
-Uh, like 50.
Gather all the goals.
You guys are making me mad.
(whistle chirping)
-A-ha, get 'em.
-Yes.
You guys--Angel, Angel,
take this seriously.
-Dude, it was going over--
-Take this seriously.
Don't be laughing around,
and don't call me "dude."
Come here, come here,
you're not gonna
talk to me that way.
-Yeah.
-Get over here!
(indistinct remarks)
Good luck.
Ow, shit.
Oh, be careful.
Oh, I sliced myself pretty good.
Oh, you got Band-Aids?
-Yeah.
-Where's your Band-Aids?
Yeah.
Wanna take 'em to Daddy?
Here.
I try to approach things
pretty similar every year.
You're welcome, sweetheart.
But, I can't get
everyone on the same page.
(squeaking)
-It's very frustrating to watch.
-Well, he wants
to play basketball in there.
(crying)
Hit it.
-Nice.
-Wow.
Maybe I've been doing things
the wrong way this whole season.
(laughing)
(sobbing)
Latest weather winds out
out of the west
at 10 miles an hour...
(indistinct intercom remarks)
(birds chirping)
(speaking Spanish)
Get all that right now
before we get going.
So, I've got my opinions.
I'm sure you guys
all have your opinions
in reflection now,
what are some things
that we could've done better.
I've been thinking
about this a lot,
and I have to own up to it.
I trust the hell
out of this team,
it's just that we--our own heads
get in our way sometimes.
Okay, I need to
take responsibility
as your head coach,
because I need
your guys's help, too.
It's--we've gotta
make a change, dudes.
Okay, and again, it starts--
it starts with me.
Okay, but it can't just be me.
Leave the past to be the past,
and we have to start writing
a new--a new story today.
So--are you guys with me?
You boys in this?
Okay, all right,
I'm all in with you guys,
okay, for the rest
of this season.
(whirring)
(speaking Spanish)
Yeah, exactly, exactly, so.
"To the person
with more experience,
like a police officer,
so he can give me
a better opinion."
I like it, you're okay,
so do (speaking Spanish.
Eh?
(clanking)
(thudding)
5,500.
My dad and my mom,
they've always been
in leadership positions.
I just assumed that
I could be a leader, too.
(crickets chirping)
(sloshing)
(beeping)
You ready?
-All right, I got it, I got it.
-Let go.
All right, all right.
(grunting)
Yes, let's go, buddy!
-Woo!
-Oh, look at those pull-ups.
I've done, like,
three actual ones.
Yeah, do it, that was good.
Yeah, you hustling or what?
(grunt)
There's a reason
you're a captain, Alec.
-Yeah.
-Obviously you're gonna be
one of the leaders,
just the way you lead
has to change, to be honest.
Long speeches
where you're telling people
how to prepare stuff,
they just don't work.
You don't just
go up to someone and say,
"This is why you're bad."
Like, someone's willing
to listen to you
if you tell them,
"Yeah, you're playing bad
because of this,"
but you've built up the--
to the point where they know
that you're giving them advice,
and so you gotta, like, get that
out of your, like, head,
that you need to fix everyone,
-because you're not.
-I was talking to my dad
about it, and he was,
like, talking about
servant leadership.
-Yeah.
-Because it's something that
he does a lot,
at his job at least,
and that's, like,
a leader is a servant
to the people that he's leading.
-Yeah, like--
-Right, and so it's, like,
me going out of my way
to do the extra nice thing
for the other person,
and not to make it, like,
a racial thing,
but I think that--
You just did by saying that.
Okay, well to make it
a racial thing,
the soccer field
is where they thrive.
-Mhm.
-Where--where it's like--
you know, and I think
that I almost disrespected them
in a way by coming out there
and pretending like
I know more than they do.
That's how they feel
on a daily basis,
so then you making that--
putting that on them
makes them, like,
feel even more--
They're like, "Ah, Erik's good
in school and all this,
but I'm better at soccer,"
then you come out
and you tell 'em what to do,
and, like,
your position as a captain,
they'll be like,
"Well, fuck this guy."
You just--that's how
you're gonna be a suc--
a successful leader, you know?
For one, leading by example,
and for two, like,
reaching out to those guys
that you wouldn't tend to
ever talk to in practice, like,
I don't know Mige or Mingo,
and you know,
you gotta find a way to, like,
break that barrier.
(whirring)
(indistinct intercom remarks)
(speaking Spanish)
(whirring)
Attendance has been
a lot better.
(indistinct remarks)
That looks really good.
So, you were a tardy in--
on Monday, but that is
really good attendance.
We need to use this
as motivation.
Domingo, you're almost there,
but you're not done.
So, you have a lot of credits
still to do, Domingo.
You have five credits
and your EA project to finish
to graduate.
(indistinct remarks)
Yeah.
(singing in Spanish)
(whirring)
Like, flying it
is multicolored--
Honestly, though, dude,
I really don't like
how they don't do
carbon fiber anymore.
-Yeah, they did carbon on--
-Dude, yeah, they--
Why did they stop doing that?
I don't know.
-What do you think, buddy?
-Sick, dude.
-Not like this?
-No, let's buy him
one of those poufy jackets,
have you seen those?
Dude, like these?
-Yeah, large.
-Extra small, extra small,
extra small, extra small.
-Oh, these are not bad, dude.
-Oh, yeah, those are really--
They only have smalls.
-We could go to Far Post.
-Oh, that's true.
(singing in Spanish)
These are dope.
Oh, yeah, these are all cheap,
yeah, they, like--
-Oh, that one was nice.
-Those ones are really--
-The ones that are not quite--
-I'd cop these for indoor.
So, what about this?
-That's good.
-That's good, dude.
-That's a good color, too.
-Rob, Rob, let's do this one.
-Yeah.
-We'll split it.
-Split it?
-Yeah, we'll split it,
-I'm gonna pay for it.
-I'll pinch in for that, too.
(overlapping remarks)
'Cause his shin guards
are always falling.
-Thank you very much.
-All right, thanks, guys.
-Thank you.
-All right, thanks.
Thank you.
Dude, I kinda want one
of those pink arm bands, though.
-For what?
-For the captains,
that'd be dope.
(dinging)
(birds chirping)
(indistinct remarks)
Okay, guys.
-High school.
-Okay, hey, so,
will you listen up,
will you listen up?
Okay, how's it feel,
how's it feel for tomorrow?
-Good.
-Yeah?
This has been
a challenging season,
but I know at the end, guys,
we're gonna look back,
and it's gonna be one
that we're never gonna forget.
You guys gotta bring it.
Tomorrow night,
it's your night.
-"Eagles" on one, one, Eagles!
-One, Eagles!
Chest, everything
down to the ground.
(indistinct remarks)
Look at that, ooh.
You got middle, you got middle,
you got middle.
(overlapping remarks)
-Yes!
-Yeah, ball to Jack!
(indistinct remarks)
Bro, that's not that way now.
Good shit today.
-Oh, thanks.
-Yeah.
Thanks, boss.
(indistinct remarks)
Have a good one, all right?
(geese squawking)
(clanking)
(cheering)
And here come the Eagles!
Do you guys realize
how excited the crowd gets
when we're passing to each other
and moving like that?
Let's make 'em happy,
guys, come on.
-"Eagles" on one, one, Eagles!
-One, Eagles!
(cheering)
Dalles dominated
four of their last five
to earn their spot
in tonight's final.
Eagles bounced back
after a series of ties
to hold onto first place.
Last year
that's as far as they got.
The Dalles came in
and beat 'em on penalty kicks.
(cheering)
This is Columbia Gorge soccer.
(clapping)
Here we go, Eagles!
Team captain Erik Siekkinen
chasing down,
right through
a Riverhawk defender,
and Jack McAfferty
comes away with it.
-Let's go, Eagles!
-Whole team's keeping
a very aggressive pace early on.
Mingo, stay back.
-What?
-Move the ball!
(overlapping exclamations)
No, no!
The shot blocked, Robbie Running
with the follow-up,
and he's in for a goal!
(whistle blowing)
(cheering)
Robbie Running strikes
first blood for the Eagles
on a beautiful rebound.
Eagles ahead one-nothing
in the division championship.
Way to move the ball away!
(whistle blowing)
Hey, don't let down,
don't let down!
Look outside, look outside!
Loose ball, Riverhawks recover,
a chip off and over
edging towards the Eagles' goal.
The Eagles saves it,
gets a piece of it.
Riverhawks reinforcements
come up the middle
and he's in for a goal!
(groaning)
We're tied: 1-1.
Final seconds
of an intense first half.
Yo, you're all right.
I don't care
if you're a bench player,
if you never get into the game.
Every single person
on this team here is important.
We're a second-half team.
Do not forget that.
-"Eagles" on one, one, Eagles!
-One, Eagles!
Domingo!
Well, that starts
the second half.
(cheering)
-No!
-Ball's stripped.
Riverhawks reverse course
and knock the ball
right back towards
the Eagle goal.
We get it back, we get it back!
(indistinct exclamations)
(whistle blowing)
Stop.
Mingo, Mingo.
Rotate over, Wesley.
Eagles' substitution now,
Domingo Barragan,
number 99,
in for Jack McAfferty.
(indistinct) in the center,
Riverhawks come away with it,
carrying the ball
back into Eagle territory,
sneaking and diving for it,
but can't seem
to get a hold of it.
Keep playing, keep playing!
Domingo Barragan
with fresh legs,
scrambling to chase it down.
It's gotta be quicker!
After a first half
of essentially
canceling each other out,
it all comes down to
who wants it more.
Let's go, that's it,
Eagles, let's go.
Let's win it back, win it back.
Domingo.
Riverhawks back out
to mid center.
Diego Sanchez is there,
gains possession
and brings it over
to Robbie Running.
Get in there,
head this goal!
35 yards out, Barragan fakes
to his right and goes left.
(thudding)
Goal!
(cheering)
Barragan, Barragan!
I don't believe it!
Goal, goal!
From way out, Barragan
gives Hood River the lead!
(indistinct remarks)
Now, can they hang on?
Get it, get it!
Both teams scramble
for control of position.
This way, this way, come on!
-No.
-Riverhawks pushing the ball
down the field.
Diego.
No!
Yes, Diego.
The Eagles anxiously
try to preserve
this one-goal lead
with the clock ticking down.
Final 45 seconds of what's been
a hard-fought battle
from minute one.
(indistinct remarks)
Both teams fighting it out
for each and every ball.
A sense of inevitability
falling over the crowd.
They can sense their Eagles have
done enough for long enough.
And that's it,
they have done it!
The Eagles have
clinched the division
and they're headed
to the state playoffs.
(cheering)
-"Eagles" on one, one, Eagles!
-One, Eagles!
Yeah, good job.
(flashing)
(indistinct remarks)
(rattling)
-You wanna go pay inside?
-Yeah, I do.
(whirring)
Everything's changing, you know.
During the weekend,
I'll work at the gas station
(coughing)
Help my mom paying bills
and all that stuff.
(rustling)
(creaking)
(coughing)
(indistinct remarks)
-Ah!
-If I get a diploma,
I can go to trade school,
a community college.
(thudding)
(whirring)
(typing)
I'm taking a class
before school starts.
(unintelligible)
I'm taking another class
after school.
...to complete your portfolio.
(typing)
I'm working hard to graduate.
(whirring)
(creaking)
(indistinct remarks)
(laughing)
(unintelligible)
Thank you, have a nice night.
(knocking)
-Mingo, what's up, man?
-Dude, what're you doing here?
-Come.
-Thank you.
I brought you some, uh, churros.
-You wanna sit down?
Yeah, sure.
Hey.
(singing in Spanish)
So, uh, I know you're,
you know--
been, uh--with, uh--
with your dad
being deported and everything,
and I know that's super tough,
and I can't--dude,
I can't even imagine.
I'm not gonna try to,
like, even sympathize,
because I don't think I can.
Yeah.
(coughing)
-He's doing okay, though?
-Yeah.
Yeah?
Break out
the churros, man.
I am gonna.
These seem like French fries.
They're like sweet French fries.
-That's true.
-What's that?
Look at this.
Do you imagine yourself
doing that?
No way.
I try singing along with him,
so we'll play some music
in his car, and I'm so bad.
Tom was like, "Oh, my God."
I know I'm not very good at it.
You're way better at English
than I am at Spanish.
-How's your Spanish?
-Bad.
I'm not even gonna--
it's bad, it's bad.
-Try it.
-No, no, no, no, no.
-Cmo es tu espaol?
-I--like, I can understand it,
but I don't know how to,
like, respond very well.
-Mal, muy mal.
-Muy mal.
That's my issue.
I'm in AP Spanish, man,
and it's killing me.
It's killing me.
Let's get a churro.
Thanks, man.
Are you going to college, dude?
-Where?
-I'm trying, uh.
Well, this last week
I was in Colorado.
-Colorado?
-Yeah.
If you could work anywhere,
where would it be?
Um, I have no idea, bro.
-I don't know yet, uh.
-You don't have a dream job?
-Be one of them.
-One of them?
Yeah?
Start--well,
you can start a one-man band.
Um, I don't know yet.
Let me graduate first.
(chuckling)
(whooshing)
(wings flapping)
(whirring)
Before we head out to the field,
I gotta tell you guys
I'm super proud
of each and every
single one of you.
You guys have
rallied around each other,
despite everything
that's been going on,
and I think that tonight,
more than any other night
in your guys' career,
you guys have the chance
to write what you want
this story to look like.
And I wanna tell you guys this
from the heart
that I love
every single one of you.
Whether you believe it or not,
I can't wait
to watch you guys play tonight.
That's something
I've been realizing all season.
I came in trying to, like,
have things a specific way,
and that was
my individual desire, right?
It took a while,
but I finally realized:
It's bigger than me,
it's bigger than Saul.
It's bigger than you,
or you, or you, or any of us.
Doesn't get
any bigger than this.
-Let's get out there, guys.
-Let's go!
Let's give it
everything we got, okay?
This is the final right now,
let's go.
-"Eagles" on one, one, Eagles!
-One, Eagles!
(cheering)
It's been
an unforgettable season
for the home team,
Hood River Valley.
-Whose house?
-Our house!
-"Eagles" on one, one, Eagles!
-One, Eagles!
A victory tonight
prevails the winning team
to the state semi-finals,
whereas a loss signals
the end of a season
as well as
the high-school careers
of their respective seniors.
(whistle blowing)
Saul Chavarria with quick kick
over to Robbie Running.
(cheering)
Takes a long shot,
but it's high.
(exclaiming)
Woodburn now making their way
down the field.
Long left footer,
right in the chest of Rodriguez.
(cheering)
40 minutes in the books
and no score here.
Eagles, Bulldogs.
We've had multiple,
like, just above the goal.
We've had three kicks
from just outside the box.
It's gonna happen,
it's gonna work for us.
We gotta believe it, man.
Eagles have a three on three.
Call it, time!
-Okay!
-Got a ball at midfield.
-About to call it.
-Eagles' Sanchez is there
looking downtown again
with the long pass.
(cheering)
Makes his shot, and oh,
he's gonna be just wide.
Whole team's ratcheting up
for defense
to prevent a last-minute goal.
Woodburn in particular
taking no chances,
as they've done all game.
(indistinct remarks)
Domingo Barragan gains control
with his quick pass
over to Wesley Carter,
who has control momentarily.
15 on the clock.
Diego Sanchez is back in again
for Domingo Barragan.
(indistinct exclamations)
(cheering)
Team captain Erik Siekkinen
with the ball kicks back out,
but it's picked up
by Woodburn number 25.
Lopez with seconds remaining,
30 yards out.
Diving save with Rodriguez.
That's the end of regulation.
The OSAA US
boy's Portland finals
will be decided in penalty case.
Not happening today, guys,
we're not doing that today.
Hell no.
We worked way too fucking hard
to end right here.
Guys, I've had
way too much Goddamn drama
to end right now, okay?
-Let's go.
-We're going all the way, boys.
Let's do it.
-"Eagles" on one, one, Eagles!
-One, Eagles!
Crowd's on their feet.
Home team's ready to go.
Wesley Carter up first
for the Eagles.
The kick is good!
(cheering)
Good job, there you go!
Eagles up 1 nothing.
Now it's Woodburn's chance
to match it.
Kick is good.
It's 1-1 as the Eagles'
team captain Saul Chavarria
gets set.
No margin for error here.
Just one mistake
can cost the game.
But, the kick is good!
Saul Chavarria.
(cheering)
Now it's Woodburn's chance
to match it.
Oh, and the kick is good!
Rodriguez got a hand on it,
but it found its way
into the back of the net.
Woodburn is still in it,
as team captain, number 8,
Erik Siekkinen steps in,
attempting to
recapture the lead.
The crowd going quiet,
the benches going quiet,
waiting to see
the outcome of this.
(indistinct remarks)
Erik Siekkinen looking up
to the sky for inspiration.
And here we go.
(groaning)
Woodburn now
with a chance to win it.
The look on the faces of
the Eagles' bench says it all,
as they're one goal away
from the end of the game
and their run for
the state championship.
-Come on, Alex!
-Let's go, Alex!
(cheering)
Here comes the shot.
And that's it.
Woodburn wins it
in penalty kicks.
(cheering)
Season ends for the Eagles.
High school careers end
for the seniors,
but not before they delivered
on a league championship.
We did everything right,
and sometimes
luck is just not on your side,
and that's how
it's gonna be in life,
but you gotta fight through it.
-I'm sorry I let you guys down.
-No, that's fine.
We win together,
we go down together.
Easy as that.
-"Eagles" on one, one, Eagles!
-One, Eagles!
(birds chirping)
(whirring)
-Thank you, looks delicious.
-You're welcome.
(indistinct remarks)
Okay, guys, so, let's put a--
let's put a closure
to the season here.
I wanted to talk to you guys
about a couple things.
In life, guys,
we have to learn how to lose.
Sometimes we're gonna fail,
and we're not
gonna land that job,
or guess what, I'm not gonna
get accepted to that school,
and I don't think
it's the end of the world.
Okay?
My job as a coach
is not just to win games.
It's to also help
prepare you guys
to be men,
to one day be a father,
to one day be able to look back
on what you guys did,
and be proud of it.
Okay, we'll get through this.
Okay, let's eat.
Well, I don't even
like tomatoes.
(chuckling)
(indistinct remarks)
Hey, Robbie, you and Erik,
can you guys help me
figure out the ball situation?
I don't know how to play golf.
-Tell us, dude.
-No, I'm sorry, you guys.
I don't know
how to play either.
It's just like--
it's kinda like baseball.
-Yeah, there you go.
-Look at that champ.
Ooh!
Zack, you're terrible.
South BK.
Oh, and he gets it,
what a strike!
Eagles!
(chuckling)
Can we get some
Happy Gilmore in here?
All right, okay.
All right,
I really want this right now.
(crickets chirping)
(whooshing)
(whirring)
(humming)
(cheering)
Yeah, buddy!
Erik, Auggie wants
a picture with you.
Okay.
Aw, very cute, guys.
We made it!
I don't know, turn on
the lights and I'll glow
To the extreme,
I rock a mic like a vandal
Light up a stage and wax
a chump like a candle, dance
(indistinct chanting)
(cheering)
By the authority vested in me,
I confirm that all
have completed
all local and state
diploma requirements,
and are now ready
to receive your diplomas.
(cheering)
Saul Chavarria.
(applauding)
Lodi Castillo.
(cheering)
Angel Sonato.
(applauding)
Erik Siekkinen.
(cheering)
Mingo, woo, Domingo!
Domingo Barragan.
(cheering)
(applauding)
We made it, class of 2018!
One, two, three!
(cheering)
(singing in Spanish)
(beeping)
(whirring)
(sloshing)