Downloaded from
YTS.MX
INSPIRED BY THE LIFE
OF NIKODEM SKOTARCZAK.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
PARTLY FICTIONALIZED.
NETFLIX PRESENTS
"IT'S BETTER TO LIVE A YEAR AS A TIGER
THAN TWENTY YEARS AS A TURTLE"
PRESENT DAY
Wait!
Fuck!
I love you.
If it weren't for the fact
I hide cash in three different places,
I couldn't even afford vodka.
My treat.
-My money.
-Fuck.
OUT OF ORDER! DO NOT USE!
Sure.
BUDAPEST
Yeah. Sure.
Thank you.
Change money?
You must have made a mistake.
I should have gotten more.
I'm not stupid, okay?
Fuck.
MARYLKA CLUB
NOVEMBER 3, 1977
I had a deal with Inkblot
on currency and contraband.
Only under those terms
could you have this turf.
But you started selling cars
and beating up the locals.
The police came sniffing around,
and yesterday they took two of my men.
You either knock it off…
Or?
Get the fuck out!
Now!
Did you understand what he said?
Not a word.
POSTNATAL ROOM
Good day. Papers, please.
Any goods with you?
What?
SEASON 1981/82
SEASON 1982/83
Good day.
It's so nice to have a boss.
I'm proud of you.
Nikoś specialized
in the so-called "requested theft."
The idea is that an average German,
an ordinary German like me,
simply gives Nikoś his car.
Nikoś legally transfers the car
to Poland, makes the key duplicates,
and acquires proper papers.
The keys then return to Germany,
the German reports the car stolen
and receives his insurance money.
As well as a cut from Nikoś.
Everyone makes money.
Only the insurer loses.
Your cassette.
Thank you.
-It's a pleasure doing business with you.
-Yeah. Thanks.
Good day.
Can we talk?
Do you remember
our meeting eight years ago?
Hello.
My dad doesn't speak German.
I'll translate.
It's astonishing
that you run a prospering business
without knowing the language.
You mean the incident in Budapest?
Let's forget it. I was there privately.
The institution I represent and I
are interested in what you're doing now.
-How old are you?
-Eight.
Tell your dad that after I lock him up,
you'll be 23 years old
when he gets out of prison.
We know the scope of your operation.
Thank you very much.
I see two options.
Either you cooperate with us
or we'll do everything
to put you behind bars.
Thank you very much.
Wouldn't you want
to see your children grow up?
Thank you very much.
Until we meet again.
FOR DEAR DAD
Good evening.
BORDER CROSSING
POLAND - EAST GERMANY
Anything in the trunk?
Get out.
Hands on the roof of the car.
Nikoś didn't go to jail.
They just fined him.
And took away his passport.
How can you validate your stay in Germany?
By marrying a German.
-Hi, Nikoś.
-Hi.
What's wrong?
What?
I love you!
My gangster.
Aren't you eating too much?
Very good.
It's an honor to welcome you all here…
I do.
CHRISTMAS EVE
GERMAN CONSULATE GENERAL IN GDAŃSK
THREE YEARS LATER
And they kept stealing cars
from rentals through "requested theft."
Dreiersex.
I love you--
-Good day.
-Name!
I spoke to the judge.
Car theft, driving under the influence,
and causing an accident.
That's 18 months to two years.
The prosecution also noticed
your alleged German roots.
At the border,
we seized two other stolen vehicles.
If your boys,
Michał Dolszewski or Paweł Kozłowski,
spill that it was you
who ordered the smuggling,
it will be worse.
I think we could rack up
a double-digit sentence.
Silvio is doing two years in Italy.
Nikoś!
It's over.
Accept my offer.
You might not get another one.
What are you… offering?
Get back.
MAXIMUM SECURITY PRISON
EVIL
ZORBA THE GREEK
That's it. Enough.
That's it.
Enough.
Because of the suicides in your family
and your general condition,
you will spend the remainder
of your sentence in the psychiatric ward.
You'll get better there.
ZORBA THE GREEK
TEGEL PRISON, BERLIN - DECEMBER 4, 1989
PSYCHIATRIC WARD
Fuck.
Good day.
It can't go on like this.
This has to end.
What Nikoś has done
is inexcusable in my country.
My superiors are demanding his head,
and I'm going to bring it to them.
His face behind bars
must be on the front pages
of all the papers
that reported his escape from Tegel.
Any ideas, my colleague?
Commissioner!
KRAKOW
ONE YEAR LATER
MARCH 13, 1992
WARSAW
A FEW MONTHS LATER
Hello?
Yes.
It's for you.
Yes?
Fuck!
Search all the safe houses in Pruszków!
SIERADZ PRISON
FEBRUARY 15, 1994
Polish workmanship…
TRICITY DAILY
PRUSZKÓW CHASED OUT OF GDAŃSK
GDYNIA FILM FESTIVAL
ZGORZELEC WAR
MORE CASUALTIES
THE ŁÓDŹ SAUSAGE KING KIDNAPPED
WACKO ASSASSINATED
APRIL 24, 1998
ZORBA THE GREEK
Fuck!
THIS STORY IS NOT A BIOGRAPHY
OF NIKODEM SKOTARCZAK.
SOME CHARACTERS WERE CREATED FOR THE FILM.