Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[dramatic music]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[keyboard clicking]
[dramatic music]
- [Sammy] "I Love Us."
When I first heard those words,
I thought they were
the corniest three little words
I ever heard in my life.
- You like it?
- I love it.
- [Sammy] I love us,
who says that?
- I know it's not much, but--
- I don't need a ring
to know how you feel.
I don't need anything.
That look in your eyes
says it all.
- Deposit's non-refundable.
- We'll take it.
- If you would have
told me five years ago,
those three little words would
be the most important words
in my life one day,
I would have told you
three other little words.
Shut the fuck up!
Well, technically four.
- What?
I'm just saying, Sammy.
This fucking guy should've
been closed an hour ago.
We're sitting here
like a bunch of yutzes
waiting for these fucking
love birds to split.
Gotta piss so bad
I can taste it.
- Are you finished?
- I'm just saying, we could've
been in and out already.
- Waiting is part
of the business, Richie.
- Yeah, waiting.
Waiting, I mean, one minute
we're cocked and loaded
and the next minute
we're watching
some fucking asshole
overcompensating
with his sidepiece
for an hour?
- One minute can
change everything.
Just so we're clear,
this mook is not my partner.
We're not even friends.
He's an associate.
An over-glorified co-worker.
Okay, here he goes.
Bring the car around.
All right, five minutes.
Right out front
and five minutes.
- I heard you, five minutes.
[dramatic music]
[car door clunking]
- [Sammy] I don't like blood
and for a job like this,
there's no need for any.
[car engine roaring]
[dramatic music]
So I bring this box.
[glass door clunking]
[dramatic music]
- We're closed!
Leave it at the door!
- [Sammy] Nobody pisses their
pants at the sight of a box.
Everybody loves boxes.
It reminds them of their
birthdays or Christmas.
Everybody loves Christmas.
- You're lucky I'm still here.
- [Sammy] A gun, though,
has a very different
and specific effect on people.
Nobody likes guns, especially
when they're pointed
at their fat belly.
[dramatic music]
The difference between
a good thief and a hack
is simple--greed.
You get greedy, you get sloppy.
[dramatic music]
[zip whooshing]
We could've cleaned this guy out
and kept the change,
but the job is the safe,
so that's all we're taking.
[dramatic music]
[zip whooshes]
And what's the difference
between a good thief
and a great one?
The getaway.
[dramatic music]
[tires screeching]
[suspenseful dramatic music]
[sirens wailing]
[wailing continues,
brakes squeal]
[bell chimes]
[bus engine roaring]
I wasn't kidding when
I said that one minute
could change everything,
but I was wrong.
It only took a second.
Hey.
- Hey.
- She could have trademarked
that smile.
Wanna get off?
- No, uh...
I'm not that type of girl,
sorry.
- No, no, not get off.
You wanna get off the bus?
Maybe we can get some dinner?
- Can't.
Girl's gotta work.
- Work, now?
- Yeah.
You?
- I just got off work.
- Lucky you.
- Lucky was an understatement.
Where do you work?
- Vincent's.
- Vincent's?
Waitress?
- Yeah.
[bus engine roaring]
- What time are you
getting off?
- [laughs] 10.
- 10?
Maybe I'll come after dinner.
I love Vincent's.
I hate Vincent's.
An Italian restaurant with
nothing but non Italians.
They can cook some
pretty incredible shit,
but nobody messes up a plate
of pasta like Vincent's.
- Hi. What can I get you?
Ooh, the caprese.
Great choice.
Fettuccine, no problem.
And for you?
- The food might be
a nightmare,
but the service is
an absolute dream.
Hey!
- [whispers] I said 10.
- [whispers] 10?
Okay.
[smooth jazz music]
- Hi.
So tell me, what is it
that you do, Sammy?
- Me?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm a thief.
I'm a diamond dealer.
- Ooh.
Girl's best friend.
- That's right.
- [chuckles]
- Well, looks like you enjoy
the finer things in life.
- That's also right.
- But why did you
take the bus?
Too many DUIs?
- No, no, no, no, nothing
serious like that, no.
Having to lie to her
tore me apart even then.
Car's in the shop,
engine trouble.
- Really?
- [Sammy] Yeah.
- Me too, suspension.
- Look at that.
- You know what
they call that?
- [Sammy] What?
- Serendipity.
Well, here's to serendipity.
- Cheers.
- Cheers, Laura.
Fenton, right?
- That's right. [laughs]
Whoo, what a day.
- Need some money?
- Yeah, I mean, a little bit.
- Okay, well,
you look good doing it.
"I Love Us."
[upbeat music]
I didn't know it then,
but that was the beginning
of my life.
♪ Speak of yourself ♪
♪ All over me, will you,
please? ♪
♪ Keep doing your thing ♪
♪ It's fascinating to me ♪
♪ Lost in your eyes ♪
♪ You are the spark
to my flame ♪
♪ In this moment like now ♪
♪ We are like one
and the same ♪
In the next few months,
I showed her
where to get real Italian food.
[upbeat music]
- [Laura] Thank you.
- And she showed me how to
stop looking over my shoulder.
♪ I know where ♪
- But just like anything else
worthwhile in this world,
a new life wasn't
gonna come easy.
[upbeat music]
[Laura laughs]
- Ticklish.
- I love it.
♪ You know me ♪
♪ It won't be long ♪
♪ On the dance floor ♪
- You okay?
- [sighs]
Um...
- You remember I told
you about my husband?
- Yeah.
Pancreatic cancer,
what a shitshow.
She said he didn't go
without a fight,
and they fought it right
through the end.
That was nine years ago,
but I could tell
she was still fighting.
- There's something
that I haven't told you.
[dramatic music]
- You don't have to do that,
Laura.
- No. Here.
[dramatic music]
If you wanna see how this goes,
it's in those photos.
[dramatic music]
Listen, I...
This has been great.
I've had an amazing time,
I don't remember the last time
I've laughed so much,
but I'm not interested
in wasting anyone's time
and...if this is, um...
if this is a problem for you...
[inhales and exhales deeply]
um, I understand.
[dramatic music]
- No.
They're beautiful.
I wanna see where this goes.
Really do.
[dramatic music]
I love you.
You're so beautiful.
- Thank you.
- [Sammy] Who is this one?
- This is Rachel.
- She looks like you.
- [Laura] And that's Audrey.
[dramatic music]
- I'm here.
For the long run.
- Thank you.
- [Sammy] Love makes you
say some stupid shit, right?
But at least
I wasn't lying to her.
- [Sammy] Thank you.
- So, are you Italian?
- No, everyone asks me that.
I'm actually Israeli.
- Sammy, he's actually
from Brooklyn.
- New York?
- Yeah, have you guys ever been?
- No.
- Dad always wanted to go
to New York.
- Yes, yes, he did.
- You're a lot shorter
than dad.
- Rachel!
- [Rachel] What?
- No, no, no,
it's totally fine.
Yeah, uh, I'm a lot shorter
than a lot of people.
- Go set the dinner table,
please.
Now!
[Rachel sighs]
I'm so sorry.
- No, Laura, it's fine, no.
I'm sure it's not easy
on them.
- You're sweet.
I'm gonna go check on dinner.
Rachel!
- This is delicious.
Really is.
- Well, I'm so glad
you like it.
- Like it? I love it.
- It's just meatloaf.
- This meatloaf,
it's a masterpiece.
- Mom's meatloaf is lit.
- Meatloaf can't be lit.
- Yes, it can.
- No it can't.
That doesn't make sense.
- It means it's really good.
- I know what it means.
- There's no competition.
It's the best meatloaf
I've ever had in my life.
- The best.
- Mm.
- And so are you.
- Well, wait till you taste
dessert. We made cupcakes.
- That's exactly what you need,
Audrey, more cupcakes.
- [Audrey] Shut up.
- [Laura] Girls.
- Make sure not to get
too many crumbs on mom
while you're kissing her ass.
- Rachel!
I'm sorry.
- No, no, no, that's fine.
It's fine.
Cheers, guys.
Thank you for having me.
- Thank you.
Cheers.
- Nice meeting you, Audrey.
- You, too.
- You're really brave,
you know that?
[insects chirping]
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- I guess.
- I'm serious.
It can't be easy for you either.
[insects chirping]
- I mean, I must seem
like an intruder
to these girls, right?
- Well...
they'll be fine.
It's just gonna take some time.
[insects chirping]
- I thought they were gonna
fall in love with me
in first sight,
just like you did.
[Audrey and Rachel laughing]
- You know, on the bus,
when I first saw you,
I kind of thought
you were a creep.
- A creep?
- [laughs]
- Really?
- I did.
You're lucky I didn't
have my other purse
with my pepper spray and taser.
- Ooh, pepper spray.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you're right, I am.
- You are what?
- Lucky.
- Yeah, you are.
[laughs]
I love them so much.
[Rachel and Audrey laughing]
- And I love you.
- [Sammy] I could've married
her right then and there.
[upbeat music]
But I married her a year later.
Her mother, who we barely
got up the stairs,
even her junkie brother
was there.
Nice guy, but a hot mess.
In front of her girls.
[upbeat music]
All these people showed up
to see us.
- [Laura] I love us.
- And all I can think about
is that one person who didn't.
[upbeat music]
[knock on door]
Hey, Pops, what are you doing?
- That's for the job
and here...
from me.
Wedding gift.
You know, showing up
to the wedding
would have been a good gift,
you know that, right, Pop?
- Uh, don't be so sure.
You haven't seen
what's inside the envelope.
[chuckles] Thank you, Pop.
I appreciate it.
- So...
You're married, huh?
- Look at this.
- I don't know what
your mother would've felt
about you marrying a goya,
but I'm sure the food was good.
The food was great.
Mom would've loved her.
- Maybe. I mean, you know
your mother better than I did.
- You gonna love her too, Pops.
She's awesome. She really is.
- How are the kids?
Ooh. Kids, tough.
Big one, Rachel,
hates my guts.
It's like I killed
her dad myself.
The little one,
Audrey, is really sweet,
but, you know,
it's just tough.
New guy coming in.
At that age, it's not easy.
- Do you want some advice?
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Don't be their friend.
They got friends.
- What part of "I don't want any
advice" don't you understand?
- They don't need a friend.
They need a father.
- Yeah, I guess.
- Here.
This is a good lead.
Take a lock.
Stake it out,
take Richie with you.
- No, no, no, no,
I don't like Richie.
- What's with you and liking
all of a sudden, huh?
You don't have to like him,
all right?
You don't have to go camping
with the guy.
You sit in the back seat,
I told you.
- I do. He doesn't stop
asking questions.
- Well then,
stop answering them then, huh?
- It's very easy to say.
The guy is unbelievable.
- Look, I told you that I'm
gonna look out for you, right?
You bang out a few more jobs,
you'll be square with Ira
before you know it.
- I know, Pops. I appreciate it.
I really do.
It's just,
I can't lie to Laura anymore.
- Lying?
You tell her you work here,
right?
- Yeah, I tell her I work here,
but...
- Well, then... [laughs]
get to work.
- I can't lie to her.
I can't lie to those girls.
I mean, it's...
It's my life now, you know?
- Sammy, I know that
we throw the word job
around here a lot, okay?
But this isn't what you do.
It's who you are.
You want some more advice?
- No, please.
- Just tell her.
You want that life?
You got to come clean.
You build it on a foundation
of bullshit,
that life will come tumbling
down one day,
right on top of your head,
and you won't be able to
do a damn thing about it
except try to take the hit.
- I guess, I don't know.
[Sammy sighing]
I don't know, Pops.
Growing up,
I didn't need a friend either,
but as far as fathers go,
mine definitely made
a better boss.
The name he just dropped,
is why my posture is
so fucked up these days.
[techno music]
Ira Prince.
Great guy,
but Ira always had one hand
in someone's pocket
and another wrapped gently
around their throats
and his grip never felt tighter.
I was a gambler.
Yes!
A good one.
Yes! Yes!
Which means I was also
a bad one.
When I would hit, I would live
it up like a goddamn king.
[upbeat music]
[ladies giggling]
But when I got hit, you've
never seen a sorer loser.
I hate this... [indistinct].
One day I got hit really bad
and I not only lost my money,
I lost my friends' money
and I lost Ira's money.
Ira and my dad go way back,
so as a favor to him,
he took it easy on me.
He agreed to let me pay
him back in installments.
They say that if you do
something for 10,000 hours,
you become a professional,
right?
Well, I became
a fucking professional.
[upbeat music]
[car door clunking]
What do we got?
- Now, why do you have
to seat in the back seat
like I'm your fucking chauffeur?
- Technically, that's what
you are now.
- Technically an asshole
is what you are.
What do we have Richie?
What's going on over here?
Explain to me, please.
I never liked pawn shops.
There's always one idiot
that wants to play the hero.
- That chubby over there,
he comes out for a smoke break
about every 15 minutes.
He's got a partner inside.
That guy comes out at the end
of the day though, all right?
- If I want to put this life
behind me,
I gotta stop thinking small time
and start thinking big time.
- [cellphone buzzes]
- Hey, sweetie.
- [Laura] Um, did you forget
that we have dinner tonight?
- Oh, shit. No, no, no,
uh, I didn't forget.
[Laura] You know that I said
dinner at seven
with the girls, right?
- [Sammy] Laura, I promise.
- [Laura] Okay, I love you.
- I love you too, sweetie.
- [Laura] I'll see you soon.
- Okay.
- I'll be there in a little bit.
- [Laura] Okay, bye.
- Okay, bye. Yo, I gotta go.
Listen, you're doing
a great job.
Keep an eye on them,
and I'll see you tomorrow.
- I thought I was just a driver.
- You are just a driver, Richie.
[car door clunking]
[insects chirping]
This was it.
Time to decide if I play
the friend card or the dad card.
As long as I didn't play
the vomit card.
[insects chirping]
- We're, like, really mean
to him and that's why--
- Dude, how old are you?
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How was your day?
- Good.
- Hi, girls.
- Hi.
- What's with the teddy bear?
- We're having a Teddy talk.
- Shit, I was playing with
the wrong fucking deck.
A Teddy talk?
- Yeah, Teddy.
He helps us get things
off our chests in a safe
and controlled manner.
Also helps us, you know,
with big family announcements.
- Are we gonna go
to Disneyland?
- Audrey, shut up.
- No, we're not going
to Disneyland.
Um...
[sighs]
Listen, um...
I know the last few years, uh,
have been tough.
Well, I've been thinking,
and I've--
- What your mom is trying
to say is--
- Shh!
- This is so dumb.
- You're not allowed to
talk unless you have Teddy.
I'm so sorry. That will
never happen again, please.
- That way everyone is heard,
right?
Without being interrupted.
Anyways, um, Sammy and I,
we have been talking and...
He's my husband now, so--
- Why are you being so weird?
- I'm not being weird.
- [Rachel] You're being
really weird.
- No.
I'm not. I'm... What I'm trying
to say is Sammy and I,
we've been talking,
and, well, I...
he's a part of our family now,
and he's an important part,
and we want... we wanna know
what you feel about him, um,
becoming your father.
[dramatic music]
- Is this a joke?
- No, it's not a joke,
actually, Rach.
- Mom, tell me you're joking.
I wasn't either. I'm not.
[gentle guitar music]
- This is bullshit.
- Sorry. Rachel, Rachel!
[gentle guitar music]
[door slams]
- Shit.
- [giggles]
[gentle guitar music]
You okay?
- I don't know.
Maybe we should've waited
until we moved in together.
You know?
Ease them into it?
- Yeah.
I mean, she misses her dad.
They both do. I get it.
I'm not him.
The application still need
to come in, so...
we'll see what happens.
Well, I made it through that
long ones.
What?
- Yeah, you are.
[giggles]
- Times didn't always suck.
[family cheering]
Sometimes they started to
look up.
- Ah, thank you.
- Well, I'll take it.
- And we started to feel like
a family.
[dramatic music]
[car door clunks]
I loved surprising her.
And nothing felt better than
to see her get a new car.
- One more step.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Step.
- Okay, okay.
- One more.
- Are you ready?
- I think so.
[dramatic music]
Oh, my gosh!
Oh my gosh!
- You like it?
- Sammy, mm! Oh, my gosh,
it's beautiful.
- It's yours.
- Girls, girls, come here!
Oh, my gosh!
- [Sammy] She was so happy.
- Girls, girls, come here!
- Are you serious?
- Oh, my God, Mom!
- And we finally felt like
a family.
You like it?
- Yes!
- Go, go. Go get your shoes on,
go get your shoes on.
- All right, get in, get in.
- Oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh.
- [Sammy] You like it?
- It's beautiful, so beautiful!
- [Sammy] Get in.
- [Audrey] Thank you.
- [Laura] Okay, ladies.
- [Rachel] Where are we going?
- Where to?
- [Sammy] Malibu!
- Ahh!
[car engine roaring]
What a view,
and I don't mean the landscape.
- This is the most amazing car
that I've ever been in.
[upbeat music]
- When are you guys
gonna get your license?
She looked so beautiful
in that car.
Would you let them
drive your car?
[Laura gasps]
- No.
- Wait, why not?
[upbeat music]
- [Sammy] Good night, Audrey.
- Good night, Sammy.
- Sweet dreams, honey.
- He really cares about you,
though.
[knock on door]
- [Sammy] Good night, Rachel.
- [Laura] He's trying to.
- [Rachel] Good night, Mom.
- Good night, sweetheart.
She said to say good night.
- No, she didn't.
- She did.
- [laughs] Okay, no, she didn't,
but maybe you, um,
maybe you wanna tuck me in.
- Mmh, I'll tuck you in.
- Mm-hmm.
- All day, every day.
- [laughs]
[dramatic music]
[car door clicking]
[suspenseful dramatic music]
[car door clunking]
[dramatic music]
- Here.
No mustard.
- Thanks.
Richie, you sure there's
only two guys in there?
- Yeah.
- [Sammy] The fat guy looks
like trouble.
You think you can handle him?
- What's there to handle?
I put my gun in his mouth and
tell the fat fuck what's what.
He's gonna understand.
- What are you gonna do if
he tries something stupid?
- Well, then I try something
stupid first.
- Listen, I don't want any
shooting on this this, okay?
Serious.
If he gets out of line,
if he says something stupid,
you talk loud and you hit him
with a fucking gun
over the head.
I heard about what happened
in Atlanta.
I should've had my head
examined sitting in a car
with this guy,
let alone do a job with him.
- [Richie] What'd you hear?
- Enough to know I don't want
any fucking shooting this week.
- It was an accident.
- That's even fucking worse. I'm
actually doing it on purpose.
- You know what? Fuck you,
Sammy, 'cause you weren't there.
- A bad feeling before a job
is never good,
but a full blown sign
from God himself--
- [Richie]
What the fuck you doing?
- That's something else
entirely.
[whispers] Oh, fuck.
Holy shit,
go, go, go, go, go, go!
- What? Why?
- Start the car! Go, go!
Oh, my God.
- And what about your car?
- Go, go, go, go, go.
I'll pick it up later.
- All right, give me a second.
- Go, go.
[car revving]
[dramatic music]
I don't care what the fuck he
said. To me it doesn't matter.
- What's the problem?
- Job's off. I'm not doing it.
- Why not?
- It doesn't feel right.
Something in my gut tells me
not to do this one, Pops.
- Richie, put the napkin down,
please.
- Oh.
- And what does your gut
tell you?
- My gut?
Looks like a piece of cake
to me.
What do I know, right?
- Sammy, do the job.
- I'm not doing the job, Pops,
seriously.
Gotta get me something bigger.
- Bigger?
- Yeah, big enough.
- Ah. Big enough for what?
- Big enough so I don't have
to do this shit anymore,
penny dime shit.
I can't do this. I can't...
I can't lie to Laura anymore.
- So tell her the truth.
- I can't do that.
- Sammy, you're trying
to be a better man, okay?
She can't hate you for that.
- Hold on. Hello?
[Dr. Bule] Sammy Silver,
this is Dr. Bule
from the Medical Center.
There's been an accident.
- And just like that, the world
dropped away from me.
[dramatic music]
[car engine starts]
They said the driver was drunk.
She didn't see it coming.
[dramatic music]
For the first time in my life,
I had nothing to say.
[dramatic music]
These girls were
the only thing I had left.
They reminded me of her.
[guitar music]
♪ There's a secret
we don't know ♪
♪ Fireflies ♪
♪ Virgin snow ♪
♪ How the wind knows when
to blow ♪
♪ Know the lights ♪
♪ Coming home ♪
♪ We're all getting older ♪
♪ Rivers carving borders ♪
♪ We can't turn
this thing around ♪
♪ Take me to your leader ♪
- Aah!
- ♪ I do love to meet her ♪
♪ Maybe slow
this whole thing down ♪
♪ Signs, if you read
between the lines ♪
♪ Hold them close inside,
they're everywhere you go ♪
♪ Oh, everywhere you go ♪
♪ Signs, you can see them
or be blind ♪
♪ They are yours to find,
all where we ever know ♪
♪ Call me where we ever know ♪
[Sammy sobbing]
[guitar music]
♪ How the seabird
knows the way ♪
♪ Baby cry ♪
♪ Saturday ♪
♪ We're all getting older ♪
♪ Rivers carving borders ♪
♪ We can't turn
this thing around ♪
♪ Take me to your leader ♪
♪ Thought you'd love
to meet her ♪
♪ Maybe slow
this whole thing down ♪
♪ Signs, if you read
between the lines ♪
♪ Hold them close inside,
they're everywhere you go ♪
♪ They're everywhere you go ♪
♪ Signs, you can see that
I'm only right ♪
I'm trying.
I'm trying to take care of...
I don't know.
♪ Will we ever know? Tell me,
will we, will we ever know? ♪
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
[guitar music]
[sighs]
- Sammy?
Sammy.
- Good morning.
- Hi.
Breakfast?
- Mm-hmm.
- All right, sit down,
I'm coming.
- Okay.
[sighing]
How'd you sleep?
- [Audrey] It was okay.
- Eggs?
- Sure.
- Where's your sister?
- She's still asleep.
- Scrambled okay?
- Sure.
Thank you.
- Breakfast?
- Sure.
So, I took the day off
from work.
We can do anything
you guys want.
[cellphone buzzing]
- [Audrey]
Can we go to Disneyland?
- Okay, we got one
for Disneyland.
What are you thinking?
- How about the beach?
- Beach?
- Yeah, mom loved the beach.
- She did?
- Yeah.
- Audrey, can we take
a rain check on Disneyland?
- Can I make the sandwiches?
- Yeah.
Please make the sandwiches.
- Okay.
[buzzing continues]
- All right, you guys...
you guys eat up and, um...
[buzzing stops]
Eat up, and I'm gonna shower.
I'll just wash up.
I went to bed so late.
All right, enjoy it.
- [Audrey] You like my bear?
- [Rachel] It's cute.
- I told her that I hated
the beach.
Couldn't stand the heat,
but I can see why she loved it.
[ocean waves crushing]
[sea gulls cawing]
How was it?
- [Rachel] It's good,
it was cold.
- [Audrey] Today, the water's
really cold.
- It is?
- Yeah.
- You guys hungry?
- [Rachel] Yeah.
- Why don't you guys eat
something?
- [Audrey] Thank you.
- Thanks for making these.
- [Audrey] Yeah, of course.
- They're really good.
I just had them.
- [Audrey] Yeah?
- [Rachel] Mom always said
you made the best sandwiches.
- Ah, we should head back
in a little bit, right?
[birds chirping]
[car engine roaring]
Guys, get in the house.
- [Rachel] Who is that?
- It's just a work thing.
Get in the house.
Go straight to your room.
Go ahead.
[dramatic music]
- Boss wants to see you.
- You know how long
I've been waiting here?
A long fucking time,
that's how long.
[car door closes]
- I'm sorry.
- Just, uh, busting your balls,
kid.
I'm sorry for your loss.
I really am.
If anything you need, I, uh...
- I'm okay, thank you.
[dramatic music]
Cried yet?
- Cry?
- You should find a spot.
Just let it all out.
Maybe in your car,
maybe in....
in the shower.
Showers are great for crying.
[inhales sharply]
Um...I asked, uh, Harvey, uh,
for an update, and he told me
that he couldn't reach you.
- Sorry about that. It's...
I took the girls
to the beach to get some food,
get some fresh air,
so I didn't pick up my phone.
- Uh...
listen...
You take some time,
get your head straight,
do what you need to do
and when you're ready,
you'll get...
Back to work.
[dramatic music]
- Thank you.
- And, uh...
[dramatic music]
- No, no, I can't.
I can't take that.
- Oh, come on. Come on.
Get those kids
some pizza or something.
- Okay.
Gangsters are a funny breed.
Some of the nicest guys
you'll ever meet.
You almost forget that
they're stone cold killers.
- And, uh, Sammy...
you stay reachable.
- Yes, sir.
Almost.
[car door clunking]
- Go.
- Shut up! This is my bear.
- So what if I cry?
- Shut up!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What's going on?!
- She killed Teddy!
- What?
- It's a fucking toy, Audrey!
Grow up!
- Give it to me.
Give me the teddy bear.
What happened?
- She's acting like
a fucking little kid!
Why are you taking her side?!
- Watch your mouth!
You're acting like it's your--
Are you serious right now?!
What are you doing?!
- I'm the one holding
the fucking bear!
Both of you shut the fuck up!
- Watch your language.
You're scaring your sister.
Give me the teddy bear.
- She's my sister,
not your daughter,
and you're not my father!
You'll never be my father!
Did you really think
one picnic and one ice cream
was gonna fucking
fix everything?!
[dramatic music]
- Give me the teddy bear, Rach.
- You're the reason
my mom's dead.
- Rachel!
[dramatic music]
[door slams]
- Can you fix him?
[slow piano music]
- It's okay.
It's so crazy when someone's
gone, just like that,
right off the face of
the earth,
and all that's left are a bunch
of pictures in your phone
and some shaky video footage.
[slow piano music]
[laughter]
God, I missed her.
[slow piano music]
[doorbell chimes]
The doorbell ringing this
early is either a delivery,
Jehovah's Witness,
or bad news.
[doorbell chimes]
Yeah, I'm coming!
This looked like bad news.
- Mr. Silverman?
- Yeah.
- Maria Campos,
Child Protective Services.
Oh, that's my guy out there,
just in case.
- In case of what?
- Just in case.
- This is a joke, right?
- This is not a joke,
Mr. Silverman.
- The girls need
to come with us.
I'll give you a minute to
get their things together
and say your goodbyes.
- No, no, no,
it's not happening.
Those are my girls in there.
- Actually, they're not.
Until your case is finalized,
the girls need to stay
with family.
This is happening.
We'll schedule the evaluations
as soon as possible
and get all of the paperwork
in order.
Look, the best case scenario,
this is temporary.
- And the worst case scenario?
- Let's just see what happens.
- What happens?
This woman coming into my house
talking about family, family.
I'm their family.
What other family do they have?
I mean, where are
they gonna stay?
Their grandmother lives
in a home.
- I am not at liberty to say.
- There was only one
other family member
I can think of at that moment.
I mean, I was still a bit drunk,
but right in that moment,
I had an idea.
What if they--
What if they lived with family?
- That's what I just said.
[laughs]
- No, no. What if they lived
with family here in the house,
with me?
[dramatic music]
- Um... Well, I mean, I guess
technically that--
- Technically is good then.
Technically is good.
I gotta make a phone call.
Would you come in for a minute?
- [Maria] Uh, okay.
- Can he stay out here?
- [Maria] Sure.
- Okay, please, come.
Five minutes.
I just gotta call somebody.
Is there anything I can get you?
- No, please don't worry
about me. I'm good, thank you.
- You sure? Okay, thank you.
- Yes.
-[doorbell rings]
There he is.
- Hey.
- There's a huge guy on your--
- I know, I know. Come inside.
I gotta introduce you
to someone.
- Is this grass real?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Come on.
Come, come, come.
Ah, Maria, this is Rob Fenton.
This is Maria Campos
from, uh, CPS.
I was telling you on the phone.
- Hi, Mr. Fenton.
- Would you like something
to drink? Uh...
Want some orange juice?
I'll get you some orange juice.
- Oh, God,
it looks different here.
- Freshly squeezed.
[juice pouring]
There you go.
Rob, listen, Missus, uh, Miss--
- Miss.
- Miss Campos is here.
She's helping me
with the adoption papers.
The only way the girls can
actually live here with me
is if there's a family member
living here.
- [Maria] That's correct.
- Correct?
- Yes.
- I mean, everyone's been
through so much,
especially the girls.
- Wow, that's really good juice.
- You like that orange juice?
You can have as much
orange juice as you want.
- But I already have a place.
- Yeah, but this is
just a couple of weeks.
- Yeah, maybe more,
and if the papers go through,
you know, it's a process.
- If the paperwork goes through.
Well, I'm sure
it's gonna go through, right?
- We'll see. We just
take it one day at a time.
- So it's temporary?
- It's definitely temporary.
[door knob clicking]
- [Audrey] Uncle Rob?
- [Rob] Hey, look at you.
How you doing?
Oh, my God!
- [Audrey]
What are you doing here?
- I invited your uncle
for breakfast.
- Yeah, I'm having orange juice.
- Teddy's dead.
- [Maria] What?
- Who's Teddy?
- It's just...
- It's nothing,
it's a teddy bear.
- Ah, honey,
can you do me a favor?
Can you give please give us
a minute?
- We'll hang out, okay?
See you.
[whispers] She's so big.
- Uh, so we're good?
- Yeah, we're good.
- Well, I just have to
update your paperwork,
but we should be good,
and I'll have to run a quick
background check on Mr. Fenton.
- Background check?
- Yes.
We'll keep in touch,
Mr. Silverman.
- [Sammy] Uh, Silver.
- Right.
- Okay, thank you.
So, you'll call me?
- I will.
- Okay, great.
I worked very hard to stay clean
on paper.
You look me up anywhere and
I'm basically squeaky clean,
but this guy...
You're clean?
- Yeah. I got allergies.
- Allergies?
- That's why I'm sniffing.
- Okay, good.
- Yeah.
- Rachel! Your uncle's here!
- Rachel's here?
- Yeah, sit,
I'll tell you everything.
- Uncle Rob.
- [laughs]
- What are you doing here?
- [Rob] I'm hanging.
- [both] Brr! [laughing]
You'll get it next time.
- What are you doing here?
- Hanging out, yeah.
- [Sammy] Your uncle's gonna
live with us.
- Really?
- For a little bit, yeah.
- Oh, that's awesome.
I'm gonna go brush my teeth.
- Okay.
I wasn't gonna say anything.
- [Sammy] All right.
- [Rachel] Shut up.
- It's crazy how much
she looks like her.
- It's crazy. Hey...
I really appreciate
you doing this.
It means a lot.
- I'd do anything for them.
- I know.
I'll get you set up.
If you need anything,
just let me know.
- [Rob] Okay.
- All right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you. Appreciate it.
All I knew about Rob is
that he loved his sister,
and she loved him.
Now I gotta go hide
all my valuables.
- You guys got any coffee?
What? No?
- Yeah, black okay?
- Please.
[coffee pouring]
You guys don't eat ever?
[mug clunks]
[dramatic music]
God, Rachel.
It's crazy how much
you look like her.
Sammy, right?
[dramatic music]
- Yeah, you really do.
- I'm not her.
- I know, I didn't...
I didn't mean it like that.
- I know what you meant.
Audrey looks like Dad.
It's hard to forget someone
when you see them every day.
- Well, you're not supposed
to forget.
You're supposed to remember.
- Yeah, well, remembering sucks.
[dramatic music]
- I'm gonna make some coffee.
You guys want some, Rachel?
- No, I'm good.
- All right, movie marathon
tonight, yeah?
We stay up late,
popcorn, burping, farting.
She's been farting all night,
so--
- No, that was Teddy's corpse.
- Teddy's?
- It's his ghost, yeah.
- Excuses.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's a school night
- School?
Don't you guys get, like,
time to grieve and stuff?
- No.
- [Sammy] They missed
enough school already.
- It's one more day, Sammy.
What's the difference?
- Can we, please?
- What a nightmare.
I was trying to move a few steps
forward with these kids,
and he was knocking me
10 steps back
every time he opened his mouth.
You guys can do marathon night
on the weekend.
- How about that?
- This weekend?
It's like Tuesday.
- Whatever.
- But I had an Ace up my sleeve.
This should definitely work.
I really gotta stop drinking.
All right, here we are.
- You guys all set?
- Yeah.
All right, I'll pick
you guys up later,
and we'll go have dinner
wherever you want.
- Okay.
- Bye, Sammy.
- Bye, Audrey.
- You know, next time
you take us to school,
how about you drop us off
on time?
- [Sammy] Sorry.
- It's okay.
[cellphone buzzing]
- Yo.
- I've been calling you
for two days,
and this is how you answer, eh?
- I'm sorry. I'm just
so busy with these girls.
- No, no, I understand
that, son, all right?
But this is important,
all right?
We need to talk.
- About what?
- Something big, Sammy.
- Okay.
All right, give me like
30 minutes.
[sighs]
- [Harvey] Hey.
- Hey.
How you doing?
You got me rushing over here.
- You know how you make
the perfect cup of tea?
- [Sammy] What?
- Timing.
Go ahead and open it.
- What is it?
- [Harvey] You'll see.
Omar Al Said.
- I don't know who that is.
- You're not supposed to know
who he is.
What you need to know
is what he has
hanging on his walls.
That piece sold to
an anonymous buyer last year
for a little over $50 mil,
all right?
The art world is crawling
with rich lunatics,
and I got one ready
to take that off our hands
once it is in our hands.
- $50 million.
What's our take?
- I haven't figured it all out
yet, but it's gonna be big.
- I'm sure a guy like that has
a lot of security with him.
- Mm. Well, stake it out,
all right?
See what your balls say.
There's always a way
around them, you know?
Always is.
- I hated to admit it,
but the old man was right.
This could be the job
to end all jobs.
The take could be $5 million
easy,
but bigger paydays
come with bigger risks.
- Oh, it's terrible.
- Yeah, of course.
You waited too long, huh?
You now, your mother got me
into tea.
I was a pure coffee guy
when we met.
Black, no fucking around.
Yeah, she changed me
in many ways,
and some things
she couldn't change.
- Pop, let me ask you,
how did you ever tell her
about the business?
- I didn't. She found out.
- Wait, I thought you told her.
That's why she left.
- No, she found out.
She was more hurt
that I didn't tell her
what I was doing than
she was about what I was doing.
You know, Sammy, once trust
goes out the door,
everything else follows.
- You never thought about
walking away?
- Oh, no.
This is all I know.
I never wanted you
to be part of this life,
but I didn't want to
hide it from you either,
and now this is all you know.
But you know you have
a choice to make now, son.
- I think I know.
This looks great, Dad.
- This, we pull off...
you don't have to worry.
We take care of those kids,
take care of Ira,
have the life you want.
- That's exactly what
I've been looking for.
I appreciate it, Pop. You always
look out for me, you really do.
Love you, Pop. Bye.
I'll take a look at this,
and I'll call you.
[dramatic music]
[car engine roaring]
A gate is usually a good sign.
It means big house
with big money,
but it also means big trouble.
Getting on the other side
of that gate,
it's gonna be
a fucking nightmare.
[dramatic music]
Hello?
- [Principal] Mr. Silverman.
- What?
- [Principal] I need you to
come to the school right now.
- Okay, I'm coming.
[dramatic music]
[car engine roaring]
- Follow me.
[dramatic music]
- What exactly did she do?
- She vandalized
school property.
She broke into
the gym's equipment locker
and then punctured every single
one of the school's basketballs
with this.
Is this from your home,
Mr. Silverman?
- Yeah, that's mine.
- Normally, I would push
for immediate suspension
or even expulsion,
but considering
the recent tragic circumstances
and the fact that, Rachel,
you've always been
a fine student,
I'm gonna show
some leniency here.
- Thank you.
- You'll be getting
a bill for all the damages.
It'll do some good for Rachel
to stay home
for a couple more days,
and her sister, too.
- What does Audrey
have to do with this?
- They're hurting.
They need to stay home.
They need to take this all in.
- I know she knows better
than this,
but, um, just send me the bill,
and I'll take care of it,
and I really appreciate it.
- Can we please go home now?
- Yeah.
Thank you. I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
Rach, why the basketballs?
- Yeah, why did you do that?
I thought you loved basketball.
- She does?
- Yeah.
- You do?
- Not anymore.
- You know how much trouble
you're in?
You know how much money
this is gonna cost me?
Do you have any idea how much
money it's gonna cost me?
- I honestly don't care.
[door slams]
- Straight to your room.
[ice cube clunking]
Rob!
The thing about ex junkies
is a nine out of 10,
their old habits never die.
Rob?
It's just a matter of
opportunity and a matter of time
before history
starts repeating itself.
Hey, put your feet down.
What are you doing?
- Just, uh, I'm just regrouping.
- You high?
Are you high?
- [exhaling]
I think I'm sunstroke.
I've been out here for hours.
- Sunstroke?
- Yeah.
- Maybe it's your allergies,
huh?
- Yeah, I mean,
these trees, the flowers,
the pollens in the pool.
You know?
Could be it.
- CPS shows up, and they see
you high as a fucking kite,
what do you think
they're gonna do?
The only reason these girls
get to live here
is because you're here.
What are you thinking?
- I didn't take that much.
- You didn't take much.
Well, I'm sorry
I'm overreacting here.
You want these girls
to see you like this?
Cool Uncle Rob?
High as a fucking kite?
I don't want drugs
in this house, do you hear me?
I'm gonna fucking fix up
your nose and your pocket
and the living room.
This is a no drug zone.
You can't follow those rules,
you need to get the fuck out.
Wake up.
Rachel!
- [Audrey] Good night.
- [Rachel] Good night.
Are we going to the movies
tomorrow like you promised?
- [Sammy] Yeah, yeah,
I swear, tomorrow.
- [Rachel] Promise?
- [Sammy] I promise.
- [Rachel] Okay.
- [Sammy] We'll do it tomorrow.
- [Audrey] All right.
- [Rachel] Good night.
- [Sammy] Goodnight.
- It's all gone.
I'm off it.
- Mazel Tov.
- You know, alcohol is a pretty
big vice, just saying.
- It's better than crack.
- Yeah, it's not crack.
Mind if I...
- Knock yourself out.
- Just a little.
[alcohol pouring]
Ooh. God,
I think I'll stick to crack.
[chuckles]
You know, my sister always knew
what to say.
She always knew what to do
to get me off that shit.
With just a few words,
I'd be off it, cold turkey.
Till I wasn't, of course,
but she never gave up on me.
She always stood by me,
and she'd say a few things
and I'd be off of it again.
- Your sister was tired, Rob.
- Yeah, I know.
- I mean...
She tried everything.
You always came back.
You always went back.
- She was stronger than
all of us, right?
- Yeah.
Yes, she was.
- To Laura.
[clink]
[inhales, exhales]
I fucking miss her, man.
- Me too.
Those girls miss her.
- [Rob] Yeah, but you're
doing a good job with them.
You really are.
[dramatic music]
- I'm trying.
[car engine roaring]
[dramatic music]
After very little thought,
I decided to take
the painting job.
"Decided" was an understatement.
[dramatic music]
[camera shutters]
- [Richie] How many you see?
- Two.
- Look again.
[dramatic music]
Still?
- Yeah.
- All right.
It's gonna be easier
to go over the wall
than go over that fence.
Just saying.
- All right,
let's get outta here.
I brought the genius
with me for the first stakeout
and quickly realized that
if this was gonna work,
I was gonna need a proper crew.
Harvey hooked me up with lunch
and a lead.
- There's David Dallas
from Milwaukee.
He's in town for
a little business,
but he's always up for
a little something on the side.
- [Sammy] David Dallas.
You wouldn't know it
by looking at this guy,
but Dallas was military,
trained killer.
If anyone can help us
with our security problems,
it was Dallas.
- Excusez-moi, mademoiselle.
When you have a moment, no rush,
I would like another espresso.
Merci.
- [Sammy]
Great guy, amazing manners,
but if you were
on his shit list,
his sweet disposition
went out the window.
[dramatic music]
With all fairness, if Dallas
showed up at your door
unannounced, you had it coming.
[dramatic music]
- No, you don't need a big crew,
'cause you've got Dallas
taking care of security,
Richie is keeping
the car running,
and you need one more thing.
- What's that?
- A decoy.
- [Sammy] Ruby Ellis.
A working girl.
- 30 minutes--
- [Sammy] And our mark's
favorite flavor.
Ruby was our decoy.
Ruby was gonna get Omar out
of the house
and give us enough time
to make the grab.
The only thing is she
wanted a fee and a cut,
and she wanted
that fee upfront.
I hate that place. Come on.
[knock on door]
- Speak of the devil.
Come in.
[dramatic music]
- Hi, Daddy.
[sighs]
- [chuckles]
You want something to eat?
- I'm good.
- [Harvey] You sure?
- You know what I like.
- Al Said has a classic weakness
and one
that we can fully exploit.
She's gonna keep Omar
very busy, okay?
So we'll have enough time
to make the grab.
- But you think
he'll be up for a date?
- Oh, yes. Omar? [laughs]
He's always up for me.
[Sammy and Harvey giggles]
- I like her.
- Right?
- How much?
- Small fee and small cut.
- Upfront, right?
- Always.
- The America dream.
[dramatic music]
Sounds about right.
Well, it was so nice
to meet you, Sammy.
- Nice to meet you.
- [Ruby] See you later, Daddy.
- [Harvey] All right, baby,
take care.
- I felt like I was getting
five different diseases
just sitting there.
[dramatic music]
Now I had a crew and a timeline,
and all I needed
was a babysitter.
[dramatic music]
Where's your uncle?
- Outside.
- What are you guys doing?
- What does it look like?
- You don't have to be so mean.
- He's annoying.
- Hey.
- Look at me.
- I'm clean as a whistle.
I promise.
- Serious?
- Yeah.
My head feels like it got
cracked open like a coconut,
but I'm good.
It's O.J.
Straight up,
just the way I like it.
- It is O.J. Proud of you.
- Yeah, well,
I'm not doing it for you.
I'm doing it for those girls
in there.
- I know. That's what
I wanna talk to you about.
- What's up?
- I got this job I gotta do.
- You got this job you gotta do.
- And I wanna make sure you can
take care of the girls for me.
- Do you really feel good
about leaving those girls
with their degenerate uncle?
- No.
- When you put it like that,
no.
- No, I'm serious.
Yes or no?
- Yes, I can do it.
- [cellphone buzzing]
- Beautiful, thank you.
Hold on.
Hello.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll be there
in 30 minutes.
- Duty calls?
- You're a real asshole
when you're sober,
but I'm proud of you.
Give me one.
- [Rob] Thanks.
- Thank you. I'll let you
know exactly what day.
Keep it up.
Rob didn't know exactly
what I did,
but he definitely knew
I was in the shade,
but as long as he didn't
ask any tough questions,
I didn't have to come up
with some tough answers.
Audrey, I gotta run
for a little bit,
can you do me a favor
and hold down the court?
- Yeah, sure.
- Wait, are you serious?
- Great, so you're the boss.
- Oh, you're putting her
in charge?
- What about Uncle Rob?
- Keep an eye on him too.
- [Rachel] Wait,
I don't need a babysitter.
- [Sammy] I think you do.
- This is bullshit.
- Language.
[dramatic music]
- Richie.
- Yeah.
- You see the street?
- Already, you can see it
by that.
There's a red barn-looking
thing.
- [Sammy] Right.
- All right,
that's a good spot to hide.
You understand?
Make sure you get all
the entrance and exits,
those guys there.
[camera shutter clicking]
- You see any street lights?
- Not right now, no.
There's none there.
You know, David, go up there.
Go up there with him. Show him
this and take some pictures
of that, all right?
Because you have to be there.
That takes about a minute and
a half, I timed it the other--
- I can work with this still,
guys.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- We'll take more pictures.
- It's very doable.
Where are they going?
- I want him to take
some pictures of there.
I spoke to my guy,
I got a figure.
- And?
What, $5, 6 million?
[dramatic music]
[speaking in foreign language]
$30 million?
- Shh!
They shouldn't hear a thing.
30.
- $30 million.
He wasn't kidding about
keeping it between us.
The others would get
a nice, decent cut,
and I can pay Ira in full
and still walk away
with a stupid amount.
[dramatic music]
- You know, it's time for
both of us to give up this life.
I'm gonna throw in the towel
as well.
- Throwing in the towel?
- Mm-hmm.
Whatever happened
to all the speeches
you used to tell me
in the office?
"This is all I know.
This is my life."
- I know, I know, but you know,
it's never been $30 million.
You can be whoever
you want to be, right?
- Absolutely.
- I'm happy for you, Pops.
- You know, Sammy, when your
mother left me, I got angry.
I kept busy non-stop, and then
when she got sick and died,
I feel guilt.
- I know.
- Keep going.
[dramatic music]
It's time that
we don't go anymore.
You understand?
Both of us.
[dramatic music]
All right.
[camera shutter clicking]
- What a fucking crock of shit.
They want more pictures?
- Relax.
- Don't tell me to relax.
- Well, you're not relaxing.
- Yeah, something's not right,
okay?
We're supposed to be crew,
and they're keeping us
out of the loop.
- What loop?
You're the fucking driver.
What more do you need to know?
Make sure there's gas in
the fucking car and relax, okay?
Don't worry about
the fucking loop.
Fucking loop,
what the hell is that?
[camera shutter clicks]
I'm gonna say it again.
- Don't you say it.
- I'm fucking saying it.
- Don't you fucking say it!
- Relax.
- Fuck off, come on.
I'll show you relax. Let's go.
- Where you going?
[car door slams]
[car engine starts]
Jesus Christ.
[car engine roaring]
Let's go around
to the other side, all right?
See if we can get some shots
over there.
[car door closes]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
what happened? What? What?
- Rachel ran away.
- What? Oh, okay, okay.
Calm down. Don't worry
about it. I'm gonna find her.
- I don't know what happened.
She just freaked.
- She was upset.
I asked her what was going on,
and she freaked out.
She just left.
Don't worry about it.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Oh, shit.
Audrey, you need to calm down
until this woman leaves, okay?
Hi!
- Hi, Mr. Silverman, did I
catch you guys at a bad time?
- Uh, no, just, um, there--
there's a spider in the house.
- Yeah.
- A spider?
- Yeah, like a big spider.
- Huge.
- I'm afraid of spiders, too.
- [Sammy] Yeah.
- She hates 'em.
- So how are you liking living
with your uncle and Sammy?
- Um...it's been fine.
- It's fine?
- Uh, fun.
It's been fun, great.
- Where's your sister?
- Rach is, uh...
Rach was in the...
She's...
- She's in the shower.
She's taking a shower right now.
- Would you like to go get her
from me?
I'd like to speak with her, too.
- I don't know, teenage girls,
you know, with the creams
and the shaving,
I don't know what
she's doing in there, really.
It's gonna be a while.
- Okay, well, I won't
keep you much longer.
I was just checking in.
- Thank you.
Uh, any news?
- Not yet, but soon, I hope.
- Me too.
- Okay then, have a good night.
- Thank you.
- You too.
- It was good to see you.
[mouths words]
All right, listen, calm down.
I'm gonna go find her.
Everything's gonna be fine,
okay?
- [Rob] Yeah, yeah.
- All right, good save.
- Thanks. Hey, uh, I think
I know where she might be.
- What I'm thinking?
- [Rob] Yeah.
- All right, go back in
the house. I'm gonna call you.
- I got you. Let's go.
- All right.
- [basketball thuds]
- [Rachel] Oh, fuck.
- Hey.
How come this ball
doesn't have a puncture?
- Give it back.
Come and take it.
No?
You know, when I was your age,
basketball saved my life.
I was a bad kid, hung out
with really bad people.
And basketball was the only
thing that kept me on track.
[gentle guitar music]
You can't run away anymore,
Rach.
- This was his ball.
We'd come out here
and shoot for hours.
Just the two of us.
It was our thing,
and I could talk to him
about anything,
and he'd always listen to me.
Not fake listen, you know?
- I know you're hurting,
and I know I'm probably
not your favorite person
in the world right now,
and I'll never be your dad,
but I can promise you one thing,
that you don't have to go
through anything alone
ever again.
I'll always be here with you.
If you wanna come out here
and play basketball,
if that makes you feel better,
do it.
If you wanna puncture every
one of those balls, go ahead.
I'll even hold that ball
for you,
and you do it at the house.
But...
You gotta come home
at some point.
Your sister misses you
like crazy.
She's crying.
[dramatic music]
- Can you show me how
to do that two shot?
- Really?
- [Rachel] Yeah.
- I'll show you
my favorite move.
- All right, do it.
- Okay!
- Let's see it.
- Up the middle, bam!
- [Rachel giggles]
- Come here.
[dramatic music]
I love you.
- [Rachel] I love you, too.
- Hold this.
Let me get my jacket.
- All right.
[sighs]
[dramatic music]
This was it, game day.
I'm not gonna lie, this was
always my favorite part.
All right, guys, listen up.
He's got two guys with him
all the time.
A date night's
not gonna change anything.
- Where is he taking you
for dinner?
- Somewhere with room service,
original.
- Classy.
- Dinner's gonna last
longer than him, so...
- All right, so there's not
gonna be a lot of time.
All right? So make sure,
Ruby, that you text me
the minute the fun time
is over.
- You got it.
- Okay.
- He's got two guys with him
at all times, like I said.
One's on the inside,
one's on the outside.
- And they never stray
too far from one another.
So when they get close enough,
I'll take them both out.
- Hey, wait, what do you
mean take out? Take out what?
- Take 'em out.
What did you hire me for?
Teach 'em a magic trick?
- Oh, no, no. This is clean,
Dallas. I want this clean.
- Yeah, no guns on this,
please.
- These guys are packing heavy,
no doubt about it.
- Richie, we're going light
on this.
- All right, it's okay.
We'll use tasers
and zip ties, then, all right?
it won't be a problem.
- All right.
Now, what about the guy
on the inside?
- We don't have any guns.
I guess we gotta go
with a ding-dong ditch.
- What's that?
- You know, it's the same thing
as a ring and run kind of thing.
- You knock on the door.
When he answers, boom!
Zip goes the weasel.
- It's pop.
Pop goes the weasel.
- [Harvey] Clean, perfect.
- All right, cameras inside,
outside, all over the property.
- What are we doing about that?
- I know a guy who knows
a guy.
- Of course you do.
- Look, you're gonna have
30 minutes
from the time the lights go out,
but that's our window.
So make sure you have watch
and synchronize.
You understand?
- All right, Richie, listen,
you sit in the car,
engine running, right?
Once the lights go down,
Dallas is gonna go in,
knock the guards out.
I come in, steal the painting,
and we'll meet back
at the house.
- [Harvey] Easy peasy.
- All right.
- Any questions?
- Is that everything?
'Cause, like, I kind of
have to go get ready.
- Yeah, we should all go.
- No, I got a question,
just one.
So, uh, I took the time to do
a little research
about these paintings,
what they might go for
and, oh, fuck me, I mean,
these things are worth a lot.
- So what's the question?
- Oh, what I'm saying is
that maybe we're being
a little shortchanged.
I mean, what if
one of our paintings
are worth that much, right?
And if I get 5% and when I
do the math, bang, bang, bang,
it just, you know,
doesn't really add up,
so what I'm trying to say is you
got me on a fucking discount.
- You know, Richie,
bang, bang, bang.
This is no time to be
negotiating salaries, okay?
You're gonna do very well,
please.
- Pops, the guy is getting 5%
for sitting in a car.
- For God's sakes,
I do less on my knees.
- How about you, Dallas?
What do you feel about 5%, huh?
- You gotta be fucking
kidding me right now.
- Listen, what he's making
is none of your business,
all right?
He's bringing much more
to the table, Richie.
You're gonna be very well
taken care of.
So just calm down.
- Do you need a ride, honey?
- Yo, Richie,
hold on one second.
We're good, right?
- Yeah, we're good, man.
- We're good.
- No, no, calm down, Richie.
- Calm down.
- We're good, we're good.
- Dallas, are we good?
- We're good. Hey, Richie,
let me catch a lift, too, huh?
[dramatic music]
- All right then.
This son of a bitch, I should
have listened to you.
- What did I tell you?
He's tearing up the whole thing.
- Ah, boy, oh boy.
You were right.
- I had a bad feeling now,
a bad taste in my mouth,
and it wasn't tea.
I kept waiting for Laura to
appear and tell me to walk away,
but it wasn't just me
and my gut.
[dramatic music]
Getting ready for a job
always made me nervous,
especially a job
I've never done before.
I don't know a thing about art,
except that it's overpriced,
and it's much easier to move
around when it's rolled up.
I do know a few things
about robberies, though.
[gun cocks]
If you bring a gun,
there's a good chance
you're gonna use it.
[dramatic music]
- That's crazy.
- Hey, guys,
don't wait up for me,
I gotta go do some work thing,
okay?
- Where are you going?
- I got a work thing I gotta do,
but, uh, the good news
is when it's done...
we're gonna spend
a lot of time together.
- What thing?
- It's just a work thing.
- Hey, can I get another beer
while you're up?
- I got you.
- Sammy.
Get out of here. I got this.
Don't worry about it.
- I just wanted to say goodbye,
you know?
- Don't you think those girls
have had enough goodbyes
for a while?
- [whispers]
Yeah, I guess you're right.
- You can tell them
when you get back.
- Okay.
- Hey, uh...
I wanted to thank you.
- For what?
- Just felt like the right thing
to say.
- When you think about
something to tell me,
you tell me what I'm back,
okay?
- Yeah.
- I love you girls.
- Bye. Love you.
- Bye.
- Take care of them for me,
okay?
- I got you.
- Take care of them.
[TV playing indistinctly]
[bottle cap clatters]
- Let's go!
- [Rachel giggles]
[dramatic music]
[radio static and chatter]
[engine idling]
[dramatic music]
[car engine roars, turns off]
- Yeah, Harvey, I'm here.
- [Harvey] All right, good.
[dramatic music]
-[rustle in distance]
- Did you hear that?
- I didn't hear anything.
[dramatic music]
- Check the back.
- All right.
[dramatic music]
- [Security] It's probably
just the circuit breaker again.
I'm gonna go check it out.
Over.
[dramatic music]
[taser buzzing]
[thud]
[cellphone buzzing]
- Ruby, what's up?
It's over, Papi.
- [Harvey] What?
- I mean, over, done,
he couldn't get it up.
- When?
- I don't know,
like 10 minutes ago
or something, maybe.
10 minutes ago?
You should've--
You should've texted.
Why didn't you text?
I ain't your fucking secretary.
The fuck? I did my job.
- Dammit.
[dramatic music]
[lock clicks, door squeaking]
- [cellphone buzzes]
- Yeah.
- Richie, the mark
is on his way.
How long I got?
- Five minutes tops.
- All right, no, I'm on it,
I'm on it, I'm on it.
[dramatic music]
- [whispers] Hey, hey. Shh, shh.
It's okay.
Shh, come, quiet.
Shh, don't scream, don't scream.
What are you doing here?
You're scaring the kid.
Put the gun away.
- No, no, the only thing
scaring this kid
is the two scary men
in the living room.
Three scary men.
- Dallas, talk some sense
into him.
He's got a gun with him.
- I think he's making
perfect sense, Sammy.
- That's right. Now his father's
gonna be here any minute,
and we were gonna do this
the hard way, right?
But I think Omar will
give us anything we want
in exchange for junior
over here.
- What are you guys doing?
Why are you doing this?
Listen to me very carefully.
I'm gonna take this painting.
I'm gonna go home,
and I'll meet you there.
- [Richie] Just like we said,
just like we said.
- We're taking all the paintings
and we're taking the kid too.
- That's right, we're emptying
Omar's whole fucking place,
then you and your dad
could go home
and have
your fucking circle jerk.
- Okay. Okay.
Don't hurt the kid, okay?
- We're not gonna hurt the kid
Sammy. We're not animals.
This isn't personal.
What can I say?
Money talks.
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
- [thud]
- Pop!
- Yeah, Sammy, the painting.
- Okay.
[dramatic music]
- Come on, hurry!
- Mama.
Dad, stop them!
[child screams]
- What's wrong?
- [child screams]
- Baby, talk to me.
What's wrong?
- [child crying]
- What's wrong?
Is somebody inside?
- [child screaming]
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
- All right,
you got the painting?
- I've got the painting.
I got the painting.
- [child] No!
- Wait right here.
Wait here for one second.
[dramatic music]
- Go. Drive, drive.
- [car engine starts]
[dramatic music]
- What the fuck?
- [Sammy] Difference between
a good thief and a hack
is simple--greed.
- Christ Almighty,
what the fuck?
- [Sammy] Get greedy,
you get sloppy.
- Junior!
Jamal, go get my kid.
[dramatic music]
Junior!
- Dunbar.
[dramatic music]
- What?
- Michael Dunbar is the buyer.
Number's in my...my phone.
- [Sammy] Okay, Pops.
- [Harvey] We have to call him.
- [Sammy] You call him
when we get there.
- My code is 0809.
You have to call.
- Wait, Pops, are you okay?
- [Harvey] [weakly] Yes.
- Fuck me, you got hit?
Oh my, God.
Oh, my God, okay, okay, Pops.
Fuck, hold on, hold on! Put
your--Put some pressure on it.
- I love you, son.
- Stay with me, stay with me!
Fuck! Fuck! Move!
[car horn honking]
Fuck me!
[honking continues]
Harvey! Fuck!
Harvey!
Don't do this to me, Harvey!
[dramatic music]
Harv, Harv, Harv, Harv, Harv.
[ocean waves crushing]
"I Love Us."
If you told me five years ago,
those three little
corny words would be
the most important words
in my life one day,
I would say I can't wait.
Now you know everything.
[ocean waves crashing]
I don't wanna lie
to you guys anymore.
Can't lie to myself.
Can't lie to anybody.
As you know, the adoption
got approved.
You guys can be my kids now,
and we can be a family,
but only on one condition.
You guys have to want me
to be your dad.
- You're wrong, you know?
- [Sammy] About what?
- About that being
the whole story.
- It's everything, I swear.
- What she means is
that this isn't the end.
- It's where it starts.
[dramatic music]
- I vote yes.
- Yes.
[pats envelope]
- I love you guys.
- [Audrey] I love you, too.
- [Rachel] I love you.
- Come here.
[dramatic music]
[Audrey and Rachel giggling]
Guys, this is my dad,
Harvey.
- You must be Audrey.
- Yeah.
- Rachel?
- [Rachel] Yeah.
- And you're the troublemaker.
- [Rob] No.
- I heard a lot about you, Rob.
Come. Come.
Beautiful girls.
You want hug?
- I want a hug.
- Come here.
- Papa Silver.
- Pops, these are the girls.
- So beautiful.
We have to teach them some--
- [Sammy] Omar never came
after us.
Turns out his son was
worth a lot more to him
than he thought.
- I love you, baby.
[dramatic music]
- Harvey always loved
giving me advice.
- [Rachel] Sammy!
Sammy, come on!
- [Audrey] Come on!
- [Sammy] But the best thing
he ever told me was
that it was time to let go.
[upbeat music]
"I...
Love...
Us."
- [Sammy] Coming!
[dramatic music]
♪ After all these years
with you ♪
♪ I just got to say ♪
♪ I love you so much more
with each and every single day ♪
♪ Just look into my eyes
and you will see ♪
♪ I swear,
I love you and beyond compare ♪
♪ From you I learn
to rise and be forgiving ♪
♪ Taught me how
to stand my ground ♪
♪ Open to just keep giving ♪
♪ And through my darkest times
when I was broken ♪
♪ I swear ♪
♪ Every time
you were always there ♪
♪ I look into your eyes
with every sunrise ♪
♪ I'm never alone ♪
♪ It suddenly hits me ♪
♪ Baby, you made me
just stand on my own ♪
♪ After all these years
with you ♪
♪ I finally understand ♪
♪ Together, baby,
we'll never fall ♪
♪ With gratitude
for all you've done ♪
♪ You always be my number one ♪
♪ Forever
I will give you my all ♪
♪ I'm gonna give you my all ♪
[guitar music]
♪ After all these years
with you ♪
♪ I'm going through
the fighting ♪
♪ I listen and I hear your
dreams and all that you desire ♪
♪ Your love and warm embraces,
my true comfort ♪
♪ I swear ♪
♪ You're the answer
to my every prayer ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I look into your eyes ♪
♪ With every sunrise,
I'm never alone ♪
♪ It suddenly hits me ♪
♪ Baby, you made me
just stand on my own ♪
♪ After all these years
with you ♪
♪ I finally understand ♪
♪ Together, baby,
we'll never fall ♪
♪ With gratitude
for all you've done ♪
♪ You'll always be my
number one ♪
♪ Forever I will give you
my all ♪
♪ Wanna give you my ♪
[guitar solo]