Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
(car door closes)
(engine starts)
(intense digital music playing)
Scott Wapner:
He started from nothing
and built a fortune
worth upwards
of $20 billion.
♪ ♪
reporter: It is not often
that a Wall Street titan
shows up on the cover
of "Time" magazine.
reporter 2: The most feared
corporate raider in the world.
reporter 3:
One of the shrewdest
investors on the planet.
reporter 4:
He moves markets
by the mere
mention of his name.
reporter 5:
"Fortune" magazine says
he may be making
more money for shareholders
than anyone else on the planet.
(applause)
Gail Golden-Icahn:
He's tenacious.
-man 1: Enigma.
-man 2: The smartest guy
I've ever met.
woman:
He's the great white shark
in the sea of capitalism.
Carl Icahn: My mother said
I have some kind of warrior
gene in me or something.
interviewer:
A warrior gene?
various voices:
Marvel Comics, Time Warner,
Texaco, US Steel,
Dell Computers,
Apple, PayPal, Caesars.
reporter: Motorola. Yahoo...
all have felt
the pointed sting
of Carl Icahn.
I do it because
in a free enterprise system,
I do it for profit,
but what I do should be done.
-Totally terrifying.
-Bully.
Great guy, but he's about
as smooth as a stucco bathtub.
I own it, it's my money.
If I lose, I'm answerable
to my bank account.
♪ ♪
I'm 85, you say, this guy's 85.
Pretty good, right?
I can get some real heat on 'em.
I don't like to start wars,
but if somebody wants
to start it with me,
there's something in me
that likes that
'cause I'm really looking
forward to going at 'em.
♪ ♪
Wall Street, they look
at Carl Icahn and they say
legend, they say genius.
There's an admiration
for what he's been able
to accomplish
and the wealth
that he's created.
The public, I think,
has a much more mixed view
about the impact he's had
on companies,
on labor, on society.
♪ ♪
Then the question is
whether he is
a activist investor,
an advocate
for the shareholder,
representing the little guy,
or corporate raider
who goes in,
extracts value
out of that company
to the detriment
of the long-term company
but to the immediate benefit
of Carl Icahn.
Let me do it.
No, I wouldn't say it that way.
It's sort of a colorful term,
"corporate raider,"
but it's far from the truth.
Absolutely is ridiculous
related to what we do.
It's the opposite of what we do.
We bring things to the party.
We don't raid 'em
and take 'em out.
That's why I think eventually
it was changed to "activist."
But activist or raider,
I haven't changed
what I do one iota.
Call me whatever you want.
(chuckles)
♪ ♪
So, how are my boys?
Ah, what good boys.
Susan Gordon:
He gets up about nine o'clock
and he's already,
he's eating his breakfast
and reading the newspaper
while he's talking,
and, you know, writing notes
and all that.
He immediately starts his day,
catches up
with what the news is,
how the market's doing.
Uber's got
one thing after another.
We work together
in his home office,
and then, about four o'clock
in the afternoon,
he starts heading over
to his "office office"
on Fifth Avenue,
for meetings, or what
current crisis is going on.
Crisis manager.
I'm like Ray Donovan.
I try to... I try to...
I try to get it done
and then I go
into another crisis.
There's always a few of 'em.
You don't have to
manufacture 'em.
Wapner: I think the way
Carl looks at business
and the way he does things
is he tries to identify
companies
that he thinks are undervalued,
and he'll secretly build
a position
until it gets large enough that
he has to reveal the size.
And he'll try and put pressure
on the CEO to do what he wants,
whether that's doing a merger
or a share buyback.
And in more cases than not,
over the years,
the CEO will end up doing
something that he wants
and the stock price will go up
and Carl will make
a lot of money.
Meissonier's, it's "Napoleon
at the Battle of Friedland."
Before hubris took over
and took it all away from him.
He was one of... Well, he was
a great strategist, no question.
But then he lost it all
because of his arrogance.
And that's one thing
you have to remember.
It doesn't stay forever
if you're not careful.
(discordant percussive
music playing)
(intense digital music
playing)
reporter: Carl Icahn, I guess,
doing what Carl Icahn does,
and he is on the attack.
reporter 2: Carl, what do you
object to most strongly?
Carl:
I object to the fact
that they did a acquisition
that puts the company at risk
and didn't go to the board
members for a vote.
Andrew Langham: Somebody
from Reuters just called.
-What did they say?
-They want to understand
what we're doing.
You know, we want to remove
some of the directors
and put us in.
They know I'm not going away,
so we just,
we just keep,
we keep going.
The idea of an activist investor
is they buy a stake
in a company
with the plan and ambition
to go to the company's
management and board and say,
"You're doing it wrong.
Here's how to do it."
Carl:
Yeah, how you doing?
I don't have to tell you
anything you don't know.
I mean, I think it was
reprehensible what went on.
I think they got no right
to do that without talking
to the shareholders.
You know,
they're betting the company,
it's not their money.
He looks at boards
and he looks at CEOs
as country club boards.
They spend no time thinking
about the company.
They're collecting their fee
and they're playing golf
all day.
Andrew Ross Sorkin:
The board of directors
of a company
are supposed to represent
the interests
of the shareholders.
They are supposed to hold
the CEO and management
to account.
That is their job.
Whether they do it is
Carl Icahn's biggest question.
(percussive music playing)
Hey, who the hell put this out?
Who got this out, that we're
replacing four directors?
-Yeah.
-We just told them that.
You told them
'cause I told you.
We filed it, and so...
(laughs) Oh, yes, we filed.
This is what he just filed.
That's just what we was talking,
and they already put this out.
Huh.
Hey, we said
a lot worse than this.
We didn't say anything bad.
Langham: We said a lot worse
a month ago.
Here it is, it just
happened while you were here.
It was a very...
you guys were here
at the making of
a lot of history today, guys.
It's not a sure thing that
when you take a big decision
and tell a CEO what to do,
they're going to listen.
It's also not a sure thing
that your advice is
the right thing to do.
You need chutzpah.
You're taking on big-deal CEOs.
You're taking on their lawyers.
It's a very high-stakes game.
You can make billions,
but you can also lose it.
That is stressful.
-Hey, Gail,
-Gail: Yes?
Come in here
for a minute.
Oh, I'm his consigliere.
At night time, we join up
and then go home together.
Bruce David Klein:
What do you think drives him?
Oh! (sighs)
It isn't money,
strangely enough.
You would think
it would be money.
I mean, it's nice
that he can do it,
but it's not money.
He just becomes
obsessed on something
and he just keeps
like a bulldog,
he just keeps going and going
until he gets what he wants.
So... that's what drives him.
I told him it's winning,
I think, competitive,
just winning.
Coming up with a new idea
to beat the competitors.
You know, we're gonna
be able to be
the biggest and the best.
That gets me excited.
♪ ♪
The money is just
sort of a goal.
It's like, the explorers,
why do they keep doing it?
They believed in going
for the gold, like Cortés
and these guys.
But I think the actual
finding and doing
is much more exciting
than having it.
♪ ♪
And I think
that's why you find
a lot of rich people
get very neurotic.
'Cause they're disappointed
when they have it.
It's not what it's
drummed up to be.
♪ ♪
reporter:
He's been successful,
say Wall Streeters,
because he's intimidating
and relentless.
He was an only child
growing up during
the Depression
in Far Rockaway, Queens,
New York.
And even as a kid, his mother
said he was like Genghis Khan.
He loves a good fight,
no doubt about it.
(percussive music playing)
announcer:
Tappan. Tappan.
The name is Tappan.
Tappan... Tappan...
Mark Stevens:
So in the late '70s,
Carl turned his attention
to a company called Tappan.
Tappan made ranges,
and it was a good
brand-name range.
Bob Barker:
Showcase number 2.
-announcer: A new kitchen!
-(audience gasps)
An electric range
from the famous Tappan.
Quality appliances since 1881.
Tappan has its first loss
in nearly half a century.
Because of the loss, and loss
of faith in the company,
the stock plummeted
to I think about
seven or eight bucks.
So Carl does his calculations,
assesses the valuation
of the company
between the stock price
and the ultimate value
of the company.
And there's a gap of about $15
that Carl feels is there.
Carl: Well, we believed the
company was very undervalued.
And Tappan fit
the program for me
where I was embarking
on activism,
where I thought it was
a great company, a great name,
that could be
a takeover candidate
being blocked by,
you know, the CEO
and a board.
The CEO was
a very strong personality,
but I don't think he knew
much about the business.
And Dick Tappan was
the founder's grandson.
I think he was intimidated
by this guy Blasius.
And I thought there was
a chance here to break through.
So we went and bought
a lot of stock in it.
And, uh, we would then
make a little noise.
(intense digital music playing)
Carl: "I'm writing this letter
to ask you to elect me
to the board of directors."
♪ ♪
"During the past five years,
"Tappan, under its
current management,
has lost $3.3 million."
The company is owned
by the shareholders
and these managements felt like,
"We don't wanna deal
with these shareholders."
"They thought they'd get
under our skin? No."
We ran a proxy fight
and they fought us like hell.
♪ ♪
It's just amazing.
Carl got a seat on the board.
I think we were the wave.
There was not anybody really
doing what we were doing.
(relaxing music playing)
Stevens:
When Carl goes to Ohio
to visit with
Tappan management,
it's an orderly life there,
and everything is in
the right place.
The CEO called me up.
He said, "I wanna have dinner
with you before the meeting."
So I thought he'd want to have
a sort of nice chat with me.
And he looked at me and he was
sort of fierce-looking.
He said, "Look,
at my board meeting,
you're an interloper.
"I don't want you to say
anything at the meetings.
I don't want you to disturb
the rest of the board
and we can get along better."
And I was just
beginning this stuff.
Today, I would have
told him to go to hell.
Alfred Kingsley:
The next day, Carl came
and we went into the meeting,
which was pretty contentious.
Carl: And the CEO decided
to buy another company.
And he brought it
to the board.
He was gonna make
the company less valuable
in a strange way
but him more powerful.
And the CEO is showing
everybody with his books
and his investment bankers
why this was
a great acquisition.
The CEO, he said, "Look, I've
done a lot of work on this.
I just want a vote
that agrees with me."
And this one guy on the board
who never really spoke either
but who owned a lot of stock,
he said, "Just a minute."
He says, "I'm looking at this.
I just don't understand
why we're buying it
with these numbers."
The CEO, he says, "Are you
questioning my judgment?"
He's glaring at the guy.
He says, "Sit down and vote
with all of us."
He really was an imperious guy.
And I'm watching
to see what to do.
And, you know, at that time,
I didn't think anybody
would support me
if I said anything,
but I said, "The hell
with this guy Blasius."
By that time, I didn't give
a damn if he liked me,
didn't like me.
(intense digital music playing)
So I go, "Screw this guy."
Stevens:
In this Tappan time,
one could think
that Carl didn't have the...
kahunas that he would have
later in big deals.
He had more then.
He had to do it with nothing.
He didn't have
billions in the bank.
Carl: I said,
"You know something, guys,
I'll tell you what I think."
"This is probably
one of the worst deals
"in, I'll say,
economic history.
"It's insane.
We're buying this company
at ten times what it's worth,
only," I say,
"to save Don Blasius' job.
That's why we're doing it."
I really let him have it.
And the guy was going nuts.
He was turning red in the face.
He says, "What are you saying?
Are you questioning my ability?"
I said, "Yes, I am.
I don't think you're a good
CEO, you're just gonna
kill this company."
All of the sudden, Carl,
he's not talking,
he's yelling, he's demanding.
"I, for one, will do everything
I can to stop this deal,
"and now I'm saying it
to this board,
so now let's have the vote."
And Blasius is looking at me,
red in the face and all.
And he says, "We'll put off
the vote till the next meeting."
And then he just glowered at me,
and I just looked at him,
and that was it.
People are scratching
their heads saying, how the--
"What the hell just happened?
Who is this guy?"
"How did he foil the plans of
the CEO of a public company?"
And then, only seven or eight
months later,
Electrolux agreed to buy Tappan
for a little over
$18 a share...
♪ ♪
...proving in absolute terms,
Carl was right from
the beginning.
Tappan was worth
a lot more than the $7
the stock was trading at
before Carl got involved.
And all the shareholders
got richer.
Carl: At the end,
Dick Tappan comes over to me
and he says, "Carl, Carl,
I wanna ask you a question.
Would you manage my money?"
And he wanted me
to manage money for him.
And I did for a little bit.
(contemplative piano music
playing)
This is Carl, Carl Icahn on.
If I could interrupt
for a minute.
The CEO was just nefarious.
He, his job in his mind was
to make himself a lot of money
at the expense of shareholders,
he didn't care.
And at the expense of
the company enriched himself.
The idea that
some management teams
were kind of not being
very smart
and taking advantage of
their position as managers
to the detriment
of the shareholders,
you know, he got that
in his head early on,
when the rest of the world
wasn't quite sure, you know,
was this greenmail,
what, what was this?
This is one of-- the most
reprehensible thing
I think I've ever seen...
But to some degree
he's been vindicated that,
yes, management often needs
to be shaken up.
He's helped stockholders
an awful lot,
including plumbers and teachers
whose pension funds
fund their retirement.
So this is not just hoity-toity
big-time investors.
The downside of that
is to say, yeah, but what about
all the people
who lost jobs because of what
Carl did at all these companies?
(somber digital music playing)
Carl and guys like him, I think
the core criticism would be that
they're not out to make
these companies better,
they're out to make
a lot of money.
Part of my values
is to make money and I
can't change my values.
A great painter loves to paint.
What do you do, criticize him
because he likes to paint?
But what makes me fulfilled
about it is
that I also believe I'm making
money by doing the right thing.
Sorkin: We've been having
a debate, it's an open debate,
'cause I've done it
in the columns,
about his role as a vulture
or a shareholder advocate,
and which is it?
And on certain days,
I've come out on the side
of shareholder advocate,
and he, you know, loves it.
And on certain days,
I have called him a vulture,
and he'll call up screaming.
What I like about Carl
is he's game for the debate,
he wants that debate.
Carl: Companies are
the backbone of our society,
and many are terribly managed
and there's no accountability.
When you can change that,
you will have
some collateral damage,
there's no question,
it's creative destruction.
But we bring in the innovation,
so we have companies
that are more productive,
create more jobs,
in a macro picture.
At the end of the day,
Carl wants to make as much
money as possible,
despite what he may come out
and say publicly
or write in one of his letters.
I mean, that's
the criticism you hear.
Carl: So everybody says,
"Well, that's great,
Carl Icahn made money
for himself."
But the real proof of
the pudding is in the eating.
If you had invested
in Icahn Enterprises in 2000,
when we really started
getting into the activism,
the value of your investment
has increased
1,931%.
During that same period,
your investment in the S&P
went up only 324%.
We have made for shareholders,
forgetting us,
literally a trillion dollars
for all investors.
I think I proved it
by making all this money.
This system should be changed
and that we should have true
corporate democracy
and accountability.
Frankly, I made this money
because the system is so bad,
not 'cause I'm a genius.
(marching band plays)
announcer:
This is New York.
A miracle city.
A monument to our nation's
restless energy.
Across the river from Manhattan
lies the borough of Queens.
(jazz band playing)
Carl: I grew up
in the streets of Queens.
It was sort of divided.
In public school, you had
some of these middle-class,
mostly Jewish kids.
From the other side
of the tracks,
a lot of
the reform school kids,
and those were the kids
I liked, really.
Used to play basketball
with the Gotti brothers.
But the more my mother said,
"Don't do it," the more
I wanted to do it.
Stevens: Bella Icahn
was the school teacher
who was always teaching school.
Carl's father was a cantor,
the guy who sings
in a synagogue,
who pressed Carl
on philosophers and philosophies
and was unrelenting,
and his mother, who was
unrelenting another way.
She wanted him to go
to medical school,
but they were both
very intense people.
He had a tough childhood.
I mean, you know, his parents
would brag about him in public
but kind of berate him,
privately.
(contemplative music playing)
I was never really happy
in that whole environment.
So I really wanted
to get out of there.
I was real smart in school,
and I had good marks.
I took the college boards,
and I think I did the best
in Queens or something on 'em.
And my father did say to me,
"If you get into Yale,
Harvard or Princeton,
we'll pay the tuition."
'Cause they figured
nobody ever got in
from Far Rockaway
High School.
And so I got into all of 'em.
And everybody
was really surprised,
including my parents.
I wanted Princeton.
But then when it came
to thinking about paying
the tuition,
it was only $750 in those days,
and the room and board was $750.
My father said, "Son, we're
not gonna go back on our word.
We're gonna pay your tuition."
I said,
"Thanks, Dad, that's great.
I appreciate it greatly."
And then it hit me, I said,
"What about
room and board, Dad?"
And then he said,
"You're a smart kid.
You gotta worry about
the room and board yourself."
(doo-wop music playing)
So, somehow
I wheedled myself a job
on Atlantic Beach,
the sort of, in quotes,
"wealthy people" came.
So I'm a cabana boy,
figure I'll work for tips.
And you could make close
to $100 a week.
And these salesmen,
for the most part from Brooklyn,
were playing poker.
And once they said,
"Kid, how much you make?"
I said, "Hey,
I made a hundred bucks."
"Okay, you got a hundred bucks,
you wanna lose it,
come here, do a game, we'll
show you what life's about."
So I said, "Yeah,
I think I could play."
And they wiped me out
in about a half an hour.
I lost the $100.
I said, "Hey, I'm smarter
than these guys."
So during the week, I went out,
I got three books on poker.
And it's really
a mathematical game.
It's luck, too, but
these guys were not that good.
To begin with,
they were drinking vodka,
and they were just having fun.
The next week,
I went in and I said,
"I'll play it again."
They said, "Okay, kid,
you haven't learned
your lesson yet."
And then I killed 'em.
I got inordinately lucky.
And literally that weekend,
I won $800.
♪ ♪
And that's how I paid
my room and board
throughout Princeton.
(playful digital music playing)
Gail: I can tell you
the first moment
I fell in love with Carl,
and that was when I
started working for him
and heard him on the phone
speaking to his uncle,
who had offended him
in some way.
And he was so frank
in that exchange.
Coming from
an Irish background
where everything
is sort of hidden,
I was not accustomed to
that kind of depth of feeling
and that honesty of feeling,
and I think that was
the first moment that I thought,
"This guy has a little bit
more substance than
I thought he did," so...
Oh, God, this elbow's
killing me.
Well, you played pretty well
with the elbow killing you.
Well, imagine the trouble
you're going to be in.
Carl: Yeah, imagine if you
didn't have a bad elbow.
You know, you hit those goddamn
little poopy shots at me,
which, you know,
it throws me off my game.
You know, that's, you know,
in some cases that's by design.
I know you don't think that,
but it's by design.
-Sometimes I just...
-Baloney, it's by design.
There are times
I play with you when
I deliberately hit it soft.
You're not good enough
to deliberately hit it soft.
You don't have a slice.
You don't, yeah.
I don't have to have a slice.
Yeah, I mean, you played well,
you played well.
You actually, you actually
really did okay yesterday,
got to admit,
with a bad elbow.
Gail: We started
living together in '92,
and didn't get married
until '99.
This is another horror story
from a client from TWA.
Gail: But I have
known him since '78.
I started working
for him in '78.
The first time I met Carl,
this employment agency said,
"Can you please come in?"
and she said,
"I have this guy,
I've had a hard time
keeping people with him."
-That's not true.
-Gail: Oh!
I've had people
with me 20 years.
I'm not gonna lie on camera,
so you can just go ahead
-and say what you wanna say.
-Eh...
But anyways, the pile of stuff
on his desk was incredible.
So he says, "Do you think
you could help me with this?"
This chaos, and in the first
two weeks, I was ready to quit.
But he was fun.
He was just very fun.
And so, you know,
it started there.
And it was, it was good.
Tony Bennett:
♪ I'm steppin' out
with my baby ♪
♪ Can't go wrong
'cause I'm in right ♪
♪ It's for sure,
not for maybe ♪
♪ That I'm all
dressed up tonight ♪
-♪ Steppin' out with my honey ♪
-You're gettin' too good...
♪ Can't be bad,
feels so good ♪
♪ Never felt quite so sunny ♪
♪ And I keep on
knockin' wood... ♪
I think what keeps it going
is respect for each other.
Um, and we laugh a lot.
I mean, there's a lot of banter,
you know, sarcasm,
back and forth.
-Doesn't matter what you think.
-Gail: It doesn't matter
what you think.
-Who cares what you think?
We can banter with each other,
but she's one of the few people
whose opinion I really value.
Some nights I fall asleep
in the bath.
And Gail turns a movie on
and doesn't bother
to tell me she leaves.
And I wake up and say,
"Holy, where am I?"
I say, "Gail, maybe you could
have waked me up, check in.
I could have been dead
in there."
-Gail: Seriously.
-What?
I could be on fire
sitting next to him
and he wouldn't spit on me.
What is this nonsense?
She wouldn't know if she left me
in the bathtub drowning.
It's a nice way to spend a life.
(phone ringing)
Oh, you should stop.
Because you have to answer
the phone because...
-Well, somebody's
gotta answer it.
-...I just can't.
-It might be important.
-Let somebody else
answer the phone.
What if it was for me?
Carl:
Eh, now I lost it.
(percussive music playing)
So, Carl goes to Princeton
and he's kind of an outsider.
♪ ♪
Peter Liebert: We started
at Princeton in 1953,
but there was clearly a social
pecking order at Princeton.
The nature
of the social situation was
that Jews didn't even apply
to certain clubs.
I never resented it.
But I think, in many ways,
Carl did.
Rana Foroohar:
That's the thing about Carl,
is he has kept that feeling
of being an outsider,
because I think that,
at seminal moments in his life,
he very much was an outsider.
Liebert:
And I think Carl felt
a desire to prove to himself
and to others
that he's smarter
than most of these people.
Stevens:
He majored in philosophy.
And the best way Carl
could exercise
his lifelong need
to show superiority
to the Brahmin culture
that dominated Princeton
in those days
was to win the senior thesis,
which is the equivalent
of being valedictorian.
Carl:
The thing I enjoy
by far the most,
and maybe in my life,
that I'm the proudest of,
was my thesis.
And I just wanted to prove
that I could accomplish
something.
Stevens:
It's almost unreadable,
it's so complex.
But he got his revenge,
and he won that senior thesis.
I'm telling you,
this is very arcane stuff.
I won an award for it,
but when I read it again,
I honestly can't understand
what I wrote.
It was just an exercise,
I won't say in futility,
but an exercise in logic,
which is... really fulfilling,
but it wasn't for me.
♪ ♪
I got accepted
to medical school,
and I really didn't
wanna go.
I didn't wanna be a doctor,
but my mother was so adamant.
She said, "It's
an anti-Semitic world,
therefore be a doctor."
And then she used
to scare me and say,
"If you don't,
you get out of Princeton,
they're gonna
take you in the army
and they're gonna kill ya."
So I quit a couple of times.
My mother always
talked me into going back.
And one time we go
into this tuberculosis ward,
and I'm a slight hypochondriac,
but not terrible.
This resident picks me
from the back, he says,
"Icahn, give me
a differential diagnosis."
I tried to be funny,
so I look at him and say,
"Hey, Doctor,
we know what he got, it says
'tuberculosis' up there."
He says, "Don't be funny,
this is medicine."
So I lean over the guy
and I tap his chest.
Coughs all over me,
I say, "Bullshit, that's it."
"I quit."
He says,
"You don't leave here.
You leave here,
you're never coming back."
I said, "It's okay with me
if I never come back.
You talk to my mother."
So I remember to this day,
I walked from 34th Street
all the way up 42nd Street,
where you could join the army.
♪ ♪
The army, to Carl, was
the witness protection program.
And he would tell me this,
"My mom couldn't get me."
There were two choices:
jail or the army.
Carl: I never liked
the discipline of anything.
I hated the army.
But I made money in the army,
I played poker in it,
but I hated it.
So I left the army
with maybe 20, 25 grand.
By his poker playing,
you start to see his ability
with numbers and strategy.
And he started thinking about
finance in a serious way.
So we're finally, we're going
to be doing the test run
-of the podcast today.
-Good idea.
My roots come from
more, um, storytelling,
and so I started doing
different projects
for my father,
like PR and his social media.
What I wanna do
in this podcast is
-call it "Outrage," you know...
-Yeah.
...and call it
"Outrage of the Week,"
AKA "How shareholders
are getting screwed."
And just tell it as it is.
And then we'll see how it
works, but we'll play with it.
All right, so this is what
we're gonna do, we're gonna
put our headphones on.
You're gonna take them,
you just open them up.
-You talk to me like
I'm a moron. I can-- Okay.
-I know. (laughs)
-Michelle, I'll show you
how to do it.
-(laughing)
Michelle:
As a child,
I didn't know how monumental
the deals were
that my dad was involved in.
I just knew he was
really, really busy.
But PayPal is
an exciting company,
but it should have been
spun off, but the board
didn't wanna lose it.
After we were fighting
to spin it off for three years,
and the CEO suddenly
had an epiphany.
"Wow, great idea I just had.
Let's spin off PayPal."
And the stock went way up.
He works all the time.
I think that was,
that's his mission.
What's surprising is
that I think Bernie Sanders
and even Elizabeth Warren
have a point.
And I don't like them, I mean,
because I don't like socialism.
I don't think it could work,
but what they are saying,
this wealth gap,
the tremendous wealth gap,
-should not exist.
-Yeah.
People on Wall Street
are tremendously overpaid.
The investment bankers make
ridiculous incomes,
relative
to what they contribute.
You know, I think my father
is an activist.
I think by nature he wants
to create change.
When I came into Wall Street,
I realized playing the market
is extremely risky,
extremely dangerous, so...
Michelle:
He talks a lot about
the market in 1962.
You know, for him that was...
I think that was one
of the most impactful moments.
(intense digital music playing)
Carl: When I got out
of the army, basically,
I went to Wall Street
because I was into stocks,
I was into making money.
I got in the training program
at Dreyfus
and started investing,
and it fit perfectly for me.
And I'm making a fortune.
I'm making all this money.
I bought a Galaxy convertible.
I had a beautiful girlfriend.
And life was good,
and I figured,
"This is the easiest
damn thing I ever did."
And Jack Dreyfus came to me,
said, "You know,
"Carl, you're a smart guy.
"You're gonna lose every penny
you got there.
Learn to be an investor,
not what you do."
He says, "You're
just one of the fools."
I said, "Come on, Jack,
move over," you know,
we're laughing.
And I learned a great lesson.
You always pay for hubris.
In '62, the market broke.
Terrible.
Jack was right.
I was wiped out.
I don't know which went first,
the Galaxy
or the girlfriend I had.
After that, I never played
the market again.
Really, literally,
I went to work.
♪ ♪
I had to learn one area
and be an expert in it.
I looked at the option world.
I realized there
was something awry,
that there was a problem.
Options were mysterious.
What should they sell for,
what should you buy them for?
You had no place
to really know and look
about what was a good deal.
(percussive music playing)
Carl:
The option brokers were all...
I wouldn't say thieves,
but you would say
they didn't give a damn.
So they would go buy
these options
and make
a huge markup on them.
So I came up
with something called
"The Midweek Option Report,"
that would tell people,
"This is what you should have
been getting for your option
and this is what you got,
and you got screwed."
And I'm an obsessive worker.
I would stay down
on Wall Street
working till midnight,
calling people up
because in California
it was only nine o'clock.
I didn't know
about mugging or anything.
I'd go back,
I'd be the only guy
on the subway going uptown.
And I was looked on
as an honest broker,
and the business boomed.
And I became one of
the biggest brokers on
Wall Street doing that.
Stevens:
But in the evolution of Carl,
to be a real player,
he had to have a seat
on the New York Stock Exchange.
Carl:
I had saved
a few hundred grand,
and my uncle had some money,
and I decided to buy
the seat on the Exchange.
Elliot Schnall:
Tell me when you're on.
(clapper claps)
I was...
17 when Carl was born.
He was like a kid brother.
Elliot was a man about town.
He was distinguished
and polished.
Carl learned a lot from Elliot.
He wanted to start
his own firm,
and in order to do that,
you had to buy a seat.
reporter: Uncle Elliot
loaned Icahn $400,000
so he could buy a seat on
the New York Stock Exchange.
No, I knew he would be
a success at it.
Then he started his own firm.
reporter: Icahn began
with options and arbitrage.
Then in 1979,
he had a new idea: takeovers.
He told Uncle Elliot
he was going to start going
after undervalued companies.
I said, "Well, what do you know
about undervalued companies?"
He says, "Look,
I'm going to do it."
I said, "Carl, forget it."
I thought he was crazy.
I'll give you some scotch here.
He just bought it today.
It's good for ya.
Here, let me give it to ya.
No, I don't want any more.
Hey, you look good, Elliot,
you look good.
-Elliot: I look good?
-You look okay.
You look fine.
Elliot:
She's gonna give me a haircut.
(crowd cheering)
Bryan Burrough:
In the early '80s,
there were an awful lot
of young, white American men
in search of fortunes
who were
flooding into Wall Street
and wanted to know
that what they were doing
was okay,
because everybody would
go home on Sunday
and your mom would say, "Jimmy,
what do you actually do?"
In the last five years,
we've moved from malaise
to hope, confidence,
and opportunity.
Burrough:
But Reagan comes
and there is a feeling
of a laying on of hands,
that this is okay,
that pursuing money,
it's not only okay,
but it's somehow
good for the country.
It was like Reagan
telling everybody that
it was okay to party.
We're going to turn
the bull loose.
(bell clanging,
traders cheering)
("Blue Monday"
by New Order playing)
Burrough: If you didn't
live through the '80s
on Wall Street,
it's almost impossible
to understand.
-Zurich 23 Citibank.
-350, Nelson.
The chaos... it was like
a financial disco.
interviewer:
What do you get out of this?
The old guard,
it took 'em years and years,
and new people on Wall Street,
they wanna do it in two days.
The 1980s was
the reimagining of Wall Street.
It was when there was
these swashbuckling
financial pioneers
who were changing the game.
♪ How does it feel ♪
♪ To treat me like you do? ♪
A new breed of businessman,
the corporate raider.
Carl is the original.
He was the guy
that reflected the '80s
and taught everybody else
how to do those corporate raider
takeover deals.
reporter 1:
It all starts when
a raider finds a company
whose stock is selling
below its true value.
reporter 2:
The raider moves in
and the battle begins.
To either sell the company,
sell some parts of the company,
reimagine the company.
And their goal is to raise
the stock price
and make money.
♪ ♪
Icahn is the man who's been
changing the face
of American business.
reporter:
Icahn raids on some big names,
like Marshall Field,
Hammermill Paper, Dan River,
Phillips Petroleum,
Uniroyal and ACF.
Burrough:
Corporate raiders
were very controversial.
A lot of people
essentially thought
they were glorified
shakedown artists.
Carl: Again, I'm not doing it
because I'm Robin Hood.
I'm doing it because of
the financial--
absolutely because
I want the financial gain,
but I think it's a very good
thing that I do, and more
people should do it.
Raider?
What in the hell am I raiding?
I'll go in here and take a big
position in the company,
I take the risk.
I make something happen.
How do you identify me
as a raider?
Oliver Stone: When we started
to do "Wall Street" in 1987,
we went to Icahn's office,
Stanley Weiser and I,
who co-wrote the script with me.
He gave us about an hour,
and it was quite interesting
because... he was arrogant,
in the sense that
he was telling us
about the new way
of doing things
and how it was necessary
to attack these companies
because these are
outdated companies.
They take profit
for the executives
and they don't care
about the shareholders.
You own the company.
That's right,
you the stockholder,
and you are all
being royally screwed over
by these... these bureaucrats
with their,
their steak lunches,
their hunting
and fishing trips, their...
their corporate jets
and golden parachutes.
man: This is an outrage!
You're out of line, Gekko!
Burrough:
You know, there's
a purity to that speech
in what's wrong
with the corporate America.
It doesn't surprise me
that part of that famous speech
is informed by talks
that Stone had with Carl.
We almost have
what I consider to be
a corporate welfare state.
You have levels and levels
of vice presidents
in corporations
that really actually
produce nothing.
Teldar Paper has 33
different vice presidents,
each earning over
$200,000 a year.
(audience members whistle)
Now, I have spent
the last two months analyzing
what all these guys do,
and I still
can't figure it out.
I couldn't figure it out,
what these people,
taking up five floors
in New York City, did.
-(laughter)
-That's a true story,
true story.
The new law of evolution
in corporate America
seems to be
survival of the unfittest.
I believe it's anti-Darwinian,
Well, in my book,
you either do it right
or you get eliminated.
Stone:
Of course, there is
some truth to that,
but nonetheless, Gordon Gekko
is out for himself.
He's for personal profit
over public profit.
So Gekko is half right
and he's half wrong.
Burrough:
As time went on
with the insider
trading scandals,
the feeling was,
"Oh, you know, right.
These guys really are
just shakedown artists."
But Carl Icahn was not known
as an insider trader,
and suddenly he emerged
from this pack
of patrolling sharks
and began to be capital-C Carl
capital-I Icahn.
♪ ♪
Carl was possessing
an intellect,
a focus,
and a sustained drive
that was unusual.
And one of the signature deals,
one of the most involved,
was Texaco,
in which Carl, uh,
played a starring role.
emcee: A household name,
please welcome Carl Icahn.
Thank you, thank you.
I'm telling you,
these stories are funnier
than the jokes you could tell,
'cause this really,
I'll give you another one
that really happened.
And I talked to this guy today,
he said I could tell it.
We were taking over Texaco.
(percussive music playing)
(acoustic guitar playing)
♪ Ooh, there's gold ♪
♪ Coming out of the ground ♪
♪ There's gold there ♪
♪ To be found ♪
♪ The oil train... ♪
Burrough:
Texaco was, you know,
one of
the fabled Seven Sisters.
It began as the Texas Company
outside Beaumont, Texas,
and it was the fifth largest
company in America
when this all started.
♪ There's money coming
out of the ground ♪
♪ There's tons of money
running 'round ♪
This all began as a fairly
plain vanilla takeover.
One medium-size oil company,
Pennzoil in Houston,
goes after another one,
Getty in Los Angeles.
So the deal is done,
when out of nowhere,
Texaco swoops in
and snatches Getty
away from Pennzoil.
reporter:
The amount boggles the mind.
$10 billion offered by Texaco
and accepted by Getty Oil
in principle
to accomplish the largest
merger in corporate history.
♪ ♪
Burrough:
Pennzoil CEO Hugh Liedtke
was fit to be tied.
He was gonna get Getty.
He was gonna go to war,
and it became a war
really unlike anything else in,
on Wall Street in the '80s.
There just had never been
anything like it.
♪ There's blood coming ♪
♪ Out of the ground ♪
♪ There's blood... ♪
analyst:
You know, it is a soap opera.
You have
the classic ingredients.
You have greed on one side
and fear and loathing
on the other.
♪ There's blood... ♪
Burrough: Pennzoil's CEO
went and hired a lawyer
named Joe Jamail in Houston,
who is a very different
type of fella.
(upbeat music playing)
Wilbur Ross:
Jamail was famous.
He wore snakeskin boots,
big pointy toes,
flew in his own private jet.
He was
a larger-than-life character.
Burrough: Joe came from
the world of personal
injury lawyers,
and the only way he gets
paid back is if he wins.
So no one had more at stake
in this than Joe Jamail.
This is a totally
irresponsible act,
and, uh, one more sleaze move
that they're gonna slide in.
Texaco, they go down there
and they say,
"We're not going
to dignify this case."
And Jamail loves that
'cause his jury
are all his cousins
and stuff up there...
And so Jamail
loves that stuff.
And Joe Jamail was as good
at orchestrating
the goings on
in a Texas courtroom
as anybody that's
ever walked the Earth.
reporter: Here in Texas,
they're calling it
the showdown in the courtroom.
(gavel banging)
And Wall Street traders have
observers in the courtroom
with cellular phones
talking to New York.
reporter 2: When the jury
returned its unanimous verdict,
Pennzoil and Jamail
emerged victorious,
the winner of the largest
jury verdict in history.
A Texas jury has ordered
the Texaco corporation
to pay more than $10.5 billion
to Pennzoil.
reporter: And would have
to start paying interest
on that amount immediately.
Peter Jennings:
The biggest bankruptcy
in American history.
Texaco Inc.
filed for protection...
reporter: It was a decision
of last resort,
said Texaco president
James Kinnear,
to file for court
bankruptcy protection
in order to prevent Texaco
from collapsing entirely.
The CEO of Texaco, Jim Kinnear,
went absolutely berserk
and in my view
was recklessly willing
to gamble the whole company.
reporter: The value of Texaco
stock has taken a nosedive.
Most of us thought, you know,
it actually did look like
Texaco could go under.
And I think the only person
who thought it might not
was Carl Icahn.
Carl:
You have to buy things
where the rest of the world
are looking at you
and thinking you're
a little bit crazy.
You're going
against the trend.
A lot of times,
events are overblown.
Overblown on the good side,
overblown on the bad side.
My instincts looked Texaco
as a really good
fundamental company.
This thing is dirt cheap.
I took a shot
and bought all that stock
'cause I knew
they had to get rational,
and I was going to get
instrumental in it.
(phone ringing)
Jamail calls me up
and he says, you know,
(southern accent):
"You're a sensible man.
I wanna come talk to you.
You own a lot of stock."
(normal voice):
And he calls me "boy."
"You got a lot riding
on this, boy."
But before he came,
I called Kinnear.
(line ringing)
I get Jim on the phone.
You know, he says,
"I'm not talking to anybody,
and I'm not making
any settlement offer,
and that's it."
I said, "Okay,
I want you to do this,
so just listen to me.
"I'm gonna start
with numbers from 12 down.
"12, 11, 10, Jim?
"And when you get to the number
that you will settle for
"and accept to get this fuckin'
thing over with,
all you gotta do is say
'okay' and hang up."
So I started, "12, 11, 10, 9..."
I get to 3, he says "okay"
and hangs up.
So now I know
he would do it for 3.
So now Jamail
walks in with Liedtke,
and Jamail says...
I said, "Come on, this is
the biggest bullshit case
I've ever seen,
so stop the bullshit."
So he goes, "We would settle
this case for $10 billion."
So I say, "You know, Joe,
you ain't never gonna get
$10 billion so forget it."
And Liedtke gets up, irate,
you know.
It's a little bit of an act,
and he says, "I'm leavin',"
and the two of them
start walking out.
Jamail turns around
as he gets to the door.
He says, "You know..."
"Let's you and I
go have a drink."
I said, "It's 10:30
in the morning.
I'm here on Sixth Avenue.
Where the hell am I
going to have a drink?"
♪ ♪
So now we go out,
walking on Sixth Avenue.
And the Parker Meridian,
we walk in there,
and it was like, you know,
they weren't ready
for lunch yet
and they had all the chairs
on the tables and all.
But I know
the maître d' a little.
I said, "I wanna have a drink."
He said, "We're not open."
I said, "Just take
those two chairs off the table
and bring me a bottle of vodka."
And that's it.
And Jamail sits down,
he's taking the vodka.
So he goes...
I said, "Don't even negotiate."
He said,
"Well, you know we ain't takin'
less than nine billion."
He's now down to nine
or something.
I said, "Do you want the number,
or you wanna just bullshit?"
He looks at me
and he goes...
I said, "Yeah, I think I know."
I said,
"There's no negotiating.
The number is $3 billion."
He looks at me and he goes,
takes his hand...
♪ ♪
And I said, "Okay."
And now he's sitting there
and he's drinking the vodka,
and he's laughing,
he's got the Stetson hat.
And all these people
are coming in now.
I say, "So, let me ask you
a question, Joe."
I say, "The way I figure it,
you just made yourself
$600 million
for three weeks' work."
"Yes, I did, yes, I did.
"You're right,
you're good at math.
"$600 million," he smiled.
People are listening now.
You know, all well-dressed
people looking at this guy
with his feet up on the table.
I said, "Well, what good works
are you gonna do?"
"What you mean 'good works'?"
I said, "Soup kitchen,
you know, medical research."
"I'll tell you what I'm
gonna do with the money.
"I'll tell you what..."
and he did it.
"I'm gonna buy pussy!"
-(crowd laughing)
-"I'm gonna buy pussy!"
The headwaiter
comes running over,
headwater comes running over
and says,
"You know, Mr. Icahn,
I think you better leave."
-I say, "Yeah."
-(laughter)
That's it, and I left.
That was it.
(applause)
A multibillion-dollar
settlement early today,
the largest legal settlement
in this country's history.
reporter: Texaco has agreed
to pay Pennzoil
a staggering $3 billion
to settle a court case.
Stephen Labaton:
Carl walked into this situation
and basically forced
a settlement down Texaco.
Carl was not done
after the settlement.
He saw
continued potential value
and made a pretty hefty profit.
I think it was around
$600 million
that he made
on that transaction.
Jennings:
On Wall Street today,
the trading was heavy.
One reason: the sale
of a huge block of Texaco,
42 million shares
worth $2 billion.
That is the biggest single trade
ever on Wall Street.
The seller is believed to be
the takeover specialist
Carl Icahn.
Let me show you something.
You can use this.
This is sort of
something for ya.
So... (laughs)
This is sort of one
of my favorite pictures.
Look. This was sent to me
by Joe Jamail.
And, you see, this is the way
he was in the restaurant,
when we talked about it.
You see the shoes.
And he was a real character.
And he writes, "Friend Carl,
shit happens."
"Joe Jamail."
So I keep this around.
(tranquil music playing)
When I started out,
I learned the hard way,
playing the market,
it's a competitive area,
it's gambling.
Too many variables, too many
people competing with you.
You can't believe that
the gambling will carry you.
♪ ♪
So, you look for something
I call a "no-brainer."
Very little risk,
but a lot of reward.
After a while, it becomes
somewhat instinctive,
that you see something
that's not really apparent
to everyone.
♪ ♪
But there's tough times
when you're not gonna enjoy it.
You know, you're gonna lose
and you gotta be
willing to say,
"Hey, if I lose, so what?"
It's like that great
Rudyard Kipling poem.
"If you can meet
with Triumph and Disaster
and treat those two impostors
just the same..."
That's important.
♪ ♪
But you have to have
a passion for it.
You get a great feeling
when you find a company,
when you find something
you can do.
You get excited by it.
And by instinct now,
something goes "click,"
and you know it's good.
It all sums up
in that movie "The Hustler,"
where, when he shoots
the ball, he says...
You know,
I got a hunch, fat man.
I got a hunch
it's me from here on in.
One ball, corner pocket.
I mean,
that ever happen to you,
where all of a sudden,
you feel like you can't miss?
When I hear the click,
I know I won.
(rhythmic percussion
music playing)
♪ Leading the way ♪
announcer:
TWA presents the difference
between getting you
where you're going
and leading the way.
(upbeat music playing)
What's that?
-(reporters laughing)
-What was that?
man: Waiting for
the equipment to warm up.
I see you have problems
with equipment as we do.
Uh...
I thank you all for coming.
I'd just like to say that, uh,
we're doing quite well
with our scheduling.
TWA, I can tell you now
for sure, is here to stay.
(somber music playing)
Burrough:
This was an awful time
in the airline business.
And a lot of these companies
were under fire,
were the focus
of corporate raiders.
And when this fella,
Frank Lorenzo,
goes after TWA...
he was deeply, deeply
unpopular in the business.
Show me a business person
that doesn't like a monopoly
and I'll show you a big liar.
-(audience laughing)
-Okay?
reporter: Lorenzo was known
for being tough on unions.
Burrough:
So, at TWA,
the unions actually
went to Carl.
Carl:
So they all met with me.
They really wanted me to come in
because they needed somebody
to fight off Lorenzo.
announcer:
Today's TWA is the new spirit
and vitality of our people.
So they said, "We'll give you
huge concessions if you do it."
So I looked at the numbers
and said, "Yeah,
"if you guys give
these concessions,
you could just save
a lot of capital here."
(music box playing)
The staff gave me
this toy plane
to commemorate the TWA deal.
(music box playing)
Carl Icahn takes control
and is now running TWA.
Carl Icahn,
the controversial financier
known for his attacks
on corporate management.
Now they will be watching
to see how he himself
handles the management
of a major corporation.
♪ ♪
Wapner: Carl had never
run anything before.
Certainly nothing
like an airline.
You're dealing with the economy,
you're dealing with unions,
and that was his biggest fight
right off the bat.
We want a TWA that can exist
and it will exist
because all the employees
have come behind us.
The employees have given.
When it came time
to give the concessions,
the pilots lived up
to their bargain
and so did the machinists,
and then the flight attendants,
Vicki Frankovich,
comes in and says,
"We can't do it."
Carl Icahn came in and demanded
changes in everything.
She said,
"You got enough, it's too bad."
I said, "Bullshit. You made
a deal, you got to stick to it."
striker:
Carl Icahn not fair
to flight attendants!
Fifteen days into the strike
by TWA flight attendants,
there is no sign of
conciliation by either side.
At issue, company-proposed
wage rollbacks.
TWA employees confronting
a bottom-line businessman.
The work rules
we must have to survive.
We are not asking
for very much.
The changes he's asking
are drastic.
Carl: This company
would have been bankrupt
if I hadn't come along
and saved the damn thing.
Carl Icahn
is a corporate raider.
♪ TWA ♪
You know, literally they'd say,
"We got you by the balls,
the great Mr. Icahn,
because you need us to fly."
♪ ♪
So, what I thought of is this,
I said, "Wait a minute,
why can't we just bring in
new flight attendants?"
"Oh, because they gotta
be licensed."
-(alert chimes)
-(air hisses)
I said, "Set up a school
for flight attendants."
"Eh, I don't know.
We can't do that."
I said, "Well, why not?"
"Nobody ever did that."
I said, "Set up
the goddamn school,"
and from all over the country,
I couldn't believe it,
all these people want
to be flight attendants.
And then Frankovich
now goes crazy.
She sees all this happening.
striker: The flight attendants
are out here today because
they want to show Carl Icahn
that we are still united
and we're still determined
to win this battle.
We're holding together better
than any other union I know
that has struck in the past.
Some woman down the road
calls me up, panicked.
"There are a thousand people
walking up the road,
chanting and screaming."
"What's going on, Carl?"
you know.
She says,
"I'm calling the police.
I'm calling the police."
(siren wails)
(intense music playing)
(strikers chanting)
reporter:
These flight attendants
took the unusual step
of taking their case
right to the home
of TWA chairman Carl Icahn.
I said, "Bullshit," and I went
out there with the kids.
"You're not taking the kids."
I said, "I'm taking the kids."
striker:
Here's the lies right here,
our new work rules.
(strikers complaining)
Well, that's what...
this is, this is...
You know, I can't...
You're being a little...
-woman: Quiet, let him talk.
-Carl: You've got an airline
that's losing
200 million bucks in '85
and it's losing a lot
in this quarter...
(strikers drowning out Icahn)
'Cause we can't compete.
-Can I finish?
-(strikers clamoring)
You wanna listen?
You come to my home
on a Saturday,
I've still
come out here to talk to you,
and I want--
and I think you should
give me the courtesy
to listen
as long as I'm talking to you.
-man: That's fair.
-Miss Frankovich
should have come
to that meeting in August,
you don't like to hear it,
because at that time
I could have got financing.
I told her I need
three people there,
she says,
"I'm going to a party,"
-and that's the truth of it.
-(crowd clamoring)
-I'm telling you what happened.
You don't wanna hear it.
-man: Cheap shot.
-That's a cheap shot.
-Carl: Now, let me finish up.
Could I? Then you can talk.
Instead of yelling.
-You're brainwashed.
-man: No, we are reasonable.
I mean this.
I am not here to hurt you.
I think a lot of people
are getting wrong
information from her.
I'm getting a lot of calls from
a lot of flight attendants,
say they'd love to come back,
they're being
intimidated by her...
-that they're being
scared by her.
-strikers: No!
-man: That's not true.
-(strikers clamoring)
(chuckles) That is good.
Yeah, I remember that.
I wanna keep that,
that's a good clip.
Show that to my grandchildren.
I have a whole group
that's willing to meet.
She says she wants me there.
You can't force me
to like somebody, okay?
I don't like dealing with her.
Okay? Because she lies.
But that doesn't mean I don't
have a whole group of people
that are there
qualified to talk to her.
We're willing to talk.
I don't wanna be there with her.
It was sort of exciting.
(strikers jeering)
Carl: The strikers
didn't understand.
Frankovich told them
a lot of bullshit.
And a lot of them
agreed with me.
After a week,
she pulled them off,
she wouldn't let them come
to my house anymore
'cause they were all
now complaining to her.
Wapner:
I don't know if Carl expected
that he was gonna have
this kind of turbulence
right off the bat.
I think he would tell you
he thought he was
fighting the good fight,
and yet what he was doing
played into every stereotype
of the evil Wall Street
financier.
The companies
that he leaves behind
incur a tremendous
amount of debt
and then they
start laying off,
and that's more
and more Americans
falling below
the poverty line.
I've been seeing
a counselor since the strike
because it is emotionally
devastating to have lost...
I mean, I've been a flight
attendant my entire adult life.
Every one
of those flight attendants
could have walked across
the picket line, which many did.
Many of them said,
"Hey, Vicki Frankovich,
the heck with it."
They could have
kept their jobs.
I didn't tell you not to cross,
we begged you to cross.
We came out, we told you
over and over.
They had work rules
that we couldn't afford.
If I hadn't come along
and borrowed $700 million
on my name,
you'd be chapter 11.
If you're chapter 11,
it wouldn't do you any damn good
'cause you wouldn't be working,
you'd be like Eastern.
Pan Am, Eastern, and Braniff,
there was a whole bunch
of them that went under.
And during that period,
we turned TWA around,
for a couple of years.
announcer:
The U.S. is a bargain
if you know where to shop.
And the best place
is today's TWA.
We've got low air fares
to terrific cities...
We brought innovation
with a business saver fare.
announcer:
Bargains on the ground, too,
like our travel value pack.
Carl: We created
the flight attendants school.
♪ You're gonna like us ♪
♪ TWA ♪
I made mistakes with it,
though, I mean, I made
a lot of mistakes with it.
And then it, then it got
from bad to worse.
(ominous music playing)
♪ Happy birthday,
Dear Carl ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you... ♪
The problems were endemic.
People weren't traveling
to Europe for a while,
you had that Desert Storm
that came.
There were a lot of
other things, too,
with the terrorism.
He was perplexed.
"Why can't I figure this out?"
He's always had a magic wand.
Didn't work here.
Carl eventually
took the company private,
but it was loaded with debt.
And TWA ended up
filing for bankruptcy.
I really believe that, you know,
you look at the results,
and if it doesn't work,
you blame yourself, I guess.
(upbeat music playing)
I'm taking you back
to where I grew up.
You've always asked me
as a little girl,
and I'm gonna show you,
before I moved to Florida.
-So little...
-I've heard so many stories.
So little,
but I grew up there.
♪ ♪
I think it wasn't...
it wasn't until I was older
that I really, I think,
got a better understanding
of where my father grew up
and the different challenges
that he probably was facing
that were maybe responsible
for making him so tenacious.
♪ ♪
Carl: My parents, they only
made around 5,000 a year,
but that's all
they would talk about.
Maybe that's why I was
so interested in money.
They hated the rich people,
but they were so into it.
-Okay, we're here.
-(engine stops)
Carl:
You're coming up to my house.
Michelle: I remember it
from photos, but this is...
-Carl: Yeah, I remember it well.
-...it's so cool seeing it.
Carl:
Yep.
Oh, Mr. Icahn, how are you?
-Carl: Okay.
-Moishe Russell.
Good to meet you, and thanks
very much for having us.
(laughs) Jeez.
Brings back memories,
that's for sure.
My father had
all this musical stuff,
because he loved to sing.
And he had
a Presto record recording.
Your mom had
a wall right here.
No, they took the wall out.
This was the dining room.
They kept telling her,
the house would fall down
if you took the thing down.
But she found a builder
that said, "Bullshit,
I'll put a beam up there,
the house is fine."
'Cause she was
tenacious, my mother.
Boy, she was tough.
♪ ♪
But you know, when you
needed her, she was there,
I'll say that.
You know, like
sometimes if I feel down
or have problems,
she was always
a real good problem solver.
But... egomaniac.
She was a complete egomaniac.
I mean, everything she did
was right, you know.
She, she had the answer
to, to everything,
and she was really...
you know.
But people liked her.
She was funny, you know,
she had a good sense of humor,
except with me.
I had to be perfect to her
because I was her kid.
So anything she did
was perfect, right?
So, I was supposed to be
perfect.
♪ ♪
She was so strong-willed
and I was strong-willed,
so... we always had
a stormy relationship.
(man singing in Hebrew
on phonograph)
Ah, look at this. Wow.
Michelle:
Where are we right now?
Temple Beth El.
I was bar-mitzvahed here.
Oh, yeah.
(song ends triumphantly)
Michelle:
It's beautiful.
Carl: My father used to sing
here and he was the cantor,
and I was bar-mitzvahed here.
-Wow.
-But he wasn't religious at all.
They would sit here,
the trustee, maybe,
and my father would sing,
I don't know which one,
maybe over there.
Yeah.
I haven't been back, I think,
for close to 70 years.
Bruce: You feel the ghost
of your father in here?
Nah. Nah.
My father was
a very strange guy.
Even though he was
the cantor at the temple,
he was a dyed-in-the-wool
dogmatic atheist.
And he was, in my opinion,
a communist.
My father was also
the Irish tenor on Sundays.
-And so...
-(Michelle laughs)
He was. He just had
a great voice, you know.
It was, Michael O'Cahn
was coming and he would
sing "Danny Boy,"
and he just wanted to sing,
you know?
I never inherited
his love for real music.
I mean,
I never had any talent.
He's the guy that said to me,
"Your mother has
great talent in art.
"I have a great voice.
We're both talented people.
"Now you, on the other hand,
have absolutely no talent.
"Go be a doctor.
The doctors,
look what they charge you."
He had no filter
for what he said.
My father was
an interesting character
'cause he didn't,
he didn't really give a damn
pretty much about...
Well, he did,
he got outraged at people.
He really, I think I got
this sense of outrage from him.
Michelle:
Yeah.
Carl:
I was never close to him.
I never respected him
or admired him.
My father, he never
asked me what I did.
Even when I went on Wall Street
and I was making the money,
he never tried
to have me explain it.
He never asked,
he never got into it.
And finally, in Florida,
I went down there once
and he had a pad and pencil.
"Come here, come here.
Explain to me what you do."
And I said,
"You finally admit it."
And then we hugged.
I still, I still cry about that.
Bruce:
Why do you cry?
I don't know.
I don't know why I do.
I felt...
a certain warmth.
A certain warmth.
That was, that was my father.
They, they say,
"Thou shall not kill,"
and later on you go,
"An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth," right?
So they're all
sort of contradictory.
(both laugh softly)
reporter 1:
Some say Carl Icahn was
20 years ahead of his time,
battling the corporate world
in the name
of shareholder value.
Aw, come on!
reporter 2:
When TWA filed for bankruptcy,
it hurt his reputation,
but he pressed on,
returning to the scene
with years of proxy fights,
all the while demonstrating
his knack
for corporate combat.
(percussive music playing)
(trance music playing)
Herbalife is
a global nutrition company
that sells our products
exclusively
through a network of people
just like you.
Herbalife is a nutrition company
based in California
that Carl Icahn probably
had never heard of.
I mean, nothing.
Until Bill Ackman showed up.
Throughout my career,
the vast majority,
particularly our most
successful investments,
have been ones that have been
controversial in one way
or another.
Bill Ackman is another one
of the major activist
investors out there.
He's a fellow billionaire.
One of these masters
of the universe in New York.
Harvard educated
versus Carl's Princeton.
reporter:
Although unlike Carl,
he was born into privilege.
He also likes to publicly
spar with companies
the way Icahn does,
but he goes about it
in a slightly different manner.
And please welcome
Bill Ackman.
(crowd applauding)
Okay, so we've got
a lot to cover today,
so we're going to move
pretty quickly.
Why don't we start...
Sorkin:
So Bill Ackman decides
that Herbalife effectively
is a fraud, it's a scam.
Herbalife is a pyramid scheme.
It's caused enormous harm
to millions around the world.
Our goal is for the facts
about Herbalife
to be made public.
And he believes that
if he's able to expose
what he believes are the
company's frauds to the public,
that regulators
are gonna jump in
and the stock is gonna tank.
I don't want to make
any money from this, okay?
I view this as blood money,
but let me be clear.
We'll short the stock.
Herbalife stock goes down,
we make money.
Herbalife stock goes up,
we lose money.
He's gonna short the company,
so he's gonna bet that
the stock is gonna fall
all the way to zero.
Ackman: A pyramid scheme is
actually a modern-day version
of a Ponzi scheme.
Carl, meanwhile,
is watching this all play out.
Ackman:
...the version is called 3.0.
It's 1.0 is the Ponzi scheme.
And he's thinking to himself
that Bill is gonna lose,
that he's never gonna
get the stock to go
even further down
and effectively bets
against him.
(discordant music plays)
Carl:
Ackman is a real,
I think, a smart guy
and a good investor.
He might have talked himself
into believing
that he was going to be
a savior,
but I felt that Ackman
had an agenda.
♪ ♪
Icahn and Ackman
had done a deal together
some years earlier
where the contract
was somewhat ambiguous.
And the court eventually said
that Icahn had to pay.
After Carl paid Bill,
the unwritten rule
on Wall Street,
"Don't gloat
about your victories."
Bill went to the newspaper
and he gloated about the victory
and that pissed Icahn off
like you don't know.
I think Herbalife was personal.
Carl: Ackman's whole thesis
is completely wrong.
I mean, I can't even
understand his argument.
I was walking through
the CNBC newsroom,
and I saw Carl on TV
on another network
absolutely annihilating Ackman.
Carl: He may believe what
he's saying, I don't know.
Herbalife gives jobs to people.
I mean, it's absurd
what Ackman is saying.
And I stopped in my tracks
and I said,
"This is unbelievable."
And I was kind of mad that
it was happening somewhere else.
But I went and I called Bill.
And I said, "Do you want
to respond to this?"
And he's like, "You know what?
"Carl's an asshole.
"I'm sick and tired
of this bullshit.
"He tried to take
advantage of me.
I'll come on, I'll do it"
So I said, "Great."
(intense music playing)
Ackman: Carl has been
maligning my reputation,
so it's very important
that we get to the facts.
Ackman comes on,
we're talking about Herbalife.
Ackman: Carl, he can try
to scare my investors
from investing with me,
which it sounds like
he's attempting.
And then Carl calls in
to the control room.
I look down at my computer
and there's a tweet
from a CNBC
colleague of mine,
and it says,
"This is gonna be good."
-(dramatic flourish plays)
-All right, welcome back
to the "Halftime Report,"
live today from
the New York Stock Exchange.
We've been speaking with
hedge fund investor Bill Ackman.
Now it's time to hear
what Carl Icahn thinks
of our conversation.
He joins us live on the phone.
Carl, are you there,
Bill, there?
-Carl: Okay,
good to talk to you.
-Ackman: I am here as well.
Wapner: You know, Carl,
you have an issue with the way
that Bill went about
the Herbalife short
as aggressive and as
publicly as he did,
and he's essentially saying
that you're a hypocrite.
How do you respond?
Carl: Let's start
with what I want to say.
I've really sort of had it
with this guy Ackman,
'cause Herbalife is a classic
example of what he does.
You scare the hell
out of people,
get the stock down
and make 600 million bucks
on paper
and tells the world
how great he is.
I had dinner with him.
I couldn't figure out
if he was
the most sanctimonious guy
I ever met in my life
or the most arrogant.
And I'd like to give Bill
a chance to respond
to you as well.
Ackman:
Carl has been-- is gonna try
to attack my integrity.
And Herbalife,
we're not scaring people
but going through the facts
about the company--
Carl:
If that wasn't scaring people,
you could have fooled me.
Ackman:
And we will either
be proven right,
or we'll be proven wrong.
There had never been
quite a showdown
between two people
of such high stature
as Carl Icahn and Bill Ackman
on live TV.
Carl:
Then he talks about charity,
that's complete (bleep).
He's not giving it to charity,
assuming they don't need
charity themselves.
-Let me do this, I mean...
Carl.
Carl: Now, that's what
I'll say about Ackman, okay?
Let me remind you that
we are on live television.
We're doing the show that day
at the stock exchange,
and it's on a delay.
So each time Carl would say
something nasty about Bill,
two seconds later
you would hear all the traders
on the trading floor...
Carl:
He's the quintessential
example on Wall Street,
if you want a friend,
get a dog.
-traders: Ohh!
-Carl: And he does
a pump-and-dump...
Wapner: Uh, the guys
on the trading floor
down here at
the New York stock exchange...
Same thing when Bill would,
you know, insult Carl,
the floor would erupt.
Ackman: This is not
an honest guy.
He's a bully, okay?
Says he doesn't like
behaviors that are bad...
It quickly devolved
into a battle, a war.
-Carl: Ackman is a liar, okay?
-(traders clamoring)
He's got one of the worst
reputations on Wall Street.
The guy is a major loser.
Ackman: The big issue about
Carl Icahn is he's not used
to someone standing up to him.
Carl, you wanna bid
for the company, go ahead
and bid for the company.
Carl: Hey, you don't have
to tell me what I'm free to do.
I'm reporting from Davos,
Switzerland,
at the World Economic Forum,
where all the CEOs
from around the globe come.
And I remember being
at a cocktail party,
trying to get Wi-Fi on my phone
so I could watch it,
and literally a swarm of CEOs
standing around,
we were all watching...
Carl: I appreciate, Bill,
that you called me
a great investor.
Unfortunately I can't
say the same for you.
It was like must-see TV.
Ackman: Simply said to him,
I said, "Look, Carl,
you are no friend of mine."
You couldn't take
your eyes off of the thing.
Ackman: Do you think
I wanna invest with you?
Carl: I wouldn't invest
with you if you were
the last man on Earth.
Volume of trading
at the New York Stock Exchange
went down 20%,
as everybody was just sort of
standing there watching TV.
Carl: I'm telling you,
he's like the crybaby
in the schoolyard.
You know, I went to
a tough school in Queens
and they used to beat up
the little Jewish boys
and he was like one
of these little Jewish boys,
crying that the world
was taking advantage of him.
Wapner:
Let me, guys, we're gonna...
we're gonna end it there.
Bill Ackman, Carl Icahn,
we'll go to break.
Herbalife played out
for a number of years,
but it was really a foregone
conclusion from that moment,
because once Carl emerged,
Bill didn't really have
a chance.
Just as the markets are falling,
Herbalife is hitting
an all-time high today.
Carl wasn't going
to go anywhere.
And Wall Street
was betting with Carl.
(trance music playing)
Herbalife is officially
the worst investment ever made
by Pershing Square.
Bill lost the majority of
his investment in Herbalife.
It was a billion-dollar short.
And eventually Bill
just threw in the towel,
and Icahn, he won.
It obviously felt good.
It felt good that I beat him.
We did have a vendetta, and I
felt he had screwed me once,
so it felt good to do it.
But I certainly have no grudge,
and at the end
of this whole thing,
he called me up and
congratulated me on the victory.
And I think it was
a classy thing to do.
But the winning, that's not
the motivation for me.
The motivation is just,
find the good one.
Find something you know
is gonna be good,
and the odds
are greatly in your favor.
Winning, it's almost...
a bit of a letdown, actually.
You know, you did it all.
Now it worked.
On to the next one.
Pretty good. I made a good one.
Fairly good. Fairly good.
(percussive music playing)
Sorkin: Carl wasn't typically
interested in tech companies
'cause they weren't
his kind of companies.
analyst: Why is Carl Icahn,
first of all, investing
in a private tech company?
Wapner: How did he end up
in the tech game?
♪ ♪
Brett Icahn: I started working
for my father as an analyst
back in 2002.
There were several
of us at the time.
I was definitely
the youngest of the group.
I sort of had
a privileged "in,"
you could, you could say.
But I had, you know,
I had learned quite a bit
about accounting
and I took economics
in school,
so it's not like I was
completely a fish out of water.
Carl:
I'll say this about Brett,
he's much more low-key
than I am.
But he's one of the most
obsessive characters,
and he'll work very hard
at something,
extremely hard,
especially if it means
beating me at something.
♪ ♪
Cara Lombardo:
He's not quite
as pushy as Carl.
He's more analytical.
He is definitely
more risk averse.
But they have
a lot of similarities too.
They both love history.
They're war buffs.
For a while, they played
a Sunday night game of chess
every week.
But they had to stop that
because Brett,
he got too good
and kept winning.
Foroohar: Carl, I think,
is very proud of Brett.
He wanted to praise Brett
to me on a couple of occasions,
but he would sort of
pull himself back
because he didn't want
to make it too easy for him.
Carl:
So he worked for me ten years.
Another guy in the firm,
a very smart guy,
named David Schecter,
they came to me, said, "Look,
we're not gonna stay here
unless we get some money
to manage."
You know, "We're not gonna
just do research."
So I figure, well,
I'll teach them a lesson.
I'll give them some money.
I made it a tough deal.
It was actually like
a very difficult deal.
You know, I said,
"Okay, you can have like
"7.5 percent profits,
each one of you,
"but you are gonna have
to meet this hurdle rate
"of 7% before
you make a penny.
No salary, no income,
no nothing."
And they both agreed to it.
♪ ♪
Lombardo: And I think Brett
really expanded Carl's mind
in terms of what makes
a good investment.
It was Brett who called
Carl's attention to Netflix.
reporter: Mr. Icahn owns
2.2 million shares.
That makes him
one of the largest
shareholders in Netflix.
reporter 2: Netflix,
Netflix the big winner
in today's trade.
Carl: Netflix was a no-brainer
when we first went into it.
Everybody didn't like it
when we bought it.
So Netflix went on to be
one of their most lucrative
investments ever.
I think they made
around $2 billion
when all was said and done.
Foroohar: As I remember
the Netflix success,
and it was a huge
success for Carl,
was, whoa.
I mean, we knew
this guy was back,
but he's now back
and he gets tech.
(laughing) You know.
If I were the CEO of
a tech company at that stage,
I would have been
a little worried
that I might be the next person
he was looking at.
(trance music playing)
Brett: Apple was
an example of a company
that was just really cheap
on a fundamental basis
of cash flow.
Brett noticed that Apple
had immense amounts of cash
sitting on its books,
and the stock price
wasn't reflecting that.
reporter:
Apple is now sitting on
almost $150 billion in cash.
It was about
the finances of Apple.
It was about, could Apple
buy back their own shares,
and if they were
able to do that,
how much more
of a higher valuation
should be ascribed
in the marketplace to Apple?
(percussive music playing)
When we pitched my father Apple,
it was just so easy for him
to see this cash problem.
For a guy like that,
to show him just
those basic fundamentals
about a company, he just
started salivating right away.
Carl:
When Twitter came out,
I, I didn't even know
what it was, frankly.
And Michelle, she comes up
with great ideas.
She said, "You ought to have
a Twitter account."
I said, "Come on,
I'm not gonna do that."
She says, "No, no, you have
to have a Twitter account."
And then, when we bought Apple,
she said,
"Well, let me tweet that,
that you own Apple."
So I said, "Okay, do it."
Foroohar: I remember
the tweet distinctly.
And, you know, the markets
kind of went nuts immediately.
reporter:
Apple shares in focus
after Carl Icahn disclosed
in a tweet
that he purchased
$500 million of Apple stock.
reporter 2: ...trying to get
a piece of Apple stock...
reporter 3: Announced he had
taken this stake on Twitter,
and Apple shares shot up.
Lombardo:
Just from that tweet,
Apple's market value
jumped $17 billion.
Sorkin:
The view on Wall Street is,
what is Tim Cook gonna do
about this?
People wanna
appease Carl Icahn.
(trance music playing)
I think people couldn't fathom
that Carl Icahn was
having dinner with Tim Cook.
Tim Cook's visit to our home
for dinner
was a very exciting time.
We very carefully
went over the menu,
but I sort of like
to add my contribution.
For dessert, we had cookies
shaped in an apple shape
with another bite
taken out of it,
to symbolize (laughs)
the shareholders' investment.
(intense music playing)
Brett: So on the night
of the dinner with Tim Cook,
normally my father would
get there late, actually, but
I think he got there on time,
which is a huge compliment
to Tim Cook.
♪ ♪
We talked to Tim
about all the different stuff
going on within Apple.
You know,
anything that he could
tell us publicly, anyway.
And then eventually
the small talk evolved
into, "Hey, you should
buy back more stock."
Sorkin:
Carl clearly wanted to get Tim
to pursue
a massive buyback program.
And I think Tim wanted
to quiet the rhetoric.
♪ ♪
Carl: Now, I don't say every
company should do buybacks
for the purpose
of financial engineering.
In fact, it's overdone.
But in this case,
it was crazy for them
to have all of this cash around
and doing nothing with it.
Lombardo:
I think Carl expected to find
the typical resistant CEO
who he'd have to
a little bit strong-arm,
and Tim Cook sounds to have
been much more Zen about it.
reporter:
Apple said it had returned
74 billion to shareholders.
It plans to return 103 billion.
When I got the feeling
as an old poker player
that he wasn't really
displeased with the fact
that I was making a ruckus
about wanting to do a buyback.
I think he wanted
to do it himself,
but he had a board that was
rather reluctant to do it.
That's what I believe,
but he never said that.
I think the board
came around to doing it.
And that's how
those buybacks started.
Apple expanding
its capital return program
to $200 billion.
That was another billion five
right there.
Between Apple and Netflix,
we made for the company
about $3 billion,
and overall,
across all the investments,
over six years,
it was about 5 billion.
I'm really happy to make
my father that much money.
But I think I was worthy
of the Icahn name before that.
He made his father
billions of dollars.
He got his own hundreds
of millions of dollars payday
at the end,
and he even flirted
with the idea
of setting up his own firm.
Brett: Wait, wait,
we start it together.
Lombardo: There were
rumblings on Wall Street
for years that,
what would come of Carl Icahn
and Icahn Enterprises?
Would his son Brett take over?
Would he not?
Was there someone else
in the picture?
(engine puttering)
Brett: I think it was always
a complicated issue for me
because he has some big shoes
that I would have to walk in.
It's like, do you want
to spend your whole life
being compared to this
larger-than-life, you know,
greatest financier
of all time?
Um...
It's an issue.
Have you read the contract?
I mean, with you and Jesse,
what Jesse sent you?
-I've been reading it, yeah.
-Are you gonna get it
finished up?
-We got a lot to talk about.
-I know.
I asked Carl, "Is it true
that Brett will be coming back?"
And Carl said,
"You know, we've been trying
to negotiate a deal."
It's been over a year now,
though,
and the contract has already
stretched to 90 pages.
It sounds like he was
approaching this negotiation
with his son
the way he would
approach a business deal.
You should see what Jesse
did to the previous version.
I mean, it's like, uh...
a totally rewritten document.
Eh, he does that.
Jesse.
Oh, Jesse, poor Jesse.
(chuckles)
I think Carl and Brett
have a very similar style
of negotiation,
which makes it very tough
to mediate between them.
I think, you know,
Carl would readily admit,
I think he, uh, he trained
Brett a little too well.
You're cheating.
If you go through the trees,
it doesn't count.
Well, he's afraid.
I beat him.
I'm afraid? I won four races
and you only won one.
Big shot, listen, big shot.
I won one, you won two.
Am I Carl Icahn's
official successor?
I just don't know if I can
say the word officially.
(contemplative music playing)
-Carl: Oh, yeah, yeah.
-Gail: You're sittin'
in the egg.
Gail: We had this house
in Miami for a long time
and didn't use it very much.
But as time went on,
we decided that it was
a very nice lifestyle
to be able to live
here on this island.
It became clear that we
enjoyed it so much
that perhaps
we should think about
moving our offices
down here as well.
♪ ♪
(upbeat music playing)
That's down 160,
no, 160-- 100?
That's further down...
Gail: Thirty minutes that
it takes to get to the office,
it's a great time for him
to just collect his thoughts
when he's starting his day.
♪ ♪
And he loves
being on the water.
♪ ♪
Carl: "I began
my career on Wall Street
"nearly 50 years ago.
"From a modest upbringing
in Queens, New York,
I have been fortunate enough
to accumulate..."
Bill Gates:
I first met Carl Icahn
at a Giving Pledge dinner,
where we were bringing together
people who had large wealth.
♪ ♪
And Carl did agree
to join the pledge,
which means the majority
of his wealth
will go
to philanthropic causes.
You know, he helped me
with polio.
He supported his wife's
activities in charter schools.
Sorkin:
Carl's, to his credit,
been charitable.
But because money is his army,
and because he still enjoys
doing what he does
and he needs the money
to have the leverage,
he probably has not obviously
been able to give away
the majority of his wealth, yet.
What's the relationship
between the two halves
of this paradox?
On the one hand, you got
all these generous rich people,
on the other hand,
you have the fact
that it's an age of inequality,
an age of anger.
(intense music playing)
The 25 richest Americans
in federal income taxes,
they paid relatively little
and sometimes nothing.
The political narrative
right now is that
average Americans should look
at guys like Carl and say,
"Ah, they shouldn't have
that much money,"
and, all right, I don't know
whether Carl should
or shouldn't.
Carl:
The wealth gap between
the very rich
and the very poor
is getting wider and wider.
Part of it is the ridiculous
amount of money
that top management is paid
for doing a poor job.
Most CEOs are way overpaid.
That's not even a secret.
However, I have
no objection to people
that risk their own capital
for profit.
I mean,
what incentivizes people
is feeling they're
going to be rewarded.
The free enterprise system
is supposed to be there.
(intense digital music playing)
(elevator bell dings)
Carl:
Thank you.
-We need a piece here.
-Yeah.
A sculpture.
Do you like the paintings
on the wall?
Carl:
I think it's too many.
Too much.
How you doing?
Everything going good today?
man: Good, yeah.
We're going to have
you guys, the brain trust.
Talk to you later.
Brettsky.
♪ ♪
Carl and Brett
finally reach a deal
for Brett to return
to Icahn Enterprises.
If you just do it
pro rata yourself,
it doesn't really help out
your return very much.
Then it doesn't matter
about the 10%, then.
Lombardo: Brett will come
to Carl with investment ideas.
Carl will get the final say
over whether or not
they do them.
Anything that they invest in,
Brett has to put a little bit
of his own money in.
You might have this job.
Cara:
So Carl got comfortable
because he's
still squarely in charge.
Brett:
It's exciting.
It's as close to
an official succession plan
as you're gonna get,
and Carl Icahn
is gonna keep working
until he cannot work anymore,
and hopefully that's
a long time from now.
Carl: I like this.
-This is nice.
-Yeah. Very nice.
(Perry Como playing
"Catch a Falling Star")
♪ Catch a falling star ♪
♪ And put it in your pocket ♪
♪ Never let it fade away ♪
And they wanted me to settle,
everybody settles.
I said, "I'm not settling."
nephew:
Happy birthday.
Oh, let me see this.
That is the coolest thing.
-Las Vegas.
-I'm keeping--
-This is the coolest.
-Yeah, it's for you.
-Wait, um...
-Where is my office?
Mom told me that you rented
this place or something?
-Gail: He owned that place.
-He owned that.
I owned the Stratosphere!
(indistinct chatter)
♪ ♪
1978 is when
our paths crossed.
Hard to believe
it's 42 years ago...
Sorkin:
I think that Carl Icahn's had
a profound impact on society.
I think he has changed the way
boards of directors operate,
the way companies think...
Gail:
Cheers!
Sorkin:
...the way shareholders think.
I think all that
has been impacted
by Carl Icahn.
(intense music playing)
Foroohar:
I sometimes wonder
if peak Carl
doesn't represent
some kind of shift
in the direction of capitalism
in this country.
♪ ♪
Lombardo:
You can't deny that Carl
is a seminal figure
of capitalism
in the last 50 years.
He's a lot of different things
rolled up in one.
I think that's part
of the reason that people
are so captivated by him.
♪ ♪
Wapner:
Maybe some people
see Carl as everything
that's wrong
with the current system,
that people are becoming
too rich.
I think the other side
of that is that you could
make an argument that...
Carl Icahn is
capitalism at its best.
A guy who grew up with
not much,
who worked his butt off
and became one of the richest
men in the world.
-Carl: Oh, God, this is it.
-♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much.
-What, do I make a wish?
-Gail: You gotta make a wish.
♪ ♪
Carl: It's like Alexander
the Great, right?
He's 31 years old
and he won Persia.
To everybody in the world,
he was the best
and the greatest.
But he cried
because he didn't think
there was any place else
to go to do a battle.
He put his army together
and then he went to India.
The army all worshiped him,
but a lot of them deserted
'cause they said he's crazy.
He just kept going and going
till they killed him.
And I think about that.
I'm a little bit like that.
Just keep going at it.
Okay, I'll leave that there.
Okay, I think you got
everything.
Bruce:
We didn't get everything.
We got a lot...
Well, I'm not doing any more.
Don't even think about it.
Bruce: No, no, no.
For this, for right now,
we did everything.
Carl: No, what do you mean,
for right now? Wait a minute.
I'm not doing this.
(intense digital music playing)
So, one time they wanted
to build this terrace
behind my house.
My grandfather lived upstairs,
see, so he said,
"Look, if you give me bricks,
I'll build a terrace."
And my mother said, "We can't
afford to pay for bricks."
So I was tired of the arguing.
So I'm in this gang
with those hoodlums,
those friends of mine,
so I said,
"Get your wagons, guys,"
and they listened to me.
"Okay, Carl,
what are we doing?"
I said, "We're gonna
take bricks, see?
"Nobody will miss them because
we'll take three bricks here,
four bricks there."
"Okay, that's fun."
♪ ♪
So we come back
with all these bricks.
My grandfather's excited.
"This is great."
"I can build a terrace."
And my mother comes home,
says, "What is that?"
I say,
"They're bricks, Ma.
I got bricks for you
to build your terrace."
And she says, "We can't steal.
That is wrong."
I said, "You cut the bullshit."
I said, "You, first of all,
you keep talking about
you hate these builders, they're
all making too much money."
And she goes,
"Don't talk to me like that."
And my father says,
"Hey, who's gonna miss 'em?
They're not gonna miss 'em."
"Yeah... I guess they weren't
gonna use them anyway."
And we, "Here's the bricks,"
and we took 'em out.
That was it.
I just, I'll never forget that.
♪ ♪