["If You Don't Want My Love"
by Jalen Ngonda playing]
INSPIRED BY TRUE EVENTS
♪ In this night, a starry sky
My baby told me with a sigh ♪
♪ Saying words
That came across as a doubt ♪
♪ I reassured that every day
My love is strong in every place ♪
[announcer] Dear travelers,
the intercity arriving from Brussels
on platform one
has reached its final destination.
We kindly ask all passengers to disembark.
Don't forget to take
your luggage with you.
Dear travelers,
the intercity arriving from Brussels
has reached its final destination.
I'm coming, thank you.
♪ …keep us dear
Not just a day, but every year ♪
♪ You were made to be a focus in my mind ♪
♪ But if you don't want my love ♪
♪ And if you want somethin' more ♪
♪ Said if you never wanted my love ♪
♪ Let me know, oh ♪
-[man] Thank you.
-[woman] Okay, thank you.
That was OC. We have pickpockets
at Dam Square to clear out.
The locals reported it?
Yeah, annoying assholes.
[male officer chuckles]
Pickpockets. Seriously?
This is why I want to go
into investigations after this.
[female officer] Investigations?
You crazy?
All the action's on the street.
♪ You're not bound by a vow
Could be tomorrow or even now ♪
♪ If you want another scope
To look inside ♪
♪ I'll be the person… ♪
Hi.
♪ …or your lover in-between ♪
REPUBLIC OF BULGARIA
Welcome back, Mr. Petrov. How are you?
Still tired and broke.
That makes two of us.
-Coming for work again?
-Yeah.
♪ If you ever wanted my love ♪
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
[neon buzzing]
[door beeps]
[door closes]
[iPhone ringing]
PRESCRIPTION MEDICINE
Hey, sweetie.
[woman on phone] Hey, my love.
You get there safe?
I did, the train ride was easy,
just a little long. You know.
I can barely hear you. Am I on speaker?
Yeah. I think I lost my earbuds.
Oh, no. Well, that sucks.
You're telling me.
Why don't you just buy some new ones,
babeche?
Good idea.
I mean, you'll be there for a while.
You'll need some earbuds.
Mm-hm.
Hopefully I find them.
Before I forget, I picked up
the application packet this morning.
What application?
For that apartment.
It's a new building.
They said that if we hurry
and put down a deposit,
we can have first pick.
Deposit. Where's that money coming from?
[music playing in background]
Are you upset?
It's all right.
I'm just sad that I lost my earbuds.
Yeah, I get it.
["Feeling Good" by Michael Bublé playing]
Hey…
-♪ And I'm feeling… ♪
-Do you hear that?
[chuckles]
-♪ Good ♪
-Yeah.
[song continues]
I miss you already, babeche.
Call you later tonight, okay?
Sounds good, babeche.
Can't wait, talk to you later tonight.
♪ Fish in the sea
You know how I feel ♪
♪ River running free
♪ Blossom on a tree
You know how I feel ♪
♪ It's a new dawn
It's a new day ♪
-Welcome. No problem.
-Thanks.
♪ …life for me ♪
[Ilian] Hi.
Hi, welcome in.
I'm looking for AirPods.
Okay, sure.
[indistinct chatter]
-Yes, uh, he will help you with that.
-Okay, thank you.
[female worker] Mm-hm.
[customers chattering]
[elevator dings]
Lukas.
-Hey, um… We ran a diagnostic for you.
-Is it done for?
[laughs] That isn't it.
You need a battery replacement.
-How can I help?
-Uh, I'm looking for AirPods.
AirPods? Sure. Uh…
I have some in the back.
All right. I got you.
[woman sighs]
So if you want, we can install
a new battery for you today.
It'll be pretty much
good as new after that.
-How long to install the battery?
-Ten minutes. Promise.
-Sure. Let's do it.
-Yeah?
-Sounds good, just a second.
-Mm-hm.
Mom, don't act like a Karen, please.
[mom sighs]
Would you like the latest edition
or the edition before that?
-Uh, latest one.
-Latest one, sure.
-I'll grab it for you.
-Thank you.
[male police officer] You know what
the best part of an all-you-can-eat is?
You always eat enough.
It doesn't cost a lot.
You know what the catch about it is?
If you order too much and don't eat it,
they make you pay for it.
And that's how they get their money.
Yeah, well I'm sticking to eating salads.
-[ominous music playing]
-[indistinct chatter]
Here you go.
[card machine beeps]
Have a great day.
[heavy footsteps echoing]
Welcome in. How can I help you?
I'm sorry, sir,
but you can't leave your belongings there.
-Everyone on the ground.
-[breathing heavily]
I need you all on the ground.
This is my store now.
-Everyone on the ground.
-[patron screaming]
No one leave the building.
Everyone, get down on the ground.
Nobody leaves here!
I said lay down on the ground!
-[panicked chatter]
-[tense music playing]
Nobody's listening.
[panicked footsteps]
[breathing heavily]
[muffled screaming]
Go, go.
[breathing heavily]
[hostage taker] You better listen to me!
Are you deaf?
They're running. No one's listening.
-Here. Come on, hurry up.
-[woman crying]
Everyone stays inside.
Get down on the ground.
Lie face down, now!
Don't run! Hey, where are you going?
-[gun shots]
-[screaming]
You should make a complaint
to the council, not us.
I hate to be rude, but…
[hostage taker] No one leaves the store.
Hey!
-Stay inside and no one gets hurt!
-[breathing heavily]
-Get down on the ground! All of you, now!
-Follow me, hurry.
-[tense music playing]
-[hostage taker] Hey!
-I see you, stop moving.
-[breathing heavily]
I said stop!
[panicked screaming in distance]
-OC, emergency!
-[woman] Go ahead,14-11.
[female officer] People are running out
of the Apple Store.
Suspected robbery. Shots have been fired.
-[operator] Shots fired?
-[male officer] Move!
Officers downtown are requesting backup
from any units in the area
for a suspected armed robbery
at the Apple Store in Leidseplein.
-[female officer] Keep running!
-Get inside!
I still don't have eyes on the situation.
There's a lot of bystanders.
Everyone, move away!
Get away, run! Go inside. Go inside.
Stay inside! Clear the area!
[screaming]
-Stay inside!
-Everyone move. Move! Move!
[hostage taker] Listen to me,
and no one gets killed!
-You understand?
-[door beeps]
No sudden movements!
Stay there, get down. On the ground!
[tense music continues]
[worker] In the closet.
-Come on.
-[hostage taker] I'm in charge now.
[panicked breathing]
Nobody goes outside.
[breathing shakily]
[panel beeps]
[hostage taker]
Don't leave! Get back here!
[breathing heavily]
-[male officer] Hey, you! Move!
-[female officer] Out of the way, move!
[breathing heavily]
[music fades]
[muffled screaming in background]
[breathing heavily]
[pop music playing faintly]
Hands, bro.
Hands.
What?
[gun clicks]
Put your hands behind your back,
stay down and shut the fuck up, okay?
[Ilian breathing heavily]
[tense, quirky music playing]
Okay, don't move.
[sirens wailing in distance]
[both panting shakily]
It's one man. He has a weapon,
camouflage clothing.
Send more units.
OC, he's wearing an explosive vest.
[breathing heavily]
Stay down, bro.
Jesus.
OC, we're being shot at.
When is our backup arriving?
Close all of Leidseplein off.
Where's the DSI?
Ten minutes out.
-Injured, dead? How many armed?
-We only know of one man.
Robbery, attack, terrorism?
What should I say?
Who should report?
Everyone.
[phone vibrating]
This is Winston.
-Yes, understood.
-[sighs]
I need a few seconds.
Hey.
Give dad a hug. Mm. I'll be right back.
I love you guys.
-[boy] You'll be back soon?
-You bet.
Okay.
I love you.
I know.
Bye.
Hey.
Be careful.
I will.
[tense music playing]
[siren wailing]
[man] Here.
[dog barks]
[operator] Call for all available units.
Priority one incident at Leidseplein.
Operation instructions to follow.
14-11, the DSI are on their way.
Stay back and keep cover.
[man] Code silver on Leidseplein.
[sirens wailing]
Attention all units,
do not enter Leidseplein.
Close off all access roads.
No one is to enter Leidseplein.
I repeat, Leidseplein is being closed off.
If you're arriving on site,
we're recommending you use Kevlar vests.
-CCTR, can you hear me?
-[man] Yes.
All cameras on the Apple Store.
-[man] I'm on it.
-Stand by.
-[music fades]
-[birds tweeting]
[phone ringing]
[clears throat]
Excuse me.
-Yeah?
-Kees, it's Karina.
We need you at operation control ASAP.
Shit's hit the fan
Possible hostage situation
in the Apple Store.
I'm on my way.
[suspenseful music playing]
Checkmate.
Sorry, man, duty calls.
-[breathing heavily]
-[distant sirens]
[hostage taker] Bro. Bro.
Stand up.
Stand up, bro.
Come on.
[Ilian panting]
Let's take a walk.
[sirens wailing]
[sirens get louder]
I want a negotiator.
I'm ready to talk.
I said go get me a negotiator.
Or I'll blow this whole block up.
What's your problem?
Stop hiding! Stop hiding!
-[gunshot fires]
-Fuck.
With me. Come on.
[tense music playing]
Sit. Sit.
Stay there.
[breathing heavily]
[pop music playing faintly]
[breathing shakily]
Sir?
Am I gonna die?
You just listen. Don't talk, okay?
INTAKE + TASKFORCE
112 Police.
What's the location of your emergency?
[hostage taker] I'm in the store
right now.
In the Apple Store.
I have demands.
I want to talk to a negotiator.
Sorry, repeat that, who are you?
I'm the hostage taker.
Get a negotiator on the phone.
A mediator. Someone I can trust.
Stop pretending.
I'm dead serious.
Get me someone who can handle this.
-Karina? He's on the phone.
-Don't play with me.
Or this whole place goes up.
Hello? Are you there? Hello!
Yeah. I'm here. I'm here.
You want to speak to a negotiator,
do I have that right?
Yeah, are you fucking deaf?
I want to negotiate.
Just a minute
while we find you a negotiator.
That's good.
You have my number now, right?
You can call me from now on. Okay?
[tense music playing]
They're gonna call me back.
[music intensifies]
[whispering] What shall we do?
[breathing shakily]
-We have to get out of here.
-[whispering] Ma'am, wait.
We have to be really quiet, okay?
He doesn't know we're in here
so if we're quiet he won't hear us.
Wait, ma'am.
We're all dead if you open that door.
Mom, we can't leave.
[mom sighing]
[breathing heavily]
Does anyone have their phone?
It's sitting out there.
Oh, man.
-Can I use your phone?
-Yeah.
[connection tone]
112 Police.
What's the location of your emergency?
[whispering] Hi, my name's Mingus.
Um, there's a group of us
in a closet in the Apple Store.
There's a man here with a machine gun.
You said you're in a closet
in the Apple Store?
Where in the store?
[Mingus] The ground floor,
across from the elevator.
I work here.
I snuck people into the closet.
[operator] Okay.
How many people are with you?
[Mingus] Four.
[operator] Are you safe in there?
Um…
Mingus?
-Hello?
-[quietly] No.
Okay. Can anyone see you?
Does anyone know you're in there?
No. The door's locked
and it can only be opened with a key card.
[tapping on keyboard]
Okay, got it.
And have you seen the assailants, Mingus?
How many are there?
-Fuck. I think it's just one guy, right?
-Yeah.
Yeah, one. He fired a gun.
But I also saw people run upstairs,
to the Genius area.
[operator] Thank you, Mingus,
we know about the people
who escaped upstairs.
They've been in contact with us already.
[whimpering]
The most important thing you can do now
is not attract attention, okay?
Our team is outside.
Just be patient, we're gonna get
this situation under control.
Just give us time.
[pilot 1] Leidseplein is on the left.
[pilot 2] Yes, I put it on the left
so you have a nice line of sight.
[pilot 1] Zulu has arrived
and we have eyes on the square.
You're good to go in, OC.
We can see the two officers in the square.
Let's get them out of there.
-[indistinct radio chatter]
-[dramatic music playing]
Hey, they're trapped.
They're pinned down over there.
Uh, 80-14 OC.
Our officers are trapped in front.
They're sitting ducks right now.
If they can't come to us,
we'll go to them. We're moving in.
[male officer]
All officers are standing by.
OC, the vehicle is heading
toward the Hirsch building.
[dramatic music continues]
The situation's stable,
but things could escalate.
Keep everyone as far away as you can.
[music fades]
[helicopter whirring]
Come, bro, come. Come!
Come. Come here. Come on.
-[tense music playing]
-[helicopter whirring]
Ready?
[indistinct radio chatter]
[officer] The officers are
walking alongside the SUV.
[tense music continues]
[hostage taker] Come here.
Don't try anything stupid, okay?
Sit.
So they can see you.
[pop music playing faintly]
My name is Ilian.
I'm from Bulgaria.
Hey. I don't care, man.
[woman] Get everyone off
the streets, understood?
Keep 'em on the line.
-Hey.
-Okay, talk to me.
We know that there's a man
inside the Leidseplein Apple Store
with an automatic weapon.
He's fired several times,
but no one's hurt.
Four people have hidden in a closet
on the ground floor
across from the elevator.
As far as we know he has one hostage,
and there are people trapped
on the floor above.
-There's 40 or 50 of them.
-Okay.
Have they called in?
Are we sure it's not a hostage situation?
Yeah, we have them on the line.
For now they're safe,
he doesn't know that they're there.
-We'll have a problem if he goes upstairs.
-Okay.
Our first priority is getting them out.
-Comms check. Valerie, can you hear me?
-Yes, Kees. I hear you.
And he's requested a negotiator.
-A negotiator, is that right?
-Yeah.
That's a first for me.
-Where do you want the command center?
-Here.
Have routine updates go to Zaanstad.
We'll run it from here.
The negotiators will go in there.
His number.
-[Kees] What's this?
-You have to call him.
The mayor's on vacation
and the commissioner's on his way.
-Now I'm an operator?
-It's what the protocol says.
My concern is the hostages,
arresting this guy and getting them out.
Kees? The DSI's closing in. One minute.
-[sirens wailing]
-[helicopter whirring]
[tense music playing]
POLICE
[radios beeping]
-[Winston] Comms check.
-[man 1 on radio] Radio check.
-[man 2 on radio] Radio check.
-[man] Winston?
-[Winston] Hey, who's in charge?
-Double Zero.
Holy shit. Double Zero?
Welcome, Winston. Sorry for calling you.
[Winston] Tell that to the wife.
I'll send Maya flowers
when this is all over, deal?
[Winston] Flowers? You'll need to buy
Keukenhof to make up for this one, chief.
Listen, there's about 40 people
trapped on the floor above the store.
We need to get them out of there ASAP.
Once we have the floor plan, I want
a tactical analysis. Then we're going in.
Not before.
-Hey.
Team Alpha, prepare for entry.
Bravo and Charlie will take
things over from the officers
on the ground.
We're covering the whole scene.
Priority, evacuate
all retailers and offices. Understood?
[Winston] Okay, copy.
Guys, we've got to get
these officers out of here. Let's go.
[suspenseful music playing]
Fall back. Fall back.
[indistinct radio chatter]
-We have the building layout?
-Some floors are missing.
Wait, what floors are missing?
The Apple Store itself.
We can't track them down.
[sirens wailing]
Call America, get us a higher up at Apple.
I want those floor plans now. Understand?
-[sniper 1] Delta in position.
-[indistinct radio chatter]
[sniper 2] Echo in position.
Hey, Abe. Glad you could make it.
Kees, the negotiators
are on their way in now.
Have fun with that. I'm going to Leidse.
[pilot 1] Leidseplein Square
on the left at ten o'clock.
[pilot 2] Holding off for now.
[pilot 1] Yes, OC, we'll descend slightly
and keep an appropriate distance.
[music continues]
[breathing heavily]
[keyboard tapping]
-Okay, Lynn, you're number one.
-What's the situation?
He has hostages, motive unknown.
We think it's just the one guy.
Okay. So is that everything?
You should know that he asked
for a negotiator almost immediately.
He insisted on it.
-Where's our set up at?
-There.
In this circus?
Ugh, I get it, but I want us all together.
It's the plan, for now.
We're not sure
if snipers can hit him or not,
the glass at the store is really thick.
Be aware that there are
explosives attached to him.
And he's holding a detonator.
So taking him out from a distance
isn't an option.
This also means letting him leave
with explosives can't be an option.
He needs to come out without explosives,
or we bide our time,
he'll crumble if we wear him down.
I'll get him out. Promise you that.
Lynn.
Make it happen.
[suspenseful music playing]
[tires screech]
[indistinct chatter]
OC? Double Zero at the scene.
Comms check.
Echo, Bravo, can we evacuate yet?
[sniper 1] Check, almost done.
Hey. Everyone ready?
[Winston] We're just waiting
for the floor plans. Any word?
-Not yet.
-[Winston] Fuck.
-Is that him?
-[Winston] Yeah.
-Get to your stations.
-[Winston] Copy.
[music crescendoes then stops]
LEIDSEPLEIN GRIPPED BY HOSTAGE SITUATION
APPLE STORE ROCKED BY VIOLENCE
[breathing heavily]
[pop music playing faintly]
-Wilco.
-Lynn.
-Rachelle.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[pop music playing faintly]
Sorry, sir.
Sir?
Sir, I need my medicine.
Why? What medicine?
I need to take it three times a day.
They're in my backpack.
[exhales sharply]
CALLING…
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing and vibrating]
-Yeah?
-This is Lynn, with the police department.
You asked for a negotiator, right?
That's right.
[call disconnects]
[Lynn] Huh?
[scoffs] He wants us to know
who the boss is?
[tense music continues]
Yes, those.
[can opens]
[pop music playing faintly]
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
Sorry, sir?
My hands, they really hurt.
Turn around.
[hostage taker grunts]
-[Ilian] Thank you. Thank you so much.
-Shut up! Shut up!
Give me your hands.
Keep your hands behind your back.
-[Ilian] Thank you for the medicine.
-I said shut up.
Shut it!
Stay down, and shut the fuck up.
[phone dialing out]
[phone ringing]
Lynn speaking.
[hostage taker] Yeah, hello.
Hi, I'm happy you called us back.
You asked for a negotiator.
-Isn't that right?
-Yeah, that's right.
-That's me. My name's Lynn.
-Yeah, you said that.
-Twice already.
-Can I have your name?
That doesn't matter.
Make something up.
You're going to find out eventually.
[Lynn] Okay.
We can talk about anything.
Shouldn't I just tell you
what you can do for me?
Huh?
Isn't that what this is all about? Right?
-Come on.
-[whispers] He's coming.
[hostage taker chuckles]
Do you think I'm stupid, is that it?
[Lynn] Well, I think we have
a situation here
and we should try
to get out of it together.
[hostage taker] I don't have a situation.
You've got a situation.
Let me tell you exactly what I want.
-My demands.
-[Lynn] That's why I called.
[hostage taker] Yeah? Okay.
I want 200 million in Bitcoin
and free passage.
200 million?
Yeah. What?
You're not hard of hearing, are you?
[Lynn muffled] No.
I just wanted to make sure
I heard you correctly.
I mean, it's a big sum, right?
It's a big sum?!
Is that a joke? That's nothing to you.
That's pocket change to you people.
Not to me, and as payment
for you've done to me,
200 million is nothing.
I'm letting you off easy.
Listen, I've got enough explosives
to incinerate this plaza, you understand?
-I understand, we--
-[phone disconnects]
Hung up.
Lay down, stay on the ground.
[tense, somber music playing]
He said he's going to blow up the plaza.
[mom sighs]
Fuck. I shouldn't even be here.
You kept me waiting here
for that fucking laptop.
If you had kept your mouth shut,
I wouldn't even be here now.
Were you helping him?
[sighs]
Hey.
-Yeah?
-[mom] Enough.
This won't help us get out of here.
[girl] What are you talking about?
He wasn't helping him.
It wasn't his fault, all right?
[ominous music playing]
[music intensifies]
Sir?
-[music fades]
-[helicopter whirring]
Excuse me, sir.
What?
You spoke to the police just now?
What did they say?
How much money do you want?
A lot.
Okay?
Enough to pay everything.
You know why?
Because they all tried to fuck me.
The police,
the justice department, the government.
They all tried to fuck me.
My life is over!
They, they ruined my fucking life!
They all tried to fuck me!
I understand.
But, please,
I don't want to fuck with you, brother.
[tense music playing]
No.
You won't fuck with me.
But you know why you won't?
If you try something,
I will kill you.
And if they try something,
I will blow up this whole building.
My brother.
Smile.
[camera clicks]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[music continues]
[Kees] What's this?
-How'd we get this?
-It appears he sent it in to AT5 just now.
-Don't let this photo go public, okay?
-Yeah, on it.
[Kees] Abe, I just sent you a photo.
-Is the bomb squad there?
-Fuck.
[whistles]
We need to know the type of explosive.
-Can you get a confirmation?
-[Abe] Stand by.
Well?
From this photo,
they look like fake explosives.
Fake?
-They won't explode then?
-I wouldn't hinge it on a photo.
-It's not that simple.
-Your advice isn't helpful, as usual.
[sighs] I'm just telling you what I see.
Do we know what's
in the other bags he has in there?
No. Why?
Let's say a detonation happens.
And he's hidden explosives inside them.
-[Abe] The Apple Store is blown up?
-Not just the Apple Store.
I'd get my men further back if I were you.
You'll never be me.
You hear that, Kees?
I heard it.
[Winston] Stop.
-[pounds on hood]
-That's good.
-[Winston] Chief.
-Hey.
Okay. I need two plans.
One, get the people upstairs out
as quickly and as quietly as possible.
-[Winston] Okay.
-Two, we rush in through the ground floor.
He's wearing explosives.
No idea if they're real or not.
We can't really tell from out here.
We know he has one hostage
and four people are holed up
in a closet
on the ground floor behind him.
[Winston] He doesn't know?
Not yet.
-[Mingus breathing heavily]
-[music fades]
[whispering] I'm sorry.
I was just trying to help you.
I had no idea that--
No, it's okay.
None of this is your fault, I know that.
I'm sorry that I said it. I was angry.
My name's Mingus, by the way.
Lukas.
[whispering] I'm Bente.
I'm Soof.
And this is my… [crying softly]
…daughter.
So, Mingus, do you have kids?
Yeah, a son.
Nigel, he's really…
[chuckles softly]
He's a great little guy.
We were gonna see Ajax tonight.
[Soof] How about you?
-Any kids?
-No.
I've got a great girlfriend, but, um…
It's just, uh…
Yeah, it's a bit complicated.
Tonight we had plans
to get dinner together.
[gentle music playing]
She's probably wondering where I am.
[sighs] We'll have another fight now.
[chuckles softly]
-[music continues]
-[beeping]
[dramatic music playing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[sighs]
[phone ringing]
[phone vibrating]
-Hello?
-Mingus, this is Mark.
I'm with the police.
I'm going to be your contact person
from now on, okay?
I'm very close by. I just parked
on Leidseplein opposite the store.
[Mingus] Okay.
How is everyone holding up?
[whispering] We're all right. Just scared.
He must have hostages right?
If he didn't,
you guys would have gone in by now.
Yes, we're in contact with him.
Negotiators are working with him now.
We're doing our best to get this over with
as soon as we can, Mingus.
We're setting aside this line
for you to call, but stay quiet.
Okay.
I hope he doesn't know we're in here.
[Mark] I don't think he does,
as far as what we can gather.
And there's music in the store,
so that helps.
Shit.
Not for long.
Why'd you say not for long?
The music turns off at closing time,
at nine o'clock.
And the alarm goes off
if there are people inside.
[Mark] Okay.
Do you know if there's a way to keep
the lights and music on for longer?
The security's automatic
and they run it from America.
[Mark] Okay, I'll look into it.
Put your phone on silent,
and on low-battery mode.
Don't use anything
that could use up battery. Okay?
Okay.
[radio beeps]
Kees, we need to contact Apple.
The security system's on a timer.
So the lights and music inside
will shut off and the alarm will trigger.
[phone ringing]
[pop music playing faintly]
Is the money ready?
Listen, there's a chance that
you're going to lose the lights and music.
Normally the store closes now,
since you're walking around,
it could set the alarm off, all right?
But that's not us, okay?
It happens automatically,
just know it's normal.
Come. Come. Come on. Get up.
[tense music playing]
[hostage taker] Stay calm.
This whole block will go up in flames.
Don't lie to me, Lynn.
Don't lie to me, okay?
[Lynn] I'm not lying to you.
You can trust me.
It's automatic security.
Just keep talking to me when it goes off.
-Please don't.
-[Lynn] You have to trust me.
Don't do this, sir.
[Lynn] It happens every night.
We don't control the alarm.
Sorry, can you tell us
what happens to the lights after nine?
[Lynn] It's just the lights and the music.
It's an automatic system.
We have no control over the alarm.
I'm married, sir.
Please don't do this.
Don't do this, sir.
Please. Please don't do this.
Please.
[lights shut off]
[pilot 1] The alarm system will activate,
don't move in, hold your positions.
[pilot 2] Everyone stay on alert,
something might happen.
OC. We're keeping a safe distance.
[Lynn] Stay with me, okay?
Everything is okay.
Stay calm. Nothing is gonna happen.
[lights buzz]
[breathing heavily]
The lights are on.
And no alarm. You lied.
I didn't, I was telling you the truth.
-I don't--
-[phone disconnects]
Shit.
What the hell, Kees, you have me lying?
I'm trying to gain his trust.
Please hold the line. Kees!
[woman] Apple took care of it.
The music and lights are staying on.
They're transferring
the feed from their cameras to us.
Okay, great. And the floor plans?
There's a separate department
that holds all the floor plans. Protocol.
It could be minutes,
couple of hours, they'll get back to us.
-They're doing their best.
-[man] We've got the feed from the store.
[typing angrily]
Can you call him back?
I don't think he trusts you.
After that call.
I can gain his trust back.
[sighs]
[phone ringing out]
[ominous music playing]
[phone ringing]
[ringing stops]
-[hostage taker] Yeah?
-Hey.
You holding up all right?
Why wouldn't I be?
Well, you hung up on me.
[hostage taker] You lied.
I don't like that.
That's fair. I'd feel the same way.
I'm going off the information I get here.
They said that after nine,
you'd lose lights and music.
-That you'd set off the alarm.
-Hm.
I thought it'd be better
if I let you know.
In case you got scared.
Okay.
Is my money ready yet?
I can confirm that we are working
really hard to get it done.
I want it in Bitcoin, okay?
You do know what a Bitcoin is, right?
Yeah, of course I know.
Hey, I, uh, I'm just realizing you…
you never told me what your name is.
I mean, it just feels so impersonal.
Double A. From now on call me Double A.
Okay, thank you. Double E, cool name.
No, wait. Not… No, no, no, no, no, no.
Not E. A.
Double A, are you deaf?
A as in angels. Double A.
Did you forget English?
No, I can still speak English.
Despite being born
right here in Amsterdam.
How about you, are you from here?
Yeah, the way you speak.
Sounds like you're from here.
Listen, it's not about me.
This is about you
and what you can do for me, understood?
We'll talk about resolving this.
I really hope we can work together
and come to an agreement, Double A.
[Double A] Oh yeah?
Who says I want to resolve this?
Well, I assume that you want to.
You want something, right?
[Double A] What I want is simple.
200 million in Bitcoin
and a way out of here.
Then this can be over.
And what are you thinking,
Double A, for a way out of there?
What's the plan?
A fast luxury car,
and free passage to the A10.
To the A10?
Then what?
You make a promise
that after we leave nobody will follow us.
-We'll make a clean getaway.
-We?
Me and my friend here.
[Lynn] Your friend?
-You want him to go with you?
-Want?
He's coming.
Once I'm safe and you're not following me,
I'll let him go.
Listen.
You've been in there a while now.
You must be getting hungry or thirsty,
or maybe he is?
I gave him a drink.
It was for his medicine.
Oh, that's very nice to hear.
Thanks for looking after him.
What kind of medicine was it?
Your medicine.
-What is the name of your medicine?
-Lisonopril. For my heart.
[Lynn] Okay.
Aren't you concerned for him?
Since he's so sick?
You should be concerned for him instead.
Deliver on what I want,
and we'll all get out of here.
My friend here, he doesn't look that sick.
The pain is in his heart.
You can't see it on the outside.
Yeah, all the more reason to get my money.
Otherwise, it'll take even longer
and if something happens to him then,
that's your fault then, friend.
[scoffs] My fault?
That's a stretch there, friend.
I'm not the one who stormed in
with weapons and took a hostage.
That was you.
Yeah, okay.
Good point, I'll give you that.
Kees?
EMPLOYEES AND CUSTOMERS
ARE TRAPPED UPSTAIRS
[Kees] Oh, God.
IN THE CANTEEN.
STAY TUNED FOR UPDATES!
What's their location?
I assume it's from someone
upstairs in the Apple Store.
It's already posted
on websites and socials.
Shit.
Abe, report.
[Abe] I'm listening.
There's an idiot
who just posted on social media
that people are trapped upstairs.
[Abe] Shit.
Getting people out is our top priority.
If he finds out
those people are upstairs…
Then we'll have 40 more hostages'
lives put at risk.
Get them out of there.
It's risky, but let's go in now.
Get those posts taken down
as soon as possible.
Understood.
Get me the network providers.
[whispering] What the hell's
taking so long?
-[Mark] Mingus?
-[Mingus] Yeah.
[Mark] Listen. We're doing our best
to get the store's floor plans,
but we don't have them yet.
We have to go in now
to get the people upstairs to safety.
Is there a quick way to get upstairs?
[whispering] The rear exit,
because it's also connected to next door.
You can get to the other building.
You can cross over to the back.
I can create a map of where it is.
[Mark] Incredible. Please do.
-Send it ASAP if you can.
-Right.
What are you doing?
[beep]
[dramatic music playing]
[Winston] I got it.
Hey, guys, gather around.
We're about to enter
via the south side of the Hirsch building.
We know there's an armed tango downstairs.
We don't know if he's acting alone.
There are 40 sierras upstairs.
We gotta get them out. Quietly.
This is the situation, got it?
Stay focused in there, okay?
Let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
Lynn, keep him on the line, okay?
Everyone, DSI's going in.
Ma'am, this is serious, I need you to--
Kees.
Intake four.
The girl who posted that message
refuses to remove it, I've tried.
Who is she?
Some influencer who insists
I call her the "opinion maker" now.
Call her back.
[phone rings out]
Yeah, Kees van Zanten. General Commander
of the Amsterdam Police.
Did you mention people
in the Apple Store in a post?
You have no idea how many innocent lives
are at risk because of you,
you stupid little shit.
My patience has run thin.
If that post isn't down
in the next ten seconds,
I will personally send an arrest team
to drag you out of your apartment
with a sack
over your goddamn stupid head!
Is that clear to you?
Is it clear or not?!
Okay, do it then!
[phone beeps]
[Lynn] I'm curious.
What happened today that upset you?
And caused you to do this?
[Winston] Okay, tactical formation.
[Double A] Don't you get it?
It's not about what happened today.
It's been happening for a while.
The injustice you have constantly
subjected me to, that's what it's about.
[Winston] Okay.
You know all about it.
It's all of you
and your infamous Bermuda triangle.
[Winston] NVGs.
[Double A] The public prosecutor,
the police, the law.
-[Winston] Get ready.
-You've abused me.
[keypad beeping]
You handcuffed me,
you threw me on the floor in a cell.
You have wronged me.
One day it has to stop.
Finally, that day has arrived.
That's why I've demanded
the money from you.
I want you to pay me off.
And I'll go away.
Since I don't matter to anyone anyway.
No one here cares.
But I do matter, just watch me.
-Okay, friend?
-[Lynn] I'm listening.
I'm working hard to get the money.
I swear.
You have no choice, though.
Or are you trying to say
you care about me?
You'll be going home after this,
to your boyfriend, your child, whatever.
I want you to stay alive
and you do matter.
There are people who care about you.
I'm sure of that, and they want to see you
come out of this unharmed.
I care about you.
About getting you out of there safely.
Double A.
It's Ammar.
[dramatic music playing]
Okay.
Ammar.
Thank you.
Like I said, I'm here for you. Okay?
But also for the man in there.
That man who's with you.
He doesn't have anything to do with this,
he went to the store
looking for something to buy.
He must be terrified too, don't you think?
What's your play?
[Lynn] I'm not playing games.
I just want to know how he's doing.
Ammar Ajar? A-J-A-R. First name Ammar.
Bus driver. You said you remembered him
from the bus?
Date of birth? April 21st '95.
Ma'am, I'm connecting you to an officer,
don't hang up.
Take over. Channel five.
Harry, big screen, now.
Ammar Ajar.
Born in Amsterdam, roots in Syria.
A few misdemeanors.
He went back to Syria as a child.
He suffers from psychiatric problems.
That's him.
You're watching, right?
Yeah.
I am. We have access
to the cameras, Ammar.
I can see you.
Then you'll see what happens
if my bitcoin isn't delivered.
[Lynn] What I've seen so far
is that you're looking after him.
That's really nice.
[dramatic music playing]
It's kind of you, Ammar.
You even gave him a cigarette.
It seemed to… to help him calm down.
Yeah, yeah.
He's only…
[Lynn] He's only human.
I agree with you.
[Ammar] Yeah, right.
[Lynn] Exactly, he's only human,
like you and me.
[Winston] You can open it.
Go. Police. Police, get back.
Hands on your head.
Hands on your head. Back up.
[music intensifies]
Bravo for Double Zero. Space is clear.
No tangos, only sierras. Standby for evac.
Move. Keep it moving. Okay, clear.
[Ilian coughing]
I'm done talking for now, Lynn.
[music fades]
[sighs]
She talks too much.
She's giving me a headache.
[tense music playing]
-Mingus?
-[Mingus] Yeah?
[Mark] Those people are safe. We were able
to get everyone out of the upper floor.
You made that happen, Mingus,
so thank you.
-We're working hard to get you out, okay?
-[Mingus] Okay.
Mark, how long is this gonna take?
We're doing our very best, Mingus.
Trust me.
They're still working on it.
[sighs]
[music intensifies]
[Abe] Great work, team. Thank you.
Get the boys together. There's coffee
and we've ordered a hundred pizzas.
-How are the negotiations going?
-He's totally unpredictable.
It's gonna take a while.
[watch beeps]
Don't worry, I'll buy the Keukenhof.
Now, take a break. Pizza's coming.
[music settles]
[phone ringing]
Is that yours?
That's my wife.
[Ammar] Wanna talk to her?
-[phone continues to ring]
-[breathes heavily]
[breathing shakily]
[ringing stops]
[somber music playing]
[all breathing heavily]
[footsteps approach]
You're not Bruce Lee.
[breathing heavily]
It's so hot.
You know,
my wife wants me to buy an apartment.
Which we can never afford, so…
I'm here to work.
A couple of months. [sniffs]
I earn some money.
It's not enough, but…
but I love her.
[sniffs]
And if she wants that apartment…
I will do my best, you know, for…
for her, for us.
She's so worried right now.
Don't you have someone
who's worried about you?
I'm not worth worrying about.
It's my own fault.
I could also get a gun.
Go in a store and take someone hostage.
But it will always be
the wrong hostage. Always.
Someone who doesn't deserve
to be so scared, or killed.
I didn't deserve
to be treated the way I was.
I understand that. I know the feeling.
They treat you like shit.
The government.
You pay everything they want you to pay.
But still they come after you
with all these extra taxes.
And you end up having nothing.
I know that.
Here…
Here, I'm nothing.
But somewhere, with that money, I am…
I will be like a king.
I will help people
who are in the same situation as me.
I will be like, like a Robin Hood king.
You know Robin Hood, right?
I'll see if that money makes me happy.
I'm honestly afraid
that you'll never make it.
They might shoot you.
This is probably
the worst place you could have picked.
I'm not afraid.
I have you.
You have me, yeah.
But let's say
they won't give you the money.
You'll kill me, and then what?
Then they win.
And they will lose.
Do you want coffee?
Sure.
Mingus?
He's slowly coming towards you.
Make sure everyone remains silent.
-[groaning]
-Shh! Mom, stay still.
[Mingus breathing heavily]
[breathing heavily]
He's coming.
Hit him with this if he comes in. Okay?
Where does it hurt?
My heart.
[coffee machine whirs]
[fire extinguisher clunks]
-[Soof groans]
-Mommy. Mom.
-Mark.
-[Mark] Yeah.
Soof isn't doing well.
What's wrong?
She's fading fast.
[Soof groans]
Her hand's over her breast.
My girl…
Kees, Abe, a woman in the closet
may be having a heart attack.
This could be a serious problem.
Lynn?
-Call him and keep him talking.
-Yeah.
Officer. We need
to get a doctor over here. Right now.
-[officer] Yes. Understood.
-Okay.
[indistinct radio chatter]
They need you there.
[phone ringing]
Hi, Lynn. We're on a coffee break.
Ah, that's good to hear.
How you holding up?
-[Mingus] Mark?
-I'm listening.
I've spoken with Kees.
If it's a serious heart attack,
we're going in immediately.
But only if it's life-threatening,
because my men would be at serious risk.
Understood, got it.
-Hi.
-Hey.
-Help give us a diagnosis here.
-Okay.
[Mark] Mingus,
I have a doctor here with me.
[doctor] Is she unconscious or awake?
[whispering] She's still awake.
[doctor] Is it radiating pain?
-Is it radiating pain?
-Nah-ah.
Shh.
No, it isn't.
He's becoming a problem, you know?
He really wants to get back to his wife.
He's scared.
He's worrying more and more.
Yeah, I can imagine.
[Ammar] Yeah, well you
should be worried too.
Sooner or later
you'll have to call his wife
to tell her her husband's not coming home.
Let's not go there just yet.
We're still talking this through.
[doctor] Is she sweating?
Are her lips blue?
[Mingus] She's sweating, yeah,
but her lips aren't blue.
[doctor] Can you feel her heartbeat?
The Apple Watch is equipped
with a heart monitor. I can measure it.
[doctor] Go ahead.
What exactly are we talking through, Lynn?
Oh, well. All the bitcoin you want?
It's not just any amount.
-What were you hoping to do?
-[laughs wryly]
-Do you want a cut or something?
-[Lynn laughs] No.
Thanks. I'm just curious.
[elevator lands and dings]
[Ammar] There's no way out of my problems.
I won't turn back.
-I can't keep suffering.
-We have support.
Have you thought of talking
to a professional about it?
There are specialists
that can really help.
The time for talking is over. Yeah.
I've had enough shit social workers
pretend to care about me, all right?
Just nodding along and smiling.
They just push you
further and further into a corner.
I leave more depressed
than when I got there.
[Mingus] Okay.
[breathing heavily]
Thanks.
READING.…
Hey, Ammar. I had an idea.
Let's say that you walk outside,
nice and slow, and calm.
Imagine that happened.
The worst was over, you're relieved.
No fear of what could happen.
You want me to give up and surrender?
You want me to come outside?
-That's never going to happen.
-Tell me why.
Because I always finish what I've started.
I'm past the point of no return.
[doctor] Is the heart rate regular?
READING…
HEART RATE 117 BPM
Yeah, a normal heart rate.
[doctor] Okay, Mingus. Thank you.
She's suffering from anxiety,
a panic attack.
Nothing to worry about.
-It's not your heart, okay?
-[Soof groans]
-Sorry.
-[Mingus] Don't be.
Don't worry, it's okay.
Abe, the doctor just talked to them
over the phone,
and it's not a heart attack.
I repeat: it's not a heart attack.
Okay, stand down, men.
Fuck you, you lying bitch!
[tense music playing]
What was that?
Fuck.
My bad, Double Zero.
I need all lasers off.
Did you want me to get shot?
-Stand up. Now I know what you're up to.
-Ammar?
Do you think I'm stupid or something?
I saw a green dot on my body.
Hey. What's going on, what's wrong?
[Ammar grunting]
[Ammar] Lynn, I swear.
I'll empty this whole clip into him.
Listen carefully now, Ammar.
You're in the store,
and you're the one who set all of this up.
Weapons, explosives, a hostage.
You had to know the response.
Did you think there'd be
a neighborhood cop standing on the corner
stopping traffic?
Come on, man!
There are all kinds of things outside.
Yes, they have lasers.
But nothing is going to happen
as long as we're still talking.
I promise. Okay?
Fuck you, Lynn. Fuck you.
Go get me a man to negotiate with.
This is business.
The next call I get better be from a man.
[call disconnects]
[Lynn breathing heavily]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[man] Back together again.
[phone chimes]
HONEY
WE'RE THINKING OF YOU.
[Winston sighs deeply]
-Does she know what you're doing?
-Of course she does.
It's all over the news. She's not stupid.
If only our friend in there
could have waited two nights.… [laughs]
-I wouldn't have to be here.
-Nah, something else would've come up.
It's not letting up any time soon.
It seems like the world's getting crazier.
They don't tell you that at the interview.
The fighting never ends.
It's not just the bad guys,
but your family too.
Yeah, unfortunately for me,
I lost that battle a long time ago.
[Winston chuckles]
So dramatic.
[man chuckles]
[Winston] How'd that pan out?
The first month was great. [chuckles]
Going out every night. Parties, girls.
[laughs] Yeah?
It doesn't take long
to realize what you're missing out on.
Someone who's always there.
Someone to share your days with.
Ah. Enough of that.
Look where we are.
It doesn't get any better than this.
My advice though…
don't take it for granted.
Nice. Pizza. Just what we needed.
[Winston] Thanks, man.
-Here.
-Thanks.
-[Wilco] Well, I think we have to.
-[Rachelle] Yeah, I agree.
-Sounds good.
-All right.
[Lynn scribbling]
-Lynn…
-I've got him, Wilco.
I've got him.
And he, he knows it too.
And that's precisely why
he won't talk to you anymore.
Give me an hour.
-And he will walk out of that store.
-Sorry, it's way too risky.
He's not going to shoot
if I'm on the phone.
-He calls me "friend."
-[Wilco] Lynn, he wants a man.
[Lynn sighs]
What do you think?
I think you definitely
have a chance with him.
You did well with the hostage.
You really dug deep.
But he's crazy and not crazy.
This guy's completely unpredictable.
-And therefore, he's dangerous.
-Yeah.
That's very clear.
He has a history of illness.
He belongs in the mental health system,
and right now he's our problem.
He needs help, now.
And that's part of our job as negotiators.
Give me an hour.
[sighs softly]
Then half an hour.
Lynn, we can't risk that he'll spiral.
You know the deal.
You can read between the lines.
-What's he really planning?
-[door opens]
That he won't survive.
[tense music playing]
[music continues]
[phone ringing]
[Ammar] Yeah?
Ammar, my name's Wilco.
I'm from the police.
I work with Lynn,
who you were speaking to.
You requested a male negotiator.
I'm speaking to a man? Are you sure?
Yes. I'm a man.
A man delivers, right?
-So? When can I get what I asked for?
-[Wilco] We're doing our best.
But you know that kind of money
isn't so readily available.
We need to see
where we can get 200 million.
Our financial experts are handling it.
That's not a real answer,
so you're not a real man.
Yeah.
If you can't do it,
all you have to do is tell me.
Then you'll face the consequences.
As a man.
You see this, right?
Are you taking me seriously?
Find out what his motivation is.
Show you think he's serious.
[Wilco] I'm taking you serious, as a man.
What do you want from all this, Ammar?
Listen, if today's the day I die,
then I'll die fighting.
Is that what he's after?
Is that what you want? To die today?
Because, um… [chuckles]
I'll stop trying
to get this money together then.
It would save a lot of time.
[Ammar] You're right,
it'll save a lot of time,
because instead of getting it done,
you're stalling. Let them shoot me then.
I won't feel any pain anyway.
You see this?
If I set it off, then all
your little snipers outside will blow up.
You don't care about me,
Lynn doesn't care about me,
nobody cares about me.
Fuck it.
Start the countdown.
Ten, nine, eight…
Take him to the here and now.
Okay, get him back.
Ask what kind of car he wants.
…five…
[Wilco] Ammar, we're working hard
for you, like I said.
As far as your getaway car.
What type of car do you want?
…one.
I want a limousine.
L-limousine?
You want a… limousine as a getaway car?
You heard me. I want a black Hummer Limo.
You guys started this game.
I'm playing along now,
get what I ask for, asshole.
Why not fuchsia?
No.
That's a color I considered.
But black is better.
Okay, Ammar. Okay. Okay. Okay.
A limousine? He's being serious.
Stay on the line.
A limousine?
If we go, we go in style.
[breathing shakily]
Ask for some water, please.
Ask for some water.
I have Red Bull.
No, that's not good for my heart, man.
They have to do what you want.
You're in charge.
Ask for some water.
Instead of water,
he wants a shitty black limousine.
You idiotic fuck!
You idiot, that's enough!
Ask for some fucking water.
Or just shoot me.
I need water for him now.
A few bottles of water.
[Wilco] Okay, Ammar. Okay.
Thank you.
I just know they have to listen to you.
Watch your mouth, or you'll get
a fucking bullet through your head, okay?
[tense music playing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[music stops]
[Lynn] Has it been delivered?
[tense music playing]
[phone dials out]
-[Ammar] Yeah?
-Ammar?
The water's ready for you.
As requested.
Several bottles.
The robot is backing up now.
We will stay away.
Ammar, are you still there?
We're coming to get the water.
Don't try anything, or the place goes up.
[Wilco] I know nothing's gonna happen.
Remember, if you keep talking to me,
you'll be fine. Promise.
[Ammar] Turn around.
Get up.
Turn around.
[music intensifies]
Stand up.
Go. Go.
Stop.
[helicopter whirring]
[pilot 1] OC, we've got eyes
on the front door.
We're going to back off a little more.
The snipers have him in their sight.
Yes, we see two men at the door. Stand by.
[Mark] Mingus?
The moment I say "get down,"
immediately drop
and get your face down on the floor, okay?
[Mingus] What… What's going on?
Mingus, just know you'll be fine, okay.
Trust me and do what I say.
If I shout "get down,"
you all need to lie down immediately.
Once it's safe, we will come and get you.
Officers from the DSI
will give you a code word.
Once you hear that, and only then,
you can open the door. Do you understand?
What's the code word?
iHostage.
[scoffs]
Nothing crazy, okay, Wilco?
[Wilco] We won't do anything.
Take the water, Ammar.
No one's going to hurt you.
We'll stay back. You can just grab it.
-Go get it.
-[grunts softly]
[helicopter whirring]
Pick it up.
[breathing heavily]
[Ilian strains]
I can't, man.
I can't.
[sighs] Fucking hell.
[music intensifies]
Get down. Get down now!
[panicked breathing]
[Ilian breathing heavily]
[tires screech]
[panting]
[gasps]
[tires screech]
[Abe] Disarm the bomb, now!
[Kees] What the fuck was that?
[indistinct shouting]
Stay back!
Keep the line of fire, stay back!
Get out of there.
Stay back!
Hold the line of fire!
Stay back, men, stay back!
[dog barking]
[breathing heavily]
[pilot 1] It's not great.
I wonder if he's still alive.
-[pilot 2] That wasn't good.
-[pilot 1] OC, he's lying in the square.
[Wilco] Ammar, can you hear me?
Say something.
I'm still here. Can you hear me?
[poignant music playing]
-[helicopter whirring]
-[indistinct radio chatter]
Alpha, it's Double Zero.
Situation at the Apple Store safe for now.
Guys, no one goes near that tango
until the explosives
have been investigated.
Bomb squad, approach the body.
Hey, you guys, get the fuck away from him.
-Guys…
-[sighs]
Attention all units in the area.
The hostage just ran out of the building,
followed by the hostage taker.
He's been hit by a DSI vehicle.
Everyone, please remain in position
until further notice. Over.
[knocking on window]
This is going to make
a shitload of noise after what happened.
But great work, brother.
[emphatic music playing]
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Great reflexes.
I'm glad he didn't explode.
I think there are a lot of people
who want to speak to you.
Can I just go home?
To Maya and the kids?
I'm afraid not until tomorrow morning.
-[dog barking]
-[breathing heavily]
[Winston] Sir?
Are you hurt?
It's okay, it's over.
-[gasps]
-[Winston] Sorry.
Sir, it's okay. You're safe now.
-Am I?
-Yeah. I promise.
I'm gonna take you
to the police station, okay?
Let's go.
Medic.
[somber music playing]
[breathing shakily]
[indistinct voices]
[officer] Police. Police.
Show yourselves.
Back here, guys.
-[breathing shakily]
-[officer muffled, indistinct]
[Mingus] Here. Your phone.
Thank you.
[officer] iHostage.
-[knocking]
-Open the door.
Open up, this is the police.
[dog barking]
Stand down.
Come on out.
Exit slowly please.
-Go ahead. It's safe.
-[officer] This way.
Go ahead. Come on. That way. It's okay.
Is everyone okay?
Is anyone hurt?
-This way. Come with me.
-[dog barking]
Don't worry, it's over.
This way.
Heading outside now.
[music swells]
[Mark] Mingus.
You pulled everyone through, man.
Great job.
You helped get those people out.
We really appreciate it.
[poignant music playing]
[Kees sighs]
Tomorrow morning at nine, debriefing.
Main office.
Go get some sleep first, hm?
[Lynn chuckles lightly]
Easier said than done.
Hey, don't forget.
While you kept him talking,
it bought everyone time
to get those people
out of that building safely.
Thanks.
I'll see you tomorrow morning.
Yeah.
[music continues]
Watch your step.
I'll get you home soon, okay?
[sighs]
[gasps lightly]
[breathing heavily]
What the fuck?
[crying]
-[gentle music playing]
-[sniffles]
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music continues]
[birds tweeting]
["Feeling Good" playing through ear buds]
[crying]
♪ And I'm feeling good ♪
♪ I'm feeling good ♪
[song gets louder]
♪ Fish in the sea… ♪
THE HOSTAGE TAKER WAS TRANSFERRED
TO HOSPITAL SEVERELY WOUNDED
AND DIED THE NEXT DAY.
ON MARCH 31ST 2022, THE HOSTAGE
AND THE FOUR PEOPLE IN THE CLOSET
RECEIVED THE HERO'S PIN FOR BRAVERY
FROM THE CITY OF AMSTERDAM.
AFTER FOUR MONTHS OF INVESTIGATION,
THE PUBLIC PROSECUTOR CONCLUDED
THAT THE DSI OPERATOR HAD ACTED LAWFULLY
WHEN CAUSING THE COLLISION,
AND WOULD NOT BE PROSECUTED.
THE HOSTAGE TAKER'S MOTIVE
HAS NEVER BECOME CLEAR.
♪ Dragonfly out in the sun
You know what I mean, don't you know ♪
♪ Butterflies all havin' fun
You know what I mean ♪
♪ Sleep in peace when day is done
That's what I mean ♪
♪ And this old world is a new world
And a bold world ♪
♪ For me ♪
♪ Stars when you shine
You know how I feel ♪
♪ Scent of the pine
♪ Oh, freedom is mine
And I know how I feel ♪
♪ It's a new dawn
It's a new day ♪
♪ It's a new life ♪
♪ It's a new dawn
It's a new day ♪
♪ It's a new life ♪
♪ It's a new dawn
It's a new day ♪
♪ It's a new life
It's a new life for me ♪
♪ And I'm feeling good ♪
♪ I'm feeling good ♪
♪ I feel so good ♪
[song ends]
[dramatic music playing]
[music stops]