Demonic invasion
Array
It wants to enter Nantianmen
How can the holy land of the gods allow monsters to set foot on it?
Stop it
All things of unknown origin run to the divine realm
What?
Do you really think you can become an immortal by entering the Nantian Gate?
Tell you
This is none of your business.
Stay aside
Don't try to steal the credit
You are crazy
The Queen Mother's Travels
The gods obey
The stars reappear in the world
It will inevitably cause trouble again
The Lords
You are in charge of the wealth and destiny of the mortal world.
This is for you to decide.
This is Xingxiu
Even the silk array can't stop it
This golden thread fruit is so small
This is how I caught one
There are still twenty-seven.
Stars are born in the sky
Contains the power of stars
Brought to the mortal world by the Weaver Girl
It has been missing for many years
Can't find it anywhere
Now suddenly there is an invasion of both worlds
There must be something fishy about this
The worlds of man and god are connected by the sky curtain
I am waiting for the offerings from the mortal world
Do your duty
This is a serious matter
God needs to be sent to deal with it
To prevent future troubles
Disciple Jinfeng
May the lower world conquer all the stars
Eliminate hidden dangers
Restoring peace to both worlds
Your mother was away from work.
Backlash from the stars
Not only will you suffer the consequences
Such a disaster has been caused
OK
There is no need to mention this matter again
The Golden Wind is Spiritual God
It has been twelve years since I came to the divine world
Always hardworking and diligent
The evil bat has just descended
If you can make up for your crime
It's also a way to atone for my mother's sins
The Weaver Girl is good at using the golden thread
Stars fear it
Let him do it
That's appropriate.
Jinfeng is willing to swear this oath
No stars
No Return to God Realm
Good one, never return to the divine world
Your mother never came back.
Disaster, world?
Like mother, like son
If you really can't return to the underworld
Wouldn't it cause more disasters?
how
I said it
Above the Star Palace
What a disgrace
Pastoral care of younger brothers
The God's lineage
Please command the lower world
Conquer the Stars
This time, the stars were conquered
Si Mu also contributed the most
Although I was rude and offensive just now
But it makes sense
Moreover, Ji hit the famous family
Loyalty and Bravery
Naturally more secure
in this way
Order the priest to go down to the world immediately
Bring
back all the stars
No mistakes
The Star Axis is a magical tool to subdue demons
Can collect stars
You are not yet deified
Tongtian Stone is the certificate for traveling between the two worlds
Keep it safe
Don't lose it
If this happens
Ordained
The pastor received the order
^7 bar
Go home when you're healed.
Ye Erfei
Pig eaves
Mother weaving cloth
Dad plows the field
I am with my little sister under the tree
Wind
Wind, look
daughter
Let me play. Let me play.
My mother taught me
good
Mom will teach you
A Niang
You are here
Master
disciple
Disciple incompetence
Last chess game
Is it not finished yet?
Accompany the teacher to finish this game
You've been here for twelve years.
It's Master
In a flash
The immortals of your generation
Or have a priesthood
Or enter the immortal gate
Nowhere to go
Only you
It's the disciple's fault
Yeah
Don't blame your mother.
Love is the magic of mortals
Even gods cannot escape
It's not her fault
she
Is he really a sinner?
So what?
So what if it's not
As long as the stars don't return
The accusations against my mother never stop.
I'm willing to fight for my life
Find the stars
Can
The stars appeared in the world because of your golden thread
I was not in a position to stand up for you in public just now.
I hope you will go down to the world this time
Put an end to this matter
Give the gods an explanation
As long as I bring back all the stars
All this
Is it all over?
yes
it's over
You will ascend to the throne of God in the future
Reviving the family
I will no longer be blamed for the past.
in this way
Live chess
I have limited time for you.
When the time comes
Must come back
Otherwise, the immortal life will be exhausted.
Fall into the Netherworld
Get out of the way!
Don't block me
Don't step on my shoes
Who stepped on your shoes?
I put the first column
What is it?
Sir, please
Mr. Zhang is burning incense, get out of the way
Hey, you don't have eyes when you walk.
Get out of the way
Thank you
Small things Small things
Get out of the way
Zx word please
Who threw it?
Slow down, sir.
Walk slowly. Walk slowly.
Hey please
You are such an idiot, you don't have eyes.
God bless you!
You come and burn incense too.
Pray for my son's safety
May the mountain of God bless you
I want to ask about my marriage
daughter
Look
I switched to Dragon
It's amazing
You try it
Let my sister try it too
Um
Sister eats
This is the first time the priest comes here.
Priest, follow me.
Come this way
The priest doesn't know
Sanxing Temple is a place where mortals burn incense and worship gods.
It is also the passage for gods to travel between the upper and lower worlds.
The big female in front treats ordinary people
The hall behind has various entrances and exits.
The gods can see the side of mortals
Mortals cannot see the side of the gods
Bless me with good luck
Wish Come True
This is it
Please check quickly
Where is the pastor?
Si Shangxian has not returned from hunting down the stars
He named you the Comet God
I left a magic weapon for you.
The visitor bestows the instrument
Dharma Instruments Arrive
Where can it be?
try to find
Jinx
Jinx holding a broom
That's it.
Sure enough, here
Finally found it
What to see
I have never seen a fairy in heaven.
The Holy Land of the Gods must be spotless
Do a good job
Don't steal.
Who are you?
Why did you come just now?
attack
Wear
Trivial Skills
I'm a fairy.
Who is making noise?
Disturbed my sleep
I am a fairy
Let me go to heaven
Fairy
What about the Tongtian Stone?
that
Even mortals want to go to heaven
Come on
Catch this faker.
I really have something to do
You let me go up
Cut the crap
Take it
Let me go up
Divine Realm
How could a mortal sneak in?
Is there an insider?
Please ask the gods to assist in the investigation
you
Isn't it quite impressive?
You are so familiar with this place
Is there any way to sneak out?
No
If it weren't for you
I've already gone to heaven
How could I be misunderstood
Why so many misunderstandings?
It's obvious that people are trying to trick you.
Open the door
You've gone down to the dungeon.
Let me out
I am following the order of God
Conquer with you
You deserve it too
Did you see it?
This is strength
Water Monkey
immortal
You
I am only worthy of staying with ordinary people.
What happened to mortals?
You're annoying.
It's annoying just looking at it
What are you pulling?
The gods are amazing
you
You and ordinary people are really one family
From childhood to adulthood, he always snatched everything from me.
Look at you this time
How to grab
Pastor
You are the land
Confusing right and wrong
Aren't you afraid of being charged?
condemn
I was originally a guard at the Weaver Girl Temple.
Because of your mother's involvement, you were demoted to land
Today is your retribution
Mother owes you
I'll return it
You don't have this chance.
See if it's him.
This is the person
Causing such a big mess
It's all his mother's fault.
yes
How can he have the face to come to the divine world?
My mother
Not a sinner
Your mother is a sinner
The Heart-searching Pond is where the gods reflect on their past.
You are the son of a criminal.
I want to come in too
As long as you work hard
When you grow up, you will be ordained as a priest.
You can revive your family
Atonement for the Mother
you
Get out of the way
Xuanwu barrier
Nandouzhusheng
You are at the door
What's wrong?
you
It's okay to try it.
How about it
Don't
What do you want to do?
Rush out
Get the Babel Stone and the Star Axis
Conquer the Stars
Return to Heaven
So many things
Wait a minute
I can help you get the stuff.
Don't alarm them.
but
You have to do me a favor.
I just helped you break the barrier.
How can you get out?
It works again
It turned out to be a barrier suppression
God, come here
immortal
You reach out
really
The Immortal should really see the boy's expression just now
Take the humiliation
What a jinx
I can't get rid of it.
that is
Who wants to eat these mortal things?
This is not
Thinking about
Transfer back soon
This little thing
Please keep this little bastard's stone for me.
That's natural
adult
The stage is ready
You can take your seat now.
Please
God will fight the monkey
Specially designed for your child
Walk
Take a look
Keep an eye on me.
Yes, sir.
Find the Tongtian Stone first
I looked at them
Find it quickly
Isn't this the baby?
Don't
Golden Wind
Oh, I'm going
Don't block me.
Golden Wind
You dare to steal the magic weapon?
Release the Stars
Believe it or not, wait for me to come back
I believe
Let's go
no
This is Xingxiu
Can't let it escape
Take me with you
Heaven and earth are blessed
Is it okay to pass every exam?
God you
Is it going to manifest?
Hitting a tree
Where are you going, God?
I was ordered by my master to go down to the world to subdue the stars.
Originally, the land and rat officials should have assisted
Find detailed location
But now
That's all
I find it myself
It's really a fairy
Gone in the blink of an eye
Look how dangerous the world is.
You are unfamiliar with the place
Let me help you
I'm good at finding things.
You are just an ordinary person
Don't disbelieve it
I'll find it for you
try to find
Wait till I come back
Why don't you bring me back both the person and the things?
Just go to the netherworld and wait for death
Call all
Find now
The gods appear and you will pass every exam
immortal
Monsters
You scared it.
this
The Second Mansion in the North
Taurus
How to
so
So cute, right?
How about it
Take me with you, you can earn money
Why help me
This
Of course I have something to ask for.
ï»¿
I'll help you find the monster
You take me to heaven
Is it possible?
Heaven
Um
I want to plant
What are you doing in the divine realm?
Don't worry about this
I have something important to do.
Leave after finishing
Never stay long
I'd better go help the pretty boy.
,maybe
Is he willing?
Where is the next one?
You promised
Hook and Hang for a 100 Years
try to find
In the Seven Ancient Towns
I am familiar with
Please help me find the stars
I'll take you to the divine realm
That's all
A while
Let me change your clothes first.
I'll take you to eat something delicious.
Good baby
That's right
My name is Xiaofan
Annoying
Ordinary
The name isn't important.
This girl has great magical powers
The Seven Ancient Town Leaders
Fortune Telling
Meet today
You're lucky
What wind are you coming from?
Didn't you say that names don't matter?
oh
It's the golden wind
Oh, yes, yes.
That's a good name.
This is like a human being.
The fairy spirit was too heavy before
Can scare away monsters from a distance
Let's go.
The Qigu Town is in front.
Go fast
Come on, come on
How about it
This is Qigu Town.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Keep up
Zhenxiang Hotpot Watch a Show and Taste the Hotpot
A series of good plays about heroes fighting tigers
elder brother
Watch the Road
Danger in the world
Watch the face
city
Let's go
So many people
This is the first of the seven ancient towns.
Stop it.
Time is limited
Do the real work first
There are stars
It's a dragon dance
What constellation
I said gods
Could you please stop being so startled?
The Dangers of the World
Why not be more cautious?
You next time
Let's see if the scroll reacts.
Feed you
You let me come
What did you say
You want to fight?
The one I hit is you
If you have the guts, try touching me.
This scroll cannot be exchanged for money
Sister Xiaofan
Are you hungry?
Eat now
Come out, sister.
It's okay
Eat this, eat this
Return the scroll to you
you
They are all in the same group.
None of their business
Come to me
What are you doing?
Didn't I find the scroll for you?
Look at them
They just want to eat something
What does it have to do with me?
Stealing is wrong
If there is any other way
Who wants to do this?
You grew up in heaven.
Who knows these
Can we get down to business?
Where are the stars?
The talisman paper is used up
No money to buy
Mortals are naughty and gods have no money
What to do
Isn't it just money?
I'll find a way
This is not stealing
Master is above
Disciple is in urgent need of some incense
After returning to the divine world,
Master is also a poor god
Master is the God of War
The former master descended to the mortal world to subdue the demon
Great military achievements
Now the two worlds have been at peace for a long time
He was forgotten
Fighting and killing is so belligerent
Who would worship him for no reason?
nonsense
Master's Battle
It is to exorcise demons.
The gods who are in charge of fame, wealth and power
How can I compare with my master's achievements?
Constellation
Need help?
Fast Chase
Give me back the scroll
You have nothing to do here.
Give me the scroll
I'll give you whatever you want.
Scroll for you
That's right.
Heaven and Earth
Whatever you want, we have it.
then
Not leaving yet
Stop for me
Let the pretty boy also taste the dangers of the world
Mr.
You don't really think I'd give him the scroll?
Let's go
Go buy some talisman paper
Apply this to the wound on your arm
It works
That's right here
As expected, it received rave reviews
There is no such fun place in the divine world
I didn't go to the divine realm for fun.
It's to find someone
Find someone
Let's go
The guest is walking inside
Please sit inside
Zhenxiang hotpot is delicious
good
Waiter, another serving of really delicious beef
How many guests?
Follow me upstairs
Watching a play and tasting hot pot
well
Five tables of spicy hot pot on the third floor
Come come come, those who eat spicy food are all brothers
Please don't steal this meal from me.
I request
Madam, take it easy.
Never mind, I'll lose weight tomorrow.
People have to eat when they are happy
Come come drink
Table No. 5 Tiger Pepper
Go
Please take care, sir.
Please write a poem at the door to reward
The wind blows the sunset
Walk on it quickly
Good Poems Good Poems
Drink and drink
Happy Birthday
Come on, come on
Sit here
How to find so many people?
Why don't I go first
Brother
Double-boiled hot pot
Come on
Herbal tea to relieve heat
Hot pot with red oil
The gods are all on top
Double-boiled hot pot
Medium spicy
Crispy pork tripe beef balls
Chopsticks soup spoon colander
Free coriander for purchases over 100 yuan
-don't want
We still first
Eat first, enjoy first
Do you want beef balls?
Tell you
Tail Fire Tiger Five Elements: Fire
Fire is hard to hide
If it's really here
Show up early and late
we
Just sit back and wait.
Can
Tripe ups and downs
Eat shrimp while they are fresh
When I reach the divine realm
Find the person you are looking for
Must bring her here'
Come come come
You try it?
Two people eat faster than one person
Also correct
Zhenxiang hotpot is delicious
Delicious, huh?
Today I finally have someone to eat with me.
Try this again
How about it
Upgraded version
Will it be too spicy?
Can't eat spicy food
Cool
Brother, hold on.
Herbal tea is effective immediately after extinguishing the fire
You are too cowardly.
Stop it.
How can we find the tiger like this?
Tail Fire Tiger
tiger
Go Go Go
Help!
Who dares to destroy my place?
My tea
good
Hurry up and block it
Block it up
My shop
good
Come and eat
What is this move?
So cool
This is called thunder punishment
My master taught me
Out, head
Quick Scroll
careful
Wear
She's still cute when she's not angry.
good
My life
Slip away
hero
Well acted
Tips
Hurry up and catch up
Yo
Isn't this Asheng?
The last time I was told by a fortune teller, I would be injured within ten days.
No
I'm still walking sideways now.
Refund Refund
There are still two hours left.
Three people are born with a lack of heart
I'm also blamed for not calculating correctly
If you can calculate
Why not count?
When can I find your mother?
That's right
Is it you who said it?
Ah leftover
You're going to heaven
Did it succeed?
What are you busy doing?
Your mother doesn't want you at all
Aren't you the one who picked out the rest?
This is correct, right?
Fly; A/
4:
And she said that my fortune teller was not accurate.
It doesn't matter who you offended.
you
Stolen
The old man who watched the play gave me a reward
Now You Know
I'm not the boss of Qigu Town
Just an orphan
The fortune teller picked me up
Bring me back and raise me
Teach me divination
As far as I can remember
Hanging out on this street
Later, my grandmother got old.
Dying
Talk to me
My mother is not missing.
She is a fairy descending from the earth
You don't believe
I have this
My mother-in-law said
This is a keepsake my mother left me.
You have lived in heaven for so many years.
Have you seen anything similar to this?
but
There are many fairies in this sky.
What I haven't seen
Doesn't mean no
But even if I can go
The God Realm is so big
So many fairies
How to find
Don't worry about this.
There is a Sutra Pavilion in the westernmost part of the God Realm
There is a book of immortals and gods in the Sutra Library
You can find everything
Sutra Library
Have you been there?
No
Sutra Library
Only open to priests
What to do then
Wait till I finish this.
Ordination
Naturally you can go in.
Then we catch the stars.
Just hurry up to heaven
Go to the Sutra Library to find my mother
Give me the Kongming lantern
That's mine
Xiaofan
you
Do you hate your mother?
No hate
She wouldn't leave me on purpose.
Leave me a token
There must be a reason for her leaving.
She must be looking forward to it
The day I met you again
so
Your mother
My mother made a big mistake
Father
younger sister
Also died because of this
Everyone said our family deserved it.
But my little sister was still in her infancy.
Master is late
I found that I was still alive
Take me back to the divine realm
Give me a chance
Atonement for the Mother
Wait till I finish this.
With priesthood
No one will care about the past anymore.
No one will blame my mother anymore.
you
Hate her?
That
Do you miss her?
At that time
They destroyed all traces of my mother in the divine world.
I'm afraid I'll forget what she looks like.
I secretly ran to the pond of inquiry
I want to see her again
Pond of Inquiry
It is a temple in the divine world.
There you can see your memories
You saw her
I just arrived at the door
He was driven away by the divine soldiers.
It doesn't matter
Wait until we catch Xingxiu
You are truly a fairy.
By then
Go wherever you want
When do you want to see my mother?
Wait for me to go to heaven
Find A Niang
Let's call everyone up.
Eat hot pot together
Sit at the big table
A promise is a promise
As long as these stars don't run away
Still pretty well behaved.
They were created when the world was first created.
Contains the power to destroy the world
Don't be careless
This is
This should be
The place where the master subdued demons
Such a big pit
How many people will die?
Are you going to be a god of food?
Go collect firewood
Yes, sir.
You are such a devoted follower.
Remind you
Jin Feng
I can do anything for my own sake.
He can grab my scroll
I can also use you, a mortal
Be more careful
Don't sell it to others.
It's almost ready to eat.
Cumin and shallots
Right
Right, right, right
Only one left
Let me make a guess
Daxian
This trick doesn't work.
What do you know?
Just wait and see
The worst
Winged Fire Snake is not easy to deal with
It is normal to have more bad luck than good luck
/or
You go back to Qigu Town and wait for my news
Don't think about getting rid of me now.
Eat your fish.
It is here
Yeah, right?
who
What do you do?
Excuse me
Is there a monster around here?
Winged Fire Snake
How to do this
How can this be good?
Wouldn't they rush into the village?
A while ago
This big snake suddenly appeared
Go down the mountain to look for food during the day
At night, I stayed in the back mountain
Seems to be guarding something
Can be on the mountain
Except for an abandoned farmhouse
There's nothing.
You continue
It is cunning by nature
Out of the box, out of the box
What we need to do
Five Elements: Fire
We can use water to overcome it.
This is the river
This is the village
Where is this
This is garlic
I'm doing some work
The executioner rushed to the river
You clean it up again
Don't we have lots of big buckets?
Everyone collects
Let's go
It's getting late.
Childhood
I don't concentrate on what I learn.
My mother-in-law was the most serious when she taught me the talismans.
My mother-in-law said
Talismans can find things
Find someone
I thought
That's so nice
Maybe someday
I found my mother.
actually
It's not that easy
rest assured
Wait until we collect all the stars
I will report this to Master.
You helped me a lot.
He will allow you to go to heaven to find your mother.
Um
Tomorrow will be fine.
Yes
Give me your pocket
Repaired
Awesome God
Go to bed early
I don't know if these talismans are enough.
Keep quiet
How did it come back?
Oh no! Oh no!
Run!
Stop stopping me
Let it leave the village.
As long as it doesn't harm our village anymore
Let it escape if it wants to
This goes on
The whole village is finished.
What a pity
Almost there
It's you
Like mother, like son
You don't have this chance.
Go away
what to do
That girl is still in there.
Help!
The gods have descended to earth
Thank you, God
Thank you so much
I have a little sister
My mother has a spinning wheel
Dad has an old cow
father
daughter
Wind
Wind, look
You go
Protecting the child
Go fast
Don't look back
A Niang
Thunder Punishment
Xiaofan
I have collected all the stars and reported them to the God Realm
It's too late for you to cause trouble now.
snort
Now
Can you take me to heaven?
I
You are just a fairy
Why take her to heaven?
Didn't you say
Your master will help me
To my master
My master
Don't ask my master
I will try my best to help you
But now is not the time
Did you see it?
These are all his excuses.
He just wants to go back and become a god.
I'm afraid your affairs will implicate him.
He made a contribution for himself
Can destroy the whole village
He doesn't care about you at all.
You are talking nonsense
His master is here.
If you don't believe it
Ask him yourself
I believe you
Let's go ask him for mercy.
No
You promised
We've made a promise
You don't keep your word
You lied to me
Xiaofan
The star axis has been sent to the sky cage
Don't worry
If I hadn't arrived in time
You've run out of life.
Master
alright
I know the world is dangerous
Mortal Cunning
Your journey has been difficult
Take a break here
There will be an immortal official who will ask you to change your clothes
From now on, you will be my general.
No one will embarrass you anymore
Immortal Jinfeng
Subdue the Stars
Chartered priesthood
God rewards hard work
Well-deserved
You go
Protecting the child
A Niang
this
This is a taboo
Golden Wind
Do you have anything to say?
Golden Wind Gratitude
We should work hard and make progress
Guarding the peace of both worlds
Very good
ï»¿
(Scripture Pavilion)
(Sky cage)
(Pool of Questioning)
You don't have to be afraid
This is the pond of inquiry.
Where memories can be seen
Come here
Mother
Have you considered it?
If this is true
The mortal world is not safe
Thousands of lives lost
This is for the entire divine world.
They'll be fine.
This matter is settled
I will return them to you
Hand over the stars
When my mother passed away
Not greedy for the mundane world
Is for
daughter
Look, look.
This is Us
Dad has an old cow
My mother has a spinning wheel
I have a little sister
A Niang
Go fast
Protecting the child
father
You've become like a human being.
Human nature
Joy, Anger, Sadness, and Happiness
You won't understand
You can't escape today
I can't escape
They can
Go fast
You are here
It's really you
good
It's me
Twelve years
The only one I believe in is you
The Great God Realm
Controlled by human will
Regardless of achievements
Only look at the incense
No rules
What about dignity?
Can't you see?
What does this have to do with my mother?
I want the divine world to be free from the filth of the human world.
Only by opening the sky
Separating Heaven and Earth
But this is not divine power.
The twenty-eight constellations are born from the stars
Use their power
This feat can be accomplished
Your mother is trying to stop a car with her arms
I just have to do this
so
You said she fell into the mortal world due to her love affair
Deserting the post and letting Xingxiu go
You said she killed her whole family.
They all lied to me
I'm doing this for your own good
Good for me
Use the moves I taught you against me
Too naive
I don't blame you.
You are still young
Suffered injustice
But you have been ordained
Avenge the previous shame
How can we lose all our previous efforts due to a moment of confusion?
Xiaofan
Such deceitful mortals
You are so naive
I want to take her to heaven.
ï»¿
So what?
She stole your magic weapon
Trespassing in the Divine Realm
You send it to the netherworld
Turned into a hairspring
So as not to be implicated by mortals again
Mislead your future
Do you think
I still care about rumors at this moment
Care about the future
Those who achieve great things do not care about gains and losses
Important
You said that the incense in the human world disturbed the solemnity of the divine world.
I ask you
If you are the one with the most incense
You are revered by the mortals
Would you still go to the trouble of planning all this?
Twelve years
I didn't want to kill you
We've all been forgotten
You three have the most incense.
Future human affairs
It's up to you to decide.
Congratulations
They don't understand
Eight You know
here
It's not up to you to decide
Stop being busy
If you don't get out quickly
The body will soon dissipate
There's no going back
here
fundamental
No life gate
It's me
I think I am
I couldn't help you.
It also hurts you
sorry
It's not your fault
I didn't see through Master's conspiracy.
I believe my mother is a sinner.
我甚至还恨过她
To make up for the so-called guilt
I tried every possible way to bring Xingxiu back to the divine realm
Kexingxiu
My mother sacrificed her life to let him go.
She saved the world
What I did
I'm so stupid
you
Have you found your mother?
You lied to me
What is the Immortal Record?
Which one is it?
My life
I've never seen so many books.
Among so many gods
No mother
Is A Niang a fairy?
Is he a sinner?
None of it matters
yes
I just want to be in this world
Someone is thinking about me
Want to have dinner with the family
But
No chance
I'll fix it for you.
Wait till we get out of here
Find her together
you
You are a
Very good fairy
Xiaofan
I'll fix it for you.
This is
This portrait
The keepsake my mother left me
It is my mother's golden shuttle
This is our father and mother.
father
daughter
You are the little sister
My name is Jinfeng
Your name is Yulu
Gyokuro
My name is Yulu
We are home
This is our home
Can
fine
We are
Home is
Um
Sky curtain opening
How can I allow you to be around?
Put down your magic weapon quickly
Ignorant rats
Report
Lingbi has opened the sky
The two worlds are separating
Go get help.
Get out of here
No, grandma is still in the village.
You mortals
It's really annoying.
Trivial Skills
how
Dying once is not enough
This time I will make you fall into ruin
Golden Shuttle
How dare you
careful
Gyokuro
I thought your golden thread could be used by me
It's a pity that you are just like your mother.
Obstinate
I will save you
Because you are useful
Kill you
Because you're in the way
ridiculous
You actually fought with me for a mortal.
It's me you should be loyal to.
What
Don't think you can do this.
Very noisy
You said that love is the law of mortals.
But you never understand
How powerful is the magic of mortals?
Four Elephants
Quickly retreat back to the divine realm
The sky is falling
I'm with you
Um
My mother used to take care of the skylight
Her magic power is above the golden shuttle
Please lend us a helping hand
It's Xingxiu
The stars return to their positions
Go ahead
Leave it to me
Um
Run for help
Help
Mother
Heartstrings
daughter
elder brother
younger sister
Closed
The Queen Mother has ordered
Descendant of the Weaver Girl, Yu Lu, please return to heaven soon
No mistakes
ah
I had a dream when I was a child
Dreaming about two birds falling in love
later
Bluebird's wings are broken
She has a wish
With her partner
Fly again
Whether it's turning into a bird in a dream
Or are you still living in a dream?
Even if I can only see you once more
I want too
Give it your all