Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
-[wind whooshing]
-[insects chittering]
[birds chirping]
[tense music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[panting]
[tense music continues]
[crickets chirping]
[footsteps approaching]
[shower running]
-[door opens]
-[footsteps approaching]
[man] How was the jog?
It was good.
Hurry up and get out of there.
This place is supposed to be fun.
[serene music playing]
[exhales softly]
[chuckles softly]
What?
You look beautiful.
-[man] All right.
-All right.
-[man] You ready?
-Yep.
[man] Let's go.
[chuckles] Wow. No phones?
This is a real-deal date night. Okay.
-[crowd chattering]
-[woman] A…
-L…
-[pop music playing]
[woman] T.
[man] "Gestalt" is a person. Sorry.
-And a word.
-That's an interesting theory.
-It's also one of those fact thingies.
-[chuckles]
-I'm gonna challenge you.
-Okay.
[pages flipping]
"Gestalt. An organized whole
that is perceived as more than…" Damn it.
-Are you sure you wanna keep fighting?
-Yeah, yeah.
It's just that I'm so much better
than you. I'm sorry. [laughs]
By the way,
speaking of an organized whole…
Beg your pardon?
I was referring to our housewarming party.
-But in the weirdest way possible.
-[laughs]
-[giggles]
-I sent out that Evite this morning.
Oh, yes. Thank you for doing that.
[pen clicks]
[woman] Oops…
Two…
So, did you, uh… did you feel anything?
Huh?
I noticed you checking in the shower.
Mm.
Okay. That makes sense.
Now, that's why you were
looking at me like that at the house.
Listen to me.
If it happens again,
we'll deal with it again.
Together.
Loser still has to do the laundry.
I hate you so much.
-[softly] I hate you too.
-[laughs]
Come here.
All right. Gimme that.
You're still good
with the party on the 18th?
'Cause that's what I put on the Evite.
Oh. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I think that's perfect.
Any later than that,
and it gets too close to Thanksgiving--
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
Wait a minute. Come here.
[crickets chirping]
What?
I'm proud of what we built.
-[woman] Well, you built it.
-[man] Yeah. But I built it for you.
-I built it for us.
-[sighs]
-How about a movie?
-[keys jangling]
Movie? I thought this was a date night.
That is a much better idea.
What?
Did you leave the back door open?
No.
[menacing music playing]
Henry?
[hurried footsteps]
[Henry] No. The back door was closed--
-[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[menacing music playing]
[door closes]
Hey. You okay?
Yeah. I, um…
What if they tried to hurt us?
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
Listen, they just…
they just wanted our stuff.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay. Then why didn't they take anything?
[sighs] I don't know.
It's kind of embarrassing, really.
Yeah. I mean, what's wrong with our stuff?
Right?
We have good stuff.
[woman sighs]
I'm gonna have one more look around. Okay?
I'll be right up.
Okay.
[tense piano music playing]
[sighs deeply]
[boy] I think it's getting
a little better.
[muffled]
I don't always feel so mad at her.
-[breathing heavily]
-[boy] The breathing exercises…
I think about having to change schools
and everything,
and I just get pissed
at her all over again.
Well, moving can be difficult.
[chuckling] It sucks.
Well, it depends where you move to.
You know,
you might even like the East Coast. I did.
-Did you grow up there?
-No. No.
I grew up in India,
and then I moved to Boston for university.
-What made you stay?
-My husband. We met there.
What did he do to convince you?
Maybe it'd work on my mom.
[chuckles]
Well, he, um,
wooed me with a cheap souvenir.
Uh, he bought me a clock
on our first date.
That's kind of a weird gift.
-No offense.
-[sighs] I still have that clock.
So, basically,
you're saying I should bribe her?
Basically, I'm saying
maybe you should not be so pissed at her.
Not for trying to be a good mom.
Were your kids pissed at you
for moving here?
Mm. We… We don't… We don't have any kids.
No.
[notification chimes]
[melancholy music playing]
[receptionist]
You know, I can get you in on…
Hi, Mom. Thanks.
How about the 23rd? You wanna get some…
[papers rustling]
[doorbell rings]
[door opens]
-[Henry] Hi. Can I help you?
-Mr. Parsons.
Detective Morse.
Corrales PD.
Hi. Yeah, um… Come on in.
[Morse] Two cell phones and one laptop.
That's it?
Pretty specific list of items they took.
Why'd you and your wife
leave your cell phones behind?
We used to be tied to 'em. Especially me.
And we decided when we moved
that when we're together,
nothing should get in the way of it.
[chuckles]
-How long the two of you been married?
-Twelve years.
And when did you move to Corrales?
Came out about a year ago to break ground,
and then we finally moved in
about two months ago.
Boston's a rat race, and we were looking
for the exact opposite.
[exhaling] Make any enemies
since you've been here?
Uh, um…
I don't think what happened
was anything personal. Why? Do you?
Part of what we're trying to figure out.
What about back in Boston?
Back in Boston?
[Morse] Did you leave
any enemies behind there?
None that would fly across the country
to… to break into my home. No.
[scoffs, inhales sharply]
[chuckles softly]
It's a nice place.
It's big.
You design it yourself?
-Yep.
-Hmm.
What? [chuckles]
I'm just surprised you didn't install
an alarm system, that's all.
Well, I was under the impression
that Corrales was safe.
[chuckles softly]
How long were you and your wife gone
from the house that night?
-Couple hours.
-So, two?
-Yeah. Like, two or three.
-Which? Two or three?
I'm trying to put together
a timeline here. So, I'd need to know--
My wife is rattled about what happened.
Okay? And I know you are doing your job.
-I am.
-[Henry] My job's to make her feel safe.
So what can I tell her you guys are doing
that might make that happen?
[pipes rattle]
[pipes groan]
Sounds like you need a plumber.
I'll add it to the list.
You tell her…
[pen clicks]
…we're tracking a few leads.
-[insects chittering]
-[suspenseful music swells]
[inhaling]
[indistinct muffled dialogue]
[breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music swells]
-[phone ringing, door closes]
-So, good news.
The lump you felt was probably
just a residual build-up of scar tissue.
-Oh.
-I see no indication of cancer returning.
[sighs] Okay.
Okay. I just, um…
I just… just wanted to be really sure.
Of course. Here, you can keep a copy.
Yeah. Thank you.
[exhaling sharply]
How are you feeling otherwise?
I'm… I'm okay. Just… just very tired.
I, um, heard about the break-in.
Corrales is a small town.
What you don't hear about at church,
you read about in the police log.
I know this is your field,
but if you ever need to speak to someone--
Oh. No. No. [chuckles]
Thank you so much. I'm… I'm okay.
-You're sure?
-Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
My… my husband, he helps in that way.
A lot, actually.
He's really good at, um, at being there
and dealing with all my stuff.
[melancholy music plays]
He could have walked away.
Most people would have in that position.
And I was impossible
to be around sometimes,
but he stayed with me
and supported me through all of it.
-Idiot.
-[both laugh]
[birds chirping]
[phone beeps]
[locks clicking]
[thunder rumbling]
[seat belt clicking]
[folk music playing]
-Henry?
-[Henry] In here.
Actually, wait a second.
-[clanking]
-What's happening?
[Henry] Okay. Come on in.
[laughs] Okay.
Ta-da!
[gasps]
-You fixed our pictures.
-Yeah. And the shelf.
And the hallway light,
and the… the desk chair.
But, hey, who's counting? Right?
Wow. Look at you.
Oh.
-[clicks music off]
-[laughing]
Oh. Hold on.
This wasn't here before. Was it?
No. I added some new ones.
-Hmm.
-Oh.
Aren't you the best?
Yeah. Well, nothing inspires you
like a good burglary.
-[kisses, chuckles]
-[sighs]
Hey. I noticed
the light and locks you installed.
-Are you expecting to need them?
-It's just me being me.
I also bought us two new phones.
-Oh.
-Uh-huh.
And I installed
a location tracker app, so,
you know, if you ever get worried
about being alone…
[woman exhales]
Did you also get a new computer?
[pages turning]
Henry?
Henry.
Come on. You can't be mad at me for this.
I just wanted to be sure
before I said something to you.
But we can't hide things
from each other, Meera.
We… We're not that couple.
You're… You're right.
I just didn't wanna worry you
if there was nothing to be worried about.
I need to know these things.
How else am I gonna take care of you?
Is everything okay?
Yeah, yeah. Everything's fine.
[melancholy music playing]
I'm sorry.
[Henry] Come here.
I love you so much.
I love you too.
[crickets chirping]
[coyotes yipping]
[lights click, electricity whirring]
[pipes banging]
[button clicking]
[light clicks]
[light clicking]
Henry?
-Henry.
-Hmm?
The power's out.
Looks like it rained earlier.
The storm probably knocked it out.
[breathing heavily]
I'll check the generator.
[Meera] Thank you.
[door opens]
[grunts]
[menacing music playing]
[menacing music swells]
God.
Whoa.
[panting]
[music crescendos]
[whimpering]
[breathing heavily]
-[whimpering]
-[footsteps approaching]
[music swells]
-[Meera whimpers]
-[Henry] Meera.
Okay. You're… You're okay.
Shh.
-[grunting]
-Okay.
[Meera panting]
-Where are they?
-I don't know. Shh.
-[tape rips]
-[Henry] Okay. Come on. Come on. Come on.
[objects clanking]
[glass breaking]
[clanking continues]
[banging]
[objects breaking]
[breathing heavily]
[whispering]
Listen. Stay here. I'll be right back.
-No, no, no. Please don't go. Please.
-Stay. No. I'll be right back.
All right. Stay.
[clanking continues]
[whispers] Okay. Come on.
[inaudible] Come on.
-Henry!
-[man] They're over here!
-[man] Get him!
-[grunting]
-[man 2] Get his gun!
-[man 3] Get him! Get him!
[Meera panting, screams]
Henry!
[thudding]
-[grunts]
-[screams]
[Henry] Go! Run! Go, go, go!
[man] Get him!
-[lock clicks]
-[Henry] Go! Go!
[man] Open the door!
[whimpering, panting]
[door banging]
-[man] Open!
-[Henry grunts]
-Here. Take these keys and get to the car.
-What? What?
I'll lower you down.
-Come on. Please. I've got you. I got you.
-[Meera shakily] Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
-Ahh! Henry! Henry!
-I've got you. Hold on! Hold on!
-[banging]
-Grab onto my arm. I'll lower you down.
-Henry. Henry.
-[man grunts, bangs]
It's okay. Ready?
-Go!
-[Meera screams]
[grunts, pants]
-I'm okay. I'm okay.
-[gunshot]
-Henry! Henry!
-[man shouting]
-Henry! What's happening?
-[man] Get him!
No! No! Don't!
-No! Please. Leave him alone! Please.
-Run! Run! Go!
[intense music playing]
-Okay. [gasping]
-[gun firing]
[gunshots]
Henry!
[breathing heavily]
-[barking]
-Oh my God!
-[strains]
Okay.
[door closing]
No. No.
[gasps]
Please.
-[gun firing]
-[wincing]
[dog whimpers]
[body thuds]
[breath trembling]
[muffled ambient noises]
[glass breaking]
[indistinct chattering]
I'm sorry.
[man] All right, buddy. Come out with me.
How long had it been there in the house?
I had it back in Boston too.
I thought we were not "that couple."
Would you have let me keep it in the house
if you had known about it?
-No.
-That is exactly why I did not tell you.
It's gone now.
-The cops have it.
-Yeah.
Instead of it being stashed
in one of my plants.
I thought it was a good idea.
A fantastic idea. Every home
should have a hidden weapons cache.
It was one gun.
And we're lucky we had it.
Okay. They're here.
[indistinct chatter]
Here they are.
[detective clears throat]
-Who… who are they?
-They're from Eagle Point.
It's a trailer park across town.
[detective] Poor community.
A lot more crime than around here.
He was a career criminal.
Mostly drug-related.
Same for these other two.
We plan on questioning him if we can.
Who?
He's in the ICU at Saint Mary's.
-It's not looking good.
-Wait. They're… they're still alive?
-Just him.
-Troopers are gonna wanna talk to him too.
-I'm sure.
-What are you talking about?
Who are these people?
I know some of their names and faces,
some of the stuff that they've done,
but beyond that…
I might even peg them
for what happened to you folks. Maybe.
You know it seems to fit…
but there's another matter.
A girl from around here
has been missing for a month.
[Morse] Christine Cobb.
Freshman at the community college.
State Police think that these men have
something to do with her disappearance.
And the thing is,
if this guy doesn't pull through,
they might never find her.
Gosh. Her poor family.
I don't think you understand, ma'am.
These men are her family.
[tense music playing]
[music swelling]
[exhales]
[chopping]
Fixed my drafting table.
You're leaving?
Yeah. I'm just gonna get the rest
of the stuff for the housewarming party.
You still wanna have it?
Yeah. Yeah. I think it'd be good for us.
Don't you?
[chopping]
I'm not gonna be gone long,
I'm just going downtown to Grayson's.
They close at eight on Sundays.
Are you okay staying here?
Or you could just not worry
about the party.
-Meera.
-Or fixing furniture.
Stop.
For God's sakes,
you're acting like nothing happened.
Yes. I am trying to.
-You killed these people.
-Who were going to kill us.
But still, does that…
does that even register for you?
Of course, it does!
It makes me sick to my stomach!
[scoffs]
Apparently, not enough
to make you shirk on social obligations.
-We have to get past this.
-It just happened! Okay?
What if there are more of them out there?
How… how do we get past that?
[melancholy music playing]
You're… you're scared.
I am too.
But we… we have been scared before,
and we got through it…
together by fixing the damage.
[Meera breathes shakily]
[softly] Hey.
By inviting friends over,
I'm just… I'm… I'm…
I'm just trying
to get back to normal. That's it.
[Meera breathes heavily]
I can… I can go to the store another day.
No. No, no, no. Just…
Just, um… [sniffles]
Just go.
[sniffles]
You sure?
Yeah. I'm sure. I'll be okay.
I love you, you know.
I love you too.
[sniffling]
[sighs deeply] Mm.
[door closes]
[chopping]
Oh.
Henry?
[car departing]
[voicemail] Hi.
You've reached Henry Parsons.
Please leave a message. [beeps]
Hey. Hey. It's me. It's me.
Well, you're not gonna have
much luck paying
'cause you left your wallet here.
Uh, hopefully, you'll listen to this
before you get there.
[smacks lips] Okay. Bye.
[sniffling]
[exhales softly]
[tense music playing]
Um, you know, I--
You know what? I think I'm gonna try
and catch up to you with it.
[melancholy music playing]
Where are you going?
[car honking]
[car crashing, skidding]
[panting]
[pop music playing]
[papers rustling]
Hey! Where you been?
Did you go for a drive or something?
I tried calling you.
Oh shit. Yeah.
It went straight to voicemail. Sorry.
Is something wrong?
I… I got into an accident.
Oh my… Oh my God. Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I… I was just trying to catch up to you,
and you turned off away from town
towards a hospital.
Yeah. I made a wrong turn.
I barely made it to… to Grayson's on time.
Oh, right. [chuckles]
I realized it, but, thankfully,
the owner said
I could come back next week, so…
-Gotta love small towns. Huh?
-Yeah.
[papers rustling]
Where's your car now?
Uh, they towed it to a body shop.
I just took an Uber home.
Okay. I'll take care of it.
Don't worry.
Good thing is you're okay. Right?
Hmm.
[footsteps receding]
[exhaling]
[floor scraping]
[scraping continues]
[intense music playing]
[panting]
[phone ringing]
Meera?
[menacing music playing]
[cell phone vibrates]
[suspenseful music playing]
Have a good night!
Yeah. Good night.
[woman] Oh, I almost forgot. Um…
-I'm sorry about your party.
-What?
The housewarming party?
I… I got the Evite cancellation.
Oh. Okay.
Okay.
God.
Heard about your accident. You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
This new?
Leather seats. In-dash GPS.
Well, it's my husband's.
There's, uh,
something I think you should know.
The man who broke into your house,
the one that was still alive?
He's not anymore.
Um. Well, um…
Wasn't he in the ICU or something?
And showing signs of improvement.
Anyway,
I figured you might feel better
knowing that it's over.
Thank you.
When did he die?
Sunday night.
Take care.
[GPS beeps]
[intense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[keys jingling]
[seat belt clicks]
[dogs barking]
[barking]
[man coughing]
[objects clanking]
[dogs barking]
[straining]
[knocking on door]
[door creaking]
[suspenseful music playing]
[glass breaking]
[Meera quietly] Oh God.
[squeaking]
[pinwheels squeaking]
The hell are you doing?
-Nothing.
-Don't tell me "nothing."
Why are you snooping around?
I'm not. I just… I…
I just came to visit someone--
Bullshit!
I seen your car here the other day too.
My car? I don't--
I've never been here before.
Mind your business. Do you hear me?
Okay. Okay. I-I'm sorry. I--
What is that?
-This is not mine.
-Give me that.
That's not mine.
You've been videotaping me?
-No.
-Huh?
No, no, no. I just--
I'm telling you it's… it's not mine. I--
No. Please. Please. Please. Please.
-Don't come back here.
-Okay. Okay. Okay.
[wind whooshing]
[thunder rumbling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[crickets chirping]
[camcorder dinging, whirring]
[tape whirring]
My daughter, Christine…
I saw the way he looked at her.
So instead of trying to blame me,
try believing me.
[tape whirring]
[whirs, stops]
[buttons clicking]
[suspenseful music playing]
[keyboard clacking]
[suspenseful music continues]
[cabinet clanking]
[drawer rattling]
[tense music builds]
[mouse clicking]
[suspenseful music swells]
[car lock beeps]
Shit.
-Oh. Hi.
-Hey.
Oh God. [chuckling]
Looks good. Doesn't it?
What?
My office.
I pretty much fixed all the damage.
Oh. I, uh, haven't…
I haven't checked it yet.
[cell phone ringing]
[chuckles] Okay.
[phone continues ringing]
Oh. It's a blocked number.
Um…
-I don't know who that is, actually.
-Oh, hey.
Using the, uh, tracking app.
-Oh yeah. I… I did. Yeah.
-I did too, actually.
-Oh.
-What were you doing across town earlier?
Oh. Um…
Uh. You know, I, um, texted you,
and I got a little worried.
Thing said you were near Eagle Point or…
Oh. Sorry. I actually did come
in here earlier. I… I was gonna vacuum.
[Henry] Hmm.
[laughs]
-With what?
-Well, that's what I was saying.
I… I came in here
and didn't need to do anything.
So… [chuckles nervously]
-So, I'm just gonna go and freshen up.
-[chuckles] Okay.
[footsteps receding]
Oh, hey, I got your car fixed.
Thank you.
Not hungry?
I'm fine.
[Henry sighs deeply]
You never really answered me.
About what you…
you were doing across town earlier.
Nothing. Just…
-Just driving.
-To where?
Um. Ho-home.
From where?
From work.
Hmm.
Seems like a real roundabout way home.
Don't you think?
[chair scrapes on floor]
[tense music plays]
What?
You're not hiding anything from me.
Are you?
What… What would I hide from you?
What would I hide from you, Henry?
Results.
Oh. Um… [chuckles nervously]
No.
I… I… I haven't even been back
to the doctors.
[Henry sighs]
[laughs]
I thought there was
a s-specialist or something
you've been going to around there.
Something you didn't wanna tell me. Hm.
[sighs heavily]
I am… I am so sorry.
[Henry breathing deeply]
[suspenseful music playing]
[mouse clicking]
[pipes banging]
[pipes continue banging]
[exhales softy]
[sighs]
[keyboard clacking]
[music swelling]
-[birds calling]
-[insects chittering]
[groans]
Meera?
[dramatic music playing]
[breathes heavily]
[cell phone ringing]
Hello?
-[receptionist] Meera. Hey. It's Joanne.
-Oh, hi.
I'm sorry to call so early. But we need
to change your schedule around a bit.
-Okay.
-[siren blaring]
[Joanne] Mrs. Hernandez called. She needs
to switch her weekly sessions to Thursdays
-because she has a…
-[siren blares]
I can switch her, but then, I'd have to…
Um. When… when was this?
[policeman 1] Hey. Wanna get out
of the car, man? Come on.
-[policeman 2] I got it.
-[man] Let me go!
Let me go or I swear…
[man] Let go! I didn't mean to hurt her!
[grunting]
You don't understand.
That bitch wanted to!
[Joanne] Meera?
Meera, are you still there?
Yeah. Y-Yes.
I'm… I'm… I'm here. I'm here. Um…
I'll come by later
and take care of everything.
Thank you so much.
[melancholy music playing]
[seat belt clicks]
[wind whooshing]
-Applesauce in the mix?
-[silverware clattering]
Okay. If you say so.
[door opens]
Hey.
Where… where have you been?
I've been trying to call you.
They found that missing girl.
Uh, they… they did? Is she okay?
I don't think so.
How do you know?
Why does he have
one of your envelopes, Henry?
-Who?
-The man who broke into our house.
I went to his trailer.
Two days after you did.
[inhales]
I need you to tell me
you have nothing to do
with any of this, Henry.
Meera…
I need you to tell me why you had
a gun that you never told me about,
or why you have some s-secret password
on your filing cabinet.
And I really need to know why you have
a picture of that missing girl, Henry.
I couldn't do it.
I thought I could, but I couldn't.
Do-- Uh…
Do… do what, Henry? Do what?
I thought if we tightened our belt
for a while,
and, you know,
got a good rate from the bank, um…
What are you talking about?
This house. Meera, look… look at it.
Did you ever ask yourself
how we were able to afford it?
Well, you… you make a good living.
Yeah. I do now.
But that wasn't always the case.
And I didn't wanna say anything
'cause I didn't wanna worry you, but…
our insurance had only covered
so much of your treatments.
We were running on fumes for a while.
Okay. Then, um, how did we afford it?
I had to find a way
to bring construction costs down.
The first step was
taking over as contractor,
and the second step was
making the IRS think
I pretty much built it alone.
But you had dozens of people building it.
Yeah. And that girl's father
was one of them.
And I knew he was a junkie,
but I didn't know he was violent
until one day
his daughter drops by the job site,
the same day
that photo must have been taken.
And she crashed his truck, like,
jumped the curb or something.
And he just starts wailing on her
in front of everybody.
I couldn't believe it. And I fired him,
right there on the spot.
And he promised me
that I was gonna pay for it,
which I did, literally, for…
almost a year.
Every month, in that envelope,
which is what I was hoping
I'd find at his trailer, 'cause I think
it's the only proof there is.
But I don't understand.
If money was the issue in the first place,
why would you pay him?
I was committing fraud.
I could've gone to prison.
-So could have he.
-But he didn't care.
This is a guy who, instead of worrying
about his missing daughter,
he decided
to break into our house be-because…
Because why?
'Cause I stopped paying him.
Oh.
Jesus, Henry.
Look. All I… all I ever wanted was for us
to be happy. It's why I built the house.
We were given a chance
to grow old together, and I…
I wanted to do that
somewhere that felt like a home.
N-Not… Not a house. A home.
And I… I made some mistakes.
But now you know what they are.
I got nothing else to hide.
And as… as for the, uh,
the code on my filing cabinet,
I wouldn't exactly call it a secret.
It's 0-8-1-2.
August 12th.
Our anniversary.
I'm sorry.
[melancholy music playing]
[door opens]
[keyboard clacking]
[exhales]
[cell phone vibrates]
[cell phone vibrating]
[soft instrumental music playing]
[cell phone vibrates]
[chuckles]
[sighs heavily]
[Joanne] …to be here Wednesday--
Please hold.
-Meera?
-Yeah?
-This package came in the mail for you.
-What's that?
Oh yeah. Thanks.
Do you wanna keep it? It's a video camera.
-Why would I keep it?
-Maybe for your son.
Oh. Well… [laughs] …you know,
I assume he'd just use his phone. Right?
[phone ringing]
-Right.
-[Joanne] Okay.
Okay. Bye.
[wind whooshing]
-[Meera] Okay. This looks good. Right?
-[spraying]
Yeah, yeah. Definitely. Hey, um,
maybe try putting all the big ones
on the same side?
Kinda like it not being too matchy-matchy.
I just design things for a living.
What do I know?
Not how to shut up and clean, apparently.
[laughs]
Yeah. Biryani, pot roast.
Oh, and the salad.
-Yeah. That should be good.
-Plus the whore d'oeuvres.
The what?
Uh, whore d'oeuvres?
[laughs]
What? Huh? [chuckles]
-Uh, it's hors d'oeuvres.
-What did I say?
-You did not say that.
-Okay. Spell it.
-Okay.
-Mm-hmm.
H-O--
-H-O-R…
-Uh, uh…
Not so smart, after all. Are we?
-Just trust me. It's hors d'oeuvres.
-Okay.
Please tell me
you've called it that in public.
Proudly.
-[laughing]
-[car horn honks]
-Oh my God, you're crazy.
-Uh, someone's here early.
Oh. That's Bill and Joanne.
Okay. I'm gonna go check in
on the biryani, and the "whores."
-[laughing]
-[door opening]
[Bill] Hey, Henry.
-Hey. I hope we're not too early.
-You're right on time. Come on up.
["Coming Home" by Leon Bridges playing]
♪ Baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ I'm coming home ♪
♪ To your tender sweet loving ♪
♪ You're my one and only woman ♪
♪ The world leaves a bitter taste ♪
♪ In my mouth, girl ♪
♪ You're the only one that I want ♪
♪ I wanna be around ♪
[inaudible dialogue]
♪ I wanna be around, girl ♪
♪ I wanna be around, girl ♪
♪ Ooh, I wanna be around ♪
♪ I need you, baby… ♪
It's like these guys…
Hey, guys. I just wanted you to know
that dessert will be out in a minute.
Thanks. The game's
pretty much over anyway.
Uh. You can-- I'll take the rest.
Don't worry. Thank you so much.
[news program music plays on TV]
[reporter] Tune in tonight
for our special report
on an Eagle Point man
who was arraigned today in district court
for charges of animal cruelty.
The lead investigator in the case made
the following statement earlier today.
Officers found several dogs locked up
in Mr. Oxbow's shed.
Most had severe cuts and bite marks
from being forced to participate
in illegal dog fights.
And one dog,
a female, was found dead at the scene.
Clint Oxbow was also a person of interest
in the disappearance
of local college student Christine Cobb
but has since been dismissed as a suspect.
[intense music playing and swelling]
[breathes deeply]
This is Dylan Cobb. I know what
you police think of me and my family,
but none of that matters anymore.
The only thing that matters now
is me finding my little girl.
Listen to me very carefully.
I've been in that house before,
before the other night.
I worked on it when it was being built.
My daughter, Christine, came over one day,
and I saw the way he looked at her.
So, when she came up missing,
the son of a bitch
was the first person I thought of.
We waited till one night nobody was home.
Took my dog, Hershel.
Sure enough,
barking like crazy,
especially in the office.
That guy's got
more evidence in that house.
I know it! So instead of trying--
[intense music playing]
[light switch clicks]
[keypad beeping]
[cabinet unlocks]
[drawer slides open]
-Here you go. Shh.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
-You got it.
-All right.
-Cheers.
Nice stretch of land you got here, Henry.
[chuckles] A lot of privacy.
Yeah.
[suspenseful music playing]
[papers rustling]
[suspenseful music builds]
[exhales]
[object clatters]
[suspenseful music swells]
[door creaking]
[sinister music playing]
[Meera softly] Oh God.
Mm.
[bolt creaks]
[door unbolts]
[breathes deeply]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Meera] Hello?
Oh.
[breath trembling]
[whispering] Oh my God.
[Meera breathing shakily]
Hello?
[gasps]
Hello, Christine?
Okay.
[breathes shakily]
Christine?
Oh my God.
[screams]
[pipes banging]
No, no, no. Stop.
It's okay, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
-Just trust me. Okay?
-[Christine whimpers]
Listen to me. There are people upstairs.
I'm gonna get some help. Okay?
-[sniffling]
-Trust me.
You're gonna be okay.
I'll be right back. I'll be right back.
Ahh!
[panting]
Henry.
What… what are you?
Um… I'm… I'm…
your husband.
It's just the urges that…
[breathes shakily]
…I've always had.
Well, I… I didn't wanna be this way.
I didn't choose to be this way.
[breath trembling]
This is why you built this house.
It was not for us.
[crying]
This is how there is an us.
[breathing heavily]
[chuckles softly]
What are you doing, Meera?
Meera, please put… put it away, put the--
Meera, put the phone down.
Put down that phone.
[Meera screams]
No!
[Meera groans]
After everything I've done for you.
[Meera whimpers]
[clanking]
[Meera] No, no, no.
[moaning]
I have always been there for you,
no matter what.
[Meera] No, no, no.
Henry, this isn't at all the same thing.
This isn't the same thing.
Let me ask you.
Did you choose for those things to happen?
Hmm?
The cancer?
The infertility that it caused?
-The depression? No.
-[breath shuddering]
Your biology and your genetics,
they chose for you.
And mine chose this.
-Meera…
-[breath trembling]
…now you're going to be here for me.
[breathes shakily, groans]
No. Henry.
No, no, no, no, no.
Henry, don't let me-- Don't leave me!
[screaming] Help! Someone help! Help me!
Henry! Henry!
Ahh!
[indistinct conversation]
Whoa! [shushing]
Yeah. I tripped, and I banged
my nose helping Meera to bed.
Is she feeling okay?
Yeah, yeah. She's fine,
just one too many mojitos
is all, you know?
Anyway, I'm, uh…
I'm sorry I have to do this,
but I think
we're gonna have to call it a night.
[chuckles]
-[Bill] Yeah, yeah.
-Okay.
-[Bill] Thank you.
-Bye, guys. Drive safe.
[indistinct conversation]
[lock clicking]
[sinister music playing]
[woman] Good night, guys. Drive safe.
[cars starting]
[clanking, rattling]
[Meera cries, strains]
[chains rattling]
[grunting]
[Christine] Who are you?
[panting]
My name is Meera.
You know him?
I… I thought I did.
[breathes shakily]
What… What did he do… What'd he do to you?
I don't know.
[voice breaks] I barely remember.
I just remember being out one night,
and then I woke up here like this.
[sobs]
[cries] I don't even know
how long it's been.
He comes down here…
and he just sits there
with…
with the bat.
And all he ever says is,
"I decide when."
[crying]
♪ Sometimes loving ♪
♪ Is so, so hard to do ♪
♪ And there are times we hurt each other ♪
♪ Just try to make it through ♪
♪ We've come too far together ♪
♪ Holding on to… ♪
[chuckles]
♪ Try to keep my heart true ♪
♪ Never gonna say ♪
♪ 'Cause baby… ♪
[song fades]
[menacing music swelling]
[grunting]
[cries] Please help me.
Please!
[panting]
Okay, okay.
Let's get this out. You're okay.
Okay. Okay.
-[sobbing]
-It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
You're okay. You're okay. You're okay.
It's okay.
[door unlocks]
He's coming.
Meera? Honey?
We can get through this.
I know… I know we can.
And we can find a way
to trust each other again,
'cause there's… there's no more secrets,
and… and there's nothing else to hide.
[intense music playing]
[inaudible]
[screaming]
[Henry screams]
Ahh!
No. This way. This way. This way.
[lock clicking]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
You know,
you used to lie on the floor for…
for hours.
Yeah. You were too weak.
You couldn't get up.
Remember that, Meera?
'Cause I do.
Yeah. Because I had to carry you to bed
every night.
Bring you your food,
bring you to the bathroom.
You see, that's what you do
for the people that you love.
You don't turn on 'em. Okay?
You don't abandon them
when things get… get hard or…
or uncomfortable.
So you're gonna choose her over me? Hmm?
Over… over us?
O-Okay. [chuckles] All right.
You're gonna save her?
Hmm?
Take care of her?
[scoffs]
You can't even take care of yourself.
[footsteps receding]
[whispering] Christine, listen to me.
-[intense music playing]
-[screaming]
-No! Run! Go. Run!
-[knife clatters]
[dishes clattering]
Help me! Help!
[voice echoing] Help! Help! Help!
Help!
[Henry grunting]
[intense music swelling]
[Christine whimpering]
No!
[screaming]
[Meera] No.
[Christine shrieking]
No! Help!
[screaming continues]
[grunts]
[voice echoing] No! Please!
Please! Please! Please!
[voice echoing] Please! No! No! No!
Please. Please. Please. Please. Please.
-[panting]
-[Christine crying]
I told you. I told you.
I decide when.
No. Please. [screaming] No!
[Henry gasping in pain]
[groans]
[screams, groans in pain]
[gasping]
-[breathing shakily]
-[Henry mumbles]
But who'll take care of you?
[breathing shakily]
I will.
[gasps]
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
-It's okay. It's okay.
-[gasps]
[Meera] Okay.
-Come on.
-[Christine cries]
Go. Go. Go.
[breathing heavily]
[gasps, gurgles]
[exhaling]
[somber music playing]
-[insects chittering]
-[birds calling]
[wind whooshing]
[melancholy music playing]
[intense music playing]
[soft instrumental music playing]
[melancholy music playing]