Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
When the primal chaos
was first differentiated,
the light and clear qi
ascended to be the sky
while the heavy and turbid qi
- descended to be the earth...
- Stop.
I don't get it.
That is,
when heaven and earth
were first separated,
the first demon was born.
His name was
primordium.
He was
the ancestor of myriad demons.
Primordium was almighty
as the progenitor of demons.
He sought to rule the three realms.
The bodhisattvas could not subdue him.
All the heavenly generals
and daluo golden immortals
were utterly defeated by him.
Eventually,
a disciple of Buddha
exerted all his qi energy
to seal primordium
once and for all
into the darkest
and coldest reaches of the earth.
Well done.
The origin of demons
is that all?
That's all.
It's just another cooked-up tale.
I could say I am
the father of the great ancestor!
Bajie,
don't curse ancestors, not even a demon.
Then tell me.
What is so great about this primordium?
According to this book,
wherever primordium set foot,
no life remained.
He could even change any living thing
into a demon.
Do you actually believe that?
The book even says
great sage equaling heaven
is all-powerful.
Yet, the monkey is now one of us
on a pilgrimage for scriptures.
That's my brochure!
My brother, you're never sure.
Against myriad worldly thoughts,
stick with our heart chakra.
If we don't understand fully,
resort to zen quotes.
With Buddha in mind,
we will see all sentient beings.
My dearest wukong,
when are you coming back?
What is with this melancholy, master?
Why are you crying?
Seeing you heartbroken,
I also feel sad.
Master, I'm so pathetic.
My tummy rumbled again.
Bajie, it was me.
I'm starving.
It's that shitty monkey's fault.
Where did he go?
Master is so hungry that he cried!
I shed a tear
for this world.
What the...
Bajie,
monks should not ingratiate themselves
or speak vulgarly.
No, I mean that whatever the tear is for,
I will wipe it.
Cool as usual.
This shitty monkey
never does anything good.
Did you make such a fuss
only to bring back a bowl of water?
Shut it.
My entrance must always be cool.
Master!
Master, this monkey always
causes trouble like a demon
because you spoil him.
Bajie,
all sentient beings dwell
in the ten worlds,
which include the six realms of rebirth.
There are tens of millions of demons.
However,
what exactly is a demon?
The book says
that all things endowed
have their own soul.
Yet,
we demons have never had a proper soul.
Master,
once we have acquired the scriptures,
will we have a soul?
Wujing,
when you think it is there,
it will be there.
A soul?
It's not worth a shit.
Wuzhuang temple
My goodness!
How sweet and dewy
these patronesses are!
Look!
Are you from the great tang in the east?
The ones on a pilgrimage to the west?
They are actually males.
Astute observation, children.
Exactly.
My Buddhist name is xuanzang.
Come with us.
This must be a well-to-do family.
Sumptuous.
Children, who is your master?
Our master's taoist name is zhenyuanzi.
The primeval lord of heaven
invited him to a banquet.
So it's great immortal zhenyuan.
Remarkable.
Try our vegetarian meal later.
Many immortals make
a trip here just to burn it off us.
Marvelous.
I can already tell you are hungry.
We are.
Just wait, then.
Hey, monkey! No touching!
You can't afford to break anything.
Watch your mouth.
You can't afford to irritate me.
You...
Let's go. Just ignore him.
Heavenly lake
So you don't worship the three pure ones?
How arrogant!
Wukong,
you are in my way.
Troublesome.
Look at how poor he is.
I don't know why master would
pluck our precious treasure
for him to eat.
Exactly. What a waste!
Pure wind, how about this?
Let's eat it.
What if master finds out?
Just give them enough food
and send them away before master returns.
Treasure?
Where has the monkey gone again?
You almost scared me to death.
Why are you not dead yet?
Beat it.
Guess what?
They have a treasure in this temple
- that is edible.
- Tell me now.
I just love to talk slowly.
Are you telling or not?
Okay, I will.
The kids said
that the treasure is so good,
they must keep it from us.
They will keep it from me?
Then I will have to eat it.
See?
That's why master dotes on you.
You are the real deal. A tough guy!
Get up here.
I nearly had my guts squeezed out!
Impressive.
What a big pit!
It really is a treasure.
Let's pick some and have a taste.
Look, wukong.
Lord monkey.
Mr. Great sage.
Make it quick!
Hurry, will you?
How impatient.
Down you come!
I can sense both heavenly
and demonic energy.
That's weird.
Come on out!
My greetings, great sage.
- I am the local god of long...
- 4-009, my ass.
You stole my treasure.
Now, you want to tell me your name?
You're mistaken!
I would never dare to mess with you.
- I am just a small...
- Bigger.
- Stop.
- A small and humble spirit.
If you don't hand it over,
I will turn your earth.
Out with it. Where is it hidden?
This treasure
is known as grass-returning cinnabar
or manfruit.
It takes at least 10,000 years
to grow from blossom to ripened fruit.
Only 30 fruits are formed
in one harvest.
If you eat one,
you would live
for 47,000 years.
What is the use in living that long?
I only care if it is tasty.
Go on.
Hold on.
The manfruits
fear only the five elements.
If they meet metal, they fall.
If they meet wood, they rot.
If they meet water, they dissolve.
If they meet fire, they burn.
And if they meet the earth, they sink.
Great sage!
It really is an amazing treasure.
So it went into the earth.
Great sage, although the fruit is good,
this tree...
Okay, stop blabbering. Leave.
Great sage, don't touch this tree!
Let's do it here.
We should wait
for them to leave before eating it.
I still feel nervous.
What are you waiting for?
Once it is picked, the fruit won't keep.
Awesome.
Wukong, pretty please.
Can I get a bite?
I was so excited
that I finished it in one gulp.
I didn't even taste its flavor.
Oh no!
Six, seven, eight, nine.
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen!
Twenty-one!
Twenty-two!
Twenty-three!
Twenty-four!
- Four short!
Get one yourself.
Venerable monkey!
Could you get
one last fruit for me?
I'll kick your ass
if you don't shut up.
You are shameless!
Stinking monster!
You ate our treasured fruit!
I didn't.
You did.
- You did!
I didn't.
We did.
So what?
You hairy-faced monster!
You're despicable!
Wukong,
what happened?
Monk, don't pretend to be ignorant!
I plucked the manfruits.
I also ate them.
My master had no idea.
It's up to you
to punch me or punish me.
Gods above, lend me your power.
Wukong, don't fight back.
Children, don't drive him mad.
You poor monk.
How could you encourage your disciples
to steal?
Four are missing.
It was obviously
one for each of you!
I admit to eating it,
but not to the amount you said.
We only ate three!
-Fouh -three!
Four!
It was indeed three.
- It was four!
- Three.
Three!
Wait. What did you eat behind my back?
-Fouh -fouh
wukong, what did you eat?
Stop pretending, monk.
Your innocent look really makes me sick.
It has nothing to do with him.
I'll make it up to you.
Until our master returns,
you aren't going anywhere!
Get lost.
Wukong, take a deep breath.
Hold your horses.
Who do you think he is?
A bastard monkey with no parents.
What can he do?
Who did you calla bastard?
Monkey, they cursed you.
Yes, I just cursed you.
You are merely a demon
that does nothing but evil.
Then I'll show you what evil is!
Oi of the eight classes of being!
Wukong!
You two bit off more than you can chew!
Return to wuzhuang temple at once!
Evil monkey,
if you dare to touch a single leaf,
great immortal zhenyuan won't let you off!
I will kick the shit out of him as well!
Pure wind, what do we do?
Go all out with this evil monkey!
Great.
Then I will send you both
to hell!
Wukong!
This is a disaster!
We are toast.
Pure wind! Bright moon!
Master, tang sanzang
allowed his evil disciples
to steal our treasured fruits!
The evil monkey, sun wukong,
even destroyed the magic tree!
All disciples,
deploy the demon-quelling array!
Without my command,
no one is to leave his position!
- Yes, master!
Forgive me, great immortal zhenyuan.
It is my failure in disciplining them.
I am willing to be punished.
I have treated you with courtesy,
yet you indulged your pupil's wicked ways.
I ate the manfruit.
I kicked down the tree.
Come at me.
Cheeky ape!
Your target is the monkey.
Why did you hit me?
Old jerk, don't run!
Great immortal,
please calm down!
Master, the array is broken!
Golden cicada,
how have you been?
Wukong!
There is no time.
Draw in!
Stupid demons!
Pure wind, bright moon, take your orders.
- Yes, master.
Report to the Jade emperor at once.
This monkey, sun wukong,
took down the magic tree
and released primordium, the primal demon!
- Yes, master!
Primordium, the primal demon?
Is there really such a demon?
You lot have committed a heinous crime.
Await punishment from heaven.
What is our crime?
This manfruit tree
was created by the qi energy
of a disciple of Buddha.
Its roots impaled primordium's acupoints
to keep him sealed in the ground.
It is just a demon.
Why is the patriarch of
the earth's immortals so scared?
I'm going to save my master.
While I'm at it, I'll get the demon too.
Easier said than done.
In three days,
primordium's original body
will be restored.
When he devours your master
and gains golden cicada's
ten lifetimes of cultivation,
chaos
and fatal destruction
will beset the three realms.
There is no demon that I cannot subdue!
You overestimate yourself.
What if I can do it?
What if you can't?
I'll be at your disposal!
All right.
If you fail to catch primordium,
you will once again be imprisoned
beneath five elements mountain
and never taste freedom.
All right.
You have a deal.
That's a deal.
Come on.
Let's save master.
Monkey, that's the ancestor of all demons!
Shut up!
But...
Where did this wild demon come from?
How dare he?
He's big enough to feed us for a few days.
What kind of demon is it?
Are you blind?
It's just a giant salamander.
Piss off! You're the blind one.
No giant salamander is this ugly.
State your name and die.
Primordium.
I am king white brows of millennium peak.
My minions and I
congratulate you on your revival,
ancestor of demons!
Primordium, the primal demon.
Yes.
Exactly!
Congratulations on your revival, ancestor.
We have been waiting for a long time.
My revival.
During those thousands of years in hell,
your qi energy
turned me into this form.
My body
was devoured by the dark earth.
It was all because of you!
Golden cicada,
in three days,
I will
once again rule over the three realms!
- My goodness! Such power!
Before my original body is restored,
take care of this monk.
Don't worry.
Leave him to us.
Wukong!
Help!
Ancestor, this monk's head disciple
is not to be messed with.
He is the powerful sun wukong,
king of demons,
who wreaked havoc at the temple in heaven
500 years ago.
The king of demons?
In the absence of a tiger,
even a monkey can take the throne.
Good point, ancestor.
Sun wukong is indeed a monkey!
We're only telling Jade emperor
that the monkey released primordium.
Don't say too much.
Pure wind, will we get in trouble too?
Don't you get it?
We need to lay the blame on that monkey.
I get it now.
Virupaksa,
we have an urgent report for his majesty.
Please let us pass.
No hurry, children.
Please wait
as I write the notification.
Heavenly king,
our master is
the patriarch of the earth's immortals.
No hurry, children.
Whoever he is,
matters must be handled impartially.
Then go ahead. Be quick.
Wukong, we must find the primal demon
before his body is restored.
Let's drop it.
We have searched all night.
Even if we do find primordium,
master must be dead already.
Bajie, don't curse master.
It's master's ghost!
Don't come to me!
Master, please forgive bajie.
Master, I will keep my mouth shut.
Please go and be reincarnated.
I shouldn't have cursed you.
Where are you from, demon?
Answer or I will bust your ass.
It's comfy.
What kind of demon are you?
I'm not a demon.
I'm qi energy.
Qi energy?
Yes!
I am qi energy.
I can catch primordium and seal him away.
I heard you were looking for primordium,
so I followed you.
Are you the qi energy
that sealed primordium under the tree?
Yes!
Do you know me?
Come here, little thing.
You're not a demon.
But we are.
Are you not afraid?
All sentient beings
dwell in the ten worlds,
which include the six realms of rebirth.
There are tens of millions of demons.
Stop it.
Qi energy, my ass.
You're just a manfruit spirit.
Primordium, where are you hiding?
Gently!
Great sage!
I just escaped from longevity mountain.
Why did you bring me back?
Why were you running?
You released primordium.
If I don't run,
I will be dead meat.
Tell me. Where is primordium hiding?
Great sage,
this is the mountain deity's territory.
He knows every move made
within the territory.
Mountain deity?
Go and bring him to me.
The mountain deity
dwells in five blessings peak.
He is an immortal with a temple.
A humble spirit like me
can't make him do anything.
I'll go see him myself.
Great sage,
primordium must be hiding
somewhere in the dark.
A demon can't be too careful
when restoring himself.
The qi energy that sealed primordium
has taken a human form
after 10,000 years of cultivation.
If he were to help you...
You have become senile.
How could that fruit spirit
seal primordium?
Wukong, look.
It is what the book says.
"A disciple of Buddha
had to exert all his qi energy
to subdue primordium."
Are those three demons looking for me?
Golden cicada,
do you really think
that they can save you?
I took them as disciples
to unite them.
A hateful demon,
a greedy monster,
and an ignorant devil.
Unite them?
Golden cicada,
you should stop dreaming.
All sentient beings are equal,
whether demon, monster, ghost,
human, deity, immortal, or spirit.
As long as we are
of one mind and one soul,
that will be enough.
Demons
have no such thing!
Great master,
you sacrificed your life
to save the world
and gave peace to future generations.
I am deeply impressed.
Fish brains,
take fruitie to five blessings peak.
Fruitie!
Let's go!
You're running?
It smells good!
Whose pig is that?
Here you are!
Get lost if you're not buying.
Brat!
Leave. Move it!
- Run!
- Wait for me!
Come on!
Come.
I love eating this!
- Demon!
- A demon!
A demon!
There is a demon!
Look at this cloth and color.
Red and green really suit your wife.
Demon!
A fruit spirit eating fruit?
How cruel!
Hide inside.
- King white brows.
- All-powerful.
- Almighty.
- A king unmatched.
Who are you
to stand in the way of king white brows?
I am...
Master shaves brows.
Cut up this scum into pieces
and eradicate that qi energy!
Golden cudgel?
Sun wukong, the king of demon?
No, stay back!
I won't hurt you!
Monkey!
Don't let that qi energy escape!
Chaseifl
catch that qi energy!
Monkey!
Don't leave us behind, my lord!
Let's go.
Those folks won't survive.
Life is fleeting.
Get used to it.
Father!
Amitébha.
Master?
What happened, father?
My son!
My son.
Great master, what's wrong?
This boy is a glutton
just like me.
Bajie, you like meat.
He's more like master.
He only likes fruit.
Fruitie, hop on!
Ancestor!
Ancestor,
I was just about
to finish off that qi energy
when all of a sudden
sun wukong turned up
with his golden cudgel
and took my men by surprise!
Bunch of losers.
Ancestor!
I have another brilliant plan!
Sun wukong.
Why must the mountain deity
live at the top of the mountain?
I'm exhausted.
When we confront primordium,
stay as far away as you can.
I'm going to seal him
and help you save your master.
Stop it.
He's my master.
I can save him.
Poor mountain deity,
you're so unpopular.
Your tributes have spoiled,
but no one's here to change them for you!
His Dharma body isn't here.
Bajie, search the mountain with Sandy.
I will wait right here for him.
I'm not going.
He may be gone,
but his temple is still here.
Wouldn't it be sweet if we all wait here?
Are you going or not?
No, find someone else who wants to.
Monkey!
Monkey, I admire you so much.
If I can't do it, who can?
Sandy, why are you just standing there?
Come with me!
Mountain deity temple
Monkey, I want some water!
Troublesome!
Monkey, I want to pee.
Hold it in.
It's comfy.
Not even my master
dares to piss on my head!
You're so annoying! Get off!
Sun wukong!
Give me the qi energy.
Fat chance.
Everyone is here.
Wind raccoon dog!
Wind raccoon dog.
This name rings a bell.
I found it!
"Wind raccoon dog,
a beast born from the wind,
comes and goes without a trace.
It can't be killed by fire or blade.
Only hammer strikes
by the thousands can kill it.
A gust of wind into its mouth
immediately revives it.
Stinker, aren't you fast?
Keep running!
Look.
Now, you're wind raccoon dog jerky!
It's all ruined!
No, it's all ruined!
My temple!
What happened to it?
Who did this?
I won't spare him!
Spill it. Where is primordium?
Aren't you the great sage?
After over 500 years of suppression,
how are you still so handsome?
Answer me. Where is primordium?
Great sage,
you released primordium, didn't you?
Why are you asking me?
I know where he is.
Quick! Come with me!
Move your ass!
Follow me now!
Go! Keep up with him!
Great sage,
maybe I'm talking too much,
but demons all over must be coming
to celebrate their ancestor's revival.
Armies of demons must be on the way.
Even a fierce tiger
is no match for a wolf pack.
Besides, he is primordium.
- He is...
- Big beard, don't worry.
Here I am.
I can seal primordium away.
The qi energy has taken a human form.
If he uses qi energy,
he will deplete it one day.
What happens then?
What do you think will happen?
He'll die?
Once his qi is depleted,
he won't be reincarnated.
Great sage,
primordium is hiding over there.
This mountain is called millennium peak.
Millennium peak?
I must go.
The plants on the mountain
cannot live without me.
Just go.
Excuse me, then.
See you later.
Hold on.
Thank you, great sage.
Take my advice.
Don't sacrifice yourself.
If you seek help from Buddha now,
there might still be a way.
My lord!
Demons from mount crow
of the eastern continent
request an audience!
My lord!
Western continent's nine-headed monster
has entered millennium peak with his men!
My lord!
Demons from mount meru
have come to pay their respects!
I am tawny lion from tiger's jaws cave
at leopard's head mountain.
Multiple-eyed creature
from ghost king mountain.
Nine-tailed Vixen
from dragon-suppressing cave.
We're from lotus cave
at flat peak mountain.
Golden horn.
Silver horn.
Congratulations on your revival
with your original body!
Monkey, when do we attack primordium?
Sleep now.
No, I won't.
Sleep.
Are you sleeping or not?
Why is your name three syllables
while mine is two syllables?
Fruitie was just off the top of my head.
I love being called fruitie.
I love this name!
That's not really even a name.
So who gave you the name sun wukong?
My master.
Do you know?
It's a terrible-sounding name.
It doesn't matter
as long as I know who I am.
Do you know who you are?
I'm a demon
that does nothing but evil.
There are good and evil demons.
Not all demons do evil.
Are you sleeping or not?
I'm an evil demon.
Don't you fear me?
You are not evil.
You have a kind soul.
I don't have a soul.
Why?
I was born from a stone!
A hard stone with no parents
and covered in hair.
That's so cool!
I like stone monkeys.
Cool, my ass.
You're always blabbering,
just like my master.
So promise me.
Let's fetch scriptures together
after we defeat primordium.
Okay, I promise.
Monkey, you're so kind.
He's asleep.
Are we going without fruitie?
Shut it. We can't go with him.
I started this.
I will finish the fight on my own.
Wukong,
we ate those manfruits together.
Sandy is right.
Hog all the fun for yourself?
No way!
Okay.
We haven't had a group battle in a while.
Scumbags,
take this cracking rake
from your piggy daddy!
800 ii of flowing sands
within which all shall sink!
Hammer of ninefold numinosity!
Marshal of the heavenly canopy?
You're nothing but a stupid pig.
Do you think you will win with your bulk?
You didn't see
the no man's land
where white bones lie uncollected.
The one with all the eyes!
Do you see now?
That's so lame.
Play it to yama in hell!
Everyone, charge!
Kill this pig!
Sun wukong!
I called your name. Dare you answer?
Sun wukong, I called your name.
Dare you answer?
Who are you to say my full name?
Buddy, use another magic weapon!
Why won't he answer me?
You can keep trying.
I'm leaving first.
All the demons in the world
have become so weak.
The weak
don't deserve to live.
Sun wukong,
give me the qi energy.
Screw you!
Give me my master!
You all are seeking death.
Is that all you have got?
Wukong, tell fruitie
to use qi energy now!
If he depletes it,
fruitie will die.
There you are.
Monkey!
Piggy!
Sandy!
Monkey!
Fruitie, don't come out!
Wukong!
I will fight you to the death!
Old demon!
Bajie!
Sandy!
Piggy!
It's your turn, qi energy.
Take on a human form,
suffer as a human!
You are such an idiot.
Monkey!
Fruitie!
Run!
Get out of here!
Monkey!
Let me give you a hand
to unite you in death.
Wukong!
- Wukong!
- Master!
Master!
Golden cicada,
all your disciples are here.
But none of them can save you.
As master and disciples,
I am content with this fate.
Even if we are killed,
our souls will never die.
Give me your golden Dharma body!
Master.
Monkey, here!
Go away.
Monkey, you promised to take me along
on the pilgrimage for scriptures!
- Fruitie, go!
- No!
Monkey!
Don't hurt him!
Only I can help them
alleviate their pain
and return them to the primal chaos.
Sun wukong,
do you really deserve
to be king of demons?
You have lost.
Lost?
I would
rather die
than admit defeat!
Then you shall die!
Monkey!
Don't forget
that his golden Dharma body is inside me.
This is my world.
Compliant golden cudgel
Who the heck are you?
Primordium,
now I will tell you
who I am!
Icome
from water curtain cave
at flowers and fruit mountain.
I am the great sage equaling heaven,
king of demons,
sun wukong!
Screw you!
Remember.
In this world,
I am the strongest demon!
I am a demon.
But the biggest difference between us is
I have a soul.
Wukong.
Master!
This magic tree's life root is damaged.
Not even I can bring it back to life.
Goddess of mercy, who can heal it?
I will find them!
Cheeky ape,
the way to save this magic tree
is right in your own hands, isn't it?
Fruitie!
Monkey!
I want to go on the pilgrimage with you!
No hurry, children.