Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
In other news,
authorities are
still investigating
a suspicious fire at the
Abernathy State Mental hospital.
Although one unidentified body
has been recovered
from the ashes,
several staff and
high-security patients
remain unaccounted for
and it is not clear
if they all perished in the
fire or if some of the inmates
may have escaped from
the burning building.
Not bad, huh?
It's going to be the
jewel of the neighborhood
when we're done.
I still say it's kinda creepy.
Oh, come on.
It's gonna be fun fixing it up.
And it's even closer
to your school.
I can sleep in an
extra five minutes.
Whoo hoo.
You're welcome.
Hello?
-Hi, I'm Frank.
-Hi, I'm Maggie.
I see you bought
the old place.
Yes. It's a beauty.
Gonna need a lot
of work though.
Mom? Mom is that you?
Hello?
-Oh my.
-Geez.
No more coffee for you.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm just a
little light headed.
That was quite the
scare you gave me.
Why don't you sit
down for a second?
Mom, I'm fine.
I think I just
freaked myself out.
I heard noises.
It's an old house.
They do that.
You'll get used to it.
I still don't get
why we had to move,
especially to an old
house in the same town.
Sometimes it's good
to have a fresh start,
make new memories.
You say that like
the old ones are bad.
Oh no, baby.
They're not bad.
They're just...
A lot.
Looks like you've already
started on your room
and you are still holding
onto that old music box.
-Does it even play anymore?
Not really, but I don't
want to get rid of it.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yep. Never better.
Come on.
Let's get all this
unpacking over with.
Guess I'm moving out.
Man.
Ah.
Oh.
My dear sweet Alex.
I'm watching over you.
Please, don't scream.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I could never hurt you.
My name is Albert.
Albert Beck.
I'm a surg--
I was a surgeon, one of
the best in the world.
So, don't you worry.
I know how beautiful
life is, how precious.
What are you doing here?
I saw the place was empty
and I didn't have
any place to stay.
The last hospital I
was at, I was cured,
So I left.
It was all just a
big misunderstanding.
I just needed them...
I needed them to love me.
My poor Albert.
So sweet.
Who couldn't love you?
I won't tell.
Morning sweetie.
Morning.
I'm leaving in a minute of
you want a ride to school.
Scott's picking me up.
One of the perks of
moving closer, right?
Well, have a good day.
Tell Scott I said hi.
Bye mom.
Morning, beautiful.
Hey.
You all right?
Yeah, it's nothing.
All right, come on.
I'm so glad you called.
This house is creepy as
hell and I'm all alone
because Mom went to
some real estate thing.
So, how's the unpacking going?
Endless.
You never realize how
much stuff you have
until you have to pack
and then unpack it.
It mean it's a good thing
this house is so big.
I need three rooms
just to hold--
Hey, what's up?
This house makes
the weirdest noises.
It's haunted, it's
definitely haunted.
Yeah, that's what I told my mom.
Babe, are you okay?
I'm just gonna get some water.
I'll call you back in a few.
-Okay babe, love you.
Oh no.
Okay.
Pulse is weak.
Irregular heartbeat.
911, what
is your emergency?
I need an ambulance,
721 Charaday Lane.
I have an 18 year old
female she's having cardiac--
I have a girl who's passed out.
I don't know what's
wrong though.
Please send somebody.
Ambulance is on the way.
What is your name, sir?
Nope.
Okay.
Hang in there, beautiful.
Help's on the way.
Paging Dr.
Stavan, Dr. Stavan please.
All nurses
to the nursing station.
Paging
Dr. Bender,
paging Dr.
Bender, please.
Mrs. Newell?
Yes, Doctor.
Your daughter is
doing just fine.
The surgery went very well.
We installed a pacemaker,
but that's just a temporary
fix for her condition.
Her condition?
Alex is suffering from the
same cardiac degeneration
as her father had.
I'm afraid that she's gonna
need a heart transplant
And I can't stress enough
that time is of the essence.
Within six months, maybe sooner.
Alex also has one of
the rarest blood types.
Finding a suitable donor is
gonna be extremely challenging.
Oh God, I can't...
I can't lose my baby girl.
We're gonna do everything
we can to help her.
Come on, let's see
if she's awake.
Okay.
Wow.
Dr. Bender
to the mental ward please.
Dr. Bender.
Paging Dr. Bender,
Paging Dr. Bender.
You're very lucky the paramedics
got there when they did.
There could have been
some serious damage.
I guess I have you
to thank for that.
I didn't call.
I don't understand. If you
didn't call, then who did?
Maybe a good Samaritan walking
by, heard your cry for help.
I don't remember doing that,
but it's still
kinda fuzzy, so I--
If it were me I'd count my
blessings and pay it forward.
Now Alex's pacemaker is wireless
so we can keep track
of any abnormalities
in case they occur.
However, that means
bedrest, minor activity.
We don't want to
worsen your condition.
I added Alex's name to
the transplant list.
So I'll keep you
involved as it develops.
In the meantime,
I recommend hiring
an at-home nurse to keep
an eye on her, help out.
We can't count on the good
Samaritan being there again.
Okay. I'll have the
nurses leave a referral.
-Thank you.
-In the meantime,
she should get some rest.
You had quite a day.
I'll check in on you later.
Are you okay, baby?
Do you need anything?
Mom, nothing's gonna happen.
I'm exhausted.
Try and get some sleep then.
I love you, baby.
I'll bring your
homework by tomorrow.
Bye baby. Love you.
See ya.
It's okay, she's
gonna be all right.
An at-home nurse.
Paging Dr.
Stavan, Dr. Stavan please.
It's clear now this
was meant to be.
Me choosing your
home, meeting you,
And you needing a new heart.
I'll get you that heart, Alex.
I'll even do the
surgery myself...
...to prove how much I love you.
Sleep well, beautiful.
Dr. Beck will take
care of everything.
Chris McCoy.
-Oh, uh...
No.
What are you
doing in my house?
Is your name Chris?
Who the hell are you?
I'm from Midhaven General.
I'm here to notify you
there's been a misunderstanding
regarding your referral.
The family won't be
needing your services
so I'm here to take your place.
Ow.
Man on man.
You did that to yourself.
Oh.
Hi.
I didn't know anyone
else was here.
I'm a friend of Chris'.
You know, she had an accident.
She tripped, she fell.
You
scared me, you dummy.
Hello, this is Chris McCoy.
This is Maggie Newell.
Hello, Mrs. Newell.
-Hi.
-Yeah, the hospital
said you might be calling.
Are you available?
-Yes ma'am.
-Tomorrow?
-Available.
-Noon?
Yes ma'am.
Wow.
It's what the
hospital recommended.
Just to make sure you're okay.
Lucky me.
You know, I've always
wanted...whatever that is.
That must be the nurse.
You mean my babysitter?
Alex, play nice.
-Okay.
-I'll be right back.
Why don't you sit down?
I'm fine.
Really, go.
Maggie. I'm nurse McCoy.
But you can call me Chris.
Oh, hi.
Sorry. I just, well
I wasn't expecting--
That's all right, I've
heard it all before.
But experience only
comes with time, right?
That's true.
Please, come in.
I'd love to.
What a lovely home.
Oh, thank you.
Still have a lot of work to do.
You're renovating.
Yeah. I adore these old
Victorians, kinda my thing.
Saving places like this.
You ever heard of St Agatha's?
No.
It's an old hospital on
the outskirts of town.
Been abandoned for years.
Our company just purchased it
and I'm renovating that too.
Turning it into a
recreation center.
Nice.
Let me introduce you to Alex.
Mmhmm.
Alex, this is Nurse McCoy.
Please, call me Chris.
Okay, Nurse Chris.
So the hospital said
you had quite the scare.
Yeah, but they
patched me back up.
I actually feel
pretty good right now.
I know what you're thinking,
that a beautiful young
woman like yourself
does not need a babysitter.
So, think of me as your
personal physician,
as if you're a big time
celebrity and I'm on your staff.
Okay, Doc.
I'll need my hand
back eventually.
Just checking your pulse.
All good.
You're so lucky your mom
found you when you collapsed.
Oh, actually I didn't.
Apparently I have a mystery
stalker who called 911.
Stalker?
Sounds more like you have
a guardian angel
watching over you.
Maybe it was Dad.
Well, I should go.
-But--
-I promise you,
she is in excellent hands.
Okay. I'll be back.
Call me if you need anything.
-Okay, love you.
-Love you.
Please.
So this must be sentimental.
Let me guess, first boyfriend.
No, my dad actually.
It reminds me of him.
Oh, I can't think of a better
reason to hang on to it.
Just because something's broken
does not mean it
should be discarded.
Let's check out your equipment
and set up your app, huh?
Okay.
Hey there.
Morning, neighbor.
How's it going?
Hi. Frank, right?
I couldn't help, but notice
your security camera.
Yeah, we had some trouble
with mail theft a while back.
It's motion activated.
Really? How long
does it store footage?
This app gives me live
updates on your pacemaker.
That way I'll be alerted if
ever anything goes wrong.
Also, it has GPS.
So it keeps track of
you if you sleep walk.
You don't sleep walk, do ya?
No.
So, I'm basically a human GPS.
Just to keep you safe.
All right, I'm need to
check your incision,
make sure everything looks good.
Tell me if anything hurts.
It's just sore.
Completely normal.
Means you're healing.
Look at me.
I'm such a freak.
Hardly.
The scar will fade.
Okay. All done.
Okay.
How about some tea?
I make a mean chamomile.
Sure. That sounds good.
'Kay.
Oh, those are lovely.
Yeah. They were in my
hospital room with no card.
I guess my boyfriend sent them
Well, whoever sent them, they
think you're very special.
It doesn't make sense.
There must have been a late
night jogger or a dog Walker.
You saw it.
There was no one.
So who called 911?
Maybe someone heard
it from the backyard.
Why would someone
be in my backyard?
And at that time of night?
We'll spend the day
together, have some lunch.
Maybe go for a walk.
Hi?
I'm Scott, Alex's boyfriend.
You must be the nurse.
Yeah, hi, I'm Chris McCoy.
Shouldn't you be in school?
Yeah, they gave me early release
so I can bring
Alex her homework.
Oh, well, Alex is resting.
It's not a good
time for a visitor.
Well, we've been texting all
day, so she knows I'm coming.
Okay then.
I was just taking
her tea and biscuits.
Yeah, cool. Let's do it.
Son of a--
Hey, I thought I
heard your voice.
What's up? How you feeling?
-Hi.
-I missed you.
Here's your tea.
-Thank you.
-Mmhmm.
And thank you for the flowers.
They're beautiful.
Flowers?
-Yeah.
-They were from you, right?
Yeah, of course.
No, they should've
left the card.
There's, there wasn't a card?
Nuh uh.
Huh, so lame.
Well, they really made my day.
I'm glad.
-You're the best.
-I love you.
I love you too.
You liar!
Liar, liar, liar.
I brought her the flowers.
I got those flowers for her.
I left 'em for you.
It was me.
-It's so hard.
-It's not hard.
All right, so Mr. Sanders
gave us so much homework.
Oh my gosh, I swear he
likes to torture us.
-Yeah, definitely.
-Alex.
You need to rest.
I know, but I'm so bored.
Just like an hour, please?
Okay. One hour.
-Thank you.
-Trust me, bro.
I can get her
anything she needs.
All right, so we have
an entire chapter due.
I'll go downstairs, then?
Yeah, please do.
What the heck
is a logarithm anyway?
-Oh beats me.
I never understood
this stuff anyway.
Okay, so we have an entire
chapter due by Tuesday.
I think we're both
in trouble here.
Oh man.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
This will do perfectly.
Dr.
Beck to the ER.
Dr. Beck, you're
needed in the ER.
Dr. Beck to the ER, urgent.
Dr. Beck to the ER,
Dr. Beck to the ER.
Dr. Beck, you're
needed in the ER.
Hi, Dr. Beck.
Hello, darling.
You're still the greatest
heart doctor in the world.
I know.
There you are.
Got outta your room again I see.
No.
I would love to talk to you,
but I'm needed in surgery.
Stop!
Time for your electrotherapy.
Electrotherapy.
I'm cured.
I don't see fake people anymore.
Like that guy,
especially that guy
in the hat and Hawaiian shirt.
I never see him.
Oh, but you do, Dr. Beck.
You see fake people
all the time.
No, no, no, no.
What do you think I am?
A fake person?
Yeah.
You are so funny.
Get the hell outta my hospital!
Oh man.
AB negative.
Hello.
Benedict, John H, 52.
Heart disease? Pass.
Daniels, Mary age 46
diabetes and chronic smoker.
You're supposed
to treat your body
like a temple, not
a temple of doom.
We only want the best.
Here we go, Carlisle,
Patrick, age 42,
no family history of disease.
Put him in the folder.
And moving on,
Matthews, Gail, age 35,
non smoker, no
underlying disease.
She might be just what
the doctor ordered.
So to speak.
Let's look her up.
She got a dating profile.
Hey, kinda sexy.
Don't be jealous.
You have nothing to worry about.
A woman her age'd
never work out for me.
She's active.
I like that.
She keeps herself in
shape, that's for sure.
In to beer.
Good thing you don't
need her liver.
All in all, I think we
might have a winner.
Let's say hello.
Saw your profile, would
love to meet you in person.
Hoping I can steal...
...your heart.
Too much?
Maybe Albert Beck
hasn't lost his charm.
Oh, I didn't realize
you were here.
Sorry to scare ya.
It's okay. I'm running late.
I'll see you later.
Alex will be down in a minute.
She's just having a shower.
Wow.
Thank you.
You really don't have
to do all of this.
Don't be silly.
The fastest way to heal is
to keep your strength up.
Looks like someone's
got a secret admirer.
No, no.
I just enjoy--
Your phone.
Looks like you've got plans
with a special someone tonight.
Oh, that.
"Looking forward to
meeting you tonight."
Followed by lots of heart
emojis and a few others.
It's nothing. Just a first date.
So, any news on your
good Samaritan?
No.
Now my mom's thinking someone
saw me from the backyard.
Why would anyone be back here?
Well maybe they
saw you from there
and they didn't want to
seem like a peeping Tom.
So why leave their name?
Maybe.
I just wish I knew who it
was so I could thank them.
Yeah. What would you say?
-I'd thank them for noticing me.
-Mmhmm.
You know they had
no idea who I was
and they still cared
enough to help me.
That's unconditional.
Like it was with my dad.
Like your dad.
Wow.
What else?
I'd tell them that
they have no reason
to be afraid to come forward
and reveal who they are.
You know, maybe...maybe they
did something in the past
but it doesn't matter
'cause they still have
a really good heart.
They proved that by caring
about someone they
didn't even know.
Right.
Alex, I um--
What?
Oh, it's Scott.
Hey.
Yeah I know, I want to go.
Of course it is.
-Whoo.
-Whoo is right.
So tell me about you, Chris.
Oh, not much to tell.
I'm in the medical profession.
A doctor!
Well a nurse, actually.
A male nurse.
You don't see too many of those.
Oh, we're more common
than you think.
So, tell me about you.
Divorced, kids?
Never married.
So, no in the kids
department, that I know of.
My family's on the other coast.
So it's just me
doing my own thing.
No baggage.
That is so refreshing to hear.
I'm the same.
Look Chris, you seem
like the type of guy
who goes after what he wants.
Oh I am.
I'm the same way.
I'm not one for wasting time.
When I want something,
I go get it.
That scares a lot of guys off.
Probably the reason
I'm still single.
Probably.
So, what do you say
we cut through all
this pre-foreplay crap
and get to the good stuff?
Your place or mine?
Definitely mine.
You okay?
Mom, I'm fine.
Goodnight, baby.
If you need anything,
just give a shout.
Okay, I love you.
I love you.
Cute place.
Thank you.
A little bit more feminine
than I expected
from a single guy.
Well, I am gonna redecorate.
I just haven't had
time what with work.
What's in here?
Oh, hold on a sec.
Oh, uh...
Uh huh.
That's just for work.
Kinky.
Is she gonna join us?
Why don't I make us
a couple of drinks?
You read my mind.
Back in a sec.
Baby, are you sure about this?
Yeah, come on. Let's go.
Okay.
Cheers!
Oh, yeah.
- Salud.
-Thank you.
-Ha!
-Whoo!
Whoo mama.
-Come here.
-Oh baby.
Yeah.
Let's lose some
of these clothes.
I'll take care of that.
You first.
Oh!
Why do you carry handcuffs?
Duh. All cops do, silly.
Oo, what's this?
Aw, I was just-
I knew you were fun.
You didn't tell
me you were a cop.
Detective actually.
I don't mention it because
the idea of a strong woman
turns a lot of guys off.
Right, right, right.
But I didn't get
that vibe from you.
Actually I um...
That's my phone.
I have to, it could be
a patient emergency.
Thanks.
It is a patient.
It's an emergency.
Heart rate is spiking.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
-I get it.
-I'm sorry.
I have to go.
We'll take a rain check.
Absolutely, we will.
Don't for a second think
you're getting away that easy.
Oh baby.
Alex.
-Alex.
-Hey come on.
You can catch me if I faint.
Oh, God.
-Alex!
-Hey, how are you?
I miss you.
We're going
crazy tonight.
Alex! Here.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
-What?
-I want to dance.
-Alex!
-Please.
-Come on.
-You wanna do too much.
-Just one night.
We'll go slow, I promise.
Slow, all right?
I promise if you start
spitting up, I'm done.
I'm serious. Please.
-Okay.
Is this a good pace?
I like it. Maybe
a little slower.
This party's gonna
be so dope. I can't wait.
What is she doing?
Man.
So this is your song?
Oh, so you wanna dance?
Yeah. Oh you wanna.
Oh okay.
Yeah.
No baby.
You've got to slow down.
-No, no. No.
Hello.
Sorry to call so late
but I'm getting some
weird readings on
Alex's pacemaker app.
Weird how?
Well the locations
are all screwy,
but can you check on
her just so I know?
Oh sure. Hang on.
Alex?
She's not here.
So the app isn't broken?
Where does it say she is?
I'll go get her.
What are you doing?
What is this?
I don't know what this is.
All right. Okay well
you're gonna go for it.
I'm going.
I mean time to go for it.
Let's go, all right.
Okay. Okay.
-Okay, I'm gonna spin.
-Ooh!
Okay. Okay.
Let's go.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Alex, I am not kidding.
You let her do this?
No ma'am.
-Not good.
We'll talk about this at home.
-Come on.
-No, I'm staying here.
Baby, baby. Whoa, whoa.
-Whoa, whoa, hey, hey.
-Baby?
Alex? Talk to me.
-Baby.
-I need to sit down.
Okay.
Irresponsible.
All of you, you know this
could kill her, right?
-Do you even care?
Hi Chris.
I just found her.
Great.
Look, I know you're probably
really upset right now
but we need to calm her down.
Her heart rate is too high.
So let her know you love her
and everything's
gonna be all right.
And please get her
some cold water.
Maggie, I know you're
pissed, but do it for Alex.
Okay?
Come on.
Baby, you're gonna be okay.
I'm sorry that I
embarrassed you.
I love you.
Great job. That's better.
I will meet you at the house.
-Yeah.
-You're okay.
-I'm scared.
-I know, baby.
-It's okay.
-I'm sorry.
I just don't get it, Alex.
What were you thinking?
I just wanted to get out
and have fun for like a few.
Is that what you
thought you were doing?
'Cause I'd say it's more
like toying with your life.
You could have
passed out or worse.
Why would you help
her sneak out?
No, I didn't--
It's not Scott's fault.
I was going with or without him.
He just came to
keep an eye on me.
At least he didn't rat me out.
Alex, I'm here to keep you safe.
I don't understand.
Are you trying to kill yourself?
No!
Then what? Explain it to me.
It's my life.
I don't want to
live it like he did.
You mean your dad?
Look, if I'm gonna die,
I just, I just want to
live first, before--
Alex, you are not going to die!
Mom, a heart's not coming.
Not in time.
It's not.
You just need to
face it, like I have.
I just want to use
what time I have left.
No matter how much or
how little that may be.
I'm not gonna spend it
trapped in a bed like dad was.
That's how I remember him.
Sick, bed bound.
Those are my last
memories of him.
Oh baby.
Not the man that he was.
And that's, that's not
gonna be how I'm remembered.
So, don't even think about
checking me into a hospital.
'Cause I, I won't go.
Alex, you can't give up hope.
I'm not.
But I'm not gonna
pretend either.
I'm just facing reality.
Maybe you should, too.
Well, I'm exhausted.
I'm going to bed.
Here, let me help.
Don't.
Scott can help me.
Goodnight, baby.
Oh, oh, everything
is gonna be okay.
She's right about her dad.
Once he got into that
bed he never came out,
he just...withered.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna lose my baby girl.
No, I won't--
That's not gonna happen.
I promise you.
You can't.
Even I can't.
The odds of a donor
popping up in time?
One will.
I've been doing
this a long time.
These things, these
things have a way
of working themselves out.
Trust me.
How can you be so sure?
Let's just call it gut instinct.
It's gonna be okay.
Good morning.
How are you feeling?
Fine.
Look...
I know you're mad
at me about last night,
but my job is to keep you safe.
And if that makes me the
bad guy, then I'll wear that
like a badge of honor.
Just to make up for it...
I brought you a little surprise.
Oh my God.
I know how much it meant to you.
So, I got you a new one.
I can't take this.
You really shouldn't
be buying me things.
Oh no, yes, yes, no.
I am here to help you heal.
And in my experience
patients do that faster
when they're surrounded by
things they love.
You're gonna put
yourself out of a job.
Good as new.
Just like you'll be soon.
This is Maggie Newell.
Hi,
this is Grace from 911,
following up on your inquiry.
Oh yes.
Thank you for
getting back to me.
I was just wondering if I
could get some information
on the night of my
daughter's emergency.
The call definitely
came from your
daughter's phone.
The audio has been deleted
but I was the dispatcher
who took the call.
Oh, you were? Great.
Did you notice
anything...unusual
about my daughter's call?
Your daughter
wasn't the one
who made the call, ma'am.
It was a man.
-A man?
-Yes ma'am.
Are you sure?
Yes ma'am.
He sounded older, whoever he
was, he had medical knowledge.
I hope that helps.
Not really, but thank
you for the information.
-No problem.
-Okay, bye.
No, next week won't work.
I need to see him
as soon as possible.
So sir, are
you having dark thoughts?
Am I having dark thoughts?
-Yes.
-Well, yes, actually, I am.
How dark, exactly?
Very dark.
Which is why I need to
speak to someone today.
-End of the day?
-End of the day is fine.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-- 30?
-- 30 is perfect.
-You're all set.
-Thank you.
Are you sure that
this is a good idea?
Why wouldn't it be?
'Cause he's a psychiatrist,
they're trained to read people.
What if he figures
out what you're doing?
I would just hate if anything
happened to you because of me.
That is so sweet, but
everything's gonna be fine.
He's a match.
That's all that matters.
It'll be fine.
So Mr. Johnson, my service noted
you were having
violent thoughts.
Sure. Sometimes.
But I mean, don't we all?
These thoughts about harming
yourself or harming others?
Others, definitely.
But only when it's
absolutely necessary.
When is violence necessary?
Sometimes you have to
make sacrifices, you know?
sacrifice for love, Doctor.
Do you believe in love?
True love.
Unconditional.
So there's a woman
involved, or a man.
A very special young woman.
How young?
Let's talk about
you for a minute.
Got any hobbies?
Any sports you play to keep fit?
I'm sensing a lot
of conflict in you.
-Conflict?
-Mmhmm.
-No.
-It seems to stem
from this young
woman you mentioned.
You know what you're
doing is wrong.
But your need to love so that
you can be loved in return,
drives you to do it anyway.
I'm not a big fan of
this psycho-babble stuff.
You came for my help, yes?
Well yes, absolutely.
And I have no doubt
that you can help me.
It's just, I don't...
I don't like people
poking around in my head.
You've been to therapy before.
Once or twice.
But let's just say it never
quite worked out for me.
What did you talk about with
your previous therapist?
Well, you know, the usual.
Think good thoughts.
Don't listen to the bad
voices in your head.
Voices?
Tell me about the voices.
There's nothing really to tell.
I mean, they're just...voices.
These voices ever appear to you?
I mean, do you, do you
ever see people who, um...
are not really there?
Come on, man.
I'm not crazy.
I just have an
overactive imagination.
Mr. Johnson, I'm
concerned about you.
I will prescribe you
something for your anxiety.
Thank you.
But I do--
Excuse me.
I do think that we need
to set up weekly meetings
to discuss these voices.
Just to make sure that these
voices that you're hearing
don't manifest into
anything more physical.
Doc, ya helped me already.
Anxiety-free.
Lucky me.
Oh my god.
-Help!
Buddy!
Where ya going?
Stay back.
Look, there's
nowhere left to run.
Be reasonable here.
I can't have you
damaging that heart.
I need it.
You're insane.
That's a little judgmental
of you, isn't it Doc?
Judgmental, you want
to hear judgmental?
-Sure.
-How about this?
You're a hyper-neurotic,
egotistical narcissistic freak.
You deserve to be
locked away forever.
In fact, in fact,
prepare to go to jail for
the rest of your life,
-you son of a--
Well that heart's no good.
Man.
The cause of the fire
at the Abernathy
state mental hospital
is still under investigation,
but authorities now strongly
suspect that it was arson
and that it was an inside job.
So far the bodies
of three people
have been pulled from the rubble
and positively identified
as hospital staff.
But several high security
inmates are still missing
-and it is not clear--
-Oh God.
if they perished in the fire
or somehow managed to escape
in the mayhem that followed.
Good morning.
So how's Alex today?
She's tired.
Says she feels weak.
Scott's upstairs with her.
Terrific.
I have to make a stop
on the way into work.
Have you noticed anything
odd around the house?
Like signs of someone
else being here?
Someone else being here?
No.
What about in the neighborhood?
Anyone who looks like
they don't belong?
Why do ask?
Just wondering.
I'll check in later.
Okay.
Hey!
You fixed it!
No.
Nurse Chris
bought me a new one.
He bought that for you?
Don't you think
that's a little odd?
I mean at first, yeah,
but then he explained
how it's like part of
the healing process.
How things that make you happy
help you heal faster.
You mean like me?
I'd give you my
heart if I could.
If anything ever happens to me
I want you to have it.
See, we're the same blood type.
We match.
I mean, it's like we're
meant to be together.
Like it was fate.
Alrighty, here we go.
Nice!
Same blood type.
Fate indeed.
Knock knock.
Oh, Scott, hi.
I didn't know you were here.
Oh, hey man.
Well, I made tea.
You can have mine, Scott.
I'm good.
No, I insist.
Plenty of herbs in this stuff.
Good for everybody.
Here you go pal.
If you insist.
Will you all excuse
me for a second?
-Mmhmm.
-We'll be right here.
-So Chris...
-Mmhmm?
Can I ask you something?
Yes.
You have a girlfriend?
I do.
Someone very special,
if you must know.
Oh yeah?
So what's her name?
-Spanish.
-Something like that.
Oh right.
Make sure Alex drinks her tea.
Will do, man.
Scott? Scott!
What's the matter?
Chris! Nurse Chris!
Hey, hey, wake up, hey, Scott.
Scott wake up.
Scott, Scott.
You should have some more tea.
What are you talking about?
Something's wrong with Scott.
We have to call an ambulance.
Actually everything
is just right.
What are you talking about?
Something's wrong with Scott!
I can't wake him up.
I know, that's because
he's, he sedated.
He'll be fine.
What?
I found it, Alex.
I found your heart
and it was right in front
of me the whole time
and I didn't even know it.
What are you, what
are you talking about?
Scott! He's a match.
I can save you again.
Again?
I was the one Alex.
I was the one who
found you that night.
-I called 911.
-You?
Yeah, I was here in the attic.
Yeah. I was watching from above.
If I hadn't have been,
you'd be dead.
Don't you see, it was fate.
I was meant to be
here to save ya.
Now with Scott I
can save you again.
Oh my god, you're crazy.
Why do people keep saying that?
Alex you've got to calm down.
That's why I drugged your tea.
So your heart wouldn't go crazy.
Just trust me Alex.
And you'll wake up
with a brand new heart.
-Get away from me!
Alex, Alex, Alex.
I did it for us.
I did it for us, Alex.
Oh.
Don't you worry.
I'll fix everything.
I need some help.
I found that in my attic.
One moment, please.
I think someone was living
in there, an escaped patient.
Gotta call you back.
I'm afraid they
might be dangerous.
Wait right here.
Hi, I'm Detective Matthews.
You said you found
this in your attic?
Yeah.
Follow me.
Nice and snug.
Man oh man.
Hate to be you.
What's it say?
It looks like this place got
hit by a pretty bad fire.
And now they're
thinking it was arson,
probably set by one
of the patients.
And it looks like a
few of the inmates
were unaccounted for.
Hospital folks thought they
must've burned up in the fire
but I guess one of them got away
and decided to
squat at your place.
Do you have photos of them?
Let me see.
What the f--
Suspect should be considered
extremely dangerous.
If possible, let me
take the bastard down.
-Come on Alex, answer.
It's Alex,
leave a message.
Alex, it's Mom, where are you?
Call me immediately.
Nurse Chris isn't
who he says he is.
When you get this lock
your bedroom door.
We're on our way.
Ready? Let's go.
No, no, no, no.
Please let me go.
Untie me!
Relax. Relax.
Everything's gonna be fine.
I've done this a million times.
Oh my god, Scott!
Scott, wake up!
You've got to try to calm down.
The strain is bad for you.
Who are you?
Name's Albert Beck,
Dr. Albert Beck.
And lucky for you,
I'm on call tonight.
Oh my God.
Help!
Someone help me.
Help.
Albert Beck, you're
under arrest.
-Alex?
-Stop!
-Wait.
She's not here.
Oh God.
Where could he have taken her?
I might have an idea.
What are the odds of a boy
who already gave you his heart
could literally
give you his heart?
No, stop!
It's what Scott wanted.
He said so.
-No!
-I know,
he wasn't my first
choice either.
But the others, they
didn't work out.
The pacemaker
isn't showing up.
-Oh come on, show me her signal.
It's not working.
I don't know why.
He probably disabled it.
Alex?
They just found something
at the McCoy home.
Oh my god.
Those are my daughter's clothes.
I need all available units
to St. Agatha's Hospital.
Suspect is believed
to be on location
with one, possibly two hostages.
Please don't hurt him.
No, no, no, no.
Please, please don't.
But this is what you wanted.
You asked me for it.
So we could be together.
What?
I never said that.
He's here.
All units, we have probable
location of suspect.
St. Agatha's Hos--
Get back--
Ms. Newell!
There's always an element
of tragedy to these things.
One person loses their
life so another can live.
But it'll make for
a great conversation
with our kids one day, right?
Scott!
Now, I haven't done
this in a while
so I might be a little rusty.
Speaking of a little rusty.
Hmm.
I'm begging you, please.
Hopefully it's
like riding a bike.
Oh no.
No, no, no, please!
Please!
Alex!
It's Mom!
Mom? Mom!
Mom, help!
Mom, I'm in here.
Help!
Mom!
-Alex.
-Help, I'm in here.
Mom!
Help!
Don't you go anywhere.
Scott? Scott wake up.
Scott!
Scott, Scott wake up.
That's it! That's it!
Come on.
Albert Beck, come out
with your hands up.
Hey, hey, hey.
Wake up, I need you
to wake up, okay?
Al.
Wake up, wake up.
We gotta go. We gotta go.
Okay. Where were we?
Oh no.
Alex, come out, come
out wherever you are.
Alex! Alex!
Where are ya?
I'm your doctor. We
have an appointment.
Alex!
Why are you running?
-Shh, shh.
I'm doing this for you, for us.
Alex, please.
Alex, you need to stop.
Your heart won't take much more.
I just want to save you.
Come on.
Scott, I need your help.
Hey, it looks like
I saved you again.
Get away from me.
Don't touch me.
Alex, stop fighting this.
This is for you, all of it.
Alex, I'm doing this
because I love you.
I don't love you.
It's okay.
I love you enough
for the both of us.
And when you have your new heart
I know you'll see
things differently.
Listen Alex, now Scott
can die for nothing
or Scott can die for you.
Take my hand.
-Alex.
-Alex!
-Mom!
-Oh baby.
Oh, careful.
You're okay.
The police are here.
It's over.
She's dying.
Look at her.
I can save her.
You'll have to kill me first.
Oh come on.
Okay.
-Gail!
-It's over, Beck.
Hi, sexy.
How 'bout that rain check?
Both the
hostages inside.
Move, move, move!
Hands up!
Drop it!
Not another step.
Down on your knees, now!
Officer
down, officer down!
Check over there.
Clear.
I
need an ambulance
to St. Agatha's Hospital
on Highway 27.
Officer down,
critical condition.
-I repeat, officer down.
-Mom!
Critical condition.
Oh baby.
Oh my god, Alex.
Alex, hang on, baby.
Somebody please, someone help.
Hang on baby,
hang on baby.
Just relax.
The doctor'll be
here any minute.
Everything's ready, Doctor.
Please, please someone help me.
Hello, Alex.
No, no, no, no, no.
Just a tad more anesthesia.
Please someone help me.
Yes, Doctor.
Please, please someone help me.
I could
never hurt you Alex.
I'm here to save you.
Where is he?
Oh, be careful, baby.
It's okay.
You're safe.
The surgeon, it was Beck.
It was him.
Oh no, baby.
No, it wasn't.
Mom yes, it was.
I saw him.
Alex, we've just
been through hell
and you're on a list of
medication that is longer than--
No, it was him. I saw him.
It was Beck.
Shh.
Something wrong?
No, no, no.
The surgery was a huge success.
Except...
What?
We just found. Dr.
Courdier in the men's room,
bound and unconscious.
He didn't perform
the transplant.
Someone else did.
I told you.
It was Beck.
He saved me just like
he said he would.
Everything's gonna be all right.
He's gone now.
Man.
Yeah, like any of these guys
are gonna give you a ride.
Man.
What the hell are
you doing here, man?
I got rid of you
back in the asylum.
I was on sabbatical.
I mean, let's face it, man.
We needed a break
from each other.
Well, I don't need you anymore.
I'm cured.
I'd hardly call what
happened back there cured.
Hey, hey, hey, where ya headed?
Oh man.
Here we go.
Hey, can I have a ride?
Well...sure.
Come on in.
Thanks, pal.
I usually don't pick up hitchers
but you seem like
a decent fellow.
Thank you.
I got to say you're
traveling awful light.
Never seen a hitcher
with no baggage.
Oh, he's got baggage, plenty.
I need a fresh new start.
New place, new clothes, new me.
Sounds like
you got woman troubles.
How'd you know?
I've had mine too.
Broken hearts are a bitch.
Ain't they?
They certainly are.
Well, where are ya headed to?
Anywhere but here.
I've been
there too, many times.
Maybe give he can give you
a lobotomy at the next stop.
Shut up.
Well, here we go.
Ask him if he has a
new teenage daughters.
Just thinking ahead.