Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Subbed by Rjgman56 subs
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
The private Hyakkaou academy
It was founded more than a hundred years ago.
There are many children from powerful people in the political and business world.
However, there is a popular event at the school.
It's gambling.
What you need in gambling is strategy, mind reading and decisive ability.
Member of the student council 1st year
Itsuki Sumeragi
Determination.
Shut up!
Young lady...
-Hurry up.   -I told you to shut up!
Are you sure?
It's decreasing right?
Huh? That's my account!
Why is my balance decreasing!?
A hacker? How did you do it!?
Through my Papa's power.
No way...
Stop that right now!
Stop it!
Hey, please stop it! I'm begging you! Can you hear me?
The beautiful colors are gradually becoming black.
Stop that right now!
Please...
Stop it...
I lost...
Just stop it already...
It's pure black...
Hey...
Where is Jabami Yumeko?
Jabami Yumeko
2nd year Hana class
Sink or swim!
I want it, I want it...
It's like a flame that can't be extinguished.
If possible come down.
I'm not sick of this!
Sink or swim!
No thank you for right now!
Seize the day!
Punishment or money?
Dive and be ambitious!
Let's bet on these glowing dice tomorrow!
Igarashi Sayaka.  Student council 2nd year.
Yumemite Yumemi.  Student council 2nd year.
Ikishima Midari.  Student council 2nd year.
Nishinotouin Yuriko.  Student council 3rd year.
Yomozuki Runa.  Student council 3rd year.
Vice president.  Student council 3rd year.
Momobami Kirari.  Student council president 3rd year.
Gambling at Hyakkaou academy is everything.
What you need is strategy, mind reading and decisive ability.
-Also...  -Money!
Those are all elements of becoming successful in the future.
The student council manages the gambling.
And the students pay fees.
In order to make this system deeply rooted into people's hearts...
We have strengthened the collection of casino usage fees and deposits.
It's the casino enforcement!
Get out of here!
I'm  the student council!
You guys are unforgivable for skipping out on fees!
Shit! The bullets are stuck!
Hey! Don't let them run away!
In addition, the ranking list is released every month.
And the top 100 non-cooperative students become housepets.
Again! Again!
Shoe shine!
Do you hear me stupid dog?
The class system created by the president works perfectly.
The power of the student council is solid as a rock.
Is that really the case?
Is that true?
Please fight me in a class battle!
I'm scared!
More and more people want to try their luck in class battles!
It's true that the class battle is a right granted solely to housepets.
You can request an unlimited amount of battles against the student council.
Nishinotouin-sama!
It's not safe here! Please run away!
How rude to treat the student council members this way!
Class battles are a special case that take precedence over all rules!
You have no right to refuse!
It's never been like this!
Don't run away!
So disgusting! Gross housepets!
Is that really the case?
Everything started with Jabami Yumeko.
Nishinotouin Yuriko.
Ikishima Midari.
Yumemite Yumemiko.
Manyuda Kaede.
More than half of the student council lost to Jabami Yumeko.
And furthermore there was the turmoil in the student representative election.
The impact of these things damaged the student council.
Jabami Yumeko.
It's her fault!
It's the woman's fault!
That woman...that woman!
That woman!
She might be revolutionary.
Or is she just a gambling fanatic?
What is this?
Jabami Yumeko...
Yumeko isn't doing well!
What's wrong Yumeko?
There's only one reason why gambling isn't enough!
That's not it...
She wants to gamble with the president!
That's not it!
Yumeko!
I'll treat you to a yummy dessert!
No thank you!
I have money.
3...3 billion!?
Manyuda-san paid me.
This is farewell for you.
Umm...
If you have 3 billion yen then why are you depressed?
Because...
A sports meeting is going to be held...
Huh? That?
Do you like sport games Suzui-san?
Yes!
Is that so?
Are you one of them? If that's the case then I won't talk to you anymore!
Why?
Saotome!
Where is Saotome?
Saotome! Saotome!
Look for her! Saotome! Saotome!
Saotome! What's wrong?
-Suzui!  -Yes!
Janken po!
Po!
That's a hit!
Alright!
Why? Why can't I even beat Suzui?
Mary-san! What's wrong?
It's so weird! I've been so unlucky recently!
Why did it turn out like this!?
The other day, Kiwatari and I made some money.
Then I destroyed him in gambling again!
It's the final hit!
Stop it! I'm begging you!
Sorry! It's so lame! How lame!
My hair!!!
I'll remember this!!
I was fine at that time...
-A pair!   -Single!
-Single!  -Pair!
-Pair!  -Single!
What the hell?
I won!
It's a royal flush!
Take a bet!
I take a bet!
I'm the student council!
You guys are unforgivable for owing money!
Hold on!
I won! I won!
This is definitely strange! Weird! Did I do something?
No way...
You got the house pet curse?
No way...that's not true!
What is that?
When you get the housepet curse then you'll slowly start losing money...
Then in the end you'll become a housepet!
Stop it!
And this curse will be contagious!
Half of the students become housepets a year ago...
How scary!
That's just a campus urban legend!
It's true!
Uchima-kun...
You look pretty bad.
Shall we go?
You pioneer!
Hold on!
If you don't have money you can work to pay off your debt!
Let's go Pioneer!
You'll work 16 hours a day in an accommodation system!
After deducting various expenses such as work clothes and tool rentals... It'll be 1850 yen a day!
I happen to have a job at the sports meeting now!
I will pay it back...
Saotome-san!
You are struck by the curse...
No!!!
Saotome-san!
Mary-san is amazing...
She runs really fast!
What about the ranking?
It's almost unchanged from last month.
Also, the amount of students with nothing is increasing.
There might be more than 100 housepets...
It's the curse of the housepet huh?
How scary!
The culprit of all of this is Jabami Yumeko.
Yumeko!
-I want to gamble against her...  -Ikishima-san!
I think it's necessary to take measures against Jabami Yumeko as soon as possible!
It's already started right?
Yumemi.
Way to go president!
I can't hide anything from you!
What? What?
The measure to deal with Yumeko-chan is...
Finding a better gambler than her!
Like I said...
Let me call the legendary gambler who can defeat Yumeko-chan!
Come in!
Ew!
Who?
Do you know who he is?
Are you in a bad mood?
Long time no see.
Shikigami Makuro...
What happened?
I disappeared...
You were suspended from school 2 years ago.
Suspended?
Because he ruined the school once!
For real?
I told Yumemite-san about him.
That's right!
Dealing with Jabami Yumeko is a high-risk gamble.
So we must have the consciousness to take the corresponding risks.
President.
Can you please formally order Shikigami Makuro to defeat Jabami Yumeko?
You can't!
Do as you please.
President!
What should I do?
Please defeat Jabami Yumeko completely!
And take back the 3 billion yen in her hands.
Even if Jabami Yumeko dies?
I don't mind.
If I destroy Jabami Yumeko...
I hope to officially return to school.
We will prepare the funds as much as possible.
I don't need money.
Also...
I ask that we take care of Saotome Mary and Sumeragi Itsuki please.
Also, Suzui-kun!
There's no need!
He's just a passerby!
Lady Sumeragi has already been destroyed.
I'll just paint Saotome Mary in black.
And Jabami Yumeko will appear.
Shikigami Makuro!
He's not a cute legend!
He's a monster!
Now, now, now!
This is a pioneering place for hopes and dreams!
Let's sing the song of the pioneers!
Where's Yumeko?
She said she won't show up until the sports meeting starts...
What the heck?
Saotome!
What if you ask Yumeko?
There's no need!
I can't rely on her!
Hey! Wanna get on? There's still room!
No thank you!
You have been cursed after all!
Saotome!
Saotome senpai!
Tsumeragi!
Don't you want money?
I want it!
Okay!
Hold on! Hold on!
This is Tsumeragi!
Shut up!
I didn't call you!
Saotome senpai!
There's someone who really wants you to beat him!
Sure!
Sorry Tsumeragi but I don't have any assets!
-You sure are cursed huh?  -Pretty much!
I will lend you all of my assets!
Sounds good!
Is this him?
Yes...
He's Shikigami.
Saotome Mary...
You're pretty beautiful huh?
Pretty much.
You are?
A passerby...
Let's start this thing.
What kind of gamble is it?
It's a simple gamble.
However...
It's not me who will gamble with you.
He will.
Who is that?
The participation fee is 1 million yen.
If you win, I'll give you 10 million yen.
10 million yen!?
However if you lose...
This housepet badge is going to be put on you instead!
You're telling me to be a housepet instead of him?
No Saotome! Being a housepet is a no go!
Take it easy!
Even if you become a housepet you only need to pay 1 million yen deposits in order to be released.
In other words...
You take a risk of 2 million but can gain 10 million yen!
What gain do you have?
You don't trust me?
Or are you scared of becoming a housepet?
Let's do this.
-Saotome! -Let's go!
It's begun fading.
Duel*Dice*Stacking
Let me explain rules.
There's the size of the 4 stacked dice.
It's the number of points on the top set times the number of layers stacked.
3 points times 2 layers is 6 points.
If you don't put it up then it's 0 points.
The person with more points wins.
Two wins in three games.
Begin.
Saotome.
Open.
Amazing!
Saotome, 12 points.
You can do it Saotome!
Way to go! She can win!
Don't be careless!
If he rolls 6 points and 2 layers then it will be a tie.
-Negimida  -Yes!
Open.
Negimida has 0 points.
Saotome wins.
Alright! Alright! You just need one more win!
I won right?
Have I been freed from the curse?
What are you doing?
No! No! I don't want to die!
Keep betting!
Huh? What does he mean?
If I lose...
Then I will jump out of the window!
Aww...they found out.
Mary-san. Don't worry about it and keep betting!
What the hell?
Are you having me get involved in your bullying?
How foolish!
H-Hold on!
Are you going to quit in the middle of it?
This isn't gambling!
Even if you win it's meaningless!
Are you leaving?
Damn right!
Hold on!
No helping it.
Jump.
I didn't lose!
Stop it!
I'm sorry!
Does this make you happy?
I will continue to bet with you!
Shit!
-Tsumeragi! -Yes?
Sorry but give me 2 million yen!
Hold on! Are you planning on losing?
Although it fucking pisses me off, it's better than regretting it afterwards!
I can't...
Why not!?
Didn't you say that you'd give her all your assets?
This is all I have...
Zero!?
You deceived me?
I didn't say any lies...
Choose Saotome Mary!
Will this guy jump?
Will you become a housepet?
How foolish!
You're trying to make me scared so I can lose?
It's just a bluff isn't it?
Saotome!
It's your fault.
No...
It's your fault! It's your fault! It's your fault!
I've actually been cursed...
Suzui.
Go buy some juice.
-What are you saying Saotome?  -Hurry up damn it!
Get out.
Saotome! What are you planning on doing?
You can't Saotome! Saotome!
Saotome! Saotome! Saotome!
Saotome!
There.
This is fine right?
What?
You want me to do it one more time?
You still have some color left.
You're jumping.
Stop it!
Saotome!
-Saotome! -Let me go!
You fucking bastard!
Listen up.
Say "I lost please forgive me."
Say it house bitch!
Saotome!
Saotome! Saotome!
Saotome! Saotome! Saotome! Saotome!
I...
Lost...
Please forgive me...
He killed her...
Amazing...
I'm better than him!
The student council has an announcement.
Jabami Yumeko-san...
I destroyed Tsumeragi Itsuki and Saotome Mary!
Come on over Jabami Yumeko!
I'm going to destroy you!
Very well done. Now all that's left is Jabami Yumeko.
I want to be sure that no matter what happens, it's the responsibility of the student council.
What are you planning on doing?
Hold on Man in black! Yumeko is mine!
What are you planning on doing with a gun that has no bullets?
This is my gun.
I have bullets too.
The president gave me that!
It's mine originally.
Right?
Shikigami Makuro is indefinitely suspended from this school.
Farewell.
Shikigami.
I thought that we'd get along.
I don't want it!
Shikigami.
Jabami Yumeko won't come because of that broadcast.
What is that?
An invitation card.
Extra! Extra!
The Saotome fiasco!
The student council's assassin Shikigami Makuro has declared war on Jabami Yumeko!
Extra! Extra!
Get on board!
I was waiting for you.
Yumeko!
Saotome is going away on the truck!
Save Saotome!
I don't have time for that.
Furthermore, I don't think that Mary-san wants that.
Are you going?
I mean...it's an invitation from the President.
It's Shikigami.
That's true.
I'm going.
Saotome!
Hold on!
Here! Here!
Saotome!
I've been thinking of ways to make you show up.
If you're looking to gamble then I'm up for it at any time.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Yumeko!
Alright! It's started!
It's a game where we bet everything.
Your 3 billion yen.
I also prepared the same amount.
However you just said "Everything".
Say it.
If you lose...
You will leave Hyakkaou academy and never come back.
Are you sure about that?
I'm sure about it.
Then if you lose...
I'll steal gambling from you.
He'll steal gambling from Yumeko!?
We're betting on each other's existence...
How exciting.
This is where Jabami Yumeko ends.
This is 3 billion yen worth of chips.
The gambling game is...
Black Texas Hold'em.
You only use clubs and spades cards.
There is only one pair or two pairs.
No flush or straights.
The rest is the same as the ordinary Texas Hold'em.
It's fairly simple and straightforward rules.
Decisive victory or defeat is the most fun to play with bare hands.
T-Texas Hold'em?
Passerby, are you stupid?
Tsumeragi!
Texas Hold'em is the most mainstream type of poker in this world!
Each player is dealt two hole cards.
At this point each player decides to bet or not.
Then they will turn over the three community on the table.
Then match those community cards with the cards in your hand.
Repeat the same thing.
Then it's a showdown after turning over the fourth and fifth community cards.
The player with the bigger card wins.
It goes Ace, King, and Queen as the strongest cards. Even a small citizen would understand right?
Jabami senpai! Please beat him and get back my money!
You betrayed us right? Right?
Round 1.
What will you do?
I bet 300 million.
3...300 million!?
That much!?
You're beautiful...Jabami Yumeko.
I call!
Shikigami-san...
What do your eyes see?
What I see is the color of desire.
A human's desire is their heart. Once you master it then nobody can violate it.
What kind of color am I?
I've only met one other person with a color like yours.
No matter what you see, it's just a mystery right?
Right?
Although you disguise yourself as a monster...
You have carefully laid everything out.
The correct analogy is like hunting with traps and poison.
Did you just compare people to bugs?
It's a compliment.
Countless prey have been caught in your lair.
I raise 300 million.
Your first prey were Nishinotouin-san and Yumemite-san?
Huh? Yumemi?
I call.
In the beginning you knotted the two of them.
Please have a class battle with me!
How scary!
Battle!
It has never been this bad!
You drove the two of them into a desperate situation and had them trap themselves right?
Thank you!
Please leave it to me!
Class battle!
You have no right to refuse!
Run away Nishitouin-san!
They were poisoned unknowingly...
And then they summoned you.
The black sinner!
Do you have any idea who that is?
President.
Can you please formally order Shikigami Makurou to defeat Jabami Yumeko?
That's not true! I...
You even used the news club to incite the students.
And you upset the student council.
What is this?
No! I just wrote what I wanted to write!
He just wrote what he wanted to write.
Your strategy is to lure your prey into a snare.
You used Tsumeragi-san to trick Mary-san.
That's really clever.
It's a very smart strategy.
It's just not in line with my liking.
I raise 400 million for a total of 1 billion.
1 billion!?
Way to go!
I call.
Showdown.
Yumeko!
She has a pair of 2!
And Shikigami?
He doesn't have one! It's Jabami senpai's win!
1 billion...
Yumeko-chan is amazing...
The biggest card is just a guise. You won in pairs with the smallest card.
Is this a gambling fanatic?
If you play cards according to common sense, you won't win.
I don't know why the student council specifically targeted you.
Why were you suspended from school?
Why do you think I was?
Shikigami...
Are there fireworks going on?
Let's continue!
You gambling fanatic.
Round 2.
Was that the data storage room in the north school building that exploded?
Why do you think that?
My cards being paired was the condition of the explosion.
The special arrangement of the cards here...
Represent the direction of the explosion. East, West, South, and north.
What? What?
What?
And the numbers 1 through 13 indicate classrooms and facilities from here.
What about the fifth card?
The center.
Is it here?
What happens if you pair with the card in your hand?
I don't know.
It's 6 times 13.
78 locations may explode.
As long as Jabami senpai has a pair there will be a place to explode...
Holy crap! Holy crap! Get out of here everyone!
-Where should we go?  -Shut up!
I'm a monster huh?
Will you fold?
What great courage.
Library on the 4th floor of West building one.
The second grade class in the South teaching building.
The hall of building number 2.
The hall of building number 2?
It's here! Run away! Run away!
The tool room on the 5th floor of building number 9.
People's lives are at stake here!
I raise 900 million.
1 billion in total.
-She raised to 1 billion? -It's Yumeko's win!
-Where will it explode? Where?  -Shut up!
I call.
Showdown.
Now then!
Prove your reasoning.
Okay.
It's called a vacant building.
So it's fine.
What the hell is going on?
Are you satisfied with my answers?
You really are an uncute woman.
Jabami senpai just won 2 billion!
She'll win!
Round 3.
100 million.
First year Chinese class in West building one.
The sports preparation warehouse on the south side.
Well...
There is a pair of Kings...
The sports warehouse will explode huh?
You look happy.
If it explodes then the sports meeting will be canceled is all I'm thinking.
There's nobody there right now.
The indoor swimming pool.
If that explodes too then the sports meeting is done right?
I raise to one billion.
1 billion!
She'll destroy him!
You're obviously bluffing!
Do you have a Queen?
Who knows...
I wonder?
I call.
I've been waiting!
Additional chips.
All in. This is 5 billion yen worth of chips.
Extra?
He can do that?
This is bad! If he has an Ace then he can create an Ace and King pair, the strongest one!
This is everything that I have.
Now then, how about you disappear?
All in!
Showdown!
What's wrong?
The sports warehouse is going to explode.
Now! Now! Now!
Let's fall into the gambling abyss together Jabami Yumeko!
What's wrong? It's a 5 billion yen showdown Jabami Yumeko!
You have a Queen right? Then it's your win because I don't have an Ace!
I'll disappear alongside the sports warehouse!
Jabami Yumeko!
You've become the color that I love!
Pure black! The color of despair!
Listen up, Your beautiful desires are mixed with despair!
Your colors are slowly getting darker and will finally turn pure black!
Once you turn black you can't turn back!
It will be soon! Go for it Jabami Yumeko! Showdown!
I lost...
The gambling fanatic has lost...
Just like we promised, we officially welcome you back to the school.
You have my thanks.
However...it's not enough.
There's one more thing that I want.
What is it?
That seat.
I can't stand him!
Give me that seat!
How rude! We can't accept that!
Are you sure about that?
No way...
Yumemite-san! Nishinotouin-san!
Please wake up!
Little girl! You're neutral right?
Pretty much...
Shit!
You and the Mask...
You guys can't beat the rest of the council.
Let me replace her.
Don't screw with me!
Gamble with me!
If I win...
You will be permanently expelled from Hyakkaou Academy.
What are you betting?
My life!
Does she know who I am?
Let's make a deal.
Farewell.
Shikigami.
Hold on to this gun for me.
When I come back...
Use this bullet.
I'll kill you.
Sayaka.
You lost.
President...
Shikigami Makurou.
As the price of misconduct...
I'll give that seat to you.
Also...
You can turn me into a housepet or whatever you want.
President!
Momobami Kirari.
There's something else you need to say.
Please...
It was only half 2 years ago.
Now it will be everyone!
I will turn your beautiful fish tank into pure black!
Hyakkaou academy collapsed.
We are near the official handover ceremony of the student council president.
Shikigami changed the rules of the school.
All the students...
We have amended the Houspet law.
The monthly payments will be 100 million yen.
100 million?
The non-cooperative students will turn into Housepets.
Everyone is going to become a housepet!
The housepet curse was Shikigami...
That's right.
2 years ago half of the students became housepets.
The man who created the Housepet curse urban legend...
Will now turn everyone into housepets and create despair.
I don't know what to say to her.
Yumeko's existence of gambling was stolen from her by Shikigami.
What will she do now?
Suzui-san...
What is it?
What should I do?
Yumeko...
The sports meeting wasn't canceled!
Now that the school has become this way, it would be natural to cancel it right?
I'll write a letter to Mary-san!
I'll tell her to mess up the preparations for the meeting so that they can cancel it!
Is the sports warehouse cold over there?
The light is lost...
Winter is coming...
The icy wings and the buried dreams.
These hands were full of hope.
I don't want to give up this life.
I want to find my friend.
This little light...
Where is the warmth?
I can't do anything...
However there's something I want to say...
-I don't want to give up.   -Don't give up.
-My life...   -Your life...
Let's find that friend and dream once more!
-Don't give up.   -I don't want to give up.
-Your life...  -My life...
The ring of the bell is coming.
La la la~
The light is lost...
Winter is coming...
Shikigami-san...
I came here to gamble against you.
You can longer gamble.
Mary-san.
Saotome!
I challenge you to a class battle.
The one who will gamble instead of me is...
Jabami Yumeko!
A class battle has precedence over all rules!
In other words she can gamble!
I see!
The student council has no right to refuse.
If I win then I will return everything you have stolen.
I'll let you go first.
I challenge you to a battle.
You have no right to refuse.
Student council president.
Alright!
What will we do?
The president too!
Yumeko and the president?
Where should I stand?
No way! Why?
The loser leaves the school.
That's fine right?
Yes.
I'll decide the gambling game!
This is bad...
We will gamble in pairs.
Kirari, your partner will be...
The secretary woman.
Don't die...
Jabami Yumeko...
Your partner will be...
You.
Me!?
Why?
Mary-san is cursed after all.
That pisses me off!
My partner will be...
Me!
Ikishima-san!
I will gamble against Yumeko and the president?
That's my dream!
Right?
Man in black.
Let's begin.
We will now have the student council president Shikigami Makuro...
Go against Momobami Kirari and Jabami Yumeko in a game.
Who will win?
The game is Russian Roulette.
This is what happened 2 years ago.
This is the game that created the Housepet curse?
This is a game where cards decide who shoots at whom.
Shoot at?
I'll explain the rules.
There's two name cards for each person.
One player card and one hostage card.
And bullet cards.
And a Bang card.
We'll give each player a card.
And put one on each card box in the field.
This is when the gambling begins.
The player will get another card.
And put one of the two cards in your hand at any time.
You'll decide who will shoot whom.
That's right.
When you get a player card or hostage card...
All players or all hostages...
Will shoot or be shot.
There's only one bullet from the start.
You can use bullet cards to increase the ammunition.
Players will get 100 million yen for every additional bullet.
Players who get a Bang card in this game must disclose it immediately.
The next player gives the last card...
Then it will be Russian roulette.
Awesome!
Shoot according to the instructions in the box.
If there is no bullet...
The player who is shot can get 100 million yen for each loaded bullet.
And a bonus of 500 million yen.
There's 5 rounds in total.
The one with the most money wins.
In addition, if a player surrenders or dies before the end of the game...
Then the last remaining person becomes the winner.
Now then, let's begin!
Hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
You said if someone dies!?
Are you a dumbass?
Of course someone is going to die!
It's a real gun after all.
I can't stand you!
Seeing you from below you're quite special!
I'm cursed again!
Start it up! Come on! Start it up!
Someone is gonna die!
This is the best!
No!!
Yumeko! Let's run away!
You are a hostage.
I won't let you run away.
Suzui-san.
Clear your mind and let's enjoy it.
I can't! This is a gambling game where we might die!
That's exactly why.
I have to do my best to fight this person to the death.
That's right.
Round one.
Me?
We're starting from the player Jabami Yumeko.
Yumeko! They're gonna shoot me!
If you're shot at but there's no bullet you're at least able to get some money.
You can't win without making money.
What are you saying?
If there's a bullet then I'll die!
That's not only you but the others as well.
Here!
Alright!
I'll make some progress.
How nice!
There are two bullets currently.
Shikigami Makurou earns 100 million yen.
President!
Do you want me to die that badly?
It's so we can win!
Hold on!
Where are you putting that card?
In the shooting area.
You can't!
-Then...  -No! No! No! Not that one either!
Because then all 3 hostages will be shot!
He's saying it...
There's only 10 cards left! What if a Bang card appears?
This is an escape game where you avoid getting shot!
You don't understand.
This is a game where you use bullet cards to make money and aim the gun at the opponent.
What you said is wrong!
Will you be shot? Will you die? Will you earn money? That's the game!
There's no helping it.
There we go.
Nice one Yumeko!
Are you satisfied with this Jabami Yumeko?
Again!? Stop it!
Please don't get a Bang card!
Bang.
Bang!
The bang card.
Please calm down Suzui-san!
The last card is my turn.
I got a good card.
Bang!
You're very murderous aren't you?
That's what kind of game it is right?
That's right!
The card has been confirmed and Russian Roulette will start.
There will be 2 bullets in this Russian Roulette.
Jabami Yumeko will shoot at Shikigami Makurou.
Really?
Will she shoot?
The probability of Shikigami dying is 1/3.
Go!
Come!
Jabami Yumeko.
You're quite bold huh?
You missed!
Shikigami Makurou has recieved 700 million as a survival bonus.
The first round is over.
Going 5 rounds is impossible!
Someone will die before it ends!
Who is going to die?
You guys!
I'm going to make you guys die by cheating!
First, I gave this guy a code.
He will give out a Bang card when I want him to.
However, that is not all.
There are two kinds of bullets.
The first one is a real bullet.
And the other one is this dummy bullet.
This kind of bullet won't shoot out even if you pull the trigger.
The real bullet is in here.
I had a dummy bullet in there when I was getting shot at and will put a real bullet in there to kill you.
Listen up Jabami Yumeko and Momobami Kirari!
I only gamble when I'm sure of winning!
I will paint the both of you in the color of despair!
Round 2.
The starting player is Shikigami Makurou.
I'm going to kill you.
Two bullets!?
3 bullets are present now and Shikigami Makurou has earned 200 million yen.
The probability is 1/2...
Come to me!
Is this fine?
That's not it...
A bang.
Bang!
This depends on Shikigami!
There's no mistaking it...He...
You.
The card is decided. Russian Roulette will start.
There are 3 bullets.
Shikigami Makurou will shoot.
I'll kill you!
-President!  -Sayaka.
Shut your mouth.
It's a real bullet.
It's the promised time.
I'll have you return my 2 years.
Be scared Momobami Kirari!
Shikigami...
You were lonely huh?
Die!
Shit!
Momobami Kirari has recieved 800 million yen as a survival bonus.
Round 3.
It starts with Momobami Kirari.
This is good right? Right?
I want to make money.
Nice!
There are 3 bullets currently.
Jabami Yumeko gets 200 million yen.
How's this?
No!
That was sexy.
Yumeko please! Turn it back!
True...
If the shot is adjusted to 1/2 of the probability...
It's a Bang.
The final turn is Shikigami.
No! No! No!
Jabami Yumeko will...
There it is! My card!
She said it...
Shikigami!
Play it!
I want to be shot by the president!
Or I can shoot Jabami Yumeko...
But I want to be shot!
Play it!
I understand.
Let's kill each other!
What are you doing you bastard?
Play the other one!
I want to see this...
The card is decided. Russian Roulette will start.
There are 3 bullets.
Suzui Ryota will shoot Jabami Yumeko.
I will shoot Yumeko?
It's going to be a real one of course.
Yumeko...
No...
I can't!
It's okay Suzui-san.
This gun will not shoot bullets.
For real?
Hurry up and shoot so I can earn money.
You're lying...
I know Yumeko...
You might die you know?
This guy can't shoot.
Just surrender.
That's right...
I can't shoot...there's now way I can shoot!
-Yumeko, let's surrender...   -Shoot it!
Will you keep running away?
What's going to happen if you run away and leave this school?
People like us will disappear like dust.
In that case being killed by that gun will be the same thing.
I...will not give up this opportunity to fight side by side with you!
Suzui-san.
Please shoot.
There will be no bullet...
I...
I'll believe you Yumeko.
If I believe you and you're wrong...
I'll shoot myself too...
Shit...
Shit!
Yumeko said it.
There's no bullets!!
He missed...
He shot...
He didn't shoot her...
Bang!
Jabami Yumeko earns 800 million yen as a survival bonus.
The amount received at the end of the third round is...
Shikigami Makurou with 1 billion yen...
And Jabami Yumeko with 1 billion yen.
Momobami Kirari with 800 million.
Who do you support?
The person who wins!
Good work.
Thank you!
Round 4.
It starts with Jabami Yumeko.
Again?
You're not scared anymore are you?
There are currently 3 bullets.
Jabami Yumeko gets 200 million yen.
I'll increase it.
4!!
Now someone really is gonna die!
There are 4 bullets.
Shikigami Makurou earns 100 million yen.
Someone's going to die huh?
You can shoot now right?
In that case...
How about this?
If Bang comes out then this will be the best.
Bang.
Now then!
There's one card left.
President, don't worry about my situation.
Jabami Yumeko.
Yes?
You'll show me a good time right?
Of course.
No way!
Why?
-Herself... -She will...
What are you doing Jabami Yumeko?
Way to go.
President!
This is the best! You are the best!
I didn't even think this...
The card is decided. Russian Roulette will start.
There are 4 bullets in this Russian Roulette.
Momobami Kirari will shoot Momobami Kirari.
I told you 2 years ago right?
You'll be destroyed by this gun.
There are 4 bullets out of 6...
Will you shake so bad you can't pull the trigger?
Why do you think you were expelled from this academy?
Because I ruined half of the students.
That's not it.
You're...boring.
Two shots...
Shikigami...
I will kill you.
She makes me so excited...
The final round.
The current score is...
Momobami Kirari with 1.7 billion yen.
And Jabami Yumeko with 1.2 billion.
And Shikigami Makuro with 1.1 billon yen.
If you want to win then you have to be shot.
Yumeko!
It came!
Don't be happy!
No!
That's my line stupid!
I will shoot myself?
Yumeko! Change it back! Change it!
Okay!
There we go!
An extra bullet...
There are two bullets.
Jabami Yumeko gets 100 million yen.
Everyone is going to shoot me?
There are 3 bullets.
Momobami Kirari gets 100 million yen.
There is a 3/6 probability that 3 people will shoot?
Die!
Die.
Bye bye!
Bang!
Shikigami is the last one.
I really wanted to kill you guys.
It's too bad.
The card is decided. The Russian Roulette will start.
There are 3 bullets. Three players will fire at Shikigami Makuro.
Hey! That's unfair!
Why?
Himself...
We're saved!
It's your loss.
I will use the dummy ones.
And they will shoot me 3 times.
The bullets won't come out.
Then I will get 2.4 billion yen.
And have a total of 3.5 billion yen.
I won.
You guys...will disappear.
Are you happy with this?
Yeah.
Now then.
You're the last one.
Are you prepared?
Shikigami Makuro.
You wanted to kill me right?
However if the bullets don't come out...
I win!
You are quite bold.
You're not scared.
The remaining 4 bullet nests contain 3 bullets.
Shoot.
Please hold on.
I have something to tell you before you die.
When I was defeated by you...
I was actually very frustrated.
That's the first time I tasted that flavor.
I started to feel so humiliated.
What are you trying to say?
I wanted to win.
I wanted to defeat you.
Shoot.
You're not afraid of the bullets...
It's over...shoot!
You put a special bullet in.
And one real bullet.
A real bullet? It's impossible for you to put a real bullet in.
I'm the only one who has the real bullet.
Now then!
Shoot!
It's the real bullet in the hands of the president.
Farewell.
Shikigami.
Hold on!
What's wrong Shikigami?
She has it...
She has a real one!
Why are you so nervous?
Wait, hold on!
Why do you know?
There's no way that bullet is in there!
They only acted on my orders!
Shoot!
Hold on!
When and where?
It's impossible!
Shoot me with that bullet!
Bye bye.
An invitation card.
It's an invitation from the president.
I'll write a letter to Mary-san!
The card is decided. The Russian Roulette will start.
There are 3 bullets. All 3 players will shoot Shikigami.
Don't shoot!
There is a bullet...
I was lying. It's a bluff.
That gun...
This kind of pathetic trick can't fool you.
I mean, you have carefully designed this.
And created a win-win game.
It's perfect.
Please shoot.
Hold on!
Oh my...
What's wrong Shikigami-san?
Are you scared?
It's okay.
When you die, I will die with you.
What are you doing Yumeko?
Because I already lost to the president!
Before I leave the school, I want to bet my life with the president!
Now then, shoot the final bullet!
Will it shoot a bullet or not?
I've become so desperate because your design was so perfect!
Now then! Let me see your color!
-Let me go!  -Shoot!
Aim straight at Shikigami's heart and shoot!
Now! Now! Now!
Let's fall into the abyss of gambling together!
Bang.
That's why you're boring.
Shikigami disappeared.
Yumeko lost the bet but nothing happened to her.
Suzui-san!
Yumeko!
It came again!
Again?
Yes!
Is that...
A notification that the sports meeting is canceled!
Saotome! Saotome!
Hey, where is Saotome?
Saotome!
Go and look for her!
Saotome! Are you in debt again?
It's weird! Wasn't the housepet curse caused by Shikigami?
Why am I always unlucky?
Oh my!
Whatever you do you will fail.
You will fail, you will fail...
Saotome!
Oh Devil!
I give you my soul and body!
Take away all the good fortune of Saotome Mary!
And give her the housepet curse!
Is this a human body?
I'm a gambler in the Devil world. Satan of the Casino.
Let's sing the pioneering song together!
Get ready to sing!
Yumemi!
Pioneer!
Since then the power of the student council has been stronger than ever.
Why is that?
It's the way it should be.
Fierce chaos is necessary before order is established.
I invited a 100 ghouls to come to the academy.
For real?
I see...
If I'm with you then I might really be able to keep betting.
Let's fall into the abyss of gambling.