Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
soft dramatic music
[Kevin Garnett]   The ingredients
that make up Kevin Garnett?
Tablespoon of fun,
a tablespoon of seriousness,
two tablespoons
of hard work,
a tablespoon of gratitude,
a teaspoon of gullibleness,
and you need
two tablespoons of hate,
because I'm driven
by the hate.
You know,
the more you hate on me,
the more you talk shit,
the more you say
I can't do something,
the more that gets me going.
I'm more motivated off the hate
than anything.
[Kevin Harlan]
Garnett and knocked it away!
While you're
in your bed sleeping,
some people are out working.
Ah!
[sportscaster]   This young man,
we're gonna see a lot of him.
-[cheers and applause]
-Oh! Kevin Garnett!
I like to think that I upped
the level for all of us.
[sportscaster]   Oh, baby!
Go to work, young fella!
[Kevin]   Yeah. It's crazy.
Crazy how small things
turn into big things.
[indistinct clamoring]
[photographer]
Really close, guys! Get closer!
[Kevin]   Who is Kevin Garnett
today versus the kid in '95?
Had a chip on his shoulder
to prove something.
[speaker]   A lot of people say
there was no KG before KG.
[Kevin]
For me, Magic was, like,
the potential of what can be
if you have some handles.
[Matt]   Yeah.
[Kevin]
So then I was thinking, like,
"Man, what if Magic
came from the hood?"
Like, what if, like,
Magic had, like,
a DMX attitude with this shit?
Just everything I do,
I want it to be as original
as it can be.
[sportscaster]   A big guy
playing like a guard.
[sportscaster]
Well, he just crossed over
and left Chris Webber standing
in his wake.
[cheers and applause]
[Kevin]   How do I dominate this?
How do I take this over?
How do I own this?
We ain't hooping no more.
-[whistle blows]
-[audience exclaims]
[Kevin]   Throw myself in,
and I'm a student.
Nothing fake about that.
Anything's possible!
That's what new things
feel like to me.
I want to be challenged
to the point where
it pushes me to the end.
[sportscaster]   Incredible!
I see you, G Money!
Shake 'em down, KG!
Shake 'em down!
[cheers and applause]
[sighs]
- music fades
-[exhales deeply]
[chuckling]
Hey, I'll say one thing
about Hollywood, boy.
Hollywood will have you gassed.
-[laughter]
-[Kevin] Straight up.
I couldn't have had none of
y'all around me while I played,
'cause I was already
a hype guy.
But Hollywood, everything is,
"Oh, you--oh, that was great!
Great!"
[laughing]
Get the fuck out of here.
sparse dramatic music
You know, it's crazy
that we're here talking about,
you know,
25 years of the decision.
And I can remember
thinking this.
Like, "Man, nobody really
did this in a long time."
I didn't know at the time
of making a decision
like this
would ignite a crazy momentum
of players to come in
to basically impact the game
in which we know today.
This is my way
of being able to speak
to the young kid right now
to understand how we got here.
How we got here
with all this swag,
how we got here
with all this drip.
Yeah. This is like
a history lesson.
We take y'all back in time.
sparse dramatic music
I'm from Greenville,
South Carolina.
I say that with pride.
When I was in seventh,
eight grade,
I moved to this neighborhood
called Mauldin,
which is probably 15 minutes
outside of Greenville.
It was more suburban.
I will never forget
this white kid named Billy.
He was probably the only
white kid on our block.
Billy was a cool kid, man.
You know,
he used to let us hoop.
Back in the day, only one kid
had a rim at they house.
I was really practice bait,
and I just got tired
of getting beat by this kid
every day,
so I started practicing
on my own,
I started going to the park.
And then you started to see me,
like, get better.
By the time I got
to eighth grade,
going to ninth grade,
I was 6'6".
And I had went out
and tried for varsity,
and came to kind of, you know,
get my mom's permission,
and she was like, "Nah."
We were Jehovah Witness,
and in Jehovah Witness,
you don't play outside
of the organization.
You don't do none of that.
But this is passion.
This is something
that was speaking to me.
This was something that,
you know, I wanted to do,
and this had nothing to do
with anybody else.
In ninth grade,
I made the team.
But I kept being a basketball
player from my mom
three years.
You know, I would
get home from school--
and my mom did hair.
Little small garage became,
like, the beauty salon.
So she would come in
and out of the house at times,
and I would make sure that
I wasn't nowhere to be seen,
or I had all the chores done.
Certain time,
I would just take off,
and I started walking
to the games.
[cheerleaders chanting]
[Kevin]   And for three years,
I did that.
And it was finally
until my mom
was actually doing
a young lady's hair
who was coming
to one of the games.
She was like, "Oh, girl, you
going to see your son play?"
She was like, "What?"
She like, "Yeah, Kevin!
He plays for Mauldin.
He good, girl!"
My mom's like, "What? Kevin
don't play no basketball!"
She like, "Shit.
Yes, Kevin do!"
And it was the first game
my mom ever saw me play.
And I was like, "Oh shit."
She's like, "Have a good game,
but motherfucker, I'ma kill
your ass when you get done!"
Like, "Oh shit. Ah!"
And then finally
she came around
when she saw how passionate,
committed I was to it.
And, uh, she just kinda
let me be after that.
And after a while, you start
to get, like, a little label
and the city start talking
about you.
Going to the mall, and people
running up on me, like,
"You play at Mauldin, huh?"
And I was like, "Damn, what?"
You know,
just walking through the mall.
And then I got the invitation
to, uh, to Nike,
and that--
and that changed everything.
[producer]
Scoop interview, take one.
[Scoop]   I, at the time,
was doing a lot
of freelance writing.
I was
a journalistic prostitute.
[chuckles]
I was selling my writing to
anybody who wanted to buy it.
[announcer on PA]   A senior
from Hampton, Virginia,
-number 11, Allen Iverson.
-[applause]
[Scoop]
So I go to the Nike camp.
It was one of the most
unique experiences ever.
You just saw the future
of what basketball
was about to become,
and you didn't know it yet.
[announcer on PA]
From Mauldin, South Carolina,
Junior, number 20,
Kevin Garnett.
[Scoop]   There was this
6'11" cat from South Carolina
who was getting
some notoriety.
But to see him play against
that talent, you're like,
"Oh, no,
this cat is really good."
And what made him so special
is that he wasn't just
posting cats up on the block
and just being bigger
and taller
and longer than everybody.
No, he had a full skillset.
And not only did
that stand out...
[announcer]   Finds Garnett.
[Scoop]
But his mouth stood out.
[Kevin screams]
[Scoop]   Who is this dude
talking this much shit,
like, nonstop?
I might have heard him
before I even saw him.
You know what I mean?
Because, on the court,
that's he do.
Like, he talk a lot.
The words are very explicit.
But what I saw
was a great talent.
You could just see
that he was gonna be special.
He was built like Kareem was
when he was in high school--
like Lew Alcindor.
Very slender.
[speaker] When this guy
walks in, he this skinny.
I said, "Can you really play?"
[chuckles]
And he's like,
"Oh, I can play."
[announcer]
William "Wolf" Nelson.
They call him Wolf.
You ask the players,
"Who's your coach?" "Wolf."
[Kevin]   I met my coach Wolf
there, William Nelson.
He coached our team.
He was always there
for advice,
always there to help me
in any way that I needed it.
Wolf was
that connecting bridge
between me and my mom,
with the idea that, you know,
"Kevin can be something
"and he just has to, you know,
be committed to this,
and he has to be, you know,
two feet in."
And he got her
to understand that.
suspenseful music
[Kevin]   Season's over.
Went in school one day,
and one of my friends, Trey,
he played soccer,
so a lot of his friends were
some white kids.
As we were walking by,
in Three's having
a disagreement
with one of the guys,
and they jumped on him
and started beating his ass.
So we jumped in,
kind of, you know,
separated or whatever,
and it ended up
being a big-ass fight.
A kid broke his foot,
and this kid's dad
was a big deal,
so he came up to school
wanting people to be arrested,
and kind of made up
this roundup of all of us
and threw us--threw us in--
threw us in jail.
I got charged with lynching.
Lynching is called mob action.
Mob action is when a group
attacks another group
and someone gets hurt.
It got all dismissed,
but coaches quit calling,
and, you know,
the phone doesn't work now.
People that was riding your
coattail or was gassing you,
they was talking more shit
to you now,
and people
was turning their back.
What's even more crazy
than this is that
three months
from me getting in trouble,
I actually visited Paul Pierce
out in Inglewood.
There was this AAU team
called the K-Swiss All Stars,
and Paul Pierce was one
of them and I was one of them.
[Paul]   Where should I start?
All right, I guess, let me
tell you about my AAU team.
I played for this team
called the K-Swiss Pacers.
We're a Southern California-
based team
between Inglewood and Compton.
Everybody was wearing Reebok,
Nike, you know, Adidas.
We were sponsored by K-Swiss.
They actually made
a basketball shoe.
That's how broke our team was.
[laughs]
But we had a lot
of hard workers.
And so every year,
from, like, junior high,
we played against a team
called South Coast.
We lose to them every year.
And so this is
the last summer coming up.
Our K-Swiss coach, Thad McGrew,
he was like,
"I got a player coming in.
You know, he's gonna play
in this last tournament."
Las Vegas, the biggest
tournament of the summer.
And I was like, "Who?"
He was like, "Kevin Garnett."
I was like, "What?
Oh, man, this is just
what we need right here."
Wow, man.
The first time I heard the name
Kevin Garnett was in Las Vegas,
matching up against him
in a big-time game
in the championship.
The result was him
putting my ass on the cover
of "Blue Chip."
I don't know if you remember
"Blue Chip" magazine.
It had him jumping over me
at the free throw line
with doing a hook shot.
And the flipping caption,
excuse my French, read,
"Kevin Garnett
soars above Jelani McCoy
and the rest
of the class of 1995."
And I'll never forget
that shit in my life.
[Paul]   Man, I really thought
he was gonna come to LA.
I remember going to the YMCA
every day,
putting in a call, like,
"Man, how you doing?
"Man, what you thinking about?
Let's do this, man.
"Come to the Wood.
You can stay with Mom.
You know, she gonna cook
for us every day."
Then, when I found out he was
going to Farragut in Chicago,
I was like, "Oh, man,
what could have been."
[Wolf]   I was trying
to recruit Kevin.
And I tell it
to Kevin's mother.
And I'll never forget this.
She says to me,
"Wolf, you don't
have to recruit Kevin.
You already got him."
She, like, dropped him
like right in my lap.
[train tracks clattering]
[Kevin]
This was my only option,
so I didn't really think
of anything else.
This was it.
And, you know,
I didn't get to choose.
This was chosen for me.
When I got in trouble
and went to jail,
my mom called Wolf
and was like,
"Listen, I need Kevin
to get up from down here.
"You know,
if I send him up there,
would you basically
watch over him?"
And that's who Wolf is.
He was more like the coach
that players came to
when they didn't have a home.
He was that calming voice
for the younger generation.
Been out here
in a minute, man.
Ain't haven't been in Farragut
since I left his muh.
Whoo!
-Where the balls at? Shit.
-[Wolf] Man, man!
They ain't said nothing.
Shit.
Hey, hey,
I remember first time
you grabbed that ball in there.
[laughs]
Hey, hey, man, hey,
feel that, man.
Feel this shit right here, boy.
You hear me?
You can't handle this, boy.
Hey, I give you
a pounding, boy.
Boy, I'll pound--
I'll pound you.
I'll pound you right now.
You got the whole shrine
in this motherfucker, right?
How the team and shit, man?
How y'all look?
How we looking this year?
They a'ight. We lost the
semi again, you know, but--
Man, somebody
told me something, man.
"Wolf always gets it done.
Always gets it done."
Let me see the gym, man.
I ain't been in the gym
in a minute, man.
[Wolf laughs]
Duck your head.
[Kevin] Oh, wow. This is crazy.
-Kids see this every day?
-[Wolf] Every day.
[Kevin]
Come in every day to that?
[Wolf] Every day.
I bet you can't even touch
the top of the rim.
-Stop playing!
-Oh, man.
[Wolf]
He ain't gotta jump, man! Stop!
-[Kevin] Ah!
-[laughter]
Kevin had been playing
in the NBA for quite a while,
and then he called me.
He said, "Yeah,
you see what I got last night?"
I said, "What?"
He said, "I got 28 rebounds
like Wilt Chamberlain!"
-[laughter]
-[Ron] "I got 28 rebounds!"
Like Stilt.
I used to tell him,
"Man, you gotta get them
rebounds, man. Get in there."
He love fucking Wilt.
He loves Wilt.
Always give credit to Wolf
and Coach Eskridge
for bringing out
the creative side of me.
Hey, man, look,
you out here on this court.
Be yourself out here.
So you know,
I used to come out here
and be very upset
or expressive
or something might be going on
off the court
that they know is fucking--
And I'll come out here and
I'll just--I'll let it out.
My mom dropped them bags off
and left us
with a couple dollars.
I went and got some change,
'cause there wasn't
no cell phones then.
Called Wolf.
He came and picked me up.
And it was like
on-the-job training
on how to survive Chicago
one-on-one from that point on.
This is the South Side,
this is the West Side,
this is the North Side.
You gotta understand gangs.
You got Vice Lords,
you got Breeds.
you got GDs,
you got Latin Kings,
and you gotta know
how it works.
And if you don't know this,
you end up dead.
And that's when I was like,
"God damn.
"We're not
in South Carolina anymore.
This is real."
There's a war going on
outside no man is safe from
You can run but
you can't hide forever
[Scoop]   Chicago has always
had a unique history
when it comes to basketball
and players
that come from the city.
There is no separation
between mostly being Black
and being from Chicago
and being connected
to the game of basketball.
I don't know what basketball
is like in South Carolina.
You know, the kid
is ridiculously skilled.
But if he ain't cut out here,
he can forget it.
Survival of the fit,
only the strong survive
Yo, we living this
till the day that we die
[speaker]   You can't understand
Chicago basketball
until you've experienced it
and lived it.
High school basketball
in Chicago,
that's where you
make your mark.
If you're a bad boy in college,
all right, that's cool.
You a bad boy in the pros,
that's cool.
But if you a bad boy
in high school,
then you got name notoriety
forever.
That's Chicago basketball.
We go to the toughest
spots.
-Toughest spots.
-It was proving grounds.
And these guys
were straight thugs.
They hitting them,
and he's dunking on them
while he getting hit
in the gut.
Boom, boom, boom.
[speaker]   We'd take them to
some of these places where,
listen,
if you call a foul,
you more than likely gonna
get your ass whooped.
Don't call no fouls in here.
You gon' have
to play through it.
[producer] Ronnie Fields
interview, take one.
[Kevin]   Ronnie was a really
gung-ho city kid.
Lived really fast.
Ronnie was a grown man
in high school.
Ronnie had been playing for us
when he was
in elementary school.
Like, from seventh grade.
By the time
he was in eighth grade,
he was dunking on grown men.
[chaotic cheers and applause]
Ronnie Fields was like
watching Michael Jordan
in high school.
He could drop 50 on you,
he could do a 360 dunk.
All he did
was drive people crazy.
They couldn't get enough
of Ronnie Fields!
[Scoop]   You know, people would
come to see Ronnie Fields
put on shows
at the summer leagues.
Like, it's that
must-see situation.
Ronnie was a superstar.
[Kevin]   I had never experienced
a player like Ronnie Fields.
Although he was a guard
and I was a big,
he would help me
on guard stuff,
and I would help him on
post-up and stuff like that.
He was probably
one of the better teammates
I've ever had in my life,
as a player and as a friend.
[Ronnie]
It's not easy, you know,
just picking up,
leaving somewhere you been at,
and adapting to
a different city.
You know, a lot of things could
have went a different way.
Moving to a city at the time
that also is not just
basketball-known
but also known for a lot
of other dangerous things.
[Kevin]   Our school
was known for rioting.
End up ending school
with a big old fight.
My first day in the cafeteria
to eat lunch,
kid threw a hot dog at me.
Here, the lunch line right
here, this whole shit stopped.
-I was like--
-[Wolf laughs]
So I used to sit
with my back against this wall,
looking like this,
so I could--you know?
It was crazy.
Hi, my name's Kevin Garnett.
I graduate in the year 1995.
I plan on taking up business
at the University of Syracuse.
[cheers and applause]
[Wolf]   When Kevin
first came to Farragut,
nobody really knew
how to react.
It's been a long time since
we had a kid as big as Kevin.
[indistinct chatter
and laughter]
[Ronnie]   We ain't never seen
a guy 6'10", 6'11"--
I haven't--to do the things
that KG did.
Most the bigs you see, you
can see is, like, not fluent,
but they working on it.
With Kevin, you could see
he already had it.
[audience exclaims]
[Jim]
Jim Blaney and David Kaplan
from Proviso West High School.
This is the game,
and this is the team
that everybody has been here
for four days to watch.
[David]   I'll tell you what,
all day I was like a kid
in a candy store.
Couldn't wait.
Ronnie Fields, Kevin Garnett,
going up against Westinghouse.
I mean, buckle in your chin
strap, put the seatbelt on.
This one's gonna be great fun.
So Farragut was always
one of the better programs.
They always had good players,
and Ronnie Fields
was an elite player.
And now, all of a sudden,
Farragut gets that guy?
[announcer]
Garnett back down yet again,
and then that's Fields
cleaning up.
That one-two duo probably the
best in the country right now.
[David]   The Garnett-Fields
combination was unbridled joy
at all times on the court.
They knew how to play
with each other.
It could be Ronnie
coming down,
you think he's gonna dunk,
off the backboard,
here comes Garnett behind him
to slam it home.
They wanted to not
only beat you,
they wanted to
put a beating on you
and do it with a big smile
on their face,
having as much fun
as they possibly could.
And all of a sudden,
it wasn't just Farragut fans
going to the game,
it wasn't the city fans
going to the game.
You would see people
coming from the suburbs,
north and south
and west, going,
"I gotta go see
these guys play!"
[speaker]
I grew up in the Chicagoland.
I was in the western suburbs
of Naperville.
I remember hearing my parents
talk around the dinner table
about this
just freak of an athlete.
We actually were able to catch
a game, fight the crowd
and the people climbing the
fences to see this guy play.
[announcer]   And boy,
the fans are into it.
[Candace]   And so it was
our chance to kind of claim
that we saw him before
the rest of the world did.
I didn't know what was
about to happen. Real shit.
But this was another level, yo.
Plus Mike ain't playing?
I'm very solid
with my decision
of not to play
the game of basketball.
[Scoop]
The fact that Jordan retired
left a door cracked for
something special to happen.
As good as the Bulls were,
they still weren't
fascinating.
And with Jordan,
we were used to fascination.
And here comes,
right at the right time,
this team from Farragut
with Kevin Garnett
that brought fascination back.
Farragut became Showtime.
[announcer]
Williams put it up.
"Get it out of there,"
says Garnett.
Washington.
Jam follow by Kevin Garnett!
-Oh, baby!
-[cheers and applause]
[Wolf]   What Farragut brought
to Chicago that year,
there was never anything
like that before.
There was nowhere that we went
that wasn't sold out.
They were scalping tickets.
Tickets cost $5,
people paying $50 for a ticket.
[journalist] Well, you two
are quite the combination,
Kevin Garnett
and Ronnie Fields.
We took over the next act
in Chicago.
It wasn't baseball,
it wasn't the Bears,
and it wasn't hockey.
It was the Bulls,
then it was Farragut.
[David]   Kevin Garnett was
one the toughest kids
I'd been around.
Nobody intimidated him.
And as that senior year here
in Chicago rolled on,
the crowds got bigger
and bigger and bigger,
to where it was like
the Beatles were coming in.
And none of that affected him.
He fed off that energy.
[Kevin]   It was my first time
feeling like a rockstar.
I never experienced basketball
in this level
going through schools--
we would win,
come to school the next day,
and there would be,
like, a pep rally.
Like, nobody in class.
Everybody cheering,
high fiving, and niggas
forgot about fighting.
Everybody
forgot about their set
or forgot about their gang,
and it was just--it was
Farragut against everybody.
I got a lot of good play
from these guys.
They've won 27 games in a row.
We haven't lost since November.
[newscaster]
Hey, Coach.
Before you go, can you
throw a basket in the hoop?
-Me?
-[newscaster]   Yeah.
Yeah, just throw one
in the hoop.
-[player] Yeah, yeah!
-[newscaster]   All right.
[chuckling]
All right, Coach.
Going through the season
that year,
and to win all of those games
in a row--
I would try to figure out
how far we could go.
would we ever lose again?
[Kevin]
Wolf would encourage me
to bring the ball up
and use some of my handles.
And, "Next time you drunk,
scream!"
And I was like, "What?"
Wolf wanted the more
personality to come out.
He wanted that animal.
"You mad?
Well, show them you mad!"
[Wolf]   He told me that
his coach in South Carolina
was a strict coach.
He wouldn't allow him
to unleash.
But when he was
playing with me,
I saw that there's a lot more
under the surface.
All you had to do
was just let it go.
[announcer]   Put it back in.
There you go!
Kevin Garnett!
Showtime!
You start seeing something
come out of him.
And I was like, okay,
a lot of people
gonna be in some trouble.
That's when I knew, like,
"All right. Oh, ain't nobody
gonna beat us."
energetic upbeat music
[Kevin]
Where's this at? Where we at?
That's the Final Four game.
This Dunbar,
the one we   almost   lost.
Aw, shit.
A lot of people think, like,
New York is the mecca
of basketball, man.
Chicago got a toughness
about the city that
it's almost like a reputation
that comes with it.
[Scoop]   In Chicago,
city championships are often
more important
than the state championship
because you could come from
some bum-ass school district
in the state of Illinois
and get a chance
to go down state,
where you have the biggest
public school system
in the nation--
only one spot to play
for a state championship.
Only one.
So winning the city
is a big deal,
and no other teams
that come from other parts
of the state have to go through
what you have to go through
to get there.
[newscaster]   Today's
Public League title tilt
between Farragut and Carver.
Much-anticipated showdown
between the two powers.
Garnett
finishes with 32 points.
He scored 16 straight
in one stretch of this game.
[announcer]
Farragut beats Carver 71-62.
Their first
Public League title.
William Nelson and company
are off to Champaign,
and they're going in style.
First trip to Champaign, man,
I have to go shopping.
I can't win in
none of this old stuff.
I got--I got to throw
all this away.
I mean--hey, see, I'm happy
as I don't know what.
[laughs]
[David]   They're in the elite
eight and everyone thought,
well, now it's just
a fait accompli.
Mail it in. They're gonna
win the state title.
suspenseful dramatic music
[announcer]
Garnett. Eight seconds.
Garnett. He's gonna shoot it.
His shot...
is no good.
The rebound battle for it.
They need three to tie.
Can they get it off?
Fields can't get it off!
It's over!
downbeat dramatic music
[cheering]
[announcer]   Players from each
team congratulating the others
after a monumental upset
in Champaign.
[Kevin]   We go down.
We lose to Thornton at state,
and it was a bunch of what-ifs
and all this other stuff
that surround it.
But at the end of the day,
we just lost.
[Wolf]   I was too young
and too inexperienced a coach.
I never went out
and scouted the other team.
They had three future
NFL football players
and a future NBA
basketball player on the team.
These guys are studs.
Again, I was young and dumb,
but I learned a lesson
the hard way.
[Ronnie]   The hardest thing
is knowing the next day
you didn't have another game.
We probably ain't finna
go back out here
and play another
high school game together.
So then I start
to really feel like,
"Okay, I gotta make a decision
on what I'm doing next,"
and it was all university,
it was all college
at this point.
It was all about test scores.
[Wolf]   After the season,
we were dealing
with his recruitment.
We were trying to improve
his test score.
I would talk to
the college coaches
and try and maintain
and keep his options open.
[sportscaster]
And you heard the schools
that he's looking at
right now, the top five?
Michigan's in there
in a big way.
He went to see
Louisville-UCLA on Sunday.
He is involved with
so many different schools.
Test scores was like a
nagging flea or a nagging fly.
It was just always there.
In was getting really
frustrated with the process.
[announcer]
This is Kevin Garnett,
our tallest of the finalists.
He told me that he definitely
wants to go to college,
count on him going
to college.
The only problem is right now,
he doesn't have his grades.
But then, Wolf tells me that
I got chosen
for the McDonald's.
I gotta go to St. Louis,
which was kind of a big deal.
That was one of the most
talented McDonald's classes
all-time.
[Jelani]   The East squad had
Marbury, Shammgod,
Vince, Jamison,
Shareef Abdur-Rahim.
We had myself, KG,
Paul, Chauncey,
"Tractor" Traylor,
rest in peace.
[announcer]   Kevin Garnett
gets the rebound, number 21.
Right side.
Goes to BJ McKie.
-Oh!
-[audience exclaiming]
[Paul]
He was a different player
from the time he played
in that tournament
with me that summer
until the Mickey D's game,
just attitude-wise.
I mean, if you go back
and watch that game...
[announcer]
Here's the stuff by Garnett.
[Paul]   I mean, it was something
every single time
he scored the ball
or made a play.
[Jelani]   By the time I got back
to him at the McDonald's game,
there was a turn.
I'm just getting excited
thinking about it right now,
'cause the fundamentals
and the work ethic,
the work ethic--the sprinting,
you know what I mean?
The want to win every 17,
wanting to stretch
and be the first person
on the floor,
last person to leave,
sending messages to his peers
and the other people
that watching
that he took the game
of basketball very seriously.
[announcer]
...with an easy one.
What's up, Mauldin?
I'm up here chilling.
What's up, dog?
Ended up being the MVP
of the game
and the
Most Outstanding Player.
sparse suspenseful music
But we had $200 to our name
to last us for two months.
The next day,
I got an eviction notice
that I was gonna get
kicked out July 1st,
so I was just
really stressing.
And to get my mind
off of the stress,
on top of I can't pass
this fucking SAT/ACT test,
my nigga said, "Let's go
downtown and play some ball."
[switch clicks and echoes]
He said, "Let's go down
to the Retroplex, man,
"you know, the joint
down near the Hilton
where they got
the really nice gym at."
I was like, "Oh, yeah.
It is Saturday.
There'll be some really
good games in there."
Yeah, maybe some guys
from South Side
and North Side would come meet
and get in there.
Mike Jordan in there.
upbeat music
And they playing in this
kind of glass-filled gym,
and we're leaning
on the thing, looking at him,
fogging up the glasses.
And I'm looking,
and all of a sudden,
security--
doom, doom, doom--pointing.
Was like,
"Hey, you. Come here."
I was like, "Me?"
And he was like,
"Let big fella in."
And when he said it,
I was like,
"Yo, throw my shoes.
Yo, throw my shoes."
So I grab my shoes.
I'm so fucking cheesy.
So I'm seeing who in here.
I see Pipp in here.
I see a couple people
that I recognize.
And then Jordan was like,
"Let's go."
So, we--we--we go.
And I was like--
[claps and whistles]
and I call for it.
Mike threw it. Boom.
And I took a couple dribbles,
and launch my shit.
Boom!
And I said something, like,
to the line of "I don't know
what you think this is. Shit."
And he was like,
"What you say?"
And I said, "You heard me!"
I was just running off emotion,
you understand?
And I don't know
how I got calmed down,
[chucking]
but I held my own in here.
And in the corner,
I see a pair of feet.
I look,
and it was Isiah Thomas.
And he was in an Avirex
purple jacket,
and he had it zipped up.
He was in the corner like this.
I'm there doing
"scouting" work.
'Cause now I'm part-owner
and the executive
of the Toronto Raptors.
So I shout to him
like I knew him.
And "Hey, Z, what's up, man?
Oh, snap, man. What's up?
Oh, damn, boy!
Yeah, yeah, yeah."
"I just saw you play
Scottie Pippen, boy.
You can play
in the league right now."
And when he said that, dog,
the world stopped.
I said, "Zeke, what you say?"
He said, "Boy, do you know
you can go to the league
from high school?"
I was like, "Nah."
And I just remember
saying to him,
"One day you gonna be a pro.
And it might be next week."
[laughs]
[Kevin] Hey, man,
they still got VCRs?
-Are you serious?
-[person] Hey, hey, hey!
I'd like to thank all you
for attending
my press conference today.
As you all know,
May 10, I declared myself
eligible for the NBA Draft.
-[Kevin] Look at your ass.
-[Wolf] I know! I know!
I know! I know! I know!
[Kevin] I was nervous as shit.
I ain't never sat
in front of no media.
Ain't nobody ever trained us
to say certain yada yada.
[journalist] Kevin,
I know you've come very close
to getting the score
that you need for the ACT.
Has it been frustrating to come
so close so many times,
and do you plan
to take the ACT again?
Well, either way,
I'ma get my degree,
no matter how long it takes.
My coach took, what,
20 years to get your degree?
[laughter]
[journalist] Kevin, do you
think you're mature enough
physically or emotionally
to handle the NBA?
Yeah.
It shouldn't be that hard.
'Cause moving from a small town
to the big city
is a real big adjustment.
I'm up here like,
"I'm finna do this.
"These niggas ain't never
lived in the 'Go.
"Man, I get--I get up to walk
through this motherfucker
every day."
Oh, no, the league
ain't hard on us. Hell nah.
[journalist] Coach Nelson,
what kind of input have you
gotten from the NBA people
regarding Kevin's likely
draft status?
So I would go out
and talk to different
NBA people on behalf of Kevin,
'cause I told him,
"You can't talk to an agent,
so I'm gonna be your surrogate.
"I will come back
and relay to you
what's--what's being said."
And so as I started to talk
with my different friends
in the NBA
that I had scouted with or for,
they all said, "Yeah,
"he's gonna have a workout
during the pre-draft camp.
"Let's see how he does there
"when we put him through
an NBA workout.
A high school kid?
No chance."
And I'm chuckling to myself,
"You guys have no idea."
I heard Pat Riley, like,
"Come on!
"Let's get this started!
Why are we even here?
"Like, what the fuck is this?
Got me watching
a high school guy?"
And I was like,
"[inhales deeply]
Hmm.
"You don't know why you here?
All right."
And I did the workout
with that energy.
90 minutes, by myself.
90 minutes,
by myself.
dramatic hip-hop beat
90 fucking minutes
by my motherfucking self.
Fuck do you think this is?
At the end of the workout,
they want to see
how high I can jump,
so I was catching them mo--
dunk, boom!
[huffs]
Boom!
"Go higher."
I dunked this thing
maybe seven, eight times,
and then I was like,
"[bellows]
"Motherfucker!
Fuck you mean,
'Why you in here?'"
[polite clap]
"Nice workout, young fella.
Nice workout."
Kevin McHale comes down from
the bottom of the bleachers.
Says, "Young fella, like
your little jumper you got."
You know,
he starts talking fast.
You ever been around Kevin
McHale, he talks really fast.
"Got a nice,
little jumper there.
"You know, on the face,
you want to get your--
you know, when you come around,
you want to--"
and I'm tired, so I'm like,
"Oh, shit,
Kevin McHale's talking to me."
He was like,
"Yeah, I'm talking to you.
God damn, I might draft you.
Shit."
Might have caught four words
out of the whole exchange,
but holy shit.
With the fifth pick
in the 1995 NBA Draft,
the Minnesota Timberwolves
select Kevin Garnett
from Farragut Academy
in Chicago.
[cheers and applause]
[Kevin]   And David Stern said,
"And with the fifth pick
in the 1995 Draft,
the Minnesota Timberwolves
select..."
and everything else
went silent.
I didn't hear nothing.
I just remember my agent
kicking me under the stage.
Says, "Showtime."
I said, "What?"
[commentator]   The high school
kid is the number five pick
in the NBA Draft.
[Paul]   "Kevin Garnett is going
to the league."
I'm like, "What?"
Nobody ever heard of this!
[commentator]   Not only the
shot blocking, rebounding,
he runs the floor
like the wind
for a player that size.
[Paul]   You got all
these established stars
getting drafted.
You know, Joe Smith
out of Maryland,
Sheed, Stackhouse,
and then you got
this skinny kid
out of Farragut High School
go in the lottery.
Well, that was the cover.
"Ready or Not."
That was the big question.
[Isiah]   Kevin McHale calls me
up a week before the draft,
and he goes,
"Are you gonna draft him?"
And I said, "If he's at seven,
I'm going to take him."
And he said, "Do you think
I should draft him at five?"
It's between he and Stoudamire.
I say, "That's what I have
on my board also."
Standing by now is Isiah Thomas
of the Toronto Raptors.
[Isiah]
I couldn't lie to McHale.
[chuckles]
So he ended up taking him,
and I ended up with Stoudamire.
And when I'm getting ready
in the mirror,
Wolf calls my room, says, "Man,
I just got your test scores.
"Man, your test scores
came in, man.
We got the score, baby!
What we doing?"
[Wolf]   Told him, I said,
"Got something for you."
[laughs]
So he was like, "What?"
"Your scores came in."
dramatic orchestral music
Like, "You know,
I'm in the middle of doing shit
right now."
[laughs]
I like, "Well, you got--
just wanna let you know
you passed."
Man, fuck them scores, man.
I'm going to the school
of hard knocks.
[applause]
But yeah, save them shit,
so I can show my kids one day,
you know what I'm saying?
I finally killed that little
gnat and that little fly.
I got him outta here.
[applause]
[Matt Winer]
Now to the critical next step
to being named
to the Basketball Hall of Fame.
The next nominee
is a South Carolina native.
He would become
the first person in 20 years
to be selected by an NBA team
directly from high school.
You know him as KG
or the Big Ticket:
-Kevin Garnett.
-[applause]
Kevin...
what would that kid
who made the leap to the NBA
in 1995 think of this?
He'd probably think that this
was pretty awesome right here.
[laughter]
-It is.
-Yeah.
The Hall of Fame
is something that
you don't really think about,
you don't really dream about,
it just happens.
I'm more than--
I'm more than honored for this.
This is over my head.
This is--this is one of
the more over, um--
ooh, get it together.
This is more--one of the more
overwhelming situations
I've ever been in.
Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
I had to do
"Regis & Kathie Lee,"
and I wore this American--
[laughs]
I wore this American jacket.
I don't even know
why I wore that,
but it felt, like, fitting.
I didn't even know
what to wear.
Well, congratulations.
This is some story.
Hasn't been done in 20 years.
-How old are you?
-I just turned 19.
-[Regis] Oh you just turned 19?
-Yeah.
Well, so what are you
gonna do with all your money?
I don't know, um...
I haven't got it yet,
so I can't really...
[laughter and applause]
-plan for it, actually.
-[applause]
Nobody really expected that,
somebody to come right out
of high school.
It wasn't illegal.
Just nobody was doing it.
At the time,
I wasn't even aware
that it had happened before.
Obviously,
learning the history,
found out there's, you know,
people before him,
but it hadn't happened
in 20 years.
[Scoop]   The first thing
that came to my mind
was Moses Malone, 'cause
I'm old enough to remember
Moses did it out of Virginia,
and he went straight
to the ABA.
He went to the Utah Stars.
And then Bill Willoughby
came around.
And then Darryl Dawkins
went into it.
You know,
the opening was there.
It's not like there were
any rules or laws
preventing this from happening
for 20 years.
Just nobody had done it.
Nobody had been bold enough.
I think he was
the perfect person for it.
When you think about
his body type,
his skillset, his athleticism,
you put all that together,
why wouldn't you go
straight into the NBA?
[indistinct chatter]
[Kevin McHale]   The transition
when I went to the NBA,
well, it knocked me
on my rear end.
It was like, "Wow, this
is a huge, huge transition."
So knowing that,
I went in with Kevin
trying to really spend
some time with him
and understand
that he's gonna go through
the same thing
that I went through,
maybe even more,
maybe even magnified more.
[Sam]
We had tough practices.
You know,
we were tired of losing,
and we felt like we needed
to be a physical team.
So Kevin, coming in as
a rookie, 19 years old,
when he would come to the hole,
we'd put him on the ground.
My first time
going to the hole,
Doug West
gave me a real hard foul.
We jumped up
and we started fighting.
Maybe 30 minutes later,
a rebounding drill,
me and another guy,
we get into it.
Boom, same thing.
I want them to know
that I would fight,
and I didn't give a fuck.
And if they wanted
to go to war, we can do that.
After the second practice,
Sam Mitchell
came and knocked on my door.
I opened up through the chain,
like, "What?"
And he was like,
"Man, open the door!"
I was like,
"Man, what you want?"
Slammed the door his face--
doom!
He was super patient.
He knocked on the door.
I let him in.
And we had, like,
a three-hour conversation.
After that practice, it was
a lot of tension in the air.
Guys were angry.
And I did not want him
to walk away
thinking that we were
against him.
Hold up. You do what I want.
Where my boy at?
[Jelani]   So when you're
a young player in the NBA,
you have to have
a support system.
You not prepared for this,
your family isn't gonna be
prepared for this,
even if they do have some sense
of financial literacy.
[Kevin]   Funny part.
[chuckles]
I didn't believe in banks.
For my first couple years,
we brown bagged it.
I had like 2, 3 million
under my mattress.
Uh, yeah, then I learned
about direct deposit.
energetic orchestral music
[Kevin McHale]
I'm very impatient
when it comes to winning
and losing.
I do not like to lose.
If something inside you isn't
torn apart when you lose,
then you're a loser.
But if that something
inside you hurts,
and you say to yourself,
"What can I do to stop this
from happening again?"
then you have a winner,
eventually, that will come out.
[Howard]   I'm not sure you could
have mapped out a better path
for Kevin Garnett
than to have Kevin McHale
and Flip Saunders.
Flip, just because
of the touch he had.
He had this ability
to communicate with players,
to get the best out of them.
But then having Kevin McHale,
an actual living legend,
who's one of the great
all-time bigs,
who had won championships,
that mattered a lot.
You know, we're gonna
probably set up situations
for Kevin to know
a lot of different people
and feel comfortable
with a lot of different people.
And if he wants to get
a home-cooked meal,
they all come out to my house.
[Sam]   Kevin McHale created
an environment for KG to grow.
He understood the pressure
that KG was under,
he understood what it took
to be a great player,
he understood
the level of work
that you had to put in
to maintain that play.
It set the tone for his career
from day one.
[Howard]   The Timberwolves
that Garnett arrives to,
they're an expansion team
in a cold weather city.
They've averaged
21 wins a season.
They're not good.
That was NBA Siberia
at that time.
They badly needed a talent
who could become the face
of that franchise.
[sportscaster]
Now Kevin Garnett,
the high schooler,
now in the NBA,
is on the floor.
Hard to believe.
Gugliotta trying to save.
Does.
Garnett gets his
first NBA basket.
[Kevin]   Rookie night, I didn't
know really what was going on.
You know, you have a sense,
but the actual reality
of what's going on
doesn't hit you
till two or three days later,
till you're, like, "Holy snap."
old-school hip-hop beat
[sportscaster]   A three
in his Target Center debut.
[Kevin screaming]
[sportscaster]   Feeds it off
to Garnett for the dunk.
Oh, how about this block?
How about the lob?
And it works!
[sportscaster]
That's a great play!
Garnett has done
a little bit of everything
so far.
There's never a time where
you get the feeling he's saying,
"Wait a second,
I was playing Chicago high
school basketball last year."
[Kevin]   We was playing Chicago
on a back-to-back,
when my high school
teammate Ronnie Fields
was in a car accident.
[doctor]
Ronnie just came out of surgery
and he's in recovery,
and we all feel good
about the fact
that the surgery is over with,
and he's moving his hands
and his legs.
[Ronnie]   At the time of that
accident, that was the year
that I was gonna
probably come out as well.
If the scouts
like what they see,
or even my performance
on the court,
whether I go pro or not.
So you're thinking about it.
It's in the back of your mind.
Yeah, it's in the back
of my mind.
soft dramatic music
And I'll never forget
when I was laying there,
the only thing I do
is hear a voice.
And then I finally opened
my eyes, and I look up,
it was him.
Right when I landed,
I went to go see him.
He was in the greatest mood.
He was like, "Hey, you got
my tickets and shit?
"Yeah, I need my tickets.
You know, I got two girls
I'm trying
to take to the game."
I was like,
"What are you talking about?"
I'm the one supposed to feel,
you know, like,
maybe upset and all this stuff.
But I really wasn't as upset
as he was, because he was like,
"I'ma just stay here.
You want me to stay here?"
I said, "Man, you--no.
You got a game."
[sportscaster]   Kevin Garnett's
high school teammate,
Ronnie Fields,
we wish him the best,
but Kevin Garnett had
a little tribute to him.
[Kevin]
The excitement that night
was playing Michael Jordan
and the Bulls.
But after I seen Ronnie,
it was about
representing Ronnie.
I felt like
I was playing for him.
And I came in there
with that energy.
[sportscaster]
Instead, it's Garnett.
Oh, what a slam
from Kevin Garnett!
[Ronnie]   Laying in bed,
trying to watch the game,
not thinking about, like,
how messed up I was,
but how proud I was of him,
and the moment of, like,
-"Man..."
-[Kevin screaming]
"Hopefully I get a chance
to join him one day."
You know, with Ronnie's
situation right now,
it's critical,
so I think everybody--
every basketball player out
there just thanking the Lord
for every God-given talent
they have.
Hmm.
No, I couldn't imagine that.
That would be death to me.
Kevin Garnett
was spectacular tonight.
We're gonna clear
a little bit of room for Kevin
to come on in right about now.
Good job, baby.
Good job.
Hey, we didn't want to make
Kevin wait too long,
as Kevin Garnett's
just gonna put the headset on.
A great finish
to tonight's game.
Like, we won, came out,
had to do some press.
And there's this kid
sitting in my seat.
And he's like, "What's up?
What's up, dog?
I'm Kobe. Kobe Bryant.
How you doing?"
I was like, "What's up, man?
You're in my seat."
And he was like,
"Oh, my fault. My fault."
And I was like, "Kobe Bryant?"
I was like,
"All right. What's up, man?"
"I'm coming out this year.
I watched you play, man.
What's it like, man?"
And, you know,
the guys are around,
so they sitting here
watching us talk.
So they like, "Tell him
what's it like, big fella."
I was like,
"Shit, this shit hard as shit.
I mean, but your dad was
in the league, so..."
"No, fuck that. No,
I want to hear it from you."
We just sat there
and we talked for like an hour.
And I said,
"I'll see you on top."
He said, "Nah, you gonna
see me next year. I'm coming."
The National Basketball
Association draft of new talent
is coming up on Wednesday.
This year's crop
is younger than ever,
and includes
a record number of players
who either
didn't finish college
or didn't even get there.
[Ernie Johnson]
A lot of kids coming out.
Childhood a not-too-distant
memory for some of these guys.
So KG comes out in '95,
and Kobe Bryant takes notice,
Jermaine O'Neal takes notice.
These guys now see
there's a path there.
Then, after that,
you see McGrady,
you see Dwight Howard,
you see LeBron.
He created them.
That's a product
of Kevin Garnett.
All greats who came
out of high school.
Opened up the floodgates.
The Milwaukee Bucks
select Stephon Marbury
-from Georgia Tech University.
-[cheers and applause]
[Kevin]
My junior year in high school,
I get a call
at my mom's house.
Ring.
About 10:00.
[clicks tongue]
"Can I speak to Kev?"
Steph called me, and we just
talked for like six hours.
Steph was on some, like, "Yo,
let's go to college together.
You see the Fab Five?"
We was on some, like,
let's have our own thing,
kind of like that.
So when he got drafted
by Milwaukee, Flip was like,
"Yo, I'm trading Ray for him.
You with that?"
I was like, "Yeah."
So we've had the ceremonial
switch of hats
over there, at the trade,
Stephon Marbury to Minnesota
for Ray Allen,
who goes to Milwaukee.
And Marbury likes
Kevin Garnett.
Now he goes to Minnesota.
It was perfect, 'cause now
I had a real friend.
I'm just, I'm so happy
to be here.
I'm getting to play
with one of my friends.
you know, when you got
a good point guard
and a great big man,
you can start something.
You can start a good franchise,
like Magic and Kareem.
Here comes the brand new
flava in ya ear
Time for new flava
in ya ear
I'm kicking new flava
Mack's the brand-new flava
in ya ear
[Howard]   Stephon Marbury
was your classic
New York point guard
coming out.
Flashy, brash,
full of bravado.
[sportscaster]
To Kevin! Oh, baby!
[Howard]   He and KG
were the perfect fit.
On day one, you could see
this could be one of
the all-time great duos.
[sportscaster]   Two-man game.
Garnett. Big-time jam!
[sportscaster]
Marbury the other way.
[Matt]   They were both
just high-energy guys.
Their ability just to raise
the level of competition
and raise the level of energy
based off their youth
and enthusiasm,
was something special
in itself.
[Paul]   I mean, who didn't want
to watch Stephon Marbury,
a New York kid
with the handles,
highly-touted
since he was a sixth-grader.
Then you had KG
out of high school.
It was just like, they could
be together a long time
running the NBA.
[Howard]   Suddenly, those
two were not just the stars
of the Timberwolves franchise,
they were stars
of the new NBA.
They were on nightly highlight
reels on SportsCenter.
Right off the bat,
there was a famous/infamous
Marbury and Garnett
"ESPN Magazine" commercial.
"ESPN Magazine"
is gonna be phat.
But please, no swimsuits.
Yeah, no bikinis.
No one-pieces.
-No thongs.
-None of that.
[both] All nude.
Tastefully done.
[chuckles]
We didn't even practice that.
We just jumped right into it.
That shit took seven minutes.
It was on everything.
And we was, like,
the new it.
upbeat music
[Matt]   I remember seeing
that classic cover on "SLAM"
with Kevin and Marbury.
It was that complete crossover
between basketball and hip hop.
You seen jewelry,
you seen the do-rags,
and you seen people
that started
reflecting people
from neighborhoods.
[Metta]   It was more of a thing
where I want to be like that.
I don't only want to make it,
but I also want that lifestyle.
[chuckles]
I want that chain, you know?
That cover was something
that validated,
"Hey, express yourself.
Show them what you got."
You know, I remember Iverson
wearing the big jewels,
and KG always had
those big earrings.
This was when we first got,
like, the visual aspect
that rappers wanted
to be athletes
and athletes wanted
to be rappers.
-[Kevin grunting]
-[basketball bouncing]
music fading
Yeah.
[basketball bouncing]
[Kevin grunts]
Could spend days in here.
I can quarantine
in a place like this.
-[net swishes]
-[cheers and applause]
-[sportscaster]   The Killa!
-[Kevin] The Killa!
-[chuckles]
-I'm the bite-sized--
I'm the bite-sized version
of KG. What's up, boy?
Soulja boy.
How you been?
Man, I'm all good.
Good to see you, man.
Everybody in here you have
on the wall is huge
in the history and the making
of the history of the NBA.
I even got Hakeem
teaching Shaq...
[Kevin] I see that!
-[Snoop] How to go big.
-[Kevin] I see that.
[Snoop] 'Cause that was
his teacher right there.
-[Kevin] Right.
-[Snoop] And see Dr. J,
the reason why I like him,
'cause I play in Chucks.
[Kevin] Facts.
[Snoop] Can't play in
no regular basketball shoes.
I gotta play in these, man.
[Kevin] You gotta play
in some Chucks.
Come on, man, that's OG-style.
[Kevin] I love it.
Fucking asses got Snooped.
-[Snoop] Oh, my God.
-Do you remember this?
Lord, this probably one of
the most unprofessional shits
-I've ever done.
-[laughing]
We get to motherfucker Toronto.
"Yo, Snoop in town!
Snoop playing tonight."
Like, "For real? Oh, hell no.
We gotta get some tickets."
So we go to the show.
The show banging.
Snoop kill that shit.
Dog, I think we hung out
till like--
Nigga, the sun came up.
I looked out my window, nigga,
I said,
"These niggas still here,
and the sun is rising."
Man, listen. We played
the Toronto Raptors at noon.
Halftime. I'm leading
the league in rebounds.
I have no rebounds.
Flip says, "God damn it, guys!
"These Toronto fans,
they get to see you once!
"God damn it,
come here and play like shit?
"You motherfuckers
hanging out with Snoop?
-You fucking got Snooped!"
-[laughing]
Yo, he cursed everybody out.
That shit was so bomb for us,
'cause, like,
you gotta understand, like,
when we get to hang out
with professional athletes,
it makes us feel like
professional athletes.
A lot of us think
that we y'all,
and a lot of y'all feel
like y'all us
when y'all listening
to that music.
It's just you take on that
spirit of "This is what I am."
Right, right.
old school hip-hop beat
[Kevin] A lot of the music
you listen to,
believe it or not,
is translated
in the moves you make.
Mm.
When in listen
to soulful R&B music,
you're a lot more finesse.
When you listen to music
with bass, and that hit?
[imitating intense music]
You hear that shit,
and that shit hits your veins,
mmm, you play like that.
Wow.
It's not--I'm not
finna finesse this nigga,
I'm finna go
through this nigga.
-I'm finna go over this nigga.
-[Snoop chuckling]
I ain't listening to
no Stephanie Mills
-before I play Charles Barkley.
-[Snoop laughs]
Hip hop and basketball
go hand-in-motherfucking-hand.
That's exactly what that is.
It was always some connection,
and that was before
it got like it is now.
That's when it was, like,
a chosen few niggas
would fuck with hip-hop,
'cause they didn't want to use
their job or be associated
with the shit that we did,
because at that time,
the NBA wasn't as lenient
as they is now,
with niggas fucking with,
you know, real motherfuckers.
'Cause the shit that we do,
y'all can't do.
But back then,
y'all couldn't be next
to the niggas that did it.
Right.
So do you think now
they got leverage
with the Black Lives movement?
I don't know, man.
I actually thought for a second
that the players had momentum
to where,
if they could've
took a stance...
-Together.
-All of them together,
Said, "No, we not playing,"
that they could have actually
went on Capitol Hill
and started a conversation.
-A real one.
And started talking
about police reform,
coming up with new programs
for the Black community.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, also real reparation.
And I thought that, you know,
just falling in line actually
didn't really help anything.
Like, it ain't just us, dog.
[Snoop] But--but--but you--but
you gotta say this to yourself:
if you, young KG, and you
in the league and you playing,
and you put in this position,
do you step out?
Because when the majority say,
"Nigga, we going."
You ain't making no money."
That's the first thing
they gonna throw in your face.
I would have had to go up
to Capitol Hill on my own.
I couldn't have just sat back
and just, what, did nothing
or chill at the crib?
It's an uncomfortable
conversation, Snoop.
It is!
But, like--
Niggas had--niggas--right!
The whole shit!
You know what I'm saying?
It's--
We used to it,
because we always be
in uncomfortable situations.
We--our ears is trained
to hear it.
It don't offend us.
But the average motherfucker
hear that shit
and get all rubbed
the wrong way!
Man, let sports shut down.
Let products not move.
Let motherfuckers stop
buying shit.
-Now it's a conversation!
-[Kevin] I'm saying, yo!
dramatic ambient music
[Jeanelle] Hey, KG,
you're not gonna remember me,
but I used to be
your ball girl.
That's what up.
Way back in the day.
It's good to see you again.
[Kevin] Good to see you, yo.
-How you doing?
-[Jeanelle] I'm doing well.
-You all right? You all right?
-I'm doing well.
I'm lead caretaker
of all this stuff,
so if you need to know anything
about anything, I got you.
[Kevin]   You know,
seeing George Floyd
in that situation,
I saw myself.
I saw my son,
I saw my friends.
This a shock to the world,
this ain't no shock
to no people of color.
This has always been like
my sanctuary.
Two months,
this will be frozen solid,
where you can drive
a car on it.
You know, this is kind of
where I've collected
all of what I've accomplished
while being in Minnesota.
It makes me think
about the visions, the goals.
This is a special room for me.
I call it the hall of memories.
I thought this was a pretty
cool picture of me and Timmy.
This pretty much sums up,
you know,
him and I
[chuckling]
in the early days,
and the early antics.
The funny part about this is
I'm able to see people's faces,
and they're reacting
to the game,
which is stuff you don't see
during the game.
I'ma tell y'all something.
Put countless hours into this.
Basically have no life.
This is your life.
And everything's
totally circled around
you getting better
in basketball or you growing.
And that's all serious stuff.
When you're able to relax,
play amongst others,
joke, be yourself around others
being themselves,
that's what I miss
about basketball.
This is what I miss.
energetic saxophone music
[sportscaster]
For the first time since 1960,
the NBA Playoffs
have hit the Twin Cities.
This is the scene
outside the Target Center,
where Timberwolves fans
are all geared up
for game number three of the
Western Conference Playoffs.
Was our first time that we
actually went to the playoffs.
We was up against
a very veteran team,
and that being
the Houston Rockets.
dramatic hip-hop beat
The city, which is usually
a football town,
and now we have
this new basketball energy
just erupting in the city.
[sportscaster]   You're seeing,
for these T-wolves, no quit.
You never know what can happen
at the end of a game.
Probably not gonna
get this one done,
but it'll help them
in the future.
-[horn blasts]
-And that's your ball game.
The Houston Rockets sweep
the Minnesota Timberwolves
three games to none.
[Kevin]   Charles Barkley
pulled Steph and I at the end,
and I didn't even want
to hear that shit.
I was livid.
He grabbed by my arm,
and I jerked away.
He was like,
"Hey, come here, god damn it!
"Listen! Y'all gotta take this
ass-whooping and learn from it.
"This is what gonna
make you hungry.
"You gonna be back here
a million times!
What you gonna do
when you come back here?"
And he walked off.
And that--and that echoed
in my head the whole summer.
peaceful music
I remember being in Jamaica.
I went there
for the first time,
and I was just relaxing,
actually just chilling.
Got up, and remember
having a bowl of fruit.
And I had the fruit in my lap.
I whip up the "USA Today,"
and I open it up,
and in the sports section,
it had "Garnett
rejects $103 million."
Kind of took me a minute.
I was like, "Garnett what?"
And I sat up.
And the bowl of fruit
went on the paper.
I just remember,
like, "God damn."
And I was reading standing up.
I read half the article.
Pfft.
I was like,
"Oh, no, no, no, no."
I got out of Jamaica
and got back to Minneapolis.
Found myself in, like, a
shitstorm of just negotiating.
It was the first time that I
had to speak on my business
without knowing
the full of the business,
and it was super
uncomfortable.
But, you know, it was what I
needed to go to the next step.
Because what I didn't know is
that I would be the bullseye.
Well, the surreal world
of sports
got a little bit
more insane this week.
[newscaster]   Kevin Garnett has
become the highest-paid player
in the history
of professional sports.
[person]
When KG's six-year,
$126 million contract hit
at that time,
it was unprecedented.
This is a young
high school kid
that just got
over $120 million
to play basketball.
[Jelani]   Changed everything.
Changed the NBA, changed
what the deals look like.
It changed, you know,
the transparency
of how much money
the owners were really making.
At the end of day,
if they could pay one person
$126 million?
There's no max salary
back then.
The concept doesn't exist,
the phrase doesn't exist,
the rule doesn't exist,
so the Timberwolves
do what it takes.
They spent $126 million
over six years
in an extension
to keep Kevin Garnett.
The league flips out.
There are people here who are
enraged by the salary figure,
particularly because
he had turned down a deal
for 103 million.
Garnett's not a household name,
obviously, there.
-[commentator] Right.
-I mean, is he worth it?
There's no way this owner's
going to make any money
in the next five or six years.
[Scoop]
Kevin Garnett and his team,
in turning down $103 million,
made a very smart
business decision,
because they wound up
getting 126.
And isn't that
what America's all about?
Making
the smartest business deal?
The racist tone they set
with saying,
"Who the fuck are you,
nigga,
to turn down $103 million?"
That was the narrative
that consistently was put out
when Kevin turned
that money down.
[Howard]
The league in '98 decides,
"We've gotta get control
over this.
"We've got way too much money
going out to players,
"and sometimes,
in the case of a Kevin Garnett,
really young players."
So the leagues wants to create
what we now know
as the max contract.
Obviously, this is not going
to be very appealing
to the players
and the players' union,
so there's a shutdown.
It was a direct response
to Kevin Garnett's contract
that, "Okay, we're gonna
shut this thing down,
and we're gonna hold it
against the players."
The owners
are almost forcing you
to look at Kevin Garnett
and be like,
"You did this."
[scoffs]
As players, we like,
"Well, shoot,
"you have the ability
to pay this kid that much?
Well, what y'all making? What's
the value of this franchise?"
People don't never talk
about that, though.
These proposals,
combined with the totality
of our other proposals,
are simply unacceptable
to them.
You know, under no circumstance
are we gonna fall on the sword,
and under no circumstance are
we gonna give away the house.
The negotiations are tough.
David Stern,
as commissioner of the NBA,
Billy Hunter,
executive director
of the players' union,
these guys are both willing
to go the distance
to defend their particular
constituencies.
Now, you probably noticed
we don't have
NBA highlights tonight.
They're still busy
talking about,
let's see,
Larry Bird exemption,
salary caps, soft caps,
hard caps, baseball caps,
league-mandated bonus
protection for those players
not held under the free agency
exemption program
based on the previous year's
revenue,
but not covered under
the rookie salary cap
that was extended--
Thank you so much.
Sound like a lawyer.
-Or worse.
-[chuckles]
How's the weekend looking?
So the lockout lasts
about 6 1/2 months.
The league got what it wanted.
It got max salaries.
But there was an absolute cap.
There was gonna be a new era
for the NBA.
Why do you need me
to be so scared?
[speaker]   It was a new
franchise.
There were a lot
of new NBA fans.
It's game time.
[speaker]
And it was a youthful team.
But as I step in to the
Minnesota Timberwolves in 1999,
all of the best-laid plans
are starting to come undone.
[journalist]   Your contract
for the time being
didn't have a lot of room
for negotiation
'cause of the cap,
but looking at what's
happening on the market
right now, are you as blown
away as you rest of us are
with the kind of money
that's being paid?
Yeah, I am.
I mean, it's out there for us.
I think that the players
who get that amount of money
are the great players.
[speaker]   We do not have as
much money in this franchise
as a New York or an LA
or a Chicago.
It does mean we're going to
have to look at
the other players on the team
and how much
we have to pay them,
and so it's all this
tied together.
tense music
[Sean]   This is the next
Stockton and Malone.
But you could tell something
just wasn't right
and Steph wanted out.
And one late night,
he was gone.
[radio host]
I'm still trying to digest
a massive, massive trade.
Stephon Marbury is going
back home to New Jersey,
the New York area.
[radio host]   It's going
to be interesting to see
how Kevin Garnett is motivated
without his pal,
Stephon Marbury.
downbeat piano music
[Howard]   They'd become this
phenomenal young duo,
and they're on the rise,
but Garnett is up here
in salary
and Marbury's
gonna be just about here.
They were on the verge of
I think,
doing something special.
But the way the salary cap
was structured,
Steph not being able
to get that kind of money,
it threw a wrench in the plan.
But there's always gonna be
the what-ifs,
how fun those guys could have
been to watch for years.
[Isiah]   The industry is set up
to pit teammates
against each other
so we can write stories and
have another business entity
where we can all make money.
And unfortunately, it takes
advantage of the young
who are not equipped to deal
with the hegemonic forces
that's working them,
and they can't even see it.
[Kevin]   For a while, man,
I used to always wonder
what it would have been like
if Steph and I would've have
actually stayed together,
but that wasn't the plan.
[Sam]   So as tough
as it was losing Steph,
it was the best thing for us,
because it brought clarity.
There was no more conversation
about who team it was.
There no more conversation
about
who gets the ball
at the end of the game.
Without a doubt, 100%,
this was Kevin Garnett's team.
[Kevin]   I get the name
of the names: the Big Ticket.
That mean there ain't
nothing else playing tonight.
-You it.
-[cheers and applause]
[sportscaster]
Duncan and Kevin Garnett!
what a matchup we're gonna
have tonight at power forward.
It was a special time
for that position,
and I remember
the power forward matchups
were some of the best matchups
to watch.
[Howard]
The power forward position,
especially in the Western
Conference at that time,
was absolutely stacked.
You had Chris Webber coming
west to the Sacramento Kings.
You had Rasheed Wallace
coming west
to the Portland Trailblazers.
You had Tim Duncan
with the Spurs.
These guys were all studs.
[Paul]   You think about
the power forward of the '90s
and early 2000s,
you think about these big,
strong, physical cats.
You ain't thinking about
no wiry, 7-foot...
[chuckling]
skinny guy at the four.
[Matt]
Traditionally, power forwards
are back-to-the-basket-type
guys.
Down low, you and the five man
take turns eating.
But then KG comes along,
and he's someone
that could really start
handling the ball like a guard
and making decisions
like a guard,
and could put you
in a blender down below
with that Kevin McHale
footwork he learned,
and even stretching it
out further.
[sportscaster]
That'll work out fine.
[Paul]   When Kevin took the game
outside the paint,
it was like, "What's going on?
How we 'posed to defend this?"
Now this kid is coming
with some finesse.
He's pump-faking me now,
putting it on the ground.
Big men can't move they feet
with this guy.
[Metta]   KG changed
the power forward position
with the flair and the style.
You started to see personality
in the position.
See how KG move,
see how he bop,
you see his jab step?
That's all rhythm,
that's all flow.
[speaker]
Defensively, I don't know
if we really seen
someone like him,
a guy that could switch one
through five and guard anybody.
And when I say anybody,
anybody.
[Isiah]   "I can do it all.
I can bring it up the court.
"I can shake you,
I can dish you,
"I can dunk on you,
"I can get back,
I can block that shot.
"And guess what,
I can go to the line
at the end, make two free
throws, if you need that, too."
He does whatever it takes
to win a basketball game.
He just a motherfucker.
Can I say that?
[chuckles]
-[cheers and applause]
-[Kevin inaudible]
[Matt]   Was there someone
that you loved,
you knew that motherfucker
could back it up
and he was gonna
talk it to you?
Believe it or not, y'all,
Tim Duncan.
Shout out to Timmy.
[Matt] Mm, mm.
Tim Duncan, people would not
see him verbally saying stuff,
because he wouldn't talk
in sentences.
[laughter]
Timmy would hit you in phrases.
-"Got you." "Ooh." "Almost."
-[laughter]
This the worst right here.
-"Nice try."
-[laughter]
[sportscaster]
Rebound Garnett, to Brandon.
Great pass.
There's Malik for the necktie.
[Kevin]   Right before
the trade of Steph,
Malik got cut from Detroit,
and we picked him up.
I had watched Malik when
he was younger at St. John's
and he was kind of one
of my favorite players
to watch in the Big East.
When we got Malik,
we were all excited.
Never did I know that
the reason KG wore number 21
was because Malik Sealy
was his favorite player.
[sportscaster]
Here comes Sealy. A three.
-[horn blasting]
-[cheers and applause]
[sportscaster]   Oh! He got it!
Minnesota wins!
I mean, we've had
so many tough losses,
and we played so well
down towards the end,
it would have been a pity
to have not come away
with this win,
but we're happy with the win.
[Sam]   God put people in your
life for different times
and different reasons.
He taught KG
how to embrace who he was.
KG life blossomed
when Malik joined the team.
Malik knocked it down!
Enough said!
You ain't gotta ask me
no more questions,
'cause I ain't got
no more answers!
Hi, Mom!
[cheers and applause]
My birthday was a blur.
Go to dinner,
had a good time there,
we left.
And we were just outside
talking, like,
for, like, two, three hours.
And I just remember getting
home and just, you know,
the TV kind of
took me to sleep,
and I turned the TV off.
It seemed like I had just hit
the pillow or something,
my aunt--
my aunt kicked my door.
Doom.
She came in, she was like,
"Kev, get up.
Get yo' ass up."
And I was kind of
looking at her a while,
like,
"What are you talking about?"
She was like, "Man,
something happened to Malik."
[words echoing]
"Something happened to Malik."
Felt like a dream, 'cause
I could hear her echoing,
and I was, like,
going back to sleep,
and I was like, "What?"
Timberwolves guard,
NBA veteran Malik Sealy,
died as a result
of a head-on car collision
in suburban Minneapolis.
His sports utility vehicle
was hit by a pickup truck
which was going the wrong way
on a highway.
Blood tests show the driver
had a blood alcohol level
of 0.19,
nearly twice the legal limit.
Sealy was returning
from teammate Kevin Garnett's
birthday party
at the time of the crash.
pensive vocalizing
[Flip]   Someone who believed
that, you know,
the team is more important
than the individual.
And I think that he stood for
what we were this past year.
And um...
he'll be missed,
but never forgotten.
[softly]
Sorry.
- Brave
Brave
[cheers and applause]
[Kevin]   And all these things
start happening, man.
And I just--
I just pumped the brakes.
I didn't want to necessarily
make any more friends
on the team,
because it seemed like
everything was leaving me,
and so I became distant.
I wasn't the same.
I wasn't the same Kevin.
[Sam]   I don't know
if we ever really recovered.
It was always like there was
this hole in our heart
and in our soul.
That group, we just--
we couldn't close it.
[sportscaster]   Five seconds,
and that'll do it.
Congratulations
to Gregg Popovich
and the San Antonio Spurs.
They have dismissed
the Minnesota Timberwolves.
[sportscaster]
Garnett with the misfire,
and the Blazers have it
as Minnesota goes down
in the first round.
[sportscaster]   The
supporting cast is not there.
[sportscaster]
Nowitzki.
That should do it.
sportscaster]   That's it.
The Los Angeles Lakers
have captured their 13th
consecutive playoff series.
Kevin Garnett
is just heartbroken right now.
[grunting]
[Kevin screams]
[Kevin]   What drives me crazy
at the end of the year,
is that I'm here
working my butt off,
and it goes unappreciated,
you know what I mean?
[Kevin panting]
You know, I work hard,
so I expect the best results,
you know?
Good work, Kev.
Good work, baby.
Good fucking work.
I guess that's why
I go so crazy...
Good fucking work.
When we don't really go far
in the playoffs
or we have setbacks.
I'm working for you, 'Sota.
I'm working for you,
I'm working for you.
I'm working for you, 'Sota!
I'm working for you!
tense downbeat music
[Sean]   Kevin Garnett
had been granted the nickname
the Big Ticket.
By the time I got there,
it had had that secondary
meaning attached to it,
because the contract
had become a burden,
because the rules had changed
around it.
So suddenly,
the Big Ticket was now
preventing the Timberwolves
from adding pieces
around him.
And I realized,
even as a very young announcer,
this Big Ticket thing
is a problem.
[Kevin]   Getting put out
of the playoffs
seven straight times
was becoming...
[clicks tongue]
Like this dark cloud.
I wanted it so bad,
it just drove me crazy.
And I start
challenging management
to have better players.
[Sam C]
Michael Jordan was gonna buy
the Milwaukee Bucks.
The salary he wanted to cut
was my salary.
Ernie Grunfeld, who was the
general manager of the team,
called me and said, "Listen,
I'm gonna make a move.
Could you play in Minnesota?"
So I get to Minnesota.
Couple days later,
Flip called me and said,
"Sam, do you know Sprewell?"
I'm like, "I do know Sprewell."
I call Spree.
I say, "Spree, man,
I'm in Minnesota right now.
You should come."
Couple hours later, trade done.
So now you got me,
Spree, and KG.
[Kevin]   I met Sam and Spree
at a perfect time in my life.
If anybody knows Sam Cassell,
he's infectious.
In a good way,
he's gonna bully
his personality on top of you.
He used to do this little thing
that used to drive me crazy.
He used to always grab Spree
and go,
" My buddy
My buddy,
My buddy and me"
And Spree and him do that shit,
and everybody start laughing.
And he say, "Come on,
sing it, me and you."
And I'm like, "Man, I'm not
going with that shit, man."
And he used
to come over there,
"I want a hug, motherfucker!
My buddy! "
And the whole room be like,
"Ah, he got you!"
And I fucking hated it.
But he used to relax me.
He made me a better player
by making me uncomfortable,
do uncomfortable things.
I like to think that '03-'04
was the first time
I got off of
being so stern and so serious
and started to actually enjoy
a little bit
and let go a little bit.
[David] It's the first time
that the Timberwolves
had the best record
in the Western Conference.
The first time--
the first time
that the Timberwolves
had the Most Valuable Player
in the NBA.
[cheers and applause]
Congratulations,
2003-2004 NBA MVP,
-Kevin Garnett.
-[cheers and applause]
swelling orchestral music
[Kevin]
I felt like I won that award
for everybody in that state
and everybody in those jerseys
and all those fans
that was in those seats.
But I had
a bigger goal in mind,
and it was the NBA
Larry O'Brien Trophy.
upbeat hip-hop beat
[Sam C]
2004 Western Conference,
we were the number one seed.
That was a big deal
for the Minnesota
Timberwolves organization.
First time ever, you know,
they was number one seed.
For a expansion team,
that's--that's huge.
[Kevin]   Sam tell me before
we even start the series,
"We getting out
the first round."
[sportscaster]
Get out the cold beverages.
Minnesota's Timberwolves
are going to the second round
of the playoffs.
This year is totally
different from the past years
I've been here.
This is bigger than me.
This is--this is for the city.
Sam Cassell, every day
in my ear, at dinner,
and when we at lunch,
when we chilling,
whatever we're doing,
he's talking about winning
and this being the year,
and, "Fuck the past.
I don't give a shit.
Nigga, I'm here.
We here."
That's the first time
I really felt like,
"wow, I'm--I'ma have a chance
to go to the Finals.
Fabolous' "Breathe"
The performance he put on
in game seven
in the semifinals--
it's classic.
[sportscaster]
Hassell across the lane
-and out to Kevin Garnett.
-[cheers and applause]
[Sam C]   He did it all
like the point guard,
he was the two guard,
he was the rebounder.
[sportscaster]   Shot clock
is at eight for Garnett.
[sportscaster]   I can tell you
for Kevin Garnett,
that feels good.
[Kevin]   Webber and I are
going at it, just mano a mano.
People know my favorite player
was Chris Webber, so it was,
like, an honor to have it be
on the stage at this level.
-[sportscaster]   Kevin Garnett!
-[cheers and applause]
[sportscaster]
He just crossed over
and left Chris Webber
standing in his wake.
Kevin Garnett is taking over
this game!
He did it all from
the big man position.
[sportscaster]
Garnett way outside.
Oh, what a shot
by Kevin Garnett!
The game was moving
like this,
but I'm moving like this.
[sportscaster]
Webber for the tie.
[horn blasting]
And the Minnesota Timberwolves
are going to the
Western Conference Finals.
Jumped on the table.
"Yeah, we did this shit!
Yeah!
We finna win this bitch!"
God damn it!
And it hit me.
"Shit."
Came in there, and I collapsed.
We got in the locker room,
and he sat in the chair,
said, "Phew, I'm going to bed."
[chuckles]
suspenseful music
[sportscaster]   The opening tip
controlled by Karl Malone.
[Sam C]   We think we can
win the championship.
I'm healthy.
I'm feeling good.
Nothing was gonna stop us
from winning the championship
but a injury--
a injury.
[sportscaster]   Cassell headed
to the locker room
with Minnesota trainer
Gregg Farnam.
[Paul]   Once Sam went down,
I was like, "Man,
they don't got no chance."
You gotta understand,
Shaq and Kobe
was rolling then.
You needed all arms on deck
if you was gonna beat them.
[sportscaster]
Bryant with a beautiful move!
Shaq and Kobe kept a lot
of great players at that time
out of the Finals.
sparse downbeat music
[Kevin]
This picture right here,
I had over my bed
for a very long time.
I heard someone say if you
wanted dreams to come to life,
then you have to actually
see it,
be able to--
you know what I mean?
So I had this made,
and I put this over my--
over my bed.
Used to wake up
to this every day.
Wake up, wake up,
and believe it, wake up,
look at it,
believe it, wake up,
see it, believe it, wake up,
ingest it,
believe it, wake up, wake up.
Every day.
The Lakers series was
a very exhausting series.
And then the rumblings
from the management was like,
"Yeah, you know,
"that Spree and Sam Cassell
thing didn't work.
Sam's not durable enough."
It just turned
into some bullshit.
Real quick.
Are you taking the full
responsibility for this?
Are you feeling--?
Got no choice.
-But it is what it is, yo.
-[fidgeting]
Shit is killing me.
[Paul]   He let it all out, man.
You saw the frustration,
you heard the frustration,
that no matter how great
he was, it wasn't enough.
[Kevin]   Flip came in
to a practice
and said he was fired.
My wife was telling me,
like, you know,
"If they doing Flip like this,
like, you know, at some point,
"they probably gonna do
Kevin McHale like this,
and it's probably gonna--
you probably gonna be next."
We took a picture one time.
It's a black-and-white picture
of Glen Taylor,
Kevin McHale,
and Flip Saunders.
And in the picture,
I sat on this wooden box.
You know, Glen's the shortest
one out of all of us,
so he needs to sit up
so it all looks symmetrically.
But when I look back on it,
it did this.
I looked at it
and I was like,
"This is how they see you.
"This is why
all of the requests
"and all the things
that you're talking about
"or trying to get done--it
ain't being viewed the same,
because they view you
on this level."
Management gave the call down
from upstairs
that I didn't have
permission to play,
because they wanted draft picks
and all this other shit.
Cops told me
I couldn't motherfucking
put the jersey on.
And that's my last time in a--
in a--in a Timberwolves jersey.
[speaker]   Watching him play,
year in and year out,
being in the West, like,
banging his head
against the wall,
I, from afar, kept saying,
"Kevin needs to get
out of there."
Now, I never thought,
in my wildest dreams,
getting out of there would mean
coming to the Celtics
and me coaching him.
[Sam M]
If Kevin Garnett had his way,
he would have played
with the same group of guys
his entire career.
But I remember telling him,
"You don't want
to be one of those guys
"labeled as one of the
greatest players to never win.
"You gotta give yourself
a chance
to win a championship."
[Kevin]   I had Golden State,
Phoenix, I had Boston,
and I had the Lakers.
And then I talked
to Danny Ainge,
and Danny Ainge had a vision.
Paul Pierce and I
had played on AAU teams
when we were really young,
and the world
I don't even think knew that.
[cheers and applause]
[Paul]   Being a Boston Celtic,
expectations is championships.
[cheers and applause]
We was on our way.
My fourth year, we was
in the Conference Finals.
And then we started
taking steps back.
You know how long
a rebuild can take?
There's teams out here that
been rebuilding for 25 years.
I don't got time for that.
[chuckles]
Everything was really fragile
in Boston.
Was Doc Rivers was gonna
last another season?
Was Paul Piece going to last?
Was Danny Ainge?
All the people
that we now look at as
these legendary
Celtics figures
I think all had
a pretty tenuous hold
on their existence in Boston
at that time.
Can we curse on this?
[producer]
Go right ahead, Perk.
Oh.
We the worst fucking team
in the league.
We getting our ass kicked.
We lose 18 games in a row.
And we like,
"What the hell is next?"
[speaker]   It was a horrible
start to my career.
To come into that season
and lose 18 straight
was a big, big shock for me.
A lot of people came to the
game with bags on their heads,
yelling, "Fire Doc."
And the direction it seemed
like the team was going--
it wasn't in a hurry to kind
of win at that particular time.
Just a heartbreaking loss
for this club, Tom.
Well, get used to it.
I guess you would call it
rock bottom
if you were a Celtic fan.
That's where they had
just about hit
with the long losing streak
and everything else.
So Danny once again
became Trader Danny.
That's his reputation
around the league.
Anybody on the roster
is possible to be traded,
and that includes draft picks
and everything else.
We have a trade.
The Boston Celtics trade
Wally Szczerbiak
and Delonte West
to the Seattle Supersonics
for Ray Allen and the
draft rights to Glen Davis.
[Howard]
Now you've got a second star.
You're not a contender yet,
but you've really set
the groundwork
to try to get Kevin Garnett
out of Minnesota.
[Doc]   That moment,
Danny's target was KG.
The problem is we traded
all the players to Seattle,
so there was no deal.
Kevin McHale, myself,
and Danny Ainge went to golf.
I remember Kevin McHale
saying,
"I just want the best
young big man in the league."
And that's the moment I knew
we were gonna get him.
'Cause Al Jefferson
was absolutely
the best young big man
coming up,
so we gave them Al
and the team.
[Rajon]   It was, like,
a seven-player deal for Kevin.
And that's when I think
I realized, like,
the impact of who he was,
'cause it was-it was my entire
team going for one person.
[emcee] The newest member
of the Boston Celtics,
-Kevin Garnett.
-[cheers and applause]
[Howard]   The second
that the Celtics unite
those three guys,
create this superteam,
this was one of those tremor
kind of moments for the NBA.
Shaq and Kobe were
a great team,
but there wasn't a third star.
You had Duncan and Robinson,
but you didn't have three guys
all still in their prime,
all Hall of Fame-caliber,
united on one team.
We hadn't seen anything
like that in a long time.
Initially, I had no interest
in leaving Minnesota.
I thought this was my--
probably my best opportunity
at winning a ring,
so I took the big steps
to make those adjustments,
and here we are.
[Howard]
Kevin Garnett and Boston
were star-crossed lovers.
You know these stories
about couples
that find each other--they
had worked in the same place,
they had lived
in the same building,
maybe bumped into each other
in the laundry room,
but it never really clicked
for whatever reason?
And then,
when Boston and Kevin Garnett
finally got together,
they both looked
at each other, like,
"Where have you been
my whole life?"
[Danny]   KG transformed us.
I mean, Paul and Ray obviously
are Hall of Fame players
and unbelievable,
but KG was that missing piece
and that energy that just gave
everybody in the franchise,
everybody in the city,
this hope that they hadn't had
for a long time.
[Kevin]   When you come into
the Celtics practice facility,
it's banners everywhere.
It's history
right in front of you.
This is the fraternity
that you're a part of now.
[sportscaster]
Bill Russell goes in.
He dunks it!
That did it!
95-85!
The first Celtic he met
was Bill Russell,
who gave him the jersey
and said, "Welcome to Boston."
I always said you
my favorite player to watch.
-Always? I don't know, you...
-You never disappoint.
Crack so many jokes, I don't
know if that's real or not.
-Oh, it's real.
-I'm joking. Joking.
-And you never disappointed me.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Hey, [murmurs].
And you finally got on
the right uniform.
-I finally got the right--
-[laughter]
It was like talking
to my grandfather, man.
It was like getting jewels
from, like,
the jeweler himself.
Was talking about battles
with Wilt,
and the Black movement,
you know, and civil rights.
Man, Bill Russell
was another level.
And I felt like I needed
that part to really cement
being in Boston
and what it meant to be there.
I needed that piece.
Doc gave us a great team
symbolism word
to unify us, which was   ubuntu.
It meant to give your own
to the next guy, next to you,
so that he
or she could be better,
and that it comes back to you,
to and fro.
[imitating Doc Rivers]
"Kevin, I got 15 minutes
"for this shoot.
I gotta get in here.
You know--you know,
my tee time is"--
I already know.
You got a tee time
you going to?
-Oh, shit, what up, Doc?
-I got a tee time every day.
-How you doing, bro?
-[Doc] What's up, my brother?
-[Kevin] Good to see you, man.
-[Doc] How you doing?
-[Kevin] I'm good.
-[Doc] Oh, good.
My man looks good.
Can you play still?
-[Kevin] Who?
-You.
-[Kevin] 'Bout ten minutes.
-You can't play ten minutes.
[Kevin] Solid. Not this shit.
You know, every time I've ever
been in Doc's presence,
I've always picked his brain,
I've always been inquisitive.
He knows I'm almost, like,
the eighth kid,
or the--how many kids you got?
Nine? Ten?
Stop it, man.
Stop it.
I'm like the bastard kid
over here,
-you know what I'm saying?
-He's the fifth kid.
He is.
But he's more than a kid.
[laughs]
Man, it's just amazing.
When you win it with a team,
it's like you've had
a blood transfusion.
For the rest of your life,
you're connected.
You can never take
our bond away. You just can't.
Celtic Pride and   ubuntu
are very parallel.
Celtic Pride, believing
in something, giving your all.
And when he said that,
it couldn't have been
more powerful in the room,
'cause we had a room full
of young beasts and young egos
and everybody
feeling they self,
but we all came together.
And then everybody had to learn
they own definition of it.
Ubuntu   is in your heart.
He pulled it out of us.
[Doc]   I had the rookies
introduce it.
They were amazing.
I was shocked.
Big Baby in particular.
He had tears.
I mean, he was talking
in passionate ways.
And right when he finishes,
Kevin yells...
-[Kevin] One, two, three!
-[all]   Ubuntu!
[Doc] Y'all go to dinner!
I'll pay for all y'all.
Yeah!
[speaker]   I was kind of
that guinea pig.
I did everything.
And I would present
that word   ubuntu   to the team.
We used that
everywhere where went.
Even if we were out there
clubbing, we would   ubuntu.
Popping bottles,   ubuntu.
[laughing]
You know what I'm saying?
Like, that's how it was.
-[sneakers squeaking]
-[whistle blows]
Fuck-ass nigga!
Fuck, nigga!
[Doc] I don't want to hear it.
I am not listening to it.
Now, I know--
That's fire, man.
No, it's a difference.
-That's fire.
-It's a difference.
-I was composed.
-No.
[Sam M]
I'm coaching in Toronto.
Doc Rivers calls me.
"Hey, man, I need you
to talk to KG for a minute."
And he goes into how
relentless KG is in practice,
and that he feels like KG
is trying to prove to them.
And I stopped him in his track.
I said, "Wait a minute, Doc.
"If you're thinking
this is fake, uh-uh.
It's real." And I said,
"Let me tell you what else.
"Don't try to get him
to tone it down,
"because before it's over,
"every player in that locker
room is gonna be just like him.
"And when every player in that
locker rooms starts acting
"like he acts in practice,
you're gonna win
a championship."
-[Kevin] Celtics!
-[all] Hoo-rah!
-[Kevin] One, two, three!
-[all]   Ubuntu!
-[announcer]   KG!
-[cheers and applause]
KG turned the TD Garden
into the Coliseum,
-and he was Maximus.
-[cheers and applause]
[Doc]   I've never seen a team,
maybe in NBA history,
play as hard as that team
played for an entire year.
People call me Jesus.
That's the Ticket.
-And this The Truth.
-The Truth.
It's like the Justice League.
We all sat here,
we all had a superpower,
and I chose to play defense
on a nightly basis.
This is what
I'ma hang my hat on.
It was an incredible level
of intense,
solid team basketball.
[sportscaster]
Pass deflected by Eddie House.
Picked off by Pierce.
Ray Allen for the game!
Got it!
At the buzzer!
[Kevin]   We viewed ourselves
as road warriors.
We'll beat your fucking team's
ass, and we out of here.
Wherever we went,
we was rockstars.
[sportscaster]   Boston Celtics
have swept the Texas triangle!
[Kevin]
When you win a championship,
you have a little bit
of luck and timing.
[indistinct chatter]
When PJ Brown
and Sam Cassell joined us,
I felt like
we were super complete.
[sportscaster]   The
Boston Celtics reminding you
this is the best team
in the NBA in '07-'08.
[producer]   Brian Scalabrine.
[Brian]   I get a phone call,
and it's KG.
He's like, "Yo, Red!
-Get yo' ass in shape!"
-[hand slaps]
And he hangs the phone up
[laughing]
and that's all he said.
That is my first interaction
with my teammate Kevin Garnett.
Slow down these
pick and rolls.
They don't want to play no
pick and roll game.
Be aggressive!
[Brian]   This team was--we were
a little psycho, right?
And we were into competition,
we were into boxing,
we'd shoot dice,
we played cards.
Like, we were nuts.
For whatever reason,
arm wrestling comes up.
And we've all established
who the champ is.
No one's beating Big Baby.
He's big, he's strong,
he's a little bit nuts.
Leon and Big Baby
got to shit-talking.
They was like, "Whatever.
What's--what's--what's up?"
Big Baby Davis and Leon Powe
are arm wrestling on the plane.
I had already
beaten Leon Powe.
Have you ever seen Leon arms?
Them look like two hippos
going at it.
When they smack hands,
and Baby was slobbering,
and talking crazy, just trying
to really intimidate.
And he slammed him--boom!
Slammed his hands.
We was like,
"Damn! Like, what the fuck?"
Everybody gassing.
First, it's Paul.
And Paul was like, "Shit!
Bet you can't beat Ticket!"
Like, "Man, get the fuck out.
I ain't arm wrestling.
Nigga, we got a game,
you know what I'm saying?"
You know, I'm a strong guy,
so I know I beat Leon,
I can beat Ticket.
I was like, "Man,
sit your little fat ass down.
"Ain't nobody trying to arm
wrestle your little ass, nigga.
"You ain't even
that strong, nigga.
"I actually saw you
grabbing the table.
"You ain't really
the strongest nigga in here.
You know, relax."
All of a sudden,
Paul Pierce comes up.
He's like,
"I got $2,000 on Garnett."
And right away,
everyone was like, "Bet!"
And niggas like,
"I'm going with Baby!"
And I heard T,
"I'm with Baby! I'm with Baby!
Oh, I'm with Baby!"
I kind of looked at everybody,
like,
"Damn, this how y'all feel?
Mm."
[clicks tongue]
Threw my hand up.
"Yeah."
And they say, "Oh, shit!"
We hit. Boom!
Okay, cool, I'ma show him.
They're going back and forth.
They are just muscles,
sweating, bulging.
[both shouting]
And he just--I'm letting him
gas his self out.
Big Baby starts sweating.
And he gets, like,
all these fucked up faces.
Like--and he's like
uhhhh--
Uhhhhhh!
All of a sudden, KG does,
like--he does that.
When his hand start moving,
I go, "Oh, shit."
[chuckling]
He just going too hard, bro.
I didn't want nobody
to get hurt.
The minute I get wind
that he gassed out,
I feel his--
I feel his hand start moving.
And when he saw it move,
you could see all,
like, the goosebumps get on.
Kevin goes down a little,
comes back.
He kept going.
"You ain't gonna beat me.
Oh, fuck no! Fuck!
You ain't gonna beat me!"
Boom!
"Fuck wrong with you, nigga?"
Takes off his shirt.
Drenched! Drenched sweat!
And then starts hitting
himself.
"I'm the fucking silverback
on this team."
"I'm the silverback
on this motherfucker!
You understand, nigga?"
Bread everywhere.
Money go in the air.
Everyone's like, "Aww, man,
I can't believe he did that."
Big Baby's devastated
on the table.
I'm smart.
We're not gonna hurt Ticket.
[laughs]
Paul grabbed me from the back
and start choking.
I get up. I pick P up.
"Fuck wrong with them, P?"
So me and P like this.
"What's wrong with them, P?"
And that told me right then
and there who this dude was.
'Cause he didn't give a damn.
And it made him
the leader of this team.
KG always said this.
"I can't get into a fight,
because if I lose,
they're gonna have to kill me."
And I--I actually really
believed him on that one.
Like, I really believe
that when he plays basketball,
it is win or die.
[sportscaster]   The
Boston Celtics have completed
the biggest single-season
turnaround in NBA history--
24 wins a year ago,
66 this year.
Now Kevin Garnett and company
are looking forward
to the playoffs.
And just touch the top.
Little clapper.
soft dramatic music
How about that, huh?
So you kept thinking,
as the season went on,
"Well, maybe. Maybe they really
are gonna win the whole thing?
Can they win the whole thing?"
You know, 'cause you just--
it had been so long.
[sportscaster]
Three on two. Smith!
[cheers and applause]
[Jackie]   So they play Atlanta
in the first round,
and you think,
"Well, this is gonna be fine."
But it wasn't.
And you started to wonder,
"Oh my gosh, are they gonna
lose in the first round?"
Of course, they didn't.
They got through it.
[Glen]   We went seven games
with Atlanta.
It was really, really tough.
And then the next series,
you got LeBron James.
Game seven again.
How did we get here, dog?
[sportscaster]
Rondo, lead for Pierce.
Sets around Delonte West.
Right-hand dribble, LeBron.
Again strong in the middle.
Puts it up with the left hand
and scores.
It became an epic battle
between Pierce
and LeBron James.
[Doc]   He almost singlehandedly
beat us that night.
That was one of
the great game sevens.
[sportscaster]
The Celtics are going back
to the Eastern Conference
Finals
for the first time since 2002.
On Tuesday, we're exactly
where we thought
we would be--game one,
at home, against Detroit.
[cheers and applause]
[sportscaster]
Pierce ahead of the pack.
Back to Garnett for the slam!
We was like, "Oh, no,
we not letting this go seven."
[chuckles]
[Kevin]
We came to Detroit,
and if anybody knows anything
about Detroit,
they got these little,
like, closet locker rooms.
And I think they had
two locker rooms in there.
I think we could have had
the bigger locker room,
and they put us
in a real small one.
And Doc was like,
"You know what, man?
"We should beat
these niggas here
just 'cause they gave us
this little-ass--"
[chuckling] He was just
picking from everywhere.
[sportscaster]   The Celtics
going back to the NBA Finals
for the first time since 1987.
And now,
it's on to face the Lakers.
[Doc]   I do remember walking in
the locker room
with the silver ball and said,
"Wrong color."
"This is not
what we're playing for.
"We're playing
for the gold ball,
not the silver ball."
Doc said,
"No one touch the trophy.
That ain't what we here for."
[all] Beat LA! Beat LA!
[Kevin]   Then P started,
"Beat LA! Beat LA!"
Ooh-whoo!
That's when
the real smoke started.
That's when you ain't sleeping
for real, for real.
orchestral music fades
pensive dramatic music
It's like that bully that
you go to school every day,
and you know when you get
out your mom's or dad car,
you know you gotta see him
soon as you walk through
the front doors.
And he'll be sitting there
with his feet up
waiting on you to pat your
pockets and mess with you.
And then it's like one day
you say to yourself,
"You know what?
This is gonna stop today."
[cheers and applause]
[Howard]   The idea that we were
going to get Celtics-Lakers
ever again,
that this rivalry
could be reborn,
you don't have to be
a Celtics or Lakers fan
to even appreciate this.
That rivalry was part of
basketball immortality, right?
You think about
the great players
that played for each team.
[Mike]   In the '80s, I think of
Larry Bird and Magic Johnson.
You go way back, and you think
of Bill Russell, Elgin Baylor.
And now, all of a sudden,
there was this new group.
It was Kevin Garnett
and Ray Allen and Paul Pierce,
and you got the matchup
with Kobe Bryant.
[Paul]
The Celtics versus the Lakers?
Are you kidding me?
This is the rivalry that
got me watching basketball,
that got me loving basketball
growing up in Inglewood
down the street from the Forum,
watching Larry Bird,
Magic in the Finals
all through the '80s.
This is why I fell in love
with the game.
-Now, I'm a part of it!
-[cheers and applause]
[Doc]   Game one,
the atmosphere was insane.
And the level of intensity
is what stood out.
[sportscaster]
Garnett has to go back.
Able to save it to Brown,
so it wasn't
a backcourt violation.
Cassell a jumper.
Pops it in!
Big play by Kevin Garnett!
Posey for three!
Back of the rim--
Garnett on the slam!
And Boston goes up two-nothing
in the NBA Finals.
[Kevin]   Everybody know why
we're going to LA, right?
-This ain't no vacation.
-[person]   Hell, nah.
[Kevin]   We're going out here
to get us a win.
Keep that in mind now.
Straight up.
-[person] You're home.
-All right.
Back at the house, baby, LA.
Know we gotta get this win.
Let's do it.
[cheers and applause]
[sportscaster]
Celtics really struggling.
One of nine from the field
and three turnovers.
[sportscaster]   Well,
it's a nightmare for Boston,
but a spectacular start
for the Lakers
as they finish
with the largest lead ever
after one quarter
in an NBA Finals game.
[Sam C]   Game four
was a strange game early.
We couldn't make a shot.
We couldn't throw a rock
in the ocean.
And the Lakers was throwing
every rock they found
in the ocean.
Come on, guys!
Keep fighting!
Keep fighting! Keep fighting!
[Doc]   The message was,
"Hey, let's get it to 18."
Got it to 18.
"Let's get it to 14."
Got it to 14.
[Kevin]   Defensively,
we were all trying
to just wear the Lakers down
at some point,
but then, at the same time,
still score.
All right, we're right there!
We're right there!
Doc was like,
"Hey, if you believe,
"get your ass in this huddle.
"If you don't,
go on to the locker room.
'Cause we ain't gonna come out
of this unless you believe."
Do you believe?
All right, let's go.
[Tom] Keep fighting!
[Celtic] One. Two. Three.
[all]   Ubuntu!
We knew what we had
to rely on--   ubuntu.
Like, we need each other.
I'll never forget, Sam always
in my ear in the huddle.
"Cut it to 15. Get it to 10."
"We gonna cut this
motherfucker,
point by point, bit by bit."
And you could see us
kind of like, "Ugh, man.
No, we ain't gonna let this go.
Come on."
Here come P. "Here we come!
Here we come! Here we come!"
Next thing, we looked up,
that shit was tied.
[sportscaster]
And the Celtics have
their first lead of the game.
[Doc]   Our belief system
was challenged,
and we never wavered.
[sportscaster]
And it's official.
The Celtics have come back
from a 24-point deficit.
[sportscaster]   And they go up
three games to one
and have a chance
to wrap it up in Los Angeles.
That's when you hear
the classic Paul Pierce
come up like,
"One more! One more!"
One more! Let's go!
That 24-point comeback
was historic,
and exciting a game
as I've been involved in.
[Kevin]   We thought we was
gonna beat they ass in LA,
then we shit the bed
game five.
[sportscaster]   Bounce
to the left high post to Pau.
Left corner to Kobe.
A three.
He buries it off-balance!
[sportscaster]
And Kobe looks like
he's on a mission tonight.
[sportscaster]
Bryant--hits a three, again!
Another hot start
just like they did
in game four.
Kobe and Kevin were
very similar creatures.
Just kill.
[laughs]
And that's just both of them.
They're both killers.
[Jackie]
There was a lot of drama here.
Kobe Bryant wanted
so desperately
to separate himself
from Shaquille O'Neal
and to prove that he could win
without Shaquille O'Neal.
And that was driving him very,
very strongly.
[Kevin]   '08, Kob wanted
that more than anything.
Told him,
"You ain't got enough!
"You out here by yourself!
Better go get Diesel.
You know you can't win it
without Diesel."
You could tell
that Kobe had the Lakers:
"Hey, we ain't trying
to befriend any of these guys."
Kevin had us:
"We're not trying to be close
to any of those guys."
There was hatred
in that series, in a good way.
[sportscaster]
And that will do it.
The series is going back to
Boston, as the Lakers survive.
suspenseful music
We get up in the morning
to fly.
The Lakers took off before us.
We got to
the airport before them.
They plane, like, right there.
We could see out the window.
We delayed like two
or three hours.
We think something up.
I'm like, "What's going on?"
The pilot comes on and says,
"We have something wrong
with the plane,
and we can't take off."
They bring another plane.
We get on this plane.
This plane is broke.
So the Lakers' two planes
took off great.
We're in LA, and now, our two
planes aren't working.
And I was going at it.
Fortunately,
the owner of the team
had a plane
for the family and friends.
I had to go on the family plane
and kick off the wives
and some of all the owners,
and we were gonna commandeer
that plane,
and they were gonna
find another plane.
[Sam C]   Get to Boston
like 10:00 at night.
We got a game the next night.
The next night!
I never bought into
any conspiracies
about the plane not taking off,
but with Phil Jackson,
you just--
you just never know, right?
Like, I'd watch
a documentary about that.
[Kevin]
I didn't sleep that night,
so I went to the gym.
I worked out.
I had a kid, a newborn kid,
and all that.
It was just haunting me.
I went and got a whole workout.
Got about 1,000 shots up.
500 makes.
Went to the crib
and just stayed off my feet,
hyperbaric chamber,
and just thought about
what I'ma do game six.
Before the game, I walked in,
and I was a little concerned
that we thought
we may not be ready
because of all that.
And I actually said, "This
is our last game this year,
and we're not gonna just win,
we're gonna win big."
I just remember, game six,
Doc saying...
[imitating Doc] "Uh, guys,
"I don't have a lot
to say tonight,
"uh, but I just want to say...
[normally] "You don't beat
this team by 25, 30,
you shouldn't
want to show up tonight."
Let's go get it.
It's right there!
I just remember being
in the locker room,
just--and I'm just, like,
hearing the crowd.
"Beat LA."
Oh, man, it gave me chills.
It was like,
"This the moment right here."
Been the best team
all year long. All year long!
Let's go out there
and show them why.
-Let's go!
-[person] Let's go.
-Showtime!
-[all] Hoo-rah!
-One, two, three!
-[all]   Ubuntu!
Right before jump ball,
I just dapped Pau.
"Hey, man,
this ain't personal."
[sportscaster]
Garnett against Gasol.
The high release.
Attack! Attack!
[sportscaster]
Pierce to the basket.
Out to Garnett.
Good open look
for Kevin Garnett.
Embarrassing the Lakers.
Garnett inside.
Banks it in!
And a foul!
What a play
from Kevin Garnett!
We went out
and played unbelievable.
Relax, baby.
[Sam C]   At halftime--
Tom Thibodeau was
our defense guy.
He's ready to go over
some defensive things,
and Doc just stopped him,
and say,
"Uh-huh. Keep doing
what the fuck y'all doing!"
The third quarter,
we was doing it.
upbeat funky music
[sportscaster]
Ray Allen for three.
Pierce, left-handed.
Pretty play from Pierce.
Pau Gasol.
And a jump ball.
Kevin Garnett, the Defensive
Player of the Year.
All year long, we searched
for the perfect game to play,
on both ends.
In search of the perfect game,
we finally played it,
and it came
at the right moment.
[sportscaster]
It's just a matter
of the clock winding down.
[Doc]   I had a whole quarter
to sit back
and look at the crowd
and take it in.
That was the first time
that whole year I was able
to take something in.
I hugged Paul.
Next thing you know,
they grab me.
And I think it was
their way of telling me
they know I've been through
a lot, too, in my career,
as a player and a coach.
They wanted me to know
that I was a champion,
and I wanted them to know
that they were a champion.
It was like we were giving
it back to each other.
When I came out the game,
he grabbed me, he said,
[imitating Doc]
"Didn't I tell you?
"Didn't I tell you we was gonna
win this motherfucker?
Didn't I tell you?"
I was like--[laughs]
That's when Paul grabbed
the Gatorade bucket.
It was like two minutes to go
in the game when he did that.
[Paul]
"Man, give me the Gatorade.
"'m about to pour it on Doc."
This ain't never been done
in the NBA.
They do it in football. Look.
[imitating splashing]
Aw, man, Doc loved it.
[laughs]
[sportscaster]
And after a 22-year absence,
the Boston Celtics are
NBA champions once again.
Hell yeah! Hell yeah!
Banner number 17 soon
to be raised to the rafters.
dramatic orchestral music
[Sean]   There was no better way
for the Celtics,
who were a wire-to-wire team
that year.
The biggest one-year
turnaround in NBA history.
This was the only way
they could win,
not just by beating a team,
but by beating a team up.
Oh, my God!
I got you. I got you.
"Just won a NBA championship.
Boy, anything is possible."
Anything's possible.
I just yelled that shit.
"Anything's possible!"
Anything's possible!
And it came from the heart.
[Wolf]   The NBA championship
is going down.
And I'm at home
the day before.
I've seen game one, game two.
Every game he's played,
I'm watching,
I'm watching, I'm watching.
Then to get that phone call day
before the game and say,
"Coach,
I need you at the game."
I said, "Damn.
You need me at the game.
So I guess you know where
I'm gonna be then, right?"
And to have him go out there
and perform the way he did,
I felt so good.
And he said, "I got my ring.
I finally did it."
And I'm like,
"That's the championship
that we didn't get
the chance to get."
[exuberant clamoring]
Me and KG stayed
in the locker room
till like 3:00 or 4:00
in the morning.
All the champagne is gone,
so now we drinking brews.
[laughs]
And we just like, "Man,
can't believe this, right?
Feel like a dream."
Made it, Ma!
Top of the world!
[Paul]   I mean, the last time
we teamed up,
we won the tournament
in Vegas,
we won in the Mickey D's game.
I mean, we were undefeated
as teammates.
Like, what if we had have
teamed up sooner?
What if we had have teamed up
from the beginning?
[exhales deeply]
Man, y'all know how it go, boy.
Whew.
Thank you all
for being patient.
Man.
Phew.
Man, man, man.
[exhales deeply]
[journalist] Scoop,
in the back, under the camera.
-[Scoop]
Scoop Jackson, espn.com.
Scoop, I'm here, son.
[Scoop]
That's what I was about to say.
-Made it, dog!
-[Scoop] That's I'm saying.
-Y'all, they don't know--
-I'm here!
[Scoop]
That's--they don't know.
We go back.
So I just want to know,
how does it finally feel
to finally let this out?
'Cause you been holding this in
for a long time.
And I don't know if anybody
in the room
knows how long
you been holding it in.
At the time, I was with ESPN.
And as KG was
answering questions, I'm like,
"Not one media member
"in this room covered him
"when he was in high school.
"Nobody here, you know,
knows what this feels like
for him."
You know, him sitting up here
with this NBA trophy
was so much more than him
just winning the championship.
Explain to them
what it feels like
to finally let this
out of your soul.
[sighs]
You ever go to school,
and you have that bully mess
with you every day?
And you sort of kind of shook,
'cause, you know what,
you just knocked the bully out,
and you don't know
he gonna come back.
So the next morning,
when you come in,
and he not there,
it's like a sigh of relief.
Every year,
it can only be one winner.
Only one winner.
Each year, you hit the bottom
and come back up
to climb this mountain,
in takes a little air
out of you.
Like, "God damn."
[sighs]
So the bully was all those
years of busting my ass,
and getting my ass kicked,
and getting in shape,
and just, just grinding,
grinding, grinding,
playoff series
after playoff series
after playoff series,
these guys, these guys, this--
all this shit--all of it!
Ah!
And it will make you question
what you're doing...
Oh, shit.
Why you going this hard.
[exhales deeply]
But as much as it kicks
your ass,
it also re-instills
that energy in you.
And then you start over,
on the bottom,
and you have to
climb this hill.
You know, it's like
getting rid of the bully.
-I knocked the bully ass out.
-[laughter]
I knocked his ass clean out.
That's what it feels like.
I got my own.
I got my own, man.
Thought about everybody who's
been with me on this journey.
Top of the world.
Made it, Ma.
music fades
[campfire crackling]
When I was younger,
I used to love to build fires.
We used to have a big-ass fire,
like, stove,
and I used to have to build
these things and all that.
Country boy.
As you evolve in, like,
your profession,
and you being a master
of your craft,
you get to a point where
physically,
your body starts to tell you
that we can't go
at this certain velocity,
or you can't go
at this certain--
this certain speed,
or this certain rage.
You can't--you know?
And that was hard for me,
'cause all I know is all-out.
Because I've always felt like
I can go to another level.
I used to say that shit.
"Take it to another level,
Kev.
"This nigga can't hold you
out here.
Take it to another level, Kev.
You the best in the building."
This my first time
going through
any of this
Hall of Fame stuff.
And they asked me, you know,
if I could choose someone
to present me
or bring me out or whatever,
and it's only right
that I ask someone
who I felt like helped me
get to a point
to where I could make
a strong decision on my future
when I was so young.
And if you would consider,
you know,
possibly introducing me
and bringing me out?
I would be honored to stand
on the stage next to you
and let the basketball world
and the community
just see Kevin Garnett.
That's what's up.
Zeke, I appreciate that, man.
And I look forward
to seeing you and hugging you.
And when I hug you,
if I start crying, just--
just don't think I'm soft.
[laughs]
No. Hey, look,
you far from that.
We all know you far
from that, man.
[switch clicks and echoes]
[Kevin]
You know, a lot of times,
I think about what
if I didn't go play?
What if I went down to
Roosevelt's Boys & Girls Club
and just got some shots up
and just wanted to think?
You know, what if
I never went to the gym
and Jordan let me come in
and hoop?
What I never seen Zeke?
What if none of that happened?
dramatic music
It would have been
what it would have been.
But at that moment
that I went in there,
and those things did happen,
like anything,
opportunity comes
when you least expect it.
It's what you gonna do with
that opportunity, you know?
And do you have the guts and
do you have the work ethic?
You got the strength
to be able to go through
what you talking about?
It's all possible.
[emcee]   Anything Is Possible:
Kevin Garnett.
[applause]
I told them
I wanted to go first, man,
'cause I know we got
the OGs in here.
I know y'all got a bed time
in a minute, so.
[laughter]
To the city of Chicago, I want
to thank you for adopting me
and bringing me in
as one of your own.
To the city of Minneapolis,
I look forward
to rebuilding you.
-To the Boston Celtics...
-[cheers and applause]
Danny Ainge, your vision,
Doc Rivers, your leadership,
helping me be not
only a better player,
but a better person.
I played the game just hard.
Played the game
with a passion.
Um, I wanted to say, Timmy,
thank you, man.
Congratulations to you and Kob.
Congratulations, Vanessa.
I love y'all. That's my time.
Thank you guys. I love y'all.
[cheers and applause]
upbeat music
I'm immortal.
Hall of Fame.
Y'all, holla at me.
So KG, man, I'm so happy
that you here, dog.
-Big Ticket!
-Right.
The motherfucking thang.
I don't know what color jacket
they give y'all
for making it to
the Basketball Hall of Fame,
but my nigga, you damn sure
going up in there.
-You deserve to be up in there.
-Appreciate it.
And just 'cause you going up
in there,
I made space for you
to get your plaque on the wall.
[Kevin] And let me say
something to you.
[Snoop] I'm putting the
KG plaque on the wall, cuz.
I'm sorry.
Hey, listen, I'ma say this.
Ain't nobody coming down.
I'm just making space for you.
[Kevin] I was about to say,
you cannot take
nobody down here.
No, no. No. Nah, nigga,
ain't nobody coming down.
I'm just gonna make space
for you.
Look, I appreciate that.
[Snoop] I'm putting you up
there 'cause you my guy.
And a little birdie told me
that the Celtics
gonna retire number five?
[Kevin] Yeah, yeah.
They gonna put the five up.
-Cinco?
-[Kevin] Right.
In the rafters?
[Kevin] In the rafters with P.
And Bird.
-With Russell.
-[Kevin] And Russell.
Bird, McHale.
-[Kevin] Facts. Facts.
-Cousy.
"Havlicek stole the ball."
-Facts. Facts.
-Quit playing, man.
They gonna put the knick knack
paddy whack up there?
-They gonna put it up there.
-Come on, KG.
What about--
now, look here, man.
If they gonna do that,
Minnesota got to put
that 21 up, man.
-They play too much.
-Yeah. Minnesota different.
Quit playing, Minnesota.
21 reasons, man.
Minnesota--Minnesota different.
They different.
Hey, I love when you got
to the mountaintop.
And I say this all the time,
because,
when real ones get there,
you don't give a fuck
what team they play for,
'cause we all play
for the same team.
Right.
And when I seen you get
to the mountaintop,
and you finally said,
"Anything's possible..."
Facts. I felt that.
-I knew your struggle.
-Facts.
'Cause I ain't just gonna
hook up with anybody.
It's got be a killa.
I tried to come out here.
Kob wouldn't pick the phone up.
Couldn't get Kob on the phone.
-Come on, man. [laughs]
-I shot this.
There's a picture--it's a
famous picture of Kob and I
on the free throw line,
chopping.
We in the Finals.
I finally get to the Finals.
I'm in Boston.
And he go, "Man,
what number you call, man?
You sure you called?" I said,
"Man, get the fuck out here.
"I don't want to hear
that shit.
-[Snoop laughing]
-"Get your ass out of here."
"Two months, dog? How long
you gonna be in China?"
[Snoop] You know, we miss him.
We sad.
But just when we bring
his name up, it's fun times.
I'm listening to you talk about
when you first seen him,
and how y'all battle, like,
and it's just--
it's those memories
of what he brought to us.
He brought that joy,
either the competitiveness
or either just the drive
to want to be just as good,
if not better than.
-Right. 'Cause he did music.
-Yeah.
Kob thought he could do it all.
And then he got to rhyming.
We was in an All-Star Game
one time, he got to rhyming
in fucking Italian.
[Snoop laughing]
And them niggas
was laughing at him.
He's like,
"See, them niggas laughing?
He don't know I just dissed
everybody in the joint."
Like, "What the fuck?"
upbeat hip-hop beat
D.O.C. is probably one of my
favorite artists of all time.
That's crazy you said that,
'cause D.O.C. is my sensei.
When I got on Death Row,
I was dope freestyling,
and I was dope
just writing dope-ass verses.
I ain't know
how to make a song.
This nigga
showed me how to make a song.
He showed me how to take
this long-ass rap,
break it down to 16 bars,
take this piece right here,
make it the hook,
and to put a little bit
of flow in your shit,
and not just rap like this,
but some of that shit--
It's the capital S,
oh yes, and fresh
N, double-O, P
Shit like that.
And you know what saying?
Follow me, follow me,
follow me, follow me
Shit like that where
it's, like, challenging me.
Like, "Nigga, I'm your teacher.
I'm finna show you some karate
that these niggas don't got."
And the blessing about me
and his relationship was
he lost his voice,
so I became his spirit.
-[Kevin] Oh, wow.
-You get what I'm saying?
[Kevin] Yeah, right, right.
[imitating D.O.C.]
Nah, Doggy Dogg,
take that part right there
and put it right there."
[Kevin] Right, right, right,
right, right.
Or, "Nigga,
that's a motherfucking hit."
You get what I'm saying?
Either confirmation
or clarification.
-Mmm.
-But you need them both.
[phone ringing]
-[D.O.C.]   Doggy Dogg!
-[Snoop] What's up, cuz?
[Kevin] Ooh, shit,
he got D.O.C. on the joint.
[chuckles]
[D.O.C.]
[indistinct] The gangstas,
the real gangstas, like,
[indistinct] real--
So what you saying, nigga?
We ain't real gangstas, nigga?
[laughter]
-KG, cuz, D.O.C.
-[Kevin] That's crazy.
Oh, shit.
He got the real D.O.C. on here.
What's up, man?
Pleasure. Pleasure. Right.
Come on.
Come on, KG, man.
I was telling Dogg, man,
you is, like,
my favorite artist, man.
-Real love, KG.
-[Kevin] Real shit, man.
-Real love, bro.
-[Kevin] Real shit.
Bro, I ran with you
even though you beat
the Lakers, nigga.
He talking about
on the video game.
Right. Oh the video--?
Niggas ran with you, nigga.
Yeah, nigga!
-[Kevin laughing]
-Quit playing, nigga!
How you living, man?
[D.O.C.]
I'm good, man. I'm blessed.
Too blessed
to be stressed, bro.
[Kevin]
Facts. Facts. That's what up.
Now, it's just hanging out
with my family
and shit,
just kicking it, bro.
[Kevin] Oh, okay, okay.
You coming tomorrow?
Yeah, I'll be in LA
tomorrow.
I'll get there tomorrow.
And I'll probably be at
Dre house tomorrow night.
I'ma pull up.
I'm coming.
[Kevin] That's what's up, man.
Pleasure meeting you, man.
That's what's up.
Thank you, Snoop.
I appreciate that, man.
All right.
-Death Row, nigga.
-[laughs]