Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[car alarm chirps]
- [fob clicks]
- [whirring]
[suspenseful music plays]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
- [exclaims softly]
- [yells]
- [blade swishes]
- [groans]
[growls]
[grunts and yells]
[groans]
[yells]
[grunts]
[groans weakly]
Take it.
[keys jingle]
[tense music plays]
[groans loudly]
Who are you?
[in Xhosa] Wait.
Let's talk about this.
Wait.
[groans]
- [blade swishes]
- [groans]
[child in Sotho] Dad?
[groans softly]
[kisses]
[alarm beeps]
[phone rings]
- [phone chimes]
- [woman] Sir.
[man on phone] The clock is ticking, Mo.
Strike teams are en route
to Johnny Klein's
last known location, sir.
We will take him within the hour.
[tense ethereal music plays]
[man breathes heavily]
We need him alive, Mo.
- We need to know what he has.
- Fuck.
[man sighs]
And why is this man coming out now,
on the eve of the release
of the State Capture report?
[sighs]
[man] The bastard will play his hand now.
Well, speak your mind, Mo.
Daza, this is the last time
I can sanction an op like this.
The Oversight Committee has caught wind.
I'm risking everything here.
Well, you know what they say, Mo.
You cannot have an omelette
without breaking a few eggs.
You're either in, or you're out.
[device beeps]
Teams are in position, ma'am.
Johnny Klein is in our sights.
[suspenseful music plays]
[device powers on and beeps]
- [man 1] Clear!
- [woman 1] Clear!
- [man 2] Clear!
- Ground floor clear, sir.
[man groans]
[officer coughs]
[continues coughing]
[suspenseful music plays]
- [gun fires nearby]
- [thudding]
[both grunting]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[both grunt]
- [blade swishes]
- [groans]
[winces loudly]
[grunts]
[groans]
[both grunting]
- [groans]
- [piano keys mashing]
[both grunting]
[groans]
[piano keys mash]
[both grunting]
- [growls]
- [groans]
- [exclaims]
- [piano keys mashing]
[blade swishes]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[both straining]
[groans]
[grunts]
[yells]
[exhales loudly]
[winces]
[grunts]
[tapping]
[child] Gotcha!
[chuckles]
[grunts] Good morning.
Morning.
Got something to show you. [grunts softly]
[sighs]
[in Xhosa] It's today, right?
[in Zulu] it's okay with you?
[man] Mmm?
Okay, then,
today is the big day.
- [in English] Want some of the good stuff?
- Hmm.
[man] Yeah.
[in Zulu] How are your beans coming along?
[English] They're ready
to be planted outside.
Think we should do it this weekend. Yeah?
Will they grow into trees?
[chuckles] No, not trees.
Aw.
Hey.
Plant our own tree some day.
[in Xhosa] An apple tree?
[in Zulu] A peach tree, mango, uh, banana...
- [laughs]
- Anything.
Check on the tomatoes.
[chuckles softly]
[knocking at door]
[knocking forcefully]
Zuko.
[softly] Hey, what are you doing here?
We got him. We can stop Mtima
from becoming president.
- Look, I told you I'm done with that life.
- But it's not done with you, Umzingeli.
- [grunts]
- Don't call me that. Leave!
[man groans and coughs]
[sighs]
[tense music plays]
[blade swishes]
Who are you?
[groaning]
[groans]
[in Xhosa] Wait. Wait, wait.
[groaning]
[in Sotho] Daddy?
Daddy!
[man in English] Zuko! Zuko, calm down!
[Zuko] He wasn't alone!
The family got an early flight home.
- You knew?
- Well, I know the risks.
So that makes me the judge,
the jury, and executioner?
If that's the cost of democracy,
of freedom, then yes.
What?
[melancholic ethereal music plays]
Sometimes, the few have to suffer
so the many can prosper, Zuko.
That means you too.
Tell me, Johnny...
who are the few?
Who are the many?
Consider my debt paid.
[neck cracks]
- [clears throat]
- Oh.
- [in Zulu] My love.
- [in Xhosa] Don't "my love" me.
I told you not to give the child
sugar in the morning.
[in Zulu] You're my sugar in the morning.
[in English] All right.
Where is the good stu...
[in Xhosa] Oh! Good morning, Mom.
Don't "Good morning, Mom" me, young man.
Get ready for school.
We're going to harvest tomatoes.
After school, Pakamile.
[English] Zuko said
you wouldn't understand.
[in Xhosa] Are you talking back to me?
Go get ready for school, Pakamile. Go on!
Now do you see what I'm saying?
His teacher says he gets too excited
when he has coffee in the morning.
[sighs]
[in Zulu] He's a man.
He must be strong and drink coffee.
- He must start while he's young.
- Mmm.
[in Xhosa] Who were you
talking to this morning?
[in Zulu] Someone from insurance.
[in Xhosa] Don't lie to me.
Insurance people so early in the morning?
[in Zulu] It's too early
to sell me insurance,
so I chased him out.
[in Xhosa] Really?
Mm-hmm.
- [in English] Okay.
- Mmm.
[in Zulu] It's Paka's bath time.
Then we can have some fun.
[in Xhosa] Stop it!
Pakamile! Pakamile, are you taking a bath?
[suspenseful musical rise plays]
[man grunts]
[forlorn music plays]
[agent sighs]
- [Mo] What do you have for me?
- [agent] It's not fucking him.
It's not Klein.
John Doe. No ID. But he was a pro.
[Mo] "Was"?
Tiger, that wasn't the deal.
You told me this guy was harmless.
He killed one of my people.
[Mo] Well, I cannot exactly
interrogate a corpse now, can I?
That was not the deal, Tiger.
I'm not paying for a body.
[sighs]
[brooding music plays]
Get me a visual.
And clean up your mess.
Ma'am.
- You tapped a wrong target, Beth.
- That's impossible.
Tiger just debriefed me.
We now have a dead John Doe on our hands.
How'd you miss Klein leaving Vlottenburg?
Naledi was on point.
We had to be discreet, ma'am.
We only had time for a single drone pass
after the rental company finally sent
their GPS tracking records.
- We're waiting on an update...
- That's not good enough.
Klein wanted this. It was a ruse.
All hands on deck. Find him!
Now!
- Yes, ma'am.
[brooding music continues]
[coughs]
[coughing]
[answering machine beeps]
[Johnny] Mr. Bressler,
if you're interested
in bringing down Mtima
and the people who ruined your career,
I suggest you sober up.
I'm having files delivered to you shortly.
They'll provide you
with everything you need.
Please,
be ready.
My name is Johnny Klein,
and I'm counting on you.
[phone beeps]
[mellow jazzy piano music plays]
Sir.
We'll get him.
I have this under control.
Do you understand what is at stake, Mo?
- Hmm?
- Yes, sir.
There is but one man standing
between me and winning this election,
and yet, you've had months,
years,
to take care of Klein.
That's ample time, wouldn't you say?
So why is he still running
circles around you?
And you still cannot tell me
exactly what he has on us.
[in Xhosa] A white man once said...
[sniffs]
[in English] "The stone
that the builder refuses
eventually becomes a cornerstone."
It was our forefathers...
[in Xhosa] slaving away,
sweating for white people,
and they'd close us
on the outside to keep us out.
[chuckles]
[in English] But now look at us.
Mmm?
[softly] It's almost harvest time.
[in Xhosa] Now it's our turn to feast.
[in English] And if you want
a seat at the table,
you might have to get
those hands dirty, Mo.
[children chattering and laughing]
But, Ma, we're going to be farmers.
Farmers don't do math or write essays.
- Can't I just go with Zuko?
- [sighs]
[in Zulu] Farmers need to know
how to read and write.
Math, so you can calculate your profits.
[in English] Mmm.
It'll be over before you know it.
[school bell rings]
I love you.
Love you, Mom.
Paka!
[in Zulu] Helmet, son.
- [chuckles]
- [engine starts]
[keyboard clacking]
[ominous music plays]
[computer chirps and beeps]
- [beeps]
- It's a match!
Latest batch of tracking records
show the same vehicle
leaving Vlottenburg
before our op this morning.
Track any other movements
he might have made.
[Naledi] Klein's last known location
is the Cape Grand Hotel.
Send in Mobile One.
Low profile. Two on standby.
[line ringing]
Mo, we found Klein.
- [in Afrikaans] Thank you, driver.
- [in Mzansi slang] You're welcome.
[in Xhosa] I'll see you later.
[in English] Sure.
And then?
[in Xhosa] I love you.
[chuckles]
[in English] Bye!
Ciao.
[engine starts]
Mobile One is in place.
Take him.
Quietly.
[suspenseful music plays]
[tools whirring]
Just double check.
[desk clerk] Nothing, sir. Nothing.
That's him! That's Johnny Klein!
- He just walked out the damn door.
- [exclaims]
[tires squeal]
[agent] Control, target's on the move.
Stay on him.
[Johnny coughs]
I spoke to you nicely
this morning, Johnny.
Permission to take him.
Not in a public place.
[Beth] Negative, One. Standby.
You'll lead them to me,
right to my family.
I'm afraid I already have. [sniffs]
They're watching us right now.
Who's the other guy?
ID the man he's talking to.
Copy that, ma'am.
- I asked you nicely two years ago.
- [man] Whoa, whoa, whoa!
So let me be.
[man] Zuko! What's gotten into you?
It's all right, sir. Sorry. Thank you.
This is between Zuko and me.
All right, all right.
- Please, Zuko.
- [sighs]
Sorry, Mr. B. It won't happen again.
You need to leave now.
You vowed to stand against all injustice
done to men, women, children,
and the elderly of Azania.
I know the oath, Johnny.
You swore that oath, Zuko.
It's bigger than you.
Bigger than your family.
But you can save them.
There are files.
Files that will expose everything,
including us,
unless you can destroy those files.
What have you gotten yourself into?
We were wrong to leave it to the courts.
Mtima, he owns them all.
And it's the State Capture report.
- If it exonerates him, it's over.
- No...
Those files are our insurance.
- They're all we got!
- I don't care! I don't care.
It's got nothing to do with me.
You need to leave.
- They'll kill you, not me.
- [coughs]
The cancer will kill me first.
You're the last man standing, Zuko.
It has to be you.
Cancer?
Johnny?
- [Johnny] There's a locker at the airport.
- [keys clink]
He just put something in his pocket.
We have a new target. Shadow him.
Go to Maseru, the birthplace of Alkebulan,
the only place Mtima doesn't know about.
No, Johnny. No.
An elder will show you the way.
But you have to go today.
Friday is D-Day.
I can't, Johnny.
I can't.
Goodbye, my boy.
[tense music plays]
[agent] Okay.
- [groans]
- [Beth] Mobile One.
Shadow new target. Stand by.
Rover One, intercept and apprehend Klein.
Contain it.
[tense music continues and intensifies]
[indistinct chatter over radio]
[coughs]
- [engine revs]
- [tires squeal]
He's on to us.
- [siren wailing]
- [engine revs]
[tires squeal]
Fuck.
[inhales sharply]
[laughs dryly]
[coughs]
[coughing]
[beeps]
[chuckles] Too easy.
- [brake lever clicks]
- [brakes screech]
[siren wails and whoops]
- [coughing]
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey! Johnny.
Now, I've had a really bad day.
Don't make it worse.
Put down your gun.
[coughs]
[grumbles]
[ethereal music plays]
September!
- Hey! Hey!
- Johnny!
[gun fires]
[Beth exhales heavily]
Shit.
[Mo sighs]
The new target is now our priority.
Do we have an ID yet?
Naledi!
On it, ma'am.
- [sighs heavily]
- [keyboard clacks]
[engine stops]
[girlfriend] I promise you,
you did not go wrong with this purchase.
- Gracias.
- [woman] Okay. Thank you.
[line rings]
[phone rings]
Oh.
[phone beeps]
Hi.
[Zuko] Uh, my love.
- Yeah?
- [in Zulu] How are you?
[Xhosa] Where are you?
It sounds like you're here.
[in Zulu] No. Listen.
I need to leave town for a few days.
[in English] It's the insurance salesman,
isn't it?
[dramatic musical flourish plays]
I knew it.
[in Zulu] I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
It's better if you don't know.
It's not safe.
I never had told my son that...
all men leave eventually.
I guess he's going to have
to find out for himself now.
[in Zulu] No, no, no, my sweetheart.
[anxious music plays]
The life I have with you and Paka
is the life I've always wanted.
If I do this,
we can continue to live that life.
Please allow me to do that for you.
[in Xhosa] Where are you going?
Hmm?
[in Zulu] I'll be back.
I promise.
Zuko?
- Zuko!
- [dial tone pulses]
[girlfriend sniffles]
[sobs] Zuko.
[dial tone pulses]
[grunts softly]
[grunts and coughs]
[phone beeps]
[Johnny on message] Mr. Bressler.
If you're interested
in bringing down Mtima
and the people who ruined your career,
I suggest you sober up.
I'm having files delivered to you shortly.
My name is Johnny Klein,
and I'm counting on you.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Fuck off, man.
[siren approaching]
Control, there's nothing in the car
and nothing on the corpse.
The guy was clean.
Scratch that. He's a fucking mess.
He's clean?
What the fuck do you mean he's clean?
Madam Director.
Twice in one day. Lucky me.
Nothing but the gun.
He's clean as a whistle.
Sorry, boss. Got to go. Too many eyes.
[unsettling droning music plays]
[man on speaker]
Attention, all passengers...
[continues indistinctly]
[man] Target is checking in
at an Air Maseru counter.
Permission to take him now?
Take him.
Discreetly.
Can you please come with us?
[in Zulu] Do you think this is a game?
Hurry up. Fast.
[in Afrikaans and English] That's it.
Nice and easy.
[music fades]
[groans]
[in Zulu] What are you going
to do in Maseru? Hmm?
[in Xhosa] What is this?
[in English] What is this?
- [exclaims]
- [man 1] Hey!
[in Xhosa] Hmm?
What did Johnny Klein give you?
Huh?
[in English] Not much of a ring. [laughs]
[man 1] Give me your fucking hand.
[dramatic music plays]
[man 2 groans and coughs]
[man 1 groans]
[Beth in earpiece] Agents down.
Repeat, agents down!
Target is in the central terminal.
All units, converge on his position now!
Stop!
[man 3] Central Terminal,
he's on the move.
[suspenseful percussive music plays]
[man 4] Damn it, man, move!
[man 3] He's heading down the stairs!
Get him! [yells and groans]
[man 5, in Zulu] Hey!
[man 3] He's disappeared into the crowd.
Anyone got eyes?
[tense pulsing music plays]
[muttering indistinctly]
[engine starts]
[breathing heavily]
[man 3] Control, negative.
No sign of target.
[sighs]
[phone beeps]
[phone crunches]
[news jingle plays on TV]
[anchor] We start in the Western Cape
this evening, where a dramatic car chase
turned deadly after it spilled
onto Cape Town's
notorious Foreshore Freeway Bridge
earlier today, claiming the life
of disgraced former Director General
of International Relations,
Johnny Klein.
Our reporter, Chanel Ebrahim
is looking into the tragedy.
[reporter] Good evening, Mandla.
- Oh, fuck.
- ...conversation I had with police...
- Hey, Roy! Volume!
- Yeah.
...eyewitnesses report
that Johnny Klein was being pursued
by private security agency, Ingwe,
before he allegedly shot himself
and plunged from the unfinished highway.
The matter is still under investigation,
and more information is forthcoming.
[phone beeps]
[on message] My name is Johnny Klein,
and I'm counting on you.
Fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
[sighs]
There. Freeze that frame and enhance.
[computer chirps and beeps]
Get me that address.
[keyboard clacking]
[beeps]
[woman] That house
is registered under the name
of Mrs. Thandiwe Makeba.
Isn't she the Minister of Foreign Affairs?
Former minister.
Print me that.
Alert Mo.
[line rings]
[woman on phone] Yes, Gemini,
w-what is it?
We're running out of time.
I have to give them something.
- [door opens]
- [alarm beeping]
- [keypad beeps]
- [alarm stops]
- [Zuko sighs]
- [chimes]
[breathing heavily]
[groans]
Fuck.
[girlfriend, in Xhosa] I love you.
[laughs]
See you later.
[in English] It's the insurance salesman,
isn't it?
[Zuko, in Zulu] I'm sorry.
[heartbeat pulses faintly]
[sniffs]
[droning music plays and swells]
[motorcycle engine revs]
[keyboard clacking]
[man sighs]
[groans softly]
[clears throat]
Excuse me, sir.
Are you Mike Bressler?
I was Mike Bressler once.
Sorry, sir. You're, like, my hero.
- What's your name, kid?
- Oh, Allison Bhaloyi, sir.
I'm the new intern here.
Allison Bhaloyi, huh?
Please, please, don't call me "sir."
I am a scoundrel and a drunk.
[softly] Okay.
Um...
What are you working on?
Probably nothing.
Okay.
Was good to meet you.
[sighs]
[computer start-up jingle plays]
Allison Bhaloyi!
AB.
- [chuckles]
- You wanna help?
Yeah!
Um... yeah. Yeah.
- Coffee, AB.
- Okay.
Strong, black coffee.
Yes.
And everything you can find
on the Johnny Klein suicide.
That's trending right now.
- It's what?
- Oh, it's trending all over social media.
- Coffee, AB?
- Yes, yes. [laughs nervously]
[melancholic music plays]
[scoffs]
- [in Xhosa] You're still up?
- Mmm.
I'm peeling vegetables for tomorrow.
Zuko will be here soon, Mom.
[in English] He has to. Him and I,
we need to harvest our tomatoes.
And we need to save up money
for a tractor.
[in Xhosa] Oh, didn't you want
to be a pilot?
- Hmm?
- [in English] Ma! That was years ago.
I was still a little child.
[in Xhosa] And like Zuko says...
- [in English] "Farming is a noble job."
- Oh.
You build, you don't destroy,
and you feed people. You don't hurt them.
[in Xhosa] You're right.
Zuko will be back.
[in English] He has to. He promised.
Mmm?
[knocking at door]
Is Malime Mambi here?
- Yes?
- You have to come with us.
- Why? Excuse me. What? No!
- Mom? Mom!
- Mom, Mom!
- No! What's going on? No!
- Mom!
- Paka, no! No!
- My child!
- Mom, wait! Mom!
- Mom! Mom!
- Paka!
- Paka! Paka!
[in Xhosa] Paka! Hurry up!
Hurry, Paka! Paka!
Hurry!
[Beth, in English] Zuko Khumalo was born
on 10 October 1987
to activist parents in Makhanda.
They died in 1990
during an Apartheid Security Police raid.
Raised by his grandmother
in Gqumahashe on the Great Fish River.
- After matric, he joined the police and...
- Shh!
[man] Okay. Let's try this differently.
This man, Johnny Klein,
came to visit Zuko this morning.
I told you,
I don't know him.
[man] That is not good enough, Ms. Mambi.
This man was a known terrorist.
Please,
I don't know.
I have to go back home to my son.
[man] The sooner you tell me the truth,
the sooner you can get back to your son.
He...
H-He might be someone from Zuko's past.
[man] What past?
[Malime] He doesn't talk about it.
- Why does he not talk about it?
- Because I don't ask!
And because Zuko knows
there's only room for love in our house.
[man] If there's only room
for love in your house,
then why did you and Zuko Khumalo
associate with a terrorist?
[sobs]
Please! Please, my boy.
SAPS service records show that Khumalo
was selected for a Special Task Force.
- Get to the point.
- [Naledi] Four years ago, he vanishes.
No bank accounts,
medical records, taxes, nothing.
Then two years ago,
an ID document application,
with a birth certificate, out of nowhere.
What does that have to do
with Johnny Klein and the John Doe?
We're working on it.
What I want to know
is what Makeba's got to do with this.
[sinister music plays]
Makeba?
As in Thandi Makeba?
You didn't tell her?
I'm so sorry. It slipped my mind.
Slipped your mi...
Slipped your fucking mind?
Get out.
[lock beeps and whirs]
I don't know if we can trust her, Mo.
Keep an eye on her.
Maybe we can use this to our advantage.
[menacing music plays]
[kwaito music plays faintly in ear buds]
[music stops]
[in Xhosa] Twice already,
and a day hasn't passed.
[sighs heavily]
[in Tswana] Johnny visited Thandi Makeba.
You knew?
[in English] Suspected.
[in Xhosa] She has dirt on her hands,
filthied by illegal miners.
She must've thought
she was helping herself up,
but she was hanging herself on a noose.
[English] That's why
she didn't come after us.
[in Xhosa] Cut out her tongue, Mo.
The real test, however,
is if you can leverage this...
[in English]...to unearth Johnny's scheme.
But most importantly,
silence his errand boy.
Mo!
[in Xhosa] Come.
- [in English] Daza, what the hell is this?
- I think you know exactly what it is, Mo.
Mmm?
[in Xhosa] Just imagine...
if the entire nation knew
that your father...
[in English] was in bed
with the apartheid regime.
[in Xhosa] What would they say?
[chuckles]
Ah.
And so they say...
[in English] "The apple does not fall
too far from the tree."
Or does it, Mo? Mmm?
So it appears...
[in Xhosa] that your hands
are also dirty.
[in English] And that's just
the tip of the iceberg.
[in Xhosa] Time waits for no one, Mo.
[in English] Tick-tock.
Tick-tock. Tick-tock.
Tick-tock. Tick-fucking-tock, Mo!
[cell phone ringing]
[in Afrikaans] My goodness!
I thought you were dead.
- I thought Mtima took you out.
- [laughs]
[in English] Good one, Neville.
Can you chat?
What could an old has-been like you
learn from a pencil pusher like myself?
[Mike] Yeah, right. Pencil pusher.
Listen, you're the IO
on the Johnny Klein suicide
from yesterday, right?
[Neville] Yeah.
What the hell is a guy
from a private security company
called "Ingwe" doing there?
Strange things are happening, all right?
Shortly after the Klein suicide,
we received an APB on a...
Zuko Khumalo.
There's a nationwide manhunt.
He took out two PIA agents at the airport.
- And he didn't even break a sweat.
- Shit.
[in Afrikaans] Yes,
you can say that again.
[in English] Uh, keep me
in the loop, yeah?
Sure. Hey, and Mike?
[in Afrikaans] Be careful.
[cell phone chimes]
[cell phone vibrating]
[tense ethereal music plays]
Umzingeli?
Gemini?
[Naledi] Yes.
Iman,
how long has it been?
Long enough for me
to no longer go by that name.
I'm inside the PIA.
[Zuko] All grown up.
Look, what am I doing here?
What's going on?
[Naledi] I'm on a need-to-know basis,
Zuko, just like you.
What about Johnny?
He showed up out of nowhere again.
He's not looking good, Iman.
He shot himself, Zuko.
[jackals howling]
[sighs softly]
[clears throat] Look, uh...
I'm sorry, Iman.
I know the two of you were close.
What about the others? Zwelibanzi?
Johnny said I was the last man standing.
[sighs] I tried to warn him.
Just do whatever Johnny asked you to do.
Whatever it is, it's big. Really big.
They brought Malime in.
They're pressuring her
about you and Johnny.
All right, this is bullshit, okay?
I'm... I'm coming back!
No. Focus on the mission.
She's a little rattled,
but she doesn't know anything.
I'll take care of it.
Remember why Johnny picked you, picked us.
We finish this fight for Alkebulan.
I told Johnny last I saw him,
I told you when I left,
I'm done with this Alkebulan bullshit.
[breath trembles]
The only reason I'm doing this
is for my family.
They know who you are, Zuko.
I know.
No. You don't understand.
You'll be all over the news tomorrow.
Mo, the boss,
she's breaking protocol,
over-reaching, doing Mtima's dirty work.
None of this is officially sanctioned.
They will hunt you down.
They can try.
- [footsteps approaching]
- I have to go.
[toilet flushes]
[water running]
All good?
Yes, ma'am.
[tense ethereal music continues
and intensifies]
[knocking at door]
You must be u... uPaka.
[Malime] Uh, Zuko, please come in.
[in Xhosa] I'm so sorry.
The taxis were striking,
and I got home late.
[in English] Paka, have you offered
our guest something to drink?
[in Zulu] Uh, I'm fine, thanks.
[Malime, in Xhosa] Okay, just a moment.
What does "handsome" mean?
[Malime] Paka!
[in Xhosa] My mom says you're handsome.
[in Xhosa] Pakamile Mambi, stop it!
[in English] I'm... I'm so sorry.
[in Zulu] I... You know how kids are.
I went past the petrol station,
and I got this for you.
[in Xhosa] Thank you.
I'll put this in the fridge.
[Zuko, in Zulu] Uh, what are you drawing?
[in English] It's for... It's for school.
[in Xhosa] These are tomatoes.
[in English] But I must still add
some cows.
Farming is a... it's a noble job, eh?
[in Xhosa] What does "noble" mean?
[sighs]
Uh...
[in Zulu] In English,
it means you're honorable.
[in English] Or you...
you build.
You don't destroy. You...
mmm, feed people.
You don't hurt them.
[in Xhosa] I like that.
[in Zulu] Your mom told me
you like farming.
So I got this for you.
She said you'd like it.
Wow!
[in Xhosa] Did you say thank you?
Thank you.
[in Zulu] You're welcome. [echoes]
[heartbeat pounding]
[Zuko in English] I'm done with that life.
[Johnny] But it's not done
with you, Umzingeli.
[Zuko] Oh, fight. Fight, we vow,
vow to devote our life to the movement.
- You swore that oath, Zuko.
- Fight.
[Zuko] Fight for Alkebulan.
I know the oath, Johnny.
We vow to devote our life
to the movement, and to vow...
[Johnny] It's bigger than you,
bigger than your family.
[Zuko] We vow to protect the innocent.
We vow...
We vow to protect the innocent.
And never give in.
[musical swell plays]
[epic classical music plays]
We've got him.
He stole a motorbike from his employer.
We're scouring CCTV footage
from the past 24 hours.
Got a few hits, we're connecting dots.
Road blocks
on all the major routes to Maseru.
We'll find him.
And the woman?
Nothing.
I don't think she's lying.
We have to squeeze her.
She knows something.
[Allison in Afrikaans]
We made the front page!
[groans]
I'm getting too old for this shit.
- Coffee?
- Mm-hmm.
[in Afrikaans] Thanks,
thanks, thanks. [groans]
Since when do you speak Afrikaans, huh?
- People can't gossip about me.
- [Mike laughs]
It wasn't us, Allison Bhaloyi.
It was all you.
- [in English] And I got more on Klein.
- Mmm?
Johnny Klein was this hot-shot lawyer,
a rising star.
He was
Director of International Relations.
Even met Obama and Mandela.
- Hmm.
- But then he was sort of demoted.
Director of Forestry,
and then junior something in...
Arts and Culture.
[laughs] Where political careers
go to die.
When did this fade start?
Four years ago.
And what happened four years ago?
- Mtima!
- [laughs]
Bingo!
A man who is about to walk free
from corruption and State Capture charges
because the state
has run out of witnesses.
A murderous, raping adulterer
is set to become our new president,
and then, my beautiful young friend,
we are all well and truly fucked.
That's everything you wrote about.
Yeah, sure. Before he fucked my career
six ways from Sunday.
Mmm.
But after that message I got from Klein,
I reckon we are back in the game,
and Zuko Khumalo is our champion striker.
[epic classical music resumes playing]
[man] Ooh! R 1250 GS!
It's a sweet bike, man.
[gas pump whirring]
My bro, map's upside down.
Don't believe everything you see.
Maybe you're upside down.
[laughs]
[mellow pop music plays on speaker]
[sighs]
You know,
none of my business,
but... the Boere were here a few hours ago
looking for a bro on a...
A massive road block there
by the Orange River outside of town.
So if I were a bro on a R 1250 GS...
I'd take the R717 North to Philippolis.
Stay on that 'til Trompsburg.
Then back onto the N1 from there.
- [attendant] It's 300.
- [nozzle clicks in gas pump]
That's for the help.
The advice is free, my bro.
I've had my fair share with the Boere.
Everyone deserves a second chance.
Salut, salut.
[engine starts]
[tense ethereal music plays]
[Naledi] Ms. Mambi.
Please don't be alarmed.
I'm a friend of Zuko.
Ex... Excuse me? What?
I can't say more.
Things are happening fast now,
but you're not safe here.
What... [exclaims]
Wha... What about my son? Is he all right?
I don't know.
What's happening? Where is Zuko?
Don't worry about him.
Just be ready.
- Wait.
- [door opens]
Wait. Be ready for what?
- Naledi.
- [ominous music plays]
Johnny's tendrils run deep,
but they're drying up one by one.
Who the hell are you?
You've been here long enough
to know how this goes.
Either you talk, or we make you talk.
Your choice.
What's it going to be?
I will never betray my oath.
Who is Zuko Khumalo,
and what does he want in Maseru?
I found this on her. Only two contacts.
Zenkosi and Umzingeli.
Run it.
I want names, addresses,
what they had for breakfast.
- [knocking at door]
- What?
Ma'am. We've located Khumalo.
Take this piece of shit away.
Copy that.
- Get Mambi to the safe house now.
- Ma'am.
What are you waiting for?
Compliments? Get to work!
[dramatic music plays]
[helicopter whirring]
[Tiger] Okay, everyone, listen up.
Alpha Team is with me.
Bravo Team,
you take up the secondary position.
If anything goes wrong,
we'll regroup at the LZ.
And remember, we need to take him alive.
He's our fucking paycheck!
[tires squeal]
[grunts]
[groans]
[both grunting]
- [groans]
- [man mutters]
[man exclaims]
[yells]
Fuck!
She fucking bit me! Fuck!
[groans]
[man grunting]
[groaning]
[helicopter whirring]
[bold music plays]
[Afrikaans] Don't let that car through!
Stop that car!
Who are you? The backup?
[laughs] Are we the backup?
Do we look like the fucking backup?
Listen, pal, I don't know where you...
Stand back.
Or I'll put you back.
[motorcycle approaches]
[in English] Get them in position.
- Let's go.
- [siren wails]
Now!
[engine revs]
[in Afrikaans] Bring it on, asshole.
[in English] On my mark.
[siren wailing]
[door beeps]
[in Afrikaans] Stop that truck!
- [man yells]
- [in English] Get down, get down!
[epic dramatic music plays]
Call it in!
[in Afrikaans] Come.
[man on radio, in English] All units,
move to intercept targets along Route One.
Cut off any escape. Over.
- Damn it! What is going on down there?
- Ma'am, it's Naledi, she's taken Mambi.
I do not want Mambi hurt.
Fix it, Beth! Fix it!
[dramatic music intensifies]
Come on!
[man] Don't move!
[groans]
Malime? Okay, listen,
you're going to have to jump.
- No!
- We are going to have to jump.
Okay? Follow me.
[breathing heavily]
[Tiger] Keep this thing steady.
I need a clean shot.
Come on! You have to do this!
Hey, come on!
Go, go, go! Get me in front of him!
Hey! You have to jump.
- Come on, look at me! Eyes on me!
- [Malime gasps]
Lower! Get me lower!
[Mo] Naledi!
Naledi, think about what you're doing.
Come on! You have to jump!
[gun clicks]
[whimpers]
[screams]
- [screams]
- No!
[engine clanks]
- [alarms beep]
- No! Fuck!
[thudding]
Shit.
Hawk One is going down!
Rover One, come pick me up.
Let's regroup at the LZ.
[fast-paced percussive music plays]
[in Zulu] Hey, you! Piss off!
[in English] Move!
[engine spluttering]
[engine cuts out]
[moody music plays]
[door closes]
[breathes heavily]
[melancholic music plays]
[breath trembles]
Fuck!
What the fuck has he done?
Okay.
[woman on phone] Gemini?
[Naledi] Zenkosi, we're compromised.
[Zenkosi] Umzingeli?
[Naledi] I don't know.
[Zenkosi] Even from beyond the grave,
Johnny gambles.
He sent the boy on a fool's errand.
We cannot rely on Zuko's luck.
Listen, it's very important.
Find Mike Bressler at the Cape Sentinel.
Tell him everything you know.
That's our last hope.
Yes, ma'am.
[Zenkosi] Do you have an exit strategy?
Yes, ma'am. What about you?
[Zenkosi] I've always had
an escape plan, Gemini.
I knew this day was coming soon.
I'll be fine. Thanks for everything.
[phone clicks]
Change in strategy. Bring me the boy.
Mambi's boy.
Insurance. Take him to a safe house.
Uh... Respectfully, ma'am,
that's not... that's not protocol.
Protocol?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Look around you, Beth.
Fuck protocol.
Yes, ma'am.
Find Zuko.
[melancholic music plays]
- Listen, we'll be five minutes.
- I'm sorry, sir, I can't let you through.
Neville!
[in Afrikaans] Good heavens!
[both laugh]
[Neville] Gosh,
you look like an old geezer.
- Who's this? Your new sidekick?
- Allison Bhaloyi. [laughs]
- Pleased to meet you.
- Likewise.
- [in English] What happened here, Neville?
- It's a suicide.
Come on, Neville.
Neville!
I know this is the PIA building.
This is connected
to the Klein and Khumalo thing, isn't it?
[laughs]
[in Afrikaans]
You're in the wrong profession.
[in English] Come on.
Just give me something. Off the record.
Reports of gunfire
in front of the building.
This was before the vic jumped. Or fell.
[softly] What the fuck
is going on, Neville?
[in Afrikaans] Either the dominoes
are collapsing...
[in English]...or someone
is cleaning house.
[cell phone ringing]
[sighs]
Bressler.
[on phone] This is Iman.
I'm a friend of Johnny's.
Molebogeng Kwena.
Hello, Thandi.
Aren't you going to invite me in?
[tense music plays]
I'm not surprised
Mtima would stoop so low.
And I suppose it was just
a matter of time before you did the same.
Oh, come off it, Thandi.
[Tswana] You think we're different?
Your hands are no cleaner than mine.
- [scoffs]
- Illegal miners?
[in English] Really?
[in Tswana] Molebogeng, what do you want?
Mtima must be so terrified
that he resorted
to sending an envoy in person.
[in English] I want to know why Johnny
sent Zuko Khumalo to Maseru.
It doesn't matter.
If I know Zuko, come Friday,
it will all be over for you
and your puppet master.
I know about Naledi Gumede.
About Johnny's decoy in Vlottenburg,
and how it all connects to you.
Now, out with it.
[Mike] So you're telling me
Thandi Makeba and Johnny Klein
were running a counter-intelligence op
with globe-trotting elite assassins
to take down Mtima?
That's exactly what I'm telling you.
Why should we believe you?
Johnny and Thandi trusted you.
And you know something's up.
When Zuko finds out
Malime died at Mo Kwena's hands...
there will be a bloodbath.
And while I don't give a shit about Kwena,
I swore an oath.
The truth must come out.
[groans]
[Thandi] We all knew what would happen
if Mtima ever became president.
And there you are,
doing all his dirty work.
Everything that we fought for,
brought low by pests.
- Treason.
- Self-determination.
[chuckles dryly]
Is that how your colonial masters
sold it to you?
Who do you think Mtima bows to?
[heart beating]
You got it all wrong.
You are the one who's upside down.
Damian?
[suspenseful music plays]
[groans]
[in Afrikaans] Wait here.
[in English] We have to corroborate
this story with Makeba...
No. Makeba is in the wind.
It's not safe for her here.
But look, even if all this is true...
[sighs]...nobody's going to believe
who or whatever it is you are.
No offense, of course.
[Naledi] None taken.
But you forget,
there's still one key player on the board.
Zuko.
Drop it.
And the other one.
Get me to the chopper now.
Why?
What's wrong
with that fancy bike of yours?
- Did I put too many holes in it?
- Move!
Tell him to turn it on.
- [button clicks and beeps]
- Stop right there.
[helicopter powering up]
[both grunting]
[grunts]
- [blade swishes]
- [groans]
[both grunt]
You created a rogue agent.
We created a weapon.
A tool.
- [in Sotho] Do you know who Mzilikazi was?
- [Mo, in Tswana] King of the Matabele.
He was a lieutenant to King Shaka.
[in English] His full name
is Mzilikazi Khumalo.
Johnny used to say that Zuko
has the spirit of Mzilikazi in him.
The heart of the hunter.
[groans]
Well, if he thinks that he can go
against me, he has another thing coming.
[Thandi in Sotho] You think Zuko
is the only one you must eliminate?
We all have secrets, you idiot,
and I know about your shady father.
Take your papers and get out of here!
[groans]
[screams]
[both grunting]
[music intensifies]
[in English] Am I going to need this?
No, sir.
So fly!
Yes, sir.
[grunts]
- [gun safety clicks]
- [sighs]
[ominous music plays]
[phone line ringing]
[line picks up]
[Mo] Yes?
[Beth] He went straight through Tiger.
[sighs softly]
I'm sorry.
Mo...
Where is Tiger?
[Beth] I recalled them.
We can't risk an op in Maseru,
not in the current climate.
And the boy?
[Beth] We've got him. At the safe house.
[gentle bittersweet vocal music plays]
[sobs]
[man chatters indistinctly on radio]
Just put her down, will you?
Copy. Will do that.
Thank you.
[percussive chanting music plays]
[Zuko groans]
[winces]
[groaning]
[coughs]
[eagle calling]
[men chattering indistinctly]
[Zuko groans]
[Johnny] My dear Umzingeli,
when you read this,
know that it was hard
for me to put pen to paper,
to find the right words.
When we met the first time,
after your grandmother's terrible fate,
I made a decision, a choice,
to always be there for you,
a father figure.
Maybe I failed,
but know that to me,
you have always been like a son.
[man, in Sotho] It's all here.
Dig, Umzingeli.
[Johnny, in English] I never meant
the words I said to you that night.
[Johnny and Zuko] You aren't a killer.
You're a warrior.
[Zuko, reading] Much braver
than I could ever be.
I understand why you left,
but you know as well as I do
that the men we hunt are no saints.
Men like us have a higher purpose
to fight and protect
those who are helpless.
In our hunt, we risk
losing sight of ourselves,
and that which we fight for.
[beeps]
Your departure drove that truth
home for me,
like a spear to the heart.
I regret dragging your family into this.
[Zuko and Johnny] You deserve their love.
Look after Pakamile. He's a good boy.
[Johnny] His eyes, like yours,
are full of promise,
determination, resourcefulness, courage.
Make him proud.
Be the father I failed to be.
[Johnny and Zuko] It's up to you now,
Zuko, to finish the fight of Alkebulan.
If not for us, do it for justice.
[Johnny] Yours, Johnny.
[in Sotho] Umzingeli, a spear for you
to guard you from shadow.
[heart beating]
[ominous musical flourish plays]
[knocks]
[man] Good evening, sir.
[suspenseful music plays]
[grunts]
[man] Passport.
[Zuko groans]
[line ringing]
[woman] Zuko Khumalo, I presume?
Where... Where is Gemini?
I'm afraid Ms. Zondo has been compromised.
So has Makeba.
The jig is up.
[in Zulu] Who are you?
[Mo in English] I have a proposal for you.
[in Zulu] Where is Malime?
- Bring me...
- [in Zulu] Where is Malime?
[chuckles softly]
[in English] There's...
been a bit of an accident.
I have the boy.
[distantly] Bring me what you have,
and I'll return him to you.
[sweeping melancholic music plays]
[echoing] Mr. Khumalo?
[grunting]
[yells]
[winces and groans]
[Tiger] Sounds like you pissed him off.
Is the boy secure?
[Tiger] Place is tight as a tick.
I want you there with him.
[sighs] Respectfully...
you're not paying me enough for this shit.
The boy is bait.
What about that do you not understand?
[Tiger] Go on.
Zuko Khumalo has been
a thorn in my flesh long enough.
I want him eliminated permanently.
If you don't kill him, we're screwed.
[chuckles]
[inhales sharply]
No.
You're screwed.
I'll just disappear.
I could help you to disappear too.
Babysit the boy.
[Mo sighs]
[telephone rings]
Yes, hello?
[Zuko] Mike Bressler?
Mm-hmm. Speaking.
[Zuko] My name is Zuko Khumalo.
I've got something
that might interest you.
Where can we meet?
[lighter cap clicks]
[mysterious music plays]
Mike Bressler?
[chuckles dryly] Um...
Hi.
You know, this is, uh...
This is some real James Bond shit,
right? [chuckles]
Strong, silent type, hmm?
There are conditions.
Name them.
My...
My family...
I... I need to find them.
I, uh... I can help with that.
I believe you two need no introduction.
[tender music plays]
Iman.
Where's Malime?
I... I did my best, Zuko.
Where is Malime?
[voice breaks] It was an accident.
Where's Malime?!
Where is she?!
I trusted you. [sniffles]
Malime...
[exclaims]
[sobs]
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
[computer chimes]
[tense music plays]
[Mike] This is it.
This is how we finally take
that malicious motherfucker down.
His bank records,
email transcripts, messages.
- We have to get this to print tonight.
- No.
We have to get this out
before the State Capture report tomorrow.
Not until I find my son.
How much time do you need?
[Naledi] We lure Mo Kwena.
Go on.
Take the fight to Mtima.
Sever the head of the snake in its hole.
This is the cabin, isn't it?
You've kept tabs on Kwena?
[Naledi] Insurance.
Mo's been visiting
this location frequently of late.
That's Mtima's love nest,
his home base when he's in Cape Town.
This is how you make them
bring Pakamile to you.
How do I get in?
[heartbeat pulses quickly]
[lightning crashes]
Looks like it's going
to piss tonight, hmm?
Hmm. The boss is going to be quick...
- [blade swishing]
- [exclaims]
[eerie music plays]
- [blade swishing]
- [man groans]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[Zuko sighs]
[peppy house music plays on speakers]
[woman 1] Hey! Life is good.
- Hey, girl!
- [woman 2] Go, girl! Do that thing.
[music stops]
[ominous music plays]
[in Zulu] Get the hell out.
[Mtima, in English] Hey!
What happened to the music, guys?
[chuckles] What?
Are we playing hide-and-seek?
Papa... [groans]
[thuds]
[heart beats]
[exclaims]
Hey!
[in Xhosa] So, you've come in person.
[in English] Yeah.
[in Xhosa] Do you really think
you'll just walk out of here?
Tell me,
how do you want to die? Eh?
- Hey!
- [groans]
[in Zulu] Watch what you say.
It'll determine if you live or die.
[in Xhosa] Who do you think
you're threatening?
You're here for your son.
[thunder rumbles distantly]
Every warrior melts
when it comes to their family.
He melts.
So,
if you harm even one hair on my head,
you'll never see him again.
[in Zulu] You sure about that? Hmm?
Want to bet your life on that?
[in English] Relax, relax, relax.
[in Xhosa] We are men.
Men talk things through, right?
Let's talk then.
Talk bullshit.
[shutter clicks in camera app]
[buttons clack]
[line ringing]
[phone chimes]
[in English] Sir.
[in Zulu] Talk to her.
- [in English] He's here, Mo.
- Who?
Johnny's fucking errand boy.
[groans]
Bring me my son.
[Mo breathes heavily]
- [phone keypad clacks]
- [line ringing]
My brother...
you're a smart man.
[in Xhosa] Let's talk.
[in English] Let's say
you walk out of here...
[in Xhosa] with your son.
[in English] We can make you rich.
[in Xhosa] Get everything you want.
Every man has a price, right?
[in English] What is your price?
[in Zulu] Mtima...
there's nothing you can do for me.
You are a disgrace,
a traitor to your own people.
You indulge yourself,
getting fat
as you suck your people's land dry.
You are stuffed,
while our parents suffer in poverty.
We are not the same, Mtima.
Do you hear me?
We are not the same.
You are a parasite, a disease.
You sicken me!
You are an enemy to our ancestors.
I should cut your head off right now,
skin your hide, and hang you out to dry.
Do you hear me?
[in English] My offer still stands.
[in Xhosa] Take what we're offering you.
Laugh and grow fat with us.
[vehicle approaches]
[ominous music plays]
[groans]
[in Zulu] Thank your ancestors.
Go, go, go, go!
[thunder rumbles]
[guns fire in distance]
[in Afrikaans] Boonsaaier, come in.
[in English] Bravo Team, report!
I've got him. You go ahead.
- [blade swishes]
- [groans]
- [grunts]
- [yells]
Alpha Team, report!
[grunting]
[groans]
September, come in!
[in Afrikaans] Oh, fuck!
[in English] Where is she?
What took you so long?
[footsteps approach]
[lightning crashes]
[exclaims softly]
Untie me!
Just shoot him!
No!
[Mtima scoffs]
[grunts softly]
I've been looking forward to this.
[huffs]
[blades swishing]
[groans]
Come on!
[both grunting]
[groaning]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[both grunt]
[groans heavily]
- [Zuko exclaims]
- [grunts]
- Ah!
- Come on!
[groans]
- [grunts]
- [yells]
[both grunting]
[yells]
[groans]
[Zuko coughs]
[groaning]
I'll tell your boy
you put up a good fight.
[thunder rumbles]
[both grunting]
[yells]
- [cracks]
- [yells]
[grunts]
[groans weakly]
[Zuko grunts]
Where's my son?
[Paka] Zuko!
[menacing music plays]
Paka?
Paka!
The spear, drop it!
He's just a boy.
The files! Hand over the files!
The files go to print tomorrow.
It's over!
[Mtima] Ah-ah!
[in Xhosa] Go ahead, Mo!
[in English] We say when it's over.
[in Xhosa] Shoot.
[lightning crashes]
- Mo!
- [Zuko, in English] Come, come!
- [Mo] Hey!
- Hey, hey, hey.
The punishment for treason
is death, comrade.
You don't have to do this!
[in Xhosa] Shut up, you dog!
[in English] Comrade...
[in Xhosa] Go ahead with your mission.
[in English] You need to prove to us...
[in Xhosa] that you aren't
like your father
who died a traitor.
[in English] It's over!
[groans]
[epic ominous music plays]
Just let us go!
You know too much.
You good?
[grunts]
Iman!
[musical swell plays and rises]
- Move!
- [groans]
[continues groaning]
Come on. Come on.
[grunts]
[Zuko] Iman!
[yells]
Iman. Iman!
Come.
- [Tiger groans]
- [Zuko] Paka!
Come on. Come on.
[ethereal, droning music plays]
[heart beating]
[music stops]
[news anchor] In your top story
this afternoon,
authorities are still no closer
to naming suspects
in the alleged assassinations
of disgraced presidential hopeful,
Daza Mtima,
and Presidential Intelligence Agency
Director, Molebogeng Kwena.
This follows
the bombshell Cape Sentinel report
that has since led to a spate
of high-profile arrests and resignations
in the wake of new evidence
being submitted
- to a parliamentary commission of...
- [radio clicks off]
This is where I grew up
when I was a boy like you.
See that?
That's the Great Fish River.
Our farm is just over there
on the Cata River.
Will we have real cows?
Not yet,
but we will.
You promise?
Promise.
[gentle bittersweet music plays]
[musical arrangement turns sweeping]
[menacing music plays]
[dramatic classical music plays]
[ethereal vocal music plays]
[percussive chanting music plays]
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/m4jnn
Help other users to choose the best subtitles