Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Forgive me, Father.
Where were you?
With a friend. Joséphine.
Joséphine? Who is she?
I've never heard of her.
You don't know her.
Bless this meal,
and those who made it,
that those who have nothing
may receive.
Amen.
Saying grace amuses you, Théophile?
No.
I won't be here tomorrow.
There's the De Beyles' debate.
Good. You can better yourself.
France needs intelligent men.
And me?
Once you join your father's office,
your high society friends
will be invaluable.
A good job,
a good marriage...
It's all I want for you.
I doubt he'll find a wife
at a salon debate.
Can I come too?
I've never been to a salon debate.
With the De Beyles?
Yes, if you'd like to.
Out of the question.
Who are you?
You frightened me.
I won't be long.
See you soon, my dear.
No, it's fine like that.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, my dear.
Eugénie.
Tell me...
You were really at the funeral
of this Victor Hugo,
weren't you?
Yes, Grandmother.
It was incredible. Such a crowd.
I'm sure there was.
You can go, now.
Yes...
-Wait...
-I know...
You never know...
Later.
Another night.
When can I see you?
No, Eugénie, no!
Father said no, and so do I.
I am not taking you to this debate.
What if he found out?
A girl like you, there?
Everyone would notice you.
They would gossip...
Will you shut up?
I don't give a damn about your debate.
Talking to you and your friends
for hours?
I'd rather die!
Drop me at the café, on the way.
I need to take the air, read, smoke...
Please, Théo!
-But if Father...
-What about him? He's not here.
Louis, let's go. To Montmartre.
Yes, ma'am.
Montmartre?
You're not serious? Montmartre?
Remember: I didn't bring you,
I don't know you,
and you'll get home on your own.
What?
Nothing. Just looking at you.
And?
You're handsome.
Don't be silly.
I have a scrawny neck, no shoulders,
long legs, a short torso...
So, no, I'm not handsome.
Well, I think you are.
Like I said.
You're a silly little girl.
I know.
Hello. One brioche, please.
Five centimes.
Thank you.
Poor old Rémi. Here's to you.
Tomorrow, at dawn,
at the moment when the land whitens
I will leave.
You see, I know
that you are waiting for me.
You're reading Contemplations?
I love that part.
And when I arrive,
I will put on your grave
A bouquet of green holly
and heather in bloom.
Is that right?
May I sit here?
Yes, it's Contemplations.
But you can't sit here.
I'd like to be alone. I'm reading.
Thank you.
Sorry for any misunderstanding.
I thought you were looking at me.
You don't often see
a girl reading poetry
turning to look at a man
who's also reading...
I wasn't looking at you.
I see.
Well...
I'll go, then.
I was looking at your book.
You were?
Then you were looking at me.
No!
You were! Because
I was holding the book.
I was holding it.
I was right here, behind it.
It was your book I was looking at.
"Man is made of three things.
Firstly, the body, the material being,
similar to an animal,
and animated by the same life force.
Secondly, the soul.
The spirit that the body contains.
Thirdly...
The connection between body and soul."
You weren't looking at my body
but at my soul.
Forgive me.
It appears I've upset you.
No.
Not at all.
I liked it.
I liked it very much.
Here.
For you.
I can't accept this.
I'm lending it to you.
You can give it back.
Promise?
I promise.
Thank you.
What's that?
More poetry?
"The Spirits Book."
Really?
With a little note from Ernest!
Looks like my sister
is making some lovely friends.
No!
Eugénie Cléry,
slumming it in Montmartre!
You lost my page.
Your friends don't have a monopoly
on the life of the spirit.
You'd be surprised who you meet
in the cafés of north Paris.
I bet I would.
Can I stay a little more?
Yes, but in silence.
Will you be seeing him again?
-Who?
Ernest. The poet.
Who sends ladies' hearts a-flutter...
Your hands are cold.
It may be too late
for me to shine on the battlefield
but I've helped our country
make progress with order and justice.
This Legion of Honour
will be a blessing for our practice.
I'll do my best
to pass on your request...
-You seem happy, Hortense.
-Yes.
I'm making my society début.
I'll be presented next month
at the Duchesse de Noailles's ball.
Presented, like a horse at market?
Will they check your teeth?
Congratulations, what will you wear?
An evening gown from Doucet.
-Silk.
-I have no doubt you'll look beautiful.
Is that what you think of me, Eugénie?
That I'm some doll?
It's not what my sister meant,
quite the contrary.
Apologies, Hortense,
I didn't mean to offend you.
I find it degrading, that's all.
-But I'm not judging.
-You are!
That's exactly what you're doing!
Hortense...
What did you do and say now?
-You always have to embarrass me.
-Father, I didn't want to...
Not another word.
My career and our name are at stake.
Think a little, you fool.
Thank you, Marthe.
My pleasure, Lady Eugénie.
Forward.
No, go back.
To the right. Careful, Louis!
To the right. No, the other right.
-It's heavy, Eugénie!
-There.
-Here?
-Yes.
Would you agree
that it's in exactly the same place?
Yes, I would totally agree.
Let's go find the decorations.
OK.
Where are he ribbons?
They're in the large trunk at the back.
-This one?
-Yes.
How can I get to it?
Could you help me?
This one...
Eugénie, come help me, I can't do it.
Eugénie?
I'm here.
Stay with me.
Tell me what I can do.
It's over. It's over...
What a fright you gave me.
Was it him again?
No, it wasn't him.
What do you mean?
I see others.
They're all different.
For the last few days,
a young woman's been speaking to me.
She's suffering.
If only you could see her.
She's asking for my help,
but I don't know how.
I feel so useless.
Brother...
I read that book,
that marvelous book
that made everything clear to me.
Talk to me, say something.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of those things,
you know I am.
That book told me that I'm not alone,
that spirits are real.
Everything's OK.
For the first time,
I'm not scared of who I am anymore.
What if you see others?
I know what happens to girls like you.
Girls like me?
I was waiting for that one!
-It is still your turn.
-Yes, it is my lucky day.
Eugénie, sit up straight.
Thank you, Marthe.
Eugénie.
What's the matter?
Darling, you're scaring me.
What's wrong?
What's going on? Stop, will you?
Stop.
Stop!
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
It's a miracle.
How is this possible?
I lost this 40 years ago.
It was an engagement gift
from your grandfather.
I thought...
I thought that our maid at the time
had stolen it.
How did you know?
I don't know.
Tell me.
Eugénie...
How did you know? Tell me, poppet.
Grandfather's the one who told me.
Eugénie...
You were right
to confide in me.
Thank you.
Hello, Mother.
Is everything OK?
Your father wants to take you to Meudon
for a second chance
with the Prevost-Roumagnacs.
And if Hortense
shows you her gown
for the Noailles Ball,
try to muster up some enthusiasm.
No scandals, no tantrums.
Pull it together.
Yes, Mother.
You're crying.
Mother...
I promise I'll be on my best behavior.
I promise I won't let you down.
Eugénie...
sit up straight, please.
Where are we?
I don't recognize the...
No, not that.
Not that. Not that, please.
Théophile...
Théophile!
Not the Salpêtrière asylum!
Théophile, not Salpêtrière.
Please.
No, I'm not sick. No, not that!
Not that, please!
Théophile!
No, please...
Please, not that. Not that.
No, not that!
Théo! Théo!
Not that!
Father!
Please... Théo! Théo!
DECEMBER 18, 1885
Have you calmed down?
I'm going to examine you,
tell me if I hurt you.
Open your mouth.
All good.
You're healthy.
I don't belong here.
That's not up to you.
It's up to your father - well, it was.
Now it's up to Dr. Charcot,
that's how it is.
Get dressed.
Take her to the dormitory.
If she causes a ruckus,
put her in cell.
That always gets the newbies going.
Give it back. Come back right now.
Julie!
Give it back! Thief.
Thief!
Here's your bed, Cléry.
Stop!
Shoo! Go on, shoo!
Go away.
Hi.
I'm Louise.
Eugénie Cléry.
Well, well,
aren't you all dressed up, Eugénie?
Damn, guys, a toff!
We don't often get ladies around here.
We're bed neighbors, that's good.
I'm a lady too, didn't you know?
I'm engaged.
-Are you engaged?
-No.
Really?
But you're so beautiful.
You must have lots of suitors.
Love just isn't fair.
That's why I'm lucky.
My man's handsome,
and he's not just anyone,
he's a doctor!
That's right,
I'm going to be high society too!
You do believe me? It's true.
Have you chosen your outfit?
-What outfit?
-For the ball.
You're a funny one.
For the mid-Lent ball!
I'm going to go for a Spanish style
with a mantilla, a flounce,
a dress that spins, gloves,
the whole shebang!
Do you know what I picture for you?
You'll look pretty!
And we'll find you a fiancé.
You'll see, you'll be Eugénie Cléry,
the belle of the ball!
Don't listen to her, she's a nutcase.
Suzanne, sit down!
She arrived 2 months ago.
She hasn't said a word,
but I'm sure she can talk.
Don't push me.
It's Marguerite.
She's never happy.
And don't look at me that way.
Henriette,
the one getting up, is depressed,
which, for me, isn't an illness.
They also call women
who stare into space for hours sick.
Then there's Therese.
She pushed her husband
into the Seine in a jealous rage.
She's been here 25 years,
knitting for the girls.
On the left is Denise.
I don't know what her illness is,
but she's nuts.
But don't worry, they're not mean.
What's your illness?
What's yours?
My aunt found me on the floor
flipping out one day.
I didn't want her husband on me.
I told her and she screamed at me.
She sent me here,
to get rid of me.
I dream of him forcing me to look
in his pants and a snake coming out.
It's pretty scary.
But when I wake up,
I'm here with another oaf.
Imagine if I'd never met Jules.
Life works out pretty well.
Up you get.
It's time, Louise.
-How's it going this morning?
-Fine.
I hope I'll be good.
Yes, as per usual.
Come on, up.
Outside.
Was that Charcot?
We've never seen Master Charcot here.
Marguerite...
-Get up.
-No!
-Hurry up.
-Leave me alone!
I want to sleep.
Right, hello, gentlemen, hello.
Introducing a patient
with acute symptomatic hysteria.
I will therefore proceed
to the hypnotic stage
and will require
the greatest attention and silence.
Thank you.
Louise, you will listen to my voice.
Nothing but my voice.
You're listening to my voice
and your eyelids are getting heavy.
Your eyes are closing.
Don't fight it, Louise.
Your eyelids are closing.
All you can hear is my voice.
And now, Louise,
go to sleep. Sleep.
Stretch your arms in front of you.
Very good, Louise.
Now touch your stomach.
Touch your chest, Louise.
Touch your throat, Louise.
Graze your chin, Louise.
Touch your mouth, Louise.
Open your lips, Louise.
Touch your lips, Louise.
Louise,
clasp your hands out in front of you.
Louise.
Clasp your hands out.
Silence.
See you all next Tuesday.
That feels good.
Does that feel good?
You want some help?
-I have a headache.
-That's normal.
You did very well.
Dr. Charcot is very happy.
Thank you, Miss Gleizes.
I'll leave my assessment report
on your desk.
Very well, Doctor.
Julie.
Louise needs to rest.
I'll take care of her.
Alone.
I'm tired, Jules.
I know.
You were wonderful.
You're so pretty, my darling Louise.
-I'm not your Louise.
-Yes, you are.
You say that to all the girls.
I only say it to you.
I want to marry you, Louise.
You know that. I already told you.
When will you propose to me?
-Soon, my darling, soon.
-But when?
At the ball.
-But it's a long way away.
-No, it's not.
It's not, Louisette...
It'll go quickly when we're engaged.
I love you.
What are you doing, Jules?
I don't know.
It's your fault.
I love you so much, Louise.
I love you so much.
-That's not the right time, is it?
-It is, Ms. Geneviève.
See you soon.
It's me, Father.
I hope so,
I've been waiting for you for an hour.
Apologies, I got held up.
I'm in a hurry, I'm late.
You're always late.
I was always late too.
I never started a meal on time,
but I always finished it early.
At this morning's Lesson,
Louise had an extraordinary fit.
She fell to the ground,
writhing and tensed up.
She didn't look human anymore.
Opisthotonos?
Under hypnosis.
Epilepsy perhaps?
Charcot may be triggering nerve activity
during his sessions.
That would explain the hysteria.
Are you a neurologist now, Dr. Gleizes?
Well, my child, if I were
to go back to studying medicine now,
that's what I would choose
to specialize in: Salpêtrière.
We'd work together
and you would assist.
We'd have lunch every afternoon,
and you'd use the time
to report back to me.
Charcot should rely on you.
You're the one who knows the girls.
There's a new girl.
What's she like?
She's...
Intense.
"Intense" isn't a symptom.
Everything OK, Eugénie?
Great, ma'am.
You can call me Geneviève.
Very well, ma'am.
I'm not staying here for much longer.
I told you, it's not up to you.
Yes, it's up to you.
And you're going to help me.
OK.
We'll go see the doctors tomorrow.
Bl...
Blan...
Are you having a seizure?
Blandine.
Is Blandine your sister?
Stop or it's ether for you.
She's a redhead, right?
If you think you'll get out like that...
You all call me crazy,
but how come you write
thousands of letters to your sister?
Is it because
you think she can hear you?
As well you do believe in spirits,
she hears you.
She watches you too, you know.
Do you want to talk to her?
She's here.
In the room.
-She's ready to listen to you.
-Shut up.
Shut up.
Cléry?
-Are you sleeping?
-No.
Are you feeling better?
I dunno.
You know...
What?
I'm really glad that you're next to me.
That makes us bed sisters.
Hey, Louise.
What will you do when you get out?
When I get out...
I don't know.
I would go pig out in Les Halles.
And then...
Then I'd go to a dive bar!
You think dive bars
will still be around?
No danger of them closing.
Then...
I'd go to the boulevard
and nick wallets off the toffs.
-How will you do, you wily fox?
-What are you talking about?
I was the best pickpocket around.
Goldfinger, they used to call me.
I'd find my husband, stab him slowly,
and watch him bleed out.
Luckily, you're not due to leave yet.
I'd take a nice hot bath,
like rich people do.
With hot water and clean towels.
White and clean.
Laudanum every night.
One tablespoon on Mondays and Fridays,
two on the other nights.
Cléry Eugénie, 26 years old,
parents in good health.
Young brother in good health.
No medical history.
Claims to talk to the dead.
Her father had her committed.
Is it true that you talk to the dead?
Answer my question.
I don't talk to the dead.
-Well...
-They're spirits.
I didn't ask for this, it just happened.
Hearing spirits isn't the norm,
young lady.
We accept that a young girl
saw the Virgin in Lourdes.
That doesn't bother anyone.
So what? That has nothing to do with it.
Why is it acceptable to believe in God
and not in spirits?
Why her and not me?
I'm asking you a question:
why her and not me?
Calm down.
I'll do so if I want.
It doesn't say that you're seeing God,
you're seeing the dead.
-If you believe everything...
-Enough. I've heard enough.
Treatment two. Hydrotherapy.
Fifteen days.
Don't touch me.
-Let's go.
-Don't touch me.
Don't touch me!
Let go of my arm!
Hysterical.
No doubt at all.
I'm calm.
I'm calm now.
I'm calm...
You don't need to do this!
I'm calm!
-Come on.
-No!
What's going on here?
Please... Please!
Out you come.
-Geneviève Gleizes?
-Who are you?
Hello, ma'am.
Don't be afraid.
My name is Théophile Cléry.
I want to know how my sister is.
I can't tell you anything.
Can you give her this book, please?
-The rules forbid it.
-Please.
Please!
Please.
Thank you, ma'am.
It seemed like the right thing.
Honestly.
I thought I was helping her.
You'll help her, won't you?
Goodbye, Mr Cléry.
Don't worry.
Your body will get used to it.
Don't worry, dear, I'll help you.
Here, like this.
Here.
Move over,
it's going to splash everywhere.
Ms. Geneviève.
Your brother gave me a book for you.
You saw Théophile?
How is he?
Well, I imagine.
He asked after you.
I have one thing to ask you
in return for the book.
What book?
The Book of Spirits.
Have you read it?
Yes.
I'd like...
to speak to my sister.
Ma'am, I'd rather forego the book
and take my freedom.
You know that's impossible.
Then so is speaking to your sister.
Very well.
I'll ask the doctor.
But only if I can speak to my sister.
-Thank you.
-I'll let you know when.
Berthe came back totally crushed.
I don't know how long
she was in there - 8, 10 days?
With Jeanne? At least 2 weeks.
It leaves its mark.
You know,
sometimes I think
she makes them like that.
Too bad.
Isolation is what they need.
You mean the dungeon.
All right, Geneviève?
You look tired. Good thing
they're not photographing you.
Ready, Peltier?
Yes, Master.
-You're late, Geneviève.
-Forgive me, Master.
Give Marie's file to the photographer
for the archives.
Hystero-epilepsy and spasms.
I'll need the last 6 months' photos
for an Academy presentation.
It's the only way
to get their attention.
Yes, Master.
Keep still, Marie.
Shoot.
"The angel of the Lord appeared
"and the Lord's glory
"shone all around."
And the sons dug for days on end,
and the whole village believed.
"I have come
"to bring you good news.
And after a month of excavation,
the house fell down!
Merry Christmas.
"And suddenly with the angel
"there was a heavenly host."
My mother
Has eyes that kill
I like her hands on my body
I like the smell under her arms
Yes
That's the way I am
In my mother's eyes
There is always light
I always find love
In my mother's eyes
There is always light
My mother always listens to me
When I'm in the shit
She knows when I'm stupid and feeble
And when I'm bloated like a whale
She knows when my feet stink
She knows when I'm naked
And when I'm sick
She's the queen of the suppository
In my mother's eyes
There is always light
My little one!
Still nothing?
No.
Anything we can do?
Nothing.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Hurry up.
-You've been lying from the start.
-No.
Enough.
Get up.
Stop, Eugénie.
Eugénie?
She's here.
-She's here?
-Yes.
-Is she speaking to you?
She doesn't want...
-She doesn't want what?
-Not now.
She doesn't want to now.
She can't...
-Can't what?
-She doesn't have time.
What are you saying?
-It's your father!
-My father?
Something's happened to your father
in the kitchen.
Go now! Hurry!
Father?
You stupid woman!
Heaven sent you, my little girl...
Don't talk.
What miracle brought you here?
How did you know?
I was suddenly worried about you.
That's good.
It's good to think of your poor father.
Yes, it is.
Now rest.
Not very good, is it?
Good isn't the word, no.
It's not good!
But it's good to hear you laugh.
How did you know?
Why did you come?
I told you, I felt it.
Is it so important?
You don't just "feel" such things.
It doesn't exist.
Tell me.
Blandine told me.
Don't mention that name, please.
A new girl has arrived.
She talks to spirits.
With Blandine.
How can you believe such a thing?
I raised you to respect science,
and you tell me this nonsense!
Aren't you ashamed?
I didn't believe it, either.
But Blandine talks to her.
I was there.
How could I have known otherwise?
She's among us,
maybe even here in this room.
Blandine's dead.
Do you hear me?
Dead!
I visit her grave every day.
I know you blame yourself, but still...
She's looking out for us.
Be quiet!
You're talking like a witch!
And to me!
You talk to me about spirits and ghosts!
I don't want to hear any more.
Father...
It's you I'm losing now,
my girl.
Those women have sent you mad.
It's contagious!
It's a plague.
Leave me now.
Dad...
Go!
Please.
Cheese soufflé!
Roast chicken!
Rabbit breast.
Bread and butter.
-Rabbit with truffles.
-Rum baba!
Pancakes with jelly.
-It's time to go.
-Please, no.
What? Come on.
I did it not long ago.
I went last week.
Don't make a fuss, Henriette.
It's just that it still hurts.
-Come with us.
-Come on, Henriette.
Can't we do it another day?
That's not possible.
-Come on.
-No, please!
Don't make us call the doctors.
-Can't it wait till tomorrow?
-No.
Sir?
I'd like to discuss the clinical trials.
It seems that...
Stop moving.
Ovaries swollen...
and painful.
Increase the bloodletting
to twice a day.
What's happening?
Eugénie!
Doctor! What's happening to me?
What happened?
An attack under hypnosis:
lateral hemiphlegia, right side.
What is it, doctor?
Why can't I move?
My hand!
-My leg!
-No reaction, fascinating.
Eugénie!
-What's happening?
-Don't you see, Louise?
It's them!
You're what's happening to her!
It's you!
You're doing it!
You're driving her mad!
Shut her up.
Oh, yes!
Shut me up, doctor!
Ether.
Go on, shut me up!
Because I know everything.
I can tell you everything!
What you're doing to us...
The Master is waiting for you.
You're too late, Miss Gleizes,
once again.
Forgive me, Master.
I was tending to my father.
Your father's not interned here.
Watch over my patients instead.
Of course.
I just saw Louise. She's calmer.
I left her to rest.
Good.
We'll try magnet therapy next week.
And the others?
Denise Platel. Feeding herself
but still refuses to speak.
Aphasia. What treatment ?
Valerian and ether by uterine catheter.
One less dose of ether a day.
Is that all?
Not quite.
There's Eugénie Cléry.
-What are your plans?
-Isolation.
She's dangerous.
I don't want her to contaminate
the weaker ones.
Fine. I'll take care of it.
No, not you.
Jeanne.
Jeanne will take care of it.
Tonight.
Goodbye, Miss Gleizes.
Goodbye, Master.
Follow me.
This is it.
The old Salpêtrière cells.
They're historic, Eugénie.
You're very lucky, you know.
Be calm.
Be calm. Everything will be fine.
You must breathe, Eugénie.
We're going to get on very well.
I'm going to keep an eye on you.
And when you get out,
you'll be a different woman.
You'll see.
Ms. Geneviève?
Yes, Louise?
When is my friend coming back?
I don't know.
It's not right, Ms. Geneviève.
She's a lady.
A real lady.
We're treated worse than animals.
Louise,
you must think about getting well.
Eugénie must be scared
down there alone.
Hello Adèle, how are we today?
I dreamt about you last night.
You were the Devil.
But I wasn't afraid.
It was ugly, pathetic.
It was you.
Because the Devil is in you, isn't he?
Vade retro satana!
Eugénie!
Do you know the eclipse game?
You'll love it!
No! Not the light!
-When did it happen?
-Yesterday.
She hurt me.
It's the third time this week.
-Maybe I did something bad.
-No.
Time to eat.
Bon appétit.
It's Geneviève.
You were right about my father.
Blandine was right.
I'm going to help you.
I'll be back, I promise.
Speak. Who's there?
What happened?
Please. Please...
Stop that... Stop that.
Stop!
How are you, Eugénie?
I don't think you're very well.
I've seen others like you,
who just give up.
But I don't want you to.
You have to eat.
I bought these in rue Bruand.
Do you know it?
No,
of course you don't.
Want one?
You're like your ghosts.
That's what they're like, isn't it?
Sad and pallid.
It'd be so much easier for you
if you didn't see them.
You poor thing.
I can help you.
I think...
-I think...
-Well!
Yes!
It's good to think.
What do you think?
I think it's your mother.
Leave my mother alone,
and keep your games for the others.
Yes.
She says she's your mother.
She forgives you
for what you did to her.
What did you do to her?
Did you lock her up in here?
She was here.
You're saying nothing new.
Everyone knows my mother was mad.
So what?
No-one knows what she did.
To your son.
François?
Is that right?
François!
She asks your forgiveness.
You shut up!
You shut up, bitch!
You've no right!
You've no right to talk!
You witch!
Ms. Jeanne!
There are fleas in my mattress,
I'm bleeding, look!
-I can't see anything.
-Look!
-There!
-I see nothing!
-Are you doing this to get ether?
-No, Ms. Jeanne.
Go back to the others.
If it takes all day, I guarantee
that I'll find that key!
If you've anything to say, say it now!
Are you sure you lost it here?
Ms. Geneviève.
She's here.
Really?
She says she's happy
to speak to you.
She thanks you for the letters.
But she wants you to stop.
She wants
you to be light...
and happy.
Your letters make her sad.
She doesn't need them
to feel loved.
She misses you.
I miss her too.
I miss her so much!
She's no longer suffering.
She's not afraid.
She wants the same for you.
She's looking over you.
She's in a woman's smile,
a sick woman's laugh,
the hands that you nurse,
the eyes that you reassure.
She's all around you.
Everywhere.
She forgives you.
She's gone.
Thank you.
I see you found my key.
Give it to me.
Eugénie Cléry is weak and anemic.
I'm going to tell Dr Charcot
immediately.
I'm going to release her.
Of course, Ms. Head Nurse.
Please go ahead.
-Master?
-Yes?
It's about Eugénie Cléry.
She's been isolation for a month
and has made real progress.
-Only...
-What?
She won't eat, doctor.
She's very weak.
I fear she'll have a stroke.
-Is she still hostile?
-No, she's calm.
She lacks the strength and the will.
She spoke rationally.
That's good.
Jeanne did the right thing.
I'd like to return her to the ward.
Isn't that a little premature?
I'll take responsibility.
I'm responsible for my patients,
Miss Gleizes.
If there is any trouble,
I will blame you.
Tell Jeanne to transfer her.
You won't regret it.
Geneviève,
empty the chamber pots,
I can smell them from here.
Yes, Master.
Paper! Le Petit Parisien!
What a day!
Have a good evening, ladies.
You're coming out tomorrow.
Wash yourself.
Open.
Hello, Louise.
Eugénie!
It's you!
It's nice to see you.
Was it hard in isolation?
How are you?
Me?
That's a joke!
My dress turns but I can't!
Unlucky.
Keep going.
That's it.
Put that in reception.
Julie, the plants,
that alcove, that one
and that one.
Pascal, put the candlesticks upstairs
and at reception.
Hello, gentlemen.
Head to the third floor balcony.
Don't tussle.
Gently! Gently!
-That's nice.
-Does it suit me?
What a beautiful wig.
It's so soft!
She has a horn!
Is that all right?
Don't touch that!
I haven't chosen my costume!
Go away!
-Thérèse?
-Yes?
Will you come to the ball?
No, I never go.
It's my only night of peace.
I don't want to spend it
with those old crocs.
Don't exaggerate!
-There are young men, too.
-They're all the same.
You'll see, Eugénie.
Well dressed or in rags,
in two hours you won't know
who's mad and who isn't.
I'm staying here.
Marguerite, calm down
or they won't let you go.
They're lovely.
-Your coat, sir?
-No, thank you.
Have a good evening.
Look, he's so handsome!
In your place, Eugénie.
Good evening, Jeanne.
Good evening, Master.
Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
Welcome to the Salpêtrière Hospital
and to our annual ball.
The nurses, the doctors,
Dr Charcot and I
are delighted and honored
to welcome you once again.
The women patients
you are about to see
are interesting in several ways.
Fascinating, even.
Some are psychotic,
others are compulsive liars.
maniacs, melancholics
or simply idiotic.
Their illnesses are often indiscernible
and could be missed
during a general medical examination.
But they are all real, diagnosed
and identified here
thanks to new methods
in research and teaching.
But what unites them
is that they are all patients of
the finest French scientist of our age.
I give you
Dr Jean-Martin
Charcot!
Now I'd like you to welcome
our main attraction.
Ladies, over to you.
Goodbye, Jeanne.
Oh, thank you, thank you!
-I'm sorry, sister.
-It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
-Sorry.
-Everything's fine.
Let me take off your make-up.
What's this then? Here.
Want some?
Go ahead.
It's nice.
What are you?
A little gypsy.
It's good, isn't it?
You're a little thief.
Let's see your hands.
What's the matter?
Tired from dancing?
You have to come.
Why are we here?
Jules!
Why have you brought me here?
So, my little kitty...
We're getting married tonight!
You're already my wife, aren't you?
Say it!
Say you're already my wife!
Wait...
Louise Plessis,
do you take Jules Lemoine
as your lawfully wedded husband?
Not like this!
Come here, my love!
Give me your mouth!
-Eugénie Cléry!
-Let her go.
Let her go!
Help!
Be quiet.
Be quiet!
-Help!
-"Help, help!"
-Louis is waiting.
-Here?
No, in front.
Get off!
You crook!
You beast!
You bastard!
Help!
Get off me!
Stop! Help!
There they are!
Geneviève, no!
-No, I won't leave you!
-Listen to me.
Go.
I'm free.
Hurry!
Stop them!
You're mad!
It's hard to know who's mad tonight,
Jeanne.
"My dear Geneviève.
"I think of you all the time.
"Here freedom is beautiful,
"but it has a bitter taste:
that of your sacrifice.
"I try to honor you
"and, as you asked me,
to do good.
"I provide help, support, evidence
and comfort.
"The trust and love shown me
overwhelm me every day.
"No-one here is scared of me.
"Here I am understood.
For you.
"Geneviève, my dear friend,
"last night your Blandine came to me.
"She is protecting you, she is with you
and she loves you, as do I.
"If your body is still there
in that ward I know so well,
"know that your heart
and spirit are here,
"close to me.
"I imagine you sitting reading this.
"But I won't let you finish.
"I take you... by the hand.
"We take a few steps.
"The wind is cool and salty.
"The horizon is far. So far.
"Can you feel it?
"Our souls dance on the waves
and our pains fly away,
"swirling,
and vanish in a cloud of spray.
"We laugh.
"Our feet in the air.
"We dance.
"And so,
my dear Geneviève,
"we are free.
"We are strong.
"We are eternal.
"Your Eugénie."
THE MAD WOMAN'S BALL
Subtitles: David Buchanan,
Jessica Hinds-Mingo, Geoff Rowlands