Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
EVERYONE ON SET TESTED NEGATIVE
FOR COVID-19
ALL PREVENTIVE MEASURES WERE TAKEN
The Sense Coach.
LEE SU-GEUN, THE SENSE COACH
I've never felt this way before.
Let's go. The Sense Coach.
LEE SU-GEUN
Gosh.
I heard this spot was quiet.
I didn't expect to hear applause.
I guess it's not so quiet here, after all.
Let's see.
The water looks clean.
The fish aren't bad either.
But they're not moving very much.
They're all fixed in place.
Is it because the weather is still cold?
What have I got here?
I heard fish go nuts over these.
I'm sure this will do. Look at this.
I paid 680,000 won for this.
All right. Let's see what will nibble.
There's one. It seems interested.
Yes, come on.
It's reacting to the bait.
It's nibbling at it.
Gosh. This is it.
Hold on.
Yes! Come on!
It took the bait! It took it!
Darn, it stole my bait.
I can't believe he took off
with just the bait.
I'm sure he knows he has to return it.
All right. Let's see here.
What have I caught today? I caught a lot.
This one's still alive. What is this?
A sea bass. My goodness.
It's still alive. Unbelievable.
I caught a shark in fresh water?
A halibut, a salmon, a sea bass…
What's this? What the heck?
I even caught some English letters.
Look at this. A Super Junior.
It's a Super Junior member.
You like this kind of joke?
What's this, then?
I've never caught
anything like this before. What is this?
Do I just put it on like this?
Testing.
NongMill Kim!
NONGMILL KIM
-Hello!
The Sense Coach
He'll coach your senses
Shut your mouths and get in line
The Sense Coach
Here to give you advice
I'm a master
With 20 years of experience
Everyone is surprised
Everyone is speechless
Me trying out hip-hop
Makes other rappers salty
Su-geun got my back
Even got me on Netflix
Foreign fans busy translating
Makes me a proud K
Professor Lee shares his wisdom
Hurry up and take notes
Me and my role model's dream
Has finally come true
Hey, bro
Tell me what to do
Listen up now
Hey, bro
Give me some advice
Hello, everyone
You should greet them first
The Sense Coach
He'll coach your senses
Shut your mouths and get in line
The Sense Coach
NongMill Kim!
When I say, "sense," you say, "coach."
-Sense!
-Coach!
Despite the pandemic,
NongMill Kim came
all the way here to help me.
He even got tested for COVID-19.
My nose hurt like crazy.
Please give it up for him.
-Thank you. This has been NongMill Kim.
-NongMill Kim!
You'll soon be performing all over Europe.
Netflix, just you wait!
People from 190 countries
are watching you right now.
A lot of people are watching this.
Anyway, it's time to get started.
Welcome to Lee Su-geun, the Sense Coach.
Set the stage!
TRANSFORMING INTO THE SENSE COACH
IS ANYONE CLUELESS ENOUGH
TO NOT BE CLAPPING RIGHT NOW?
Hello. Welcome, everyone.
-Hello.
All right. I'm Lee Su-geun.
The global company, Netflix, told me
that they have some money to spend.
That's why I dressed up like this.
I'm wearing a gold tracksuit.
It's 18K gold.
Check out this necklace.
What does it say? I think it's rented.
Whatever.
Also, I'm wearing a gold whistle
since I'm a coach.
Nice. Isn't it great?
Anyway… What's this? Take this away.
Take this away already.
Where are your senses?
Take it. How could you forget?
What are you doing?
Who are you?
-Goodness.
-Who are you?
-It's Park Sung-kwang.
-Hello.
PARK SUNG-KWANG
I'm flexing my crew.
-There's a celebrity in the crew.
-Hold on.
Why are you wearing a mic?
-I thought I was doing this with you.
-I was surprised to see you.
-You were?
-But when you tripped for no reason,
I knew you were a comedian.
I was told to take the bucket,
-but as a comedian, I had to do something.
-Good job.
The next comedy show should be yours.
-Me?
-Yes.
Then the viewers would think
all Korean comedians are short.
-You and I are both short.
-Then…
Someone tall should do it before me.
Then it's not stand-up comedy.
-It's sit-down comedy.
-Exactly.
What's the point? It makes no difference.
Right. It would be sit-down comedy.
Anyway, thank you so much.
-Thank you, Sung-kwang.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy the show!
-All right.
-See you.
-Okay.
Take the bucket and cap with you.
How is this different from Gag Concert?
-Sorry.
-Europeans will be shocked.
-I'm sorry.
-This is stand-up comedy.
-It should be high-quality.
-Yes, stand-up comedy.
-You can leave now.
-Okay.
-Sit back and enjoy.
-I will.
Thank you so much,
NongMill and Sung-kwang.
Stand-up comedy shows
usually have a bigger audience.
You all even got tested for COVID-19
to come and see me.
-Aren't your seats comfortable?
-Yes.
Then I guess you won't be laughing a lot.
I'm on many TV shows these days.
I took up fishing recently.
I first learned to fish on the show,
The Fishermen and the City.
Fishing skills aren't anything special.
You just need to have a feel for it.
When a fish is nibbling,
just notice it and reel it in.
If Kyung-kyu yells at you
for catching all the fish yourself,
just stop catching them.
Then he stops complaining.
He becomes quiet again.
You have to take a hint.
There is a type of fish
called the barbel steed.
Do you know it? Its name sounds
just like the Korean word for "sense."
You can see it on the screen. Cool, right?
Only our show can do this.
It looks like this.
It's actually a dialectal variant.
It's often caught in fresh water,
and it's pretty strong.
This fish just refuses to take a hint.
It has a lot of bones
and a really strong fishy smell.
Once you touch it,
your hands smell fishy for days.
So when people catch it, they swear at it,
making it feel uncomfortable.
Instead of moving its mouth,
it glances at you.
That's what it does.
The reason I brought this up
is because this fish is just like me.
Not that I have many bones,
smell a lot, or am unpopular.
I'm over 40 now,
and for most of my life,
I've walked on eggshells around people.
Do you know who makes me
walk on eggshells the most?
-Kang Ho-dong.
You guys answered right away.
Everybody seems to know.
It's Kang Ho-dong.
While I'm a mere barbel steed,
he is an intimidating amberjack
that's longer than one meter.
It's massive.
When you try to reel in this fish,
it feels like it yells at you.
"Let me go!"
You can almost hear that. It's that big.
Recently, I caught an amberjack
that was longer than a meter.
It was huge. That's what I caught.
It was on the Christmas special episode.
Reeling it in was really exhausting.
Ho-dong is the amberjack of variety shows.
Not just a regular amberjack,
but a deadly one.
His power and strength are no joke.
I first met him on the show,
2 Days & 1 Night.
-Two Days!
-One Night!
You're supposed to say, "Two Days."
Everyone will know
this was shot in Korea now.
As you all know,
everyone on the show was amazing
and they all achieved stardom.
We camped a lot in 2 Days & 1 Night.
We basically camped all the time.
In the end, I got so tired of it
and wanted to try something new.
So I tried suspending all my activities.
I thought that'd be better.
Sung-kwang, you're clapping.
That's why I left the show.
At first,
it was really hard.
On Gag Concert,
everything was already planned.
But on a variety show,
I had no idea what to do.
During the shoot,
I couldn't even look at the camera.
I stared at the amberjack the whole time.
I kept glancing at Ho-dong
because I had no idea what to do.
I decided,
"I'll only do what I'm told to do.
I won't try too hard to be funny.
I'll just do my job.
I can do this."
One day, the amberjack, Ho-dong,
complimented me for the first time.
For my driving skills.
Some of you probably know.
"I didn't even notice you brake.
How did the car stop?
We just turned left,
but I didn't feel a thing.
How did we arrive
in Gangwon Province so fast?"
My work vehicle at the time
was a Carnival,
like many other celebrities.
The minivan that's very festive.
I changed cars about six times.
They would install cameras in my van
using a lot of duct tape.
These days, they use better equipment.
Back then, they used duct tape
for everything.
And duct tape is impossible
to remove completely.
Once, I dozed off in my van.
When I woke up and tried to get out,
my arm wouldn't move because
it was stuck to the duct tape residue.
Duct tape can even make
an unhappy couple
stick together all the time.
Duct tape really is amazing.
Since I'm only human,
I get tired if I drive a lot.
One day, I'd been driving for many hours.
But the others in the van…
What's the point of having cameras?
No one talked to me.
They were all fast asleep
with their mouths open.
Eun Ji-won was banging his head
on the window repeatedly,
but he wouldn't wake up.
Ho-dong's snores were deafening.
I was angry. No one said a word to me.
"Do they think of me as their driver?
What's my role in this team?"
The scenery is magnificent
along the Dong River.
But you need to drive carefully,
or else you might fall off the cliff.
I thought, "Should I drive off the cliff?
Then I could become the main host.
I'll cast my six favorite people
and take over 2 Days & 1 Night."
While I was thinking that,
I noticed Seung-gi
in the back seat.
He was sleeping like an angel,
not making a single sound.
I couldn't bring myself to do that
for his sake.
One more thing. I looked at Ho-dong.
Even if we fell off the cliff,
his head is basically a helmet.
So if he survived,
you can guess what would've happened.
I would've wished I was dead
rather than face him.
In the end, I changed my mind
and was able to smile like that again.
You have no idea
how much I drove back then.
I'm sick of driving.
I still try to avoid driving.
Even when I'm not drunk,
I use a chauffeur service
so that I don't have to drive.
After using the chauffeur service so much,
I even ended up being a model for them.
Phone number
That's the same…
-On both sides
That's how it happened.
A person should be the same
on both sides as well.
The thing about Ho-dong is, though,
once someone stands out to him,
he can turn that person into a star.
Remember how he shouted,
"Seung-gi!", all the time?
I also managed to grab his attention.
It was when we were shooting
our very first opening.
We started introducing ourselves.
"Hello, I'm Eun Ji-won."
Seung-gi mentioned his song,
"You're My Girl."
I don't know whether he had a girl or not.
Anyway, it was all going well.
Then it was my turn.
Ho-dong suddenly said, "Everyone.
The greatest comedian of our time.
This amazing man
can make everyone crack up
just by introducing himself.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Everyone, you won't be disappointed."
He was setting me up to fail.
You know what I mean, right?
I broke out in a cold sweat.
I still have nightmares.
But you know what?
I managed to make everyone laugh.
"Howdy, everyone."
That greeting even got me a commercial.
Back then, I was the one
walking on eggshells around Ho-dong.
But these days,
Ho-dong walks on eggshells
around me as well.
"Su-geun, put your hand to your face.
I'll pretend to slap you in the face."
Then he will slap me and I'll fake it.
Before, he would call my name
and just slap me right away.
Now, he's more careful with me.
But if it hadn't been for Ho-dong,
I wouldn't have made it this far.
But most of all,
some of you may remember this.
On 2 Days & 1 Night,
we once went on a retreat
and had tea time together.
And someone brought persimmons.
Instead of eating them right away,
Ho-dong suddenly asked,
"Do any of you know how to say,
'persimmon,' in English?"
If Seung-gi knew the answer, that'd be it.
It wouldn't have been funny.
But even Seung-gi seemed clueless.
No one knew the answer.
I thought this was my chance
to make a joke.
"None of you know the answer?
Repeat after me.
'Bitter.'"
Everyone cracked up.
Ho-dong found it hilarious.
"Then what's 'mandarin' in English?"
"Sour."
"Sour." It was perfect.
I was actually debating
between "sour" and "Jeju."
I couldn't decide.
I can say any fruit names.
What's "watermelon" in English?
In one syllable, "spit."
What else?
-What?
-"Banana."
That's already English.
"Korean melon"? Gosh.
That one is a bit long.
"Seeds in poop."
That's "Korean melon" in English.
Don't pretend you don't understand.
I've been walking on eggshells
around Ho-dong a lot,
but recently, I've met another person
who makes me walk on eggshells.
Let me show you.
It's this person.
He's extremely poisonous
and always angry.
With his cheeks puffed up,
he's ready to attack you at any moment.
It's comedian Lee Kyung-kyu.
I met him recently and told him,
"I'm doing a stand-up comedy show
with Netflix.
It's called The Sense Coach."
He went, "What? 'Sense Coach'?
What's that?"
He yelled at me
when he could just talk calmly.
I asked him if I could portray him
as a pufferfish.
"No! I'm not an ordinary pufferfish.
I'm a striped pufferfish!
It's delicious.
But its poison can kill you."
He is extremely kind
to the people who are nice to him.
But if you get on his wrong side,
you can get killed.
He's always frowning.
He's always ready to attack.
As if he has duct tape on his forehead.
We go fishing together,
and everything upsets him.
Good weather upsets him,
and rain upsets him, too.
He gets angry at the captain
if fish don't bite.
"Why did you pick today?"
He gets angry if one of us get a hit.
And if we catch a lot,
he's angry his arms hurt.
Sometimes, after being on a boat
for a long time, he gets tired.
Then he makes a joke,
and it's important to notice this.
You have to figure out
whether he's joking or serious.
Since I spend so much time with him,
I can tell right away
if he's joking or not.
While fishing,
he'll suddenly yell at me,
"What are you staring at?"
Then I respond right away.
"What are you staring at?" "Kyung-kyu."
"What are you?" "Your fellow comedian."
"Look at you." "Fine, look at me."
"Look at me." Kyung-kyu cracks up.
He's so happy that I play along with him.
But some people can't tell.
When Kyung-kyu is joking, it shows
because he sounds extra aggressive.
"What are you staring at?" He's joking.
Sometimes, he sounds more serious.
"What are you staring at?"
It means he's not in a good mood
and he genuinely wants you
to stop staring at him.
But some people can't take a hint.
I won't mention names, though.
"What are you staring at?"
"What do you think?
My cornea is scanning you
and I am looking at you.
Do you have a problem with that?"
They say that.
-Ji Sang-ryeol.
-That's right. It's Ji Sang-ryeol.
Then Kyung-kyu says, "What's with you?
We can't even air that.
Are you out of your mind?"
It's important to take a hint.
I'm one of the senior comedians now.
Since I usually appear on TV
with Ho-dong and Kyung-kyu,
you may think I'm still young,
but I'm one of the older ones now.
When I'm shooting,
I sometimes have to walk on eggshells
around people younger than me.
I often do shows with idol groups.
I usually come to work dressed casually.
But the clothes that younger people wear
look weird to me.
I just don't understand.
They're all designer clothes,
but I don't get it.
Who do you think I'm talking about?
Song Min-ho. I mean MINO.
His clothes look so fancy.
People in their teens and 20s love them.
But I don't get it.
They're all designer clothes.
I greet MINO like this.
"Hey, BB!"
"Hey, BB, what's up?"
He'd ask me, "What does BB mean?"
I'd say, "It means bling-bling."
He wears so much jewelry.
You like that. You must be a fan of MINO.
I thought that since people
of all ages watch our show,
it'd be better if he dressed more neatly.
But if I say, "What's with your outfit?",
he says, "It's my style."
Young people started treating me
the same way I treated Kyung-kyu.
It's a wake up call.
"They all have their own styles.
Instead of finding fault,
I should accept them as who they are."
Back in the day,
it was even more important to take a hint
while shooting TV shows.
We were supposed to be shooting
a hidden camera show,
but the cameras were all visible.
Then a call came.
"Can you lend me 40 million won?"
Since you can see the cameras,
you say,
"Okay. Send me your account number."
Who does that?
So you knew what was going on,
but you had to pretend to be oblivious.
Back then, hypnosis shows were common
but they were really awkward.
I know you're laughing
because you remember.
Some other comedians and I
were gathered in the waiting room,
and the producer walked in.
"This hypnotist is incredible.
We tested him, and he managed to hypnotize
all ten crew members.
One of them saw his late mother,
one of them said
she was a princess in her past life.
It worked for all ten of them."
Why did he tell us that?
-So that you play along.
-He was trying to tell us…
to play along.
That's what he was saying indirectly.
I could take a hint,
so I entered the room.
Then it started.
"Look at this marble.
As soon as I say, 'Red sun!',
you'll fall asleep.
Red sun!"
You'd normally fall asleep like this.
But I was overzealous.
"Red sun!"
I dropped my head. All comedians do that.
I couldn't get the producer's face
off my mind.
I wanted to do a good job.
"What kind of questions
will the hypnotist ask?
What should I answer?"
My head was full of these questions.
The hypnotist asked me.
"Su-geun, where are you now?"
"Next to you."
"I'm right next to you."
"Who is with you?"
"Who else? You. It's just the two of us."
If I'd said that,
it would've been hilarious.
But I couldn't.
I told him. "I see a chimney.
Someone is starting a fire
in the furnace."
"Who is that person?"
"I think it's my grandma.
She's crying."
I wasn't under hypnosis.
I was making things up.
He would then ask me more questions.
"Why is she crying?"
"Because of you."
I wanted to say that, but I couldn't.
I said, "I have no idea.
She's just crying."
That gave the hypnotist confidence.
He thought I was completely hypnotized.
He handed me something.
I grabbed it and it smelled like an onion.
"From now on,
whatever you put in your mouth
will taste like a delicious apple.
You'll be eating an apple."
But it was obviously an onion.
He shoved it in my mouth.
But I could smell it.
I took a bite.
It made me cry.
But I couldn't say it was an onion.
"What is this?
I've never tasted an apple this delicious.
Grandma. Have some.
Go on, grandma."
"What does she say?"
"'You lunatic.
Do you expect me to eat this?'
That's what she says." I told him.
He took the hint and said,
"You're waking up now."
The producer at the back looked satisfied.
He gave me a sign.
Those who can't take a hint.
They frown as soon as they bite the onion.
They eat one more and frown again.
After eating five onions,
they finally say, "It's delicious."
They can't take a hint.
It's important to take a hint
when shooting TV shows.
Since I'm good at that,
I thought my kids would be the same.
But it seems to have nothing
to do with genes.
I actually learned to do it on my own.
My son, Tae-jun, is into gymnastics.
He's my eldest.
I think it's called the Tkatchev.
Let me show you some pictures.
That's him doing gymnastics.
He's in seventh grade.
Look at that. He's up in the air.
That's gymnastics. Look at that.
He's on a horizontal bar.
He's so brave.
He can pull off all kinds of things.
One day, I heard him giggling in his room.
It sounded like he was
asking someone questions.
When I went to see,
he was watching a live broadcast online.
It looked as if there were
hundreds of viewers,
but there were only three.
My son was the most active participant.
One day, he told me seriously,
"Dad, I want to go to the US."
I thought he was finally growing up.
He must want to broaden his horizons,
learn English, and experience new things.
So I decided to support him at all costs.
I asked him,
"Tae-jun, why do you
want to go to the US?"
He says, "There are
many horizontal bars in the US."
Is that true?
There must be people
from Netflix headquarters here.
I really wanted to ask them this.
"How many horizontal bars…"
I have no idea who told him that.
There's another live broadcast tonight,
so I'm going to ask him.
He's Tae-jun's role model.
I'd be his fourth viewer.
He must know the answer.
It really made me realize
that wits are not inherited.
I have another son,
and he's more like me.
One day, I was having a drink.
My wife and two sons were with me.
I told my sons seriously,
"Mom and Dad are going to build
a small house in the countryside
and live there until we die.
If your mom dies first, I'll follow her.
That's our plan.
You guys do whatever you want.
Forget about horizontal bars."
I told them seriously to wake them up.
"But we'll leave some money behind
for you guys."
My other son, Tae-seo, said,
"Dad, you can't leave us like that."
I asked him, "Why not?"
He said,
"Tell us where the money is first."
I found it so funny.
He really said that.
He's clever. He wants to know.
Tae-jun, my eldest son, sure is
more mature.
"Hey, do you care more about money
than Mom and Dad? How could you?
It's more important
that they are healthy and stay with us."
Then he asked me. "Dad, will there be
horizontal bars in the countryside?"
I made that up.
Did you like that?
I think it was due to how I was raised
that made me so quick-witted.
I changed schools so many times.
I attended two elementary school
graduation ceremonies.
In all my childhood photos,
I'm glancing at someone.
Where am I looking?
Look at that.
Where is this kid looking?
He's glancing at someone.
One day
back in elementary school,
I was playing soccer with some friends.
I was in third or fourth grade.
That's my school.
And I was playing soccer.
Suddenly, a cultivator
rolled into the schoolyard.
On the cultivator,
there was a small wardrobe.
Yes, like that.
I said, a "small" wardrobe.
It's fine. Leave it.
There was even an electric fan
loaded on the cultivator.
It wasn't that big, either.
It's okay. Leave it.
It's an electric fan.
Anyway, the cultivator rolled in
all of a sudden.
I thought it was some crazy old man.
There were kids playing,
and it could've been dangerous.
Why drive a cultivator there?
But when I looked closely,
it was my father.
My father was driving the cultivator
loaded with all that stuff.
So… Wait, he wasn't wearing a cap.
It's okay. Let's pretend he did.
Anyway, it was him.
Then he told me to hop on.
I said to my friends, "See you tomorrow.
Sorry I have to leave early," as usual.
Then we set off.
But my dad started driving
in the opposite direction of home.
The cultivator rolled on.
On and on.
My dad turned around now and then.
It wasn't to make sure I was still there,
but to make sure
the electric fan hadn't fallen off.
I didn't even ask him.
I was just sitting there at the back.
We arrived in a completely
different neighborhood.
He told me, "You and I are
living in this house starting today."
There was a tiny school nearby.
"You're going to that school
starting tomorrow."
I didn't understand what was going on.
Then a lady showed up.
I'd seen her a few times
in the neighborhood.
My dad told me, "She's your mom now."
But I already had a mom.
I wet the bed
all the way through middle school.
It was because
my dad and my step…
I used to call her "lady"
but she's "Mother" now.
She's old now
and has been with my dad for decades.
I couldn't go to the bathroom
because I was afraid I'd wake them up.
For some reason,
my dad would sometimes wave his hand
in front of my face
to check if I was asleep.
I don't know why he did that, though.
Anyway, he used to do this.
I don't know why.
I doubt he wanted to check
if I was still alive.
That went on for months.
He kept waving his hand
in front of me at night.
I still don't know what that was about.
I was too young to understand.
I visited my dad over the holidays
and recreated this scene.
Here's a photo.
It was taken during the New Year holidays.
I'm out of frame, right?
I'll tell you why.
We couldn't find anyone
who could take a photo of us.
My dad is 80,
and he's the youngest around there.
This was taken by a 90-year-old man
who was passing by.
He kept pressing the button too long
and ended up taking videos.
And I don't know what he pressed
but he left eight selfies on my phone.
Some photos only show
a part of the cultivator.
This is the best shot we got.
What I wanted to recreate was the moment
where I asked my dad,
"Dad, where are we going?"
And that's exactly how he looked
back then.
His son is successful
and even gives him money sometimes,
so he should smile more
but he still looks so stiff.
But shortly after taking that photo,
my dad fell ill
and had a major surgery.
I'm not sure if I should say this here,
but last week, he…
he regained his health.
I got a call.
He's very healthy now.
My dad never walks on eggshells
around anyone.
He always pushes forward no matter what.
One day back in elementary school,
my dad was gone
when I woke up in the morning.
My brother and I panicked.
We didn't have anything to eat,
so my brother made
whatever dishes he could make.
On the third day, my dad came back.
"Dad, where have you been?"
"I went sightseeing."
He went sightseeing.
"Why didn't you leave any money?"
"You didn't find it?"
In the corner of the small room,
he picked up a 5,000-won bill
and gave it to us.
He had crumpled it and chucked it there.
Once, it was Christmas Eve.
My dad said,
"Oh, it's Christmas tomorrow."
He said nothing else.
We thought, "Dad knows
it's Christmas tomorrow?"
So at night before bed, we took a pair
of Dad's military socks.
Those huge ones.
We hung them before going to bed.
The next morning, we found
that Dad had worn them and left.
He wore them and left.
He must have wanted to wear
thick socks on Christmas Day.
That's the only memory of Christmas
my brother and I have.
Once, a TV show needed
a picture of me on my first birthday.
So I called Dad and asked
if he had any pictures from that day.
"No." "Why not?"
"We didn't have a party."
In the end, I had to borrow
a picture from Byung-man.
He was the one who looked most like me
that I could find.
I asked him if he had any pictures,
and he did.
As far as I know,
his family wasn't well-off, either.
That's Kim Byung-man there.
Who could tell? So I asked Dad,
"Does this look like me?"
"It's a spitting image of you.
No one will tell. The boy looks smart."
I thought he'd apologize to me.
But all he said was
that this looks just like me.
Speaking of kids,
have you ever seen kids
who are vaguely cute?
Not all kids are pretty and cute.
Sometimes, a friend
brings his or her baby.
And I go,
"Goodness. My dear.
He's become so big.
It feels like yesterday you were pregnant.
Oh, my. And look how big he is now."
I don't comment on how the baby looks,
just on how much he's grown.
"My goodness. Unbelievable. Gosh."
You know what I mean, right?
I don't want to offend anyone.
Sometimes, you say,
"A boy…",
but the parent says, "It's a girl."
Then I say, "A boy is all you need then.
I'm sure he'll be as beautiful
as this girl.
You'll be a great dad."
You have to come up with something quick.
And it's always better to assume
a baby is a girl.
"My, look at this beautiful princess."
Even if it's a boy,
mothers like to hear that.
"Oh, it's a boy? But he's so pretty.
He must take after you."
That's not going to offend anyone.
How much cash do you give
as a wedding gift? Do you have any rules?
If it's just an acquaintance, 50,000 won.
If it's a close friend, 100,000 won.
If it's a family member,
200,000 to 300,000 won.
If you haven't talked in five, six years,
an emoji will do.
An emoji will do.
If you reply and start a conversation,
you have to go to the wedding.
An emoji will signal
that the friendship is over.
It's a bad idea to start a conversation.
It's vague, right?
An acquaintance invited me to his wedding,
so I brought 100,000 won.
A friend of mine
hadn't withdrawn cash yet,
so I followed him to the ATM.
But then I saw him withdraw 200,000 won.
The thing is, I was closer to the groom
than he was.
I was worried
the groom would be disappointed in me.
Gosh. So I ended up withdrawing
an extra 200,000 won.
I thought I should give more.
So I handed in 300,000 won.
When it was my friend's turn,
he asked for four envelopes
and put 50,000 won in each.
He was handing them in
on behalf of other friends.
If only he'd handed them in first.
Then I would've handed in
just 100,000 won.
I handed in mine first,
and he handed in four envelopes.
No one compensated me.
So annoying, right?
Isn't it so vague?
It's not just weddings.
Kids' first birthday parties are the same.
I'll take Sung-kwang for example.
Let's say my beloved fellow comedian's
baby is turning one.
Since we're close,
I decide to give him a million won.
I'm his senior, so of course.
I arrive at the party with a million won.
"Sung-kwang, congratulations."
But I see that his wife is pregnant.
"Oh, no. If I give him a million won now,
I'll have to give him another million
next time. Hold on."
I go into the bathroom
and take 500,000 won out.
I give Sung-kwang 500,000 won.
Because I'd have to do the same thing
in a year.
So, this is what I do these days.
When I hear about a birthday party,
I call and ask,
"Should I MC the party for you?"
If I'm the host…
You know what I mean, right?
I get paid.
So I try to be the host
instead of giving a gift.
I used to be a recreation instructor.
I've led many events in different regions.
Different regions have different dialects.
The Chungcheong dialect
was the most interesting.
"Forget it. Stop it. Come on."
Everything they say ends in "yu."
"Next up is IU." Like this.
But not everything ends with "yu".
The dialect in Cheonan and Asan
is really interesting.
My friend, Sang-won, lives there.
When I'm leaving,
he says, "Are you leaving already?
Stay and eat with us, huh?"
"Stay and eat with us, huh?"
"What are you doing over the holidays?
Why do you never call, huh?"
Like the singer, Lee Seung-chul,
holds a note,
he speaks like that.
"What are you up to?
Come over for coffee, huh?"
Why doesn't he just say
the whole sentence slowly?
He says the first part really fast
and drags out the latter part.
"Come see me when you have time, huh?"
That's the Chungcheong dialect.
I wonder if foreigners will be able
to understand this.
Even in our daily lives,
we often walk on eggshells around people.
Some of you may have even felt bad
about coming here today.
So now, I'd like to give you some advice
on how to behave.
I'm your coach today.
Do any of you want me
to give you some advice?
Raise your hand,
and I'll answer your questions.
The woman at the back. Go on.
-Should I stand up?
-Just read the room.
All right. What's troubling you?
I'm the eldest child.
In both families.
-You mean both your mom and dad's sides?
-Yes.
Gosh, okay.
I don't know if that's why,
but I feel uncomfortable at home.
I'm always walking on eggshells at home.
-And?
-And I'm always the mediator.
-You feel uncomfortable at home?
-Yes, at home.
If I'm away from home for a few days,
my family always fights
and things become awkward.
-You live with your parents?
-Yes.
-It's not like my family, is it?
-No.
-It's not like that.
-Then what?
I can't relax at home.
I walk on eggshells all the time.
Even when my parents are eating together,
if they start raising their voices,
I have to come out and sit with them
but my sister--
I'm sorry, but I'm not sure
how I can help you with that.
If you decide to move out,
I could help you find a place.
-Do you have any siblings?
-I have a little sister.
-How old is she?
-She's 20.
-She doesn't walk on eggshells?
-No.
Then live like her.
It's simple.
Why should you shoulder all the burden?
Since you're the eldest child
on both sides of the family,
it's understandable
that your parents rely on you a lot.
-Yes.
-And you can't just ignore that.
It's okay if it's your family.
It's annoying to walk on eggshells
at work or something,
but if it's your family, it's no big deal.
That's just a way of communicating,
isn't it?
If your parents never fought,
you wouldn't even talk to them at all.
You'd be busy on your phone in your room.
They're fighting on purpose
just to talk to you.
They're bringing the family together.
These days, conversations are rare.
We all only talk about ourselves.
Your parents seem to be using
a very advanced technique.
They're not divorced or anything.
They still live together.
-Do you need duct tape?
-No.
No, right? Then it's fine.
-I'm rooting for you.
-Thank you.
Since you can talk about it comfortably,
it's not a serious problem.
Anyone else?
The man at the front.
I graduated from college last year
and am looking for a job at the moment.
Since I've been unemployed for a year now,
I have to walk on eggshells
when I'm at home.
During the holidays, my aunts ask me
-when I'll find a job.
-Right.
They ask those questions, right?
Thankfully, I didn't visit my relatives
because of the pandemic this year.
I was relieved that I didn't have to see
my grandma and aunts.
So you want the pandemic to continue?
No, it's not like that.
It should end soon
so I can find a job more easily.
I really hope so.
But I feel uncomfortable at home.
Could you give me some advice on this?
How old are you?
I'm 27.
You're young.
You've done military service, too.
Your life is yours.
You said you're 27.
Who knows if you'll make it
when you're 28, 29, or 30?
When that happens,
be good to your parents,
and they'll be happy.
My father used to hang up right away
when I called him.
When I was a nobody,
he'd hang up immediately.
So I never visited him. It's true.
"Your friend so-and-so
became a car mechanic
and is a manager now.
What are you doing with your life?"
But he's like this now.
"Look at this party Su-geun threw for me."
It's like that.
Just wait for that day to come.
You're family.
Your family is just concerned about you.
They're not trying to find fault with you.
No one can wait for you longer
than your family can.
That's very important. Your family.
Sung-kwang, include things like this,
or people won't like it.
Anyone else? Ask away.
Go ahead. The woman over there.
I got a job last November.
Congratulations.
I found a job straight out of high school.
-Right away?
-Yes.
Look at her.
She can do it, you can do it.
-And?
-I'm a lot younger
-than my bosses and colleagues…
-Go on.
…so I feel uncomfortable.
How much older are they?
About nine years older and more.
Don't you just call them
using their titles?
But apart from Manager and Deputy Manager,
my workplace doesn't have
a clear hierarchy.
There aren't many different levels.
And there are more men than women.
I usually call them by their first names
or just say, "Excuse me."
How about using sir and ma'am?
I think that sounds best.
If someone much younger at work
calls you by your first name, like,
"Su-geun, can you do this?",
I think it creates more distance.
Don't you think?
They use honorifics with me.
-Who?
-My colleagues.
Get up on your desk and shout,
"Hey, drop the honorifics immediately."
They use honorifics to show respect.
-I see.
-It's only natural.
Just because you're younger…
-What's your name?
-It's Yeon-u.
"Yeon-u. Do this. Come here."
That's not acceptable
when you're interacting with other people.
You deserve respect.
Of course they should show respect.
Since they respect
even the youngest employee,
I'm sure it's a very good workplace.
It's impossible to not be concerned
about what others are thinking.
But whose thoughts should we be
concerned about the most?
It's our own.
People are concerned more about
their own thoughts than that of others.
But only you can decide
what you want to be concerned about.
One last piece of advice
I want to give you is this.
Live as yourself.
Be who you are.
Don't care about what others think.
Just do what you want.
Regardless of your gender and age,
and what point you're at in your life,
live the life you want
without worrying about what others think.
Wherever you are in life.
Then where are we now?
We're at the end of our show.
But don't be sad.
If Netflix can take a hint,
they'll do one more of these shows.
When the pandemic is over
and we can have a bigger audience,
I'm sure they'll give me
an even greater opportunity.
Lastly… Are we ready?
We're going to release doves.
Please look up.
Be careful when they're released.
Here come the doves, the symbol of peace.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim