Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
- Because the situation
is blowing up.
I don't have time put out
every fire your client
feels like starting, that's why.
Well, sure, but enough
with the demurrals
and the stalling
tactics, counselor.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
I suggest that you settle.
You know if I get you into court
I'll burn this
case to the ground.
- And the kitchen's
on fire again.
- What?
I was gonna make us eggs.
- But then you
answered your phone.
- I did, yeah, I did.
It's the Phitzer case.
The opposing counsel is
being really uncooperative.
- Well, they are the
opposing counsel.
- Thank you.
Oh, hey, I'm not gonna be
able to get away to pick up
that silver tray for my parents'
anniversary party tonight.
Can you do it?
- I have history tutoring
after my last class.
You know that.
- Josh, can you cancel
it just this once please?
Honey, this case
has got me really-
- That's every case.
And I'm always the one
that picks up the slack.
- Please.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Maggie Turner.
- Bon appetit.
- Hey, Melissa.
- You're
in bright and early.
- Good morning, Mr. Baxter.
I didn't think anyone
else would be in.
- There were
transactions I needed
to manage before the
day gets started.
- I'm just taking care
of some things myself
'cause I have to leave
an hour early today.
It's my parents' 40th
wedding anniversary.
A big party, tent in the
backyard, that kinda thing.
I will be taking work with me,
and I'll be
available on my cell.
- I like that attitude.
And what you did
with the Inova case,
the way you completely
dismantled opposing counsel
in the courtroom, that
was very impressive.
- Thank you, sir.
- Yeah, you've become
quite the barracuda.
- Well, I'm just hoping to
swim with the sharks one day.
- Reviews come up next month.
We should discuss a
junior partner slot.
- That's very
exciting, Mr. Baxter.
Thank you.
- You know the real carnivores
in the firm can call me Mal.
- All right, Mal, I
will keep that in mind.
I'll leave you to it.
- Please do.
- I'm here!
Where's my contract?
Whoa, haven't seen you this
intense since rush week.
- Kappas forever.
- So, I was thinking
that after I sign
my life altering contract,
we could play hooky.
I wanna go shopping
for something
for your parents'
40th anniversary.
- Oh, honey, that's so sweet.
You don't have to come.
- I wouldn't miss it, but I
do need to know the dress code
'cause currently all I have
are swimsuit prototypes
for next year's line and
old bridesmaid dresses.
- I asked mom.
She said, "festive casual."
I told her nobody
knows what that means.
- How would you know?
So, when was the last
time you went anywhere
that wasn't business attire?
- Okay, fine.
If you're giving me a hard time,
I can bill you for
this conversation.
I was going to congratulate you.
Sign where the flags are
and you will officially
have expanded into
premium outlets.
- Yes.
Maybe now my mother will stop
bothering me about Lester.
See, I can commit.
- What about Lester?
- Ugh, we broke up.
I just couldn't see
myself marrying Lester.
- Fair.
- I just need to find
what you and Josh have.
- I don't know if you
want that .
- No, you guys are good, right?
- I don't know,
I don't know what we are.
I feel like he's always
so disappointed in me,
and I thought that we both
knew what it would take
for me to make
partner here, right?
I have to be a killer.
And sometimes it's like I
can't turn it off with him,
and I just wonder sometimes
if he would be
happier without me.
- No, don't say that.
If you two can't make it
work, then I have no chance.
I am pinning all my
hopes on you guys.
- Oh, that's good,
no, that's great.
Thank you so much.
That's just what I
need, more pressure.
Congratulations,
Miss Entrepreneur.
- Oh, that actually reminds me.
You will never guess who
I ran into in the lobby.
- Who?
- Rick Morgan.
- What?
- He had an entourage.
- I thought he was
based in Seattle?
- Yeah, he is, but he's here
meeting with some PR firm.
Something about a
new solar company.
- You talked?
- Yeah.
He actually recognized me.
- Wow.
- And he asked about you.
- He asked about me?
I am surprised he
even remembers me.
- Oh, because you only
dated all through college.
Honestly, I always thought you
and Rick would get married.
- Hm, the road not taken.
That is my conference call.
- Oh, so no hooky?
- Sorry.
- I'll see you Saturday.
- Hello, this is Maggie Turner.
- Kappas forever.
- Hey, Jackson, I meant
to tell you earlier.
We're expected Callahan.
- Tell him we'd like to see
a deck for the new campaign
by Monday and I'm gonna send
it to the Seattle office.
- And to accept
that counter offer
sometime later this afternoon.
- And then we'll see
if we're able to buy-
- Not so much.
Oh, excuse me.
- Excuse...
Maggie.
- Rick, hi.
- Hi.
- Carrie was just up.
She told me that you
were in the building.
- This is crazy.
How are you?
Do you wanna grab a coffee?
- Yeah, yes.
- Uh, bump the- 00 to a- 30,
and the00 to a video
call from the jet.
- You know what, I
just realized I can't.
I'm sorry.
I'm so late, Josh
is gonna kill me.
- Oh, yeah, Josh.
How is he?
I heard you two got married.
- We did, yeah, we got married.
After I passed the bar and he
got his doctorate in history.
- Well, I won't keep you then.
But I'll be back
here in three weeks
if this PR things work out.
Call your office to setup lunch.
- Yeah, I'd like that very much.
- Looking forward to it.
- I'll see you then.
- Yeah.
- Bye.
Well, no, because it's
not a counter offer.
It's an insult.
Listen, I need a real
offer on my desk by Monday,
and I'm talking mid sixes or
the deal is off the table.
Yeah, fine.
Oh, come on.
- We wouldn't be traffic if-
- Yes, I know, thank you.
That must be a good book.
What's it about?
- About 200 more pages.
I'm testing the kids on Monday.
- Hm.
You know it's not like you can
get an F, you're the teacher.
- Just because I don't
negotiate six figure deals,
it doesn't mean what
I do doesn't matter.
- I don't, I didn't say that.
I never say that.
You used to like to tell me
about what you were reading.
- Oh, hey, can you pull over?
- Mm hm, yeah.
You thinking about
the old library?
- Yeah, the city tore it
down and the lot sat empty
for so long they
built this eyesore.
- Yeah, who knew the
developers would run off
to South America with
the investors' money.
I know you love the library,
but I miss Flannigan's.
- This whole place
really went downhill
after the library was gone.
- Hm.
It wasn't all bad though.
It brought us
together, didn't it?
- I don't think pity
makes a great foundation
for a relationship.
- Why would you say that?
- The only reason we
started hanging out, Maggie,
was because you
felt sorry for me.
- That is...
That's not entirely true, Josh.
- Oh, come on.
I tried to save the
library, it got demolished,
I was crushed, it's not like
you noticed me much beforehand.
Let's not rewrite history.
- There they are!
- Hi, Mommy.
- Hi, honey.
- You can hire a
gardener you know?
- Oh, I'm
just cleaning up
the beds before the party.
- Yeah, what happened
to all your flowers?
- Oh, you know, I just,
I didn't really feel
up for it this year.
- Hm.
- How's my favorite son-in-law?
- Your only son-in-law?
- Tomato, tomato.
How's your dad?
Is he still liking Phoenix?
- Yeah, he says he'll take
the heat as long as he doesn't
have to live through
another Illinois winter.
- George!
- Is that Mags and Josh?
Or are you talking
to yourself again?
- Oh, hush, you.
Your father thinks
I'm losing it.
- She scurried around for half
an hour the other day looking
for her keys and they were
in her hand the whole time.
- This one didn't even
give me the heads up.
- I couldn't get a word in.
You keep talking to yourself.
- Ah.
- To be fair,
I also talk to myself.
- Well, don't blame me.
You get it from her.
Ash, come say hello
to your sister.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Hi, how are you?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
I wish people would
stop worrying.
- Hey, George.
- Hello, son.
- Ash isn't still
living with you, is he?
- No, he has that
studio apartment behind
the Pick 'N Save.
- Huh.
- Sup?
- Hey.
- I made a pitcher of lemonade.
I thought we might all
eat out on the patio.
- Okay.
- Sounds great.
Ash, what are you
up to these days?
- Just the same thing.
- That's not entirely true.
Ash got a promotion last month.
He's now assistant
in charge of...
What is it again?
- Software upgrades
and app installations.
Really not a big deal.
- But still, assistant in
charge, that's pretty cool.
- As smart as Ash is with
computers and all those things,
he could be running the
entire place over there
if he'd show a little
more confidence.
- Oh, whatever.
It's just a, it's a dumb job.
- So, Maggie, how's
work with you?
- Mm, work is pretty
great actually.
I won a big court
case last week.
And this morning one of the
senior partners mentioned
there might be a junior
partner slot coming up, so.
- How about that?
- Hey, is Dad okay?
It seems like he's having
more trouble getting around.
- Oh, well, you know, he
has good days and bad days.
But the way the fall
tore his spinal cord,
you know I just kick myself.
I shoulda made him throw out
that rickety old
ladder years ago.
- It's not your fault, Mom.
- Are you going back to work?
- I'm just, I'm
checking my email.
I always check my email
before bed at home.
- But we're not at home.
- I'm aware that
we're not at home.
Do you think maybe
here you can tell me
what's going on with you?
- Us, Maggie.
What's going on with us?
Sometimes I look at your
parents and I get sad.
They've been
together for 40 years
and they still like each other.
We've been together for 15-
- And you...
Are you saying that
you don't like me?
- I'm saying that
sometimes I'm not sure
if we ever should've gotten
married in the first place.
- Okay, okay, that's not...
That would be something that
we would need to talk about.
- Not here though, okay?
We'll talk about it when
we get back to Chicago.
- Sure.
Should I, should I just
sleep in my old room?
Should I-
- Whatever you want, Maggie.
- Whatever I want, okay.
Um, I'm gonna go for a walk.
- Okay.
- I wish I had a do-over.
Oh, shoot.
Ow!
Ow.
Josh?
Where's my phone?
I'm gonna kill him.
Mom?
- In here.
- Mom, where's Ash?
He took my phone.
I can't do anything with
something this ancient.
- Your dad and I
just bought that
for your graduation last week.
How fast is technology moving?
- Mom, you look great.
Your hair looks good.
- Stop teasing.
I have an appointment to get
it done before the party.
- What?
- Honestly, George,
we do have glasses.
- Dad, what's happening?
What's going on?
- Okay, I admit it.
I was jogging.
I'm trying to up my cardio
so I can spin your mother
on the dance floor
all night long, huh?
Whoa, hey.
- You're a sweaty mess.
- Oh.
Come on, babe.
Oh, shake it.
- George, stop it.
- And the big spin.
- Oh, no.
- Stop it!
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Woo hoo.
- Use the hips.
- Okay, look, I know
you're mad, but Josh...
Carrie.
- Mags.
- Carrie, oh my
gosh, okay, listen.
I don't know what's going on.
Something happened.
I had a fight with Josh
and then I went for a walk,
and then I, I, I, I made
a stupid wish I guess.
And then I hit my head
and then I woke up.
Okay, but now,
everything's different,
but it's not different.
It's the same as it was,
but it's not the same.
It's the same as before, but
like before, before, you know?
- Mags, what
are you talking about?
Sounds like you just
had a strange dream.
I dreamt about this big octopus,
and now I feel kinda weird
about going into the water.
BT dubs, you need
to get here soon.
Derrick is rocking
some board shorts.
- Sweetie, are you okay?
You looked a little pale
when you dashed out.
- Yes, I'm, listen, Carrie-
I'm gonna have to get back
to you on the shorts, bye.
- Rick, she'll be
down in a minute.
- Okay.
- What? Wait? Who?
- Hey, babe, are you coming?
Everyone's gonna be
at the lake already.
- Uh, you know what?
I don't think I can.
I have too much to do today.
- Yeah, going to the lake.
- What are you talking
about too much to do?
Yesterday, all you and Carrie
talked about was the lake.
Look, your beach bag
is already packed.
Oh, honey, I know it's
been stressful with LSATs
and law school applications,
but that's all behind you now.
Go, enjoy yourself.
You're only young once.
- Hi.
- Hey, beautiful.
- Hello.
- Oh, cute beach bag.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Hi, ooh, holy moly.
- Oh?
- That's just, needs
to be over there.
- You're not still
mad at me are you?
- I don't know.
Maybe, why?
- I was just repeating
something stupid my dad said,
and I'm sorry.
Can we just get a do-over?
- Yes.
Yes, we can because
this, this is a do-over.
- And I know just how
to make it up to you.
- Okay.
Ah, ooh, yep.
Just, just one of those.
- Okay.
Oh, my gosh, it's Flannigan's.
I loved Flannigan's.
- Best banana cream
pie in the world.
- It is.
- Am I forgiven?
- I think so, yeah.
Wow.
- Thanks so much, I'll
see you at the rally.
- Josh.
- Maggie, you're back.
- Yeah, hi.
- Hi.
- What's up, Turner?
- Just trying to save
the library, Rick.
Getting ready for a
big rally tomorrow.
You should come.
- Ah, no can do.
And besides, it's not
even the library anymore.
So, what's the point?
- It's part of our
town's history.
We wanna repurpose it.
What about you, Maggie?
- I can try, yeah.
- Hey, we're hitting
the lake, so good luck.
Come on, Mags.
- Sure.
Bye, Josh.
- She's back.
- Whoa.
- They
haven't even built
the pavilion yet or the park.
- Okay, you're kind of
in a weird mood today,
but can we go be
weird in the lake?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Yeah, sure.
- Oh, there she is!
- Hey, oh, my god.
Hi, hey, hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hi.
- Okay, check it.
Derrick at 10 o'clock.
- That certainly is, yeah.
- It's purely professional.
Look, if I'm gonna be the
next Vera Wang swimwear,
I'm gonna need a men's line.
- Man, you are just exactly
the same as I
remember you being.
Sorry, today, now, now,
that I remember you being
currently the way that you are.
- And you're a nut job.
- Yeah, um, I'm kinda
dealing with a lot.
- Ugh, yeah, I know.
I'm dealing with
this best friend
who's being a total buzzkill.
Mags, I'm gonna need
you to just chill out,
and go with the flow
this summer, okay?
- Yeah, that's...
Yeah.
- Exactly.
Like I'm not even
gonna think about
being an adult until September.
- Okay.
- Okay, I have an idea.
Come on.
- Okay, whoa.
- Woo hoo!
Kappas forever!
- Kappas forever.
No, no, no, no.
- Um, I guess have fun
at the club tomorrow.
- Oh, yeah, I get to be
my dad's golf partner.
I hate it when
he's between wives.
Oh.
- I, I will, I'll see ya.
- Yeah.
- Hey, you know what?
I um, I had fun today.
This was a whole day and
all I did was have fun.
- Well, there's more
where that came from.
See ya later.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Dad, Dad, Dad, Dad,
Dad, what are you doing?
- Just hanging some lights.
I'm trying to
dress this place up
before the party next week.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
This is too old.
It is shaky, you
need to throw it out.
- Don't be ridiculous.
You don't throw something away
just because it's
a little shaky.
Fine.
- Thank you.
Hi.
- Speak, what brings
you to the realm of Ash?
- Oh, I remember this.
Okay, so-
- No, don't mix those up.
Don't mix those up.
- I'm not mixing them up,
you dork, I'm sitting down.
- Well you're touching them.
Don't don't them.
- I'm not touching your stuff.
Relax, okay, this is important.
Something's going on with me
and I don't think Mom
and Dad would understand.
- Hm sounds ominous.
I'll pass.
- I'm going to
tell you something.
And you are probably going
to think that I am crazy.
- Er, you're crazier.
- Duly noted.
- Mm hm.
- Okay, , yesterday
I was 37 years old.
I lived in Chicago
with my husband.
I was a lawyer at a
prestige law firm.
I was about to make
a junior partner,
and this morning I woke up
and it was 15 years earlier.
At first I thought that
maybe it was a dream,
but my dreams are
never this linear,
and they usually involve Sonia
Sotomayor, so she's not here.
Um, say something.
- Are you outta your mind?
- Maybe.
- Okay, why should
I think you're doing
anything besides
yanking my chain?
Okay, fine, tell me something
from the future then.
Yeah, go ahead.
- Um .
Oh, oh, oh, so those books.
That book series that you
like with the dragons.
- Mm hm.
- They make it
into an epic series,
everybody loves it.
It's all anybody
talks about for ages,
especially at the end when
like nobody thinks that Arya's-
- Stop!
Don't say anymore.
- Okay.
- Okay, okay, okay.
I'm not saying that believe you.
Okay, I'm not.
But if I did, I do happen to
have a time traveling theory.
A couple months ago I
was having an argument
with some of my guys
in my DND group, right?
- Department of Defense?
- What? No.
Dungeons and Dragons.
- Okay super nerd.
- Oh, I'm sorry, did I
just walk into your lair
and claim to be a time traveler?
- That's a good point.
I may have lost the high ground.
- We were arguing about
time nomads, right?
- That sounds like
a comic book, yes.
- It's a graphic novel, okay?
Can you please take
this seriously?
- Yep.
- All right, thanks.
Anyways, there are
articles out there.
A couple by actual
neuroscientists.
They have case studies of people
who have claimed to have
slipped back in time.
They theorize there was
some kinda mutation inside
their brains that is
triggered by stress.
The article describes
it as amnesia,
but instead of people
forgetting who they are,
in these rare individuals,
they seem to have
forgotten when they are.
- I mean, that could be me.
- Yeah.
- I am stressed.
What is that anyway?
- Oh, this?
This is my prized possession.
I've been working
on it for six weeks.
Sweet, huh?
- That's a long time.
- Yeah.
- Can I see it?
- Um, yeah, just be
very careful, okay?
- I'm a grown up.
- Hm, okay.
- So, like...
- Not yet.
- Hey, you know what?
I got some upstairs stuff to do,
so I'm just gonna
leave you with that.
Thank you so much
for all of your help.
Good bye.
A time nomad.
Okay, well, if that's
true, I should just,
I should just be
able to remember.
Right?
Okay.
I am 37 years old and
I am gonna wake up
in Chicago with my husband.
Ugh.
No, come on.
37, Chicago, husband, go.
Fine.
Hello?
- Well, I'm heading
off for a fun day at the club.
Dad and I are playing golf,
so there will be lots of
criticism on my swing.
Yay.
I just wanted to hear your voice
so I'd have something
to be happy about.
- Aw, well that's really sweet.
Hey, I'm rooting for you today.
Do good, uh, do you
know, good golf.
- Thanks.
Have I told you that I'm
just crazy about you?
- I think you just did it.
Bye.
- Bye.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Where's Mom and Dad?
- Errands stuff.
- Hm.
You're staring.
- Were you goofing
on me last night?
Are you gonna tell me
you're an alien today?
Or what's new?
- Nope.
Still just your run of the
mill regular old time traveler.
- So you still remember being 37
and you're married
to some Chicago dude?
- Oh, no, not some Chicago dude.
I married Josh Turner.
- Your dorky friend
from high school?
The guy you were on the
academic decathlon team with?
- Yeah, Josh.
- Oh, my gosh.
- After he couldn't save the
library from being demolished
I felt really bad for him and
we started hanging out more.
And we fell
for each other.
I guess that's how it started.
- Yeah, for you maybe.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- That guy's like-liked you
since he was a freshman.
- What, okay, how, how
did I not pick up on this?
Can you come to his save
the library rally with me?
I'm starting to feel like
I need to get closure
on a whole relationship
that hasn't even happened.
- I don't even wanna
know what that means.
- It's just in the
future it seems like
we're such different people.
I feel like a bad
guy all the time,
and he just seems so defeated.
And well, not now, he will be.
And I just, I feel like
the library is the key.
If I help Josh save the
library, then he'll be fine.
And he can go down whatever
path makes him happy,
and Rick and I can go
on like we should be.
Like we should have been...
I don't, I don't know.
- Wow, I was hoping
you'd tell me the future
is filled with flying cars.
Who knew it would just be
you and your boring drama.
Yeah, I'm good.
Thanks.
- Come on.
Your classmates
are gonna be there.
Cheerleaders are gonna be there.
Mom says you like one.
- What? No.
No, I don't, okay you know what?
That's none of your
business actually.
Mom shouldn't be
telling you that.
- Not my, but I'm your sister.
I'm allowed to know
stuff about you.
Come on.
- Okay, fine.
But I'm only going
in case you do
any weird time traveling stuff.
I wanna see that.
- Yeah, totally.
- Hey, um, what am I like?
- You're like a
big, huge dork, duh.
- No, no, I mean in the future.
I'm not gonna be you
know, like this forever.
Am I?
- Oh, honey.
Hey, you know what?
In the future, you're like,
you're kind of amazing.
- Yeah, sure.
- No, you are, trust me.
You're this like big
genius software developer.
Apps.
- Those stupid
little phone games?
- Okay, but in the future
there's an app for everything.
'Cause right now, phones
are just getting started.
But just, just trust me.
Remember apps, boom!
They explode, huge.
Dad brags about
you all the time.
- No way.
Your dad brags about me?
- Yeah, he does.
He talks about your confidence.
Be ready in an hour or I
will leave without you.
I've never noticed that at all.
- No?
- Hi.
- I already said that.
- Yeah.
- I just, I wasn't sure
if you'd show up or not,
so hi.
- Hi.
Yeah, I'm sorry we're late.
My timing lately has
been a little uh,
it's been a little weird.
- True story, bro.
- How's it going, Ash?
- Well, I'm at a save
the library rally,
so I'm livin', man.
- Thanks anyway.
- No problem.
- Really sorry about him.
Um, how can we help?
What's the plan?
- Uh, well,
we got a bunch of
high school kids.
The cheerleaders are
over there making signs.
There's another group
trying to paint the signs.
So far it's been a
lot like herding cats.
- Well, you know what?
It is your lucky day
because Ash is really great
at making signs-
- Painting.
Making signs.
- You're doing a good job.
Okay, go.
- Um, yeah, there's girls.
- Mm hm.
- And they're
cheerleaders.
- Remember what Dad said.
Confidence.
- Okay, you're right.
- I believe in you.
- Have fun.
- Thanks, man.
- He'll be fine.
- Wow, this is awesome.
Do you need help?
- Bulldozers come in two days.
- Tearing it down is not
gonna be an improvement.
- I know, right?
I mean, sure it's old
and needs repairs,
but this is part of
our town's history.
Part of our country's history.
Benjamin Franklin started the
first lending library in 1731.
Did you know that?
- No.
- We got to where we are
today because libraries
like this offer education for
everyone, not just the rich.
It's places like this
that make America
truly the land of the free.
What?
You're staring at me.
Is something on my face or?
- No, I'm not.
I'm not, I'm really not.
Okay, I was a little bit.
Sorry, I just...
You're just different.
I haven't seen you this
passionate in a while.
- You haven't seen
me in a while.
- Sort of, yeah.
Kinda.
So, okay, bear with me.
I get it, libraries
are important,
but they built a new one on
Parkside and they've already
moved all the books over, so
what's this really about, Josh?
- Some of my earliest memories
are my mom bringing
me to story time.
She loved books and this
place in particular.
Growing up spending
so many hours here,
after she died I guess I liked
to go and sit in her favorite
spot in the reading room
just to feel closer to her.
- How could I not know that?
- Why would you know that?
- No reason.
- Hey, we have a bunch
of water and snacks.
Where do you want them?
- Uh, listen, how about
you deal with that,
and I'll go motivate
the sign painting crew.
- Oh, thanks.
- Yeah.
Sounds like they're ready.
- Why are the cops here?
I have a permit for this.
- It's okay, I got it.
- Yeah, you really got it.
Thanks for bailing
me out, Mr. H,
but you really didn't need to.
My dad, he'd come pick me up
as soon as he got off work.
- Nah, I figure you're
good for the 50 bucks.
We'll drop you at your house,
but don't even think
about skipping town.
- We will find you.
- Don't worry about my parents.
They're harmless.
Oh, you're not.
Come on, what are
you doing here?
- Are you kidding me?
I'm here to witness the
utter demise of my saintly,
perfect, straight-A,
favorite child sister.
I wouldn't miss this
if you threatened me
with the Hydralon
Seven torture pod.
- Okay, smart guy.
First of all, I do not
consider this my utter demise.
Second of all, there's
no way I'm the favorite.
- Quit sniping, you two.
You know your father and
I don't have favorites.
You're my favorite.
- I'm standing right here.
- Excuse me if I'm a little
bias toward the offspring
who will not be spending
time in front of a judge.
- That's not gonna age well.
- Besides, honey, I'm sure you
are your father's favorite.
- I hate to break it
to you, buttercup,
but I just wanted a dog.
If your mother wasn't allergic
both of you kids would
be cocker spaniels.
Who's a good boy?
That's my little puppy.
- Oh, Mom, I can help
clear if you want.
- Oh, no, honey, you relax.
You must be exhausted.
- From jail.
- We're getting a lotta
mileage outta this one.
- For at least a
couple more days, yeah.
- Mm hm, got you.
- Hey, it's our song.
- Aw!
- Come on, come on.
You have to.
We must dance.
- No.
- Honey, if we don't stop
you won't get dessert.
- I have everything
sweet I need right here.
- I'm gonna throw up.
Can you please just get a room?
- I did, a bunch of 'em.
So as long as I'm paying
the mortgage here,
I'll dance with my wife.
- Nope, still happening.
- I just don't feel good about
you going in there alone.
- I'm not alone, Mom.
I have you guys.
- We should've called
your dad's friend.
What's his name?
Helped us with
the room addition.
- Yeah, Sid Lawrence.
Smart fella.
He works close by.
We could get him
here pretty quick.
- Daddy, I love you, your
friend is a paralegal,
and this is just a
preliminary hearing.
Josh and I will be fine.
- I just don't want
you to do anything
that's gonna get you in trouble.
- But don't worry
if anything happens,
we'll visit you in prison.
- Prison.
- Boys, this is serious.
- I am serious.
- Okay, family, family.
Hi, focus.
I've got this, okay?
- Just don't push it.
You're not a lawyer yet.
- Sure.
Come on.
- In the case of Maggie
Hartman and Josh Turner,
do you have representation?
- Your Honor, I'll be
acting as my own attorney.
- Oh, boy, here we go.
- I would also like to speak
on behalf of Mr. Turner.
- Could we have a moment please?
- Why not?
I doubt any of us wants to get
out of here at decent hour.
- Ah, thank you, Your Honor.
What do you think you're doing?
I thought we just plead guilty
and do community
service or something?
- No, we don't wanna do that.
I've got this.
- That's what you
said yesterday.
- Okay, I can understand
your skepticism, Josh.
I need you to trust me.
Can you do that?
- Mr. Turner, do you suppose
we will be continuing
with these proceedings
anytime soon?
- I also would like Miss
Hartman to represent me.
- Very well.
What do you have to
say for yourselves?
- Your Honor,
we are being charged with
the incitement of civil
disorder, is that right?
- You are correct, young lady.
- So, the definition of
this infraction is willfully
causing or creating
an impediment with
the sole intention
of interfering with a
law enforcement officer
carrying out their
official duties.
Is that right?
- Well, at least you've done
your research on the charges,
which is more than 90% of
people who represent themselves.
But Miss Hartman,
do you have a point
that actually
addresses this charge?
- I do, Your Honor,
submitted into evidence
is the authorized permit for
the rally at the library.
- I see, and?
- Well, given that the permit
for the rally is valid,
the issue of underlying
cause is absent.
Therefore, as issued in the
State of Illinois versus Camden,
the lack of underlying
causes renders
the subsequent arrest invalid.
I move that this case be
dismissed with prejudice.
- Hm, well, this
certainly took a turn.
Illinois versus Camden you say?
Good reference.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- Underlying cause is
quite relevant here.
With that in mind, I'm
going to rule in your favor.
This case is dismissed
with prejudice,
and the arrests
shall be stricken.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
Um, Your Honor, while I
have the court's attention,
I would like to beg a moment
of your indulgence if I may.
- Oh, dear.
there is an issue
of grave importance
that I'd like to discuss.
- Hm, this afternoon
is turning out
much differently than expected.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
We believe that
the very character
of this town can be
found in the old library.
Yes, the plaster is
cracked, the paint is faded,
but there's a good foundation.
And the library is important
not only to the history
of our town, but to
each of us individually.
And currently, bulldozers are
set to destroy this building.
Now, I have here
paperwork to file
a temporary restraining
order against the demolition
of the library at
Main and Grand.
May I approach?
- You may do so.
You know as a child,
that library was where
I learned to read.
I have to admit it's
not often I'm surprised,
but you, Miss Hartman,
have done just that.
All your T's are crossed
and your I's are dotted.
Very well.
Unless evidence to the
contrary is presented
as to why demolition of
the library is imperative,
a temporary restraining
order is granted for 14 days.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- Where did that come from?
- I uh, I watch a
lot of Law and Order.
- You must.
- That was my daughter.
- Hi.
- She did it!
She saved the library.
- Hey, buddy, back off the girl.
It's bad enough you
got her arrested.
- Okay, wow, wow.
First of all, the girl, hi.
Second, Josh didn't
get me arrested.
It was the other way around.
- I don't think that
matters to my father.
I had to spend the better
part of my morning explaining
why I'm dating a jailbird.
- A jail, sheesh.
A jailbird, seriously?
- You can explain it to him.
He has requested
that you join us
for dinner tonight at the club.
- Your dad did?
- Yeah.
- Wow, okay, yeah.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
- It won't be so bad.
I'll see you tonight.
- Okay, bye.
- Objection, overruled!
- Oh, hi.
Hi, you.
- Oh, you were a boss out there.
Okay, so, your friend
Josh, he's a cutie.
I was thinking about
asking him out.
What do you think?
- Yeah, you know what?
He is great and you're great,
so that would be, that's...
Why wouldn't that be great?
- Awesome possum.
Okay, I'm gonna see if
I can catch up with him.
- Okay.
- You getting in or are we
camping in the parking lot?
- I mean, honestly, Dad, at
this point I'd take either one.
- Right?
- So, what's this
nonsense I hear
about my son's girlfriend
getting arrested?
- Oh, that, yes.
Well, um, the case
has been dismissed
and the arrest has
been expunged, so it's-
- Expunged?
- It's expunged.
- This is how you kids
are talking these days?
- Oh, .
No, I just meant that
it's been totally like,
like, like wiped
from the record, so.
- Okay, well that's
fine and good.
But why were you even
there in the first place?
- Oh, I was helping a friend.
He's trying to save the library.
- Why?
I personally donated money
to the new library
out in Parkside.
It's much better, trust me.
- Well, you know, just
because there's a new library
doesn't mean we have to let
developers bulldoze the old one.
- Oh boy.
- When did developers
become a dirty word?
This country was
built by developers.
- Okay, nobody's saying
developers are evil, Dad.
So, can we please save
the lecture about how
the first vehicles on the
road to progress were...
Okay.
- Michael Williams is trying
to turn that property
into something useful.
And he's a friend.
- Is he?
Is he a friend that
you do business with?
I'm just curious.
- Yes, I plan to
invest in the project.
And do you know how
much tax revenue
this new development
will bring into the city?
In addition to a community
center for at risk youth.
Housing for low income seniors.
- What Maggie came here to
say is that it was a mistake
being there and she's sorry.
- No, no, it's not.
The situation was blown
out of proportion.
It was not a
mistake to be there.
And I am not sorry.
- But she's never done
this sorta thing before,
so let's just cut
her some slack.
- Some slack he says.
I never needed slack.
- Thank you.
- Looks great, mm.
- Well, I'm so sorry to have
caused problems for you.
I would at very least like to
hear more about the project.
- Okay then.
Maybe this girlfriend of yours
has some sense after all.
Dig in.
- Are you okay?
- I just wanna make so
much money that I never
have to hear one of his
condescending lectures again.
- Hey, you will, okay?
I know that you will.
- I'm glad at least
you believe in me.
Thank you for that.
Promise me you won't let
me turn into him, okay?
- Yeah, I promise.
Hey.
- Oh, hey, honey.
- What you doing?
- Just looking at
pictures for the party.
Oh, will you look at that.
Were you old enough to remember?
That summer your father grew
that handlebar mustache.
- Seriously?
- Ugh.
- Wow.
- Aw, there it is.
That is where your
father proposed.
- Huh.
How did you know that he
was the one do you think?
- Oh, I don't know if he is.
- What do you mean,
what does that mean?
Are you guys having problems?
- No, honey, no, it's
nothing like that.
- Okay.
- No.
I adore your father.
And he had better
say the same for me.
But I think this notion of the
one does people a disservice.
It gives folks the idea
that all you have to do
is meet the one and then
it's smooth sailing forever.
People buy into that and
then when things get rough,
and there's always a point
when things get rough.
It makes it too easy to bail
and look for the
one somewhere else.
- How did you two get together?
- Well, when I was your age
there were several young men
vying for my attention.
All of them were very nice.
I think any one of them
coulda been the one.
Although, your father did
check off a lotta boxes for me.
He was handsome and bright
and always good for a laugh.
But I didn't go into the
relationship thinking,
"oh, he's definitely the one."
Because I think that
love is a choice.
It's a choice we make
on a continual basis.
Hey, is everything okay?
- Mm hm, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just, I had a bit
of a strange day.
I think I might go to
Flannigan's and get a piece of
banana cream pie.
- Ooh
- Always makes me feel better.
Do you wanna come?
- No, I think I
should go through
this other box of pictures.
- Okay.
- Hey, I love you.
- I love you too, Mommy.
Do you live there now?
Are you wearing aftershave?
That's a new shirt.
What's going on?
- So, what if it is?
Nicki and I are going on
a picnic this afternoon.
- Nicki, no, no,
no, no, no, hold on.
I thought you were hitting it
off with um, what's her name?
Veronica.
- Yeah, duh, Veronica.
But her friends call her Nicki.
And now, I'm one of her friends.
- That girl was Nicki.
Oh, no, no, no,
what have I done?
Hey, no, you come back.
I have questions.
No fancy towel stuff.
- Mm mm.
- Come back, come back here.
Do not slam that door.
I will take you back
to the brontosaur!
- Kids, stop slamming the doors.
I'm doing a load of whites.
- Nope, nope, nope,
nope, nope, nope, no.
- Feel strongly
about laundry, do we?
- We can't let Ash
date this Nicki person.
- What are you talking about?
He's finally come out of
his shell a little bit.
- Mom, you don't get it.
Okay, she is horrible.
She's the girl who toys
with him all summer.
And then when they go back to
school she breaks up with him
in front of everybody
at the Homecoming Dance.
It destroys him.
He never recovers.
- Someone's a negative Nancy.
And what's with the grammar?
Your tenses are
all over the place.
Is it too late to get
a refund on college?
- Yes!
- Oh, your young man is here.
- Rick?
- No, the other one.
- Oh, gosh.
- The game was
unbelievable last night.
- Don't even talk
to me about it.
- I mean, we were
completely robbed.
- Wait, robbed, who was robbed?
What?
- The Cubs.
But that's nothing new.
- Okay, hi.
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, right, barracudas.
- Okay, care to expand?
- You know how yesterday I
told you you saved the library.
- Yeah.
- And I was so
pumped about that.
- Mm hm.
- That might've been
a bit premature.
This morning I got a phone call.
Apparently Michael
Williams Investments-
- Who wants to buy the library?
- Yeah.
- They're teamed up
with a high octane
law firm out of Chicago.
Luckman and -
- Seriously?
Luckman, Reed and Baxter?
- No, just Luckman, Reed.
- Oh, of course, Baxter
wouldn't be partner yet.
- What?
- Why, have you heard of them?
Is this bad news?
- Uh, I think ironic is the
word that I'm looking for.
Of course the developer
would have them on retainer.
They're one of the best
law firms in Chicago.
- That's not reassuring.
I'm headed to Chicago
to meet with one
of the lawyers this afternoon.
I barely had enough
money to print fliers.
I certainly don't have
enough to hire a lawyer.
I'm doomed.
- Mm, no you're not.
You are not doomed because I
am gonna be at that meeting.
Huh.
Oh, wow.
You look, you look great.
- I'm sorry?
- Your suit is lovely.
It's a great, it's a great suit.
Good afternoon.
- Good afternoon.
I'm Malcolm Baxter,
senior counsel
for Michael Williams
Investments.
- Hi, I'm Maggie Turn...
Maggie Hartman is
me, is my name,
and this is Josh Turner.
- Well, I'm gonna get
right down to business.
My client has put
considerable time
and effort into the
property at Main and Grand.
Now, we understand that
you might have some
emotional attachment to
the existing structure.
So, we are prepared to offer
you a stipend for your trouble.
Take your time.
- Okay, rule number one
of settling out of court,
you throw money at it
and see if it goes away.
- Are you kids trying
to play hardball?
That is cute.
I have to admit, that is cute.
But I'm sure you can think
of more enjoyable ways
to spend your summer, so.
Maybe this will help.
- Why is he doing
it like that again?
- I don't know, it's
just such a long table.
I, we got your point,
just thank you so much.
- Take your time.
- Yeah, you
definitely took yours.
Okay, rule number two, if a
little money doesn't work,
you throw a lotta money at it.
- That would buy a lotta books.
Never have to go
to a library again.
- Mr. Baxter, that's
not why I'm doing this.
There are more
important issues here.
- You have issues?
- Yes!
I have issues with your client
disregarding
heritage and history.
- Right, because anytime someone
wants to develop a property
people start throwing
around the word history.
Listen, I'm gonna write
another number down-
- No, no, you're not listening.
Do you know anything
about this building
that we're trying to save?
Does your client?
In the 1800s, after Andrew
Carnegie made his fortune,
he decided he wanted to make
the world a more peaceful place.
And he knew the only way to
do that was through education.
So he built 2,500 libraries
all over the country.
And this building that your
client's so anxious to tear down
was one of the very
first ones completed.
And I know as strongly
as I know anything,
that he had the right idea.
And that idea lives
in this library.
I don't think we should
tear something down
just because it's old.
I think we should leave things
better than we find them.
I'm sure you can agree.
- Do you do this a lot?
Does he do this a lot?
Listen, I have
dinner reservations.
And the minute I walk out,
that offer disappears,
and so does your library.
- Well, we hope you
enjoy your dinner
because we will
see you in court.
Okay, we're storming
out now, Josh.
- So, you want me to-
- Yes, please.
- Got it.
- Thanks.
You have yourself a nice day.
- Miss Hartman,
might I have a word alone?
- It's all right.
- I'll wait outside.
- Okay.
How can I help you?
- I think the question is
how can we help each other?
After a brief consultation
with my client,
I'm prepared to take the
offer we made you in there,
and increase it by 50%.
You'd have it in your
bank account today,
and no one needs to know.
Throw in a little something
for your boyfriend.
- He's not my boyfriend.
- Oh, I don't care.
- Okay, listen, as much as
I am enjoying this riveting
little round of
divide and conquer,
we've made it
pretty clear that we
are not interested in money.
So at this point you're starting
to look a little desperate.
- Okay, what is it you want?
- The library, were
you not listening?
- Well, that's not
going to happen.
- I mean, a judge might
disagree with you.
Isn't that why you're in
here with your big numbers
on your little pieces of paper?
- Listen, young lady, I
understand you're having fun
playing dress-up and
interfering with the adults who
are trying to do business,
but I am part of a machine.
It's the kinda
machine that grinds
little naive girls
like you into dust.
So, don't mess with me
because you have no idea
who you're dealing with.
- Actually, Mal, I know
exactly who I'm dealing with.
I think the problem
is that you don't.
How much do you know
about your client?
Did you do your due diligence
on Michael Williams?
Or were you just really fast
to cash that retainer check?
Because I happen to
know more about you
and your client than you
could possibly imagine.
So, I guess the
real unknown factor
in this equation would be me.
And there is nothing,
nothing more dangerous
than an opponent you don't know.
And you know where
I learned that from?
From you.
- Tenets that are
outlined in Kelo v. New London,
and Lingle v. Chevron USA Inc.
- Your Honor, Mr. Baxter is
misrepresenting those rulings.
- If I might be
allowed to finish.
- Miss Hartman, you will be
given your turn to present.
Proceed, counselor.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
Allowing these kids to stop
the demolition is not only
a grave infringement
of my client's rights,
but it could leave the city open
to charges of
breach of contract.
Therefore, we demand
that you overturn
the restraining order.
Thank you.
- Miss Hartman, you have
some thoughts on this matter?
- Yes, I do, Your
Honor, thank you.
The case law that
Mr. Baxter is citing
is only relevant in issues
of property ownership.
Now, the court should be
aware that at no point has
Michael Williams Investments
purchased the library property.
We'd like to enter into
evidence the city's contract
with Michael Williams
Investments as
exhibit 4-c please.
- Duly noted.
- Now, a review of
this contract reveals
that Michael Williams
Investments entered
into a favorable lease
agreement with the city.
In return they promised
to build a youth center
and low income seniors housing,
and therefore access large
city redevelopment grants.
Now, those of us who oppose
the demolition of the library
understand and respect the
rights of legitimate developers,
but we believe that Michael
Williams Investments
quite frankly aided and
abetted by opposing counsel
have been deliberately
misrepresenting
their intentions.
- Your Honor, that
is conjecture.
- He has a point, Miss Hartman.
Can you back this up?
- Well, we've noted in the
contract where the city
is provided a good faith
deposit with the company.
However, the majority of
the construction grants
won't be made available
until after Williams
carries out the demolition.
This is why they're
following through on this.
Michael Williams
has no intention
of delivering on his contact.
He's just desperate
for a payout.
- That is not only rank
conjecture, but also slander.
- Miss Hartman,
do you have proof?
- I do not at this
moment, Your Honor.
If I had some more time
I would probably be-
- Time, time.
Your Honor, every day
these people delay
inflicts financial
hardship upon my client.
We strongly urge you
to overturn the stay.
- Understood.
Is there anything else
before I make my ruling?
- No, Your Honor.
- The weight of the law
leans heavily towards
the validity of legally
binding contracts.
Lacking any new and
significant information
as to why Michael Williams
Investment should not
be allowed to fulfill
this contract,
I'm afraid I have
to rule in favor of
Michael Williams Investments.
Your order barring demolition
of the library is overturned.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
We expect demolition to start
within the next few days.
- I was supposed to fix this.
I was supposed to make
sure it would be okay.
I was supposed to make sure
that you would be okay.
- Hey, you did the
best that anyone could.
- Thanks.
- Well, Miss Hartman,
A for effort.
Now, I do hope you're able
to find more useful ways
of spending your time instead
of interfering with grown-ups.
- Hi.
- Hey, I'm sorry you lost.
But for what's it
worth you were amazing.
- Thank you.
I just, I don't know.
I can't help but feel like
that should have
gone differently.
- Hm.
- At least your dad's friend
will be happy, right?
- Maybe, but let's
forget about all that
'cause I'm gonna take
you somewhere nice
for dinner tonight.
- Okay.
Why would they do that?
You know this actually
is cheering me up.
- Oh, I'm glad because now
that the whole library thing
is behind us, I
wanna move forward.
- What do you mean?
- Now that the case
went in my dad's favor,
I know he can
forgive and forget.
- Sorry, what do I need
to be forgiven for?
Isn't your dad an
investor in this project?
- Not yet, he was waiting to see
how the case would shake out.
Now that it's settled,
he's going for lunch
with Michael Williams
at the club tomorrow
to go over the financials
and finalize the investment.
- He really shouldn't
do that, Rick.
- Look, I know you don't
like Michael Williams,
but it would make it
lot easier on everybody
if you just got over it.
You making things difficult
for my dad's friends,
I'm sure you could see how he
would take that as an affront.
I know your heart was
in the right place.
You were just helping a friend.
- What? No.
And I don't want them to
demolish the library, Rick.
- Yeah, but what does it matter?
We're meant for far greater
things than this town.
And I have seen how
forceful and passionate
you were in that courtroom.
You have ambition.
That's how I feel about the
businesses I wanna start.
We're gonna go places.
So, what does it matter
if there is or isn't
an old library in a town that
we're gonna leave behind?
- Because we should leave places
better than we found them.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Well, talking about better,
I wanna talk about us.
- What about us?
- The term power couple,
that could describe us.
Wouldn't that be something
you're interested in?
Well, I have been
thinking about it since
we first started
dating freshman year.
And three and a half years
later, I am even more impressed
and more in love
with you than ever.
Maggie Hartman, would you
conquer the world with me?
- Yeah, okay.
Yeah .
Oh my gosh.
Cheers.
Dad.
- I'm just texting Ash
so he can come hear
your big secret news.
- Dad, use your thumbs.
- What?
- Gotta use your thumbs.
It's faster if your
use your thumbs.
No, okay, so you have to
hit the key the number
of times for the
letter that you want.
- I just deleted everything.
- Dad.
- Oh this is never
gonna catch on.
Okay, we'll just tell him later.
What is it?
- Okay.
- Oh, would you look at that.
- You suppose that boy might
come inside the house now
instead of just honking outside?
- I mean, maybe.
- Invite him for lunch tomorrow.
We'll celebrate.
- We should plan that.
I know that tomorrow he has
to be the fourth for golf
for his dad and
Michael Williams.
- No.
- Thought I might find you here.
- Yeah, figured I'd
come say goodbye
before the bulldozer showed up.
Congratulations.
- Oh, yeah, I wanted
to tell you myself,
but I guess news travels fast.
- It is a small town.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
- About the engagement?
- No, about the library.
- Right.
I know it's just
an empty building,
but it's about
what it represents.
- Mm hm.
- The power and importance
of words; words are
knowledge, they're ideas,
they're the tools we use
to build our thoughts.
So, they're important.
Words like community,
justice and I love you.
- Josh, Josh, I...
I don't think you
really know me.
I don't know if you ever did.
- I know you're
smart and passionate.
You fight for what
you believe in.
You help where help is needed.
You're brave, tenacious.
You always see the
best in people.
Even Rick.
- He's not a bad guy.
And he loves me, he really does.
- I know, I know.
I can tell by the
way he looks at you.
- Listen, I would
be lying if I said
I don't have feelings
for you because I do.
But I don't wanna hurt you.
I've only ever wanted
you to be happy, Josh.
- I'm sorry, I shouldn't
have said anything-
- Oh, no, no, no,
no, please don't.
Don't be sorry.
- I want you to be happy too.
I mean it.
So, I guess Rick's the one, huh?
- Ah, yeah, I guess.
- So, do you think you're
gonna do a big country club
wedding or an over-the-top
destination wedding?
I don't know, somewhere exotic.
Brazil, I dunno.
- Brazil.
- Nah, you're right.
You should probably do
like Paris or something.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
not the wedding,
Michael Williams.
Brazil doesn't have
extradition reciprocity,
that's why he goes there.
- Why do you know
so many things?
- Michael Williams is getting
checks from Rick's father
and another investor at
the country club tomorrow.
I would love to know what kind
of financials he's claiming.
- Well, we could...
Nah, it's stupid.
- What, what?
- Oh, I was just gonna say
that we could I don't know,
sneak in and steal
his briefcase.
But that's just-
- Yeah, that's the kinda
thing that gets me disbarred.
If I were a lawyer, which I
am absolutely totally not, so.
- I mean, like I said, it
was a stupid idea okay?
- Is it?
Hi, there.
We're just looking
for job applications.
- All right,
go on through.
- Thank you so much.
Have a good day.
- Just some normal people.
- You go get job
applications for our cover,
and I'm gonna get the laundry.
- Okay, let's go.
- Hello.
Listen, I know you
have thing about
wearing other people's clothes.
- What, how would
you know about that?
I mean, not that that's a thing
that I have a thing about.
I don't have a thing about that.
- No, of course you don't.
Um, can you wear
this shirt please?
- On my body.
- Josh.
We're not members.
We have like two seconds
before they kick us out.
Nobody gives the
staff a second look.
It's like an invisibility cloak.
- Okay, Brett, Brett,
my name is Brett.
I play a lot of Xbox.
I wanna put sweet, sweet
rims on my Hyundai Elantra.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- I don't know how you make it
through the world as yourself.
You good?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You gonna live?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm good.
- Good, great, great.
And if I have timed
this correctly.
- There you go.
- All right.
- Nice.
- Let's do it.
- You just have to trust me.
It's not that hard.
All right.
Hi, hey, there, Helms.
Listen, there's a little
old lady in the sauna.
What'd she say her
name was, Brett?
- Vermelle.
- Vermelle, Vermelle is saying
that she lost the
key to her locker,
and now she's headed towards
the dining room in a towel.
So, do you have a
spare we could borrow?
- Are you kids new?
- Yes, yes, we're very new.
- Yes.
- We started a couple weeks ago.
- You processed my badge.
- You did.
- You kids are starting
to blend together.
I stay the same, but y'all
just keep getting younger.
It's chow time, so I
got nobody to take over.
So, take the master key.
But if this isn't back in my
ring by the end of my shift,
I will come and
find you, Jocelyn.
- Hope you do.
You have yourself
a great day, sir.
Okay, let's hit the
men's locker room.
Oh, gentlemen,
I'm gonna need you
to give me just one minute.
Thank you so much.
- Um, hi.
Uh, I just fired up the
sauna if you wanna you know,
grab a fresh towel.
15 minutes in there and
you'll be new men, huh?
Maybe?
Nice and refreshing.
Get a good schvitz in.
Yeah, enjoy.
It's fine.
Nothing to see here.
Just Brett with some towels.
Go, go, go.
- You should keep that name tag.
You seem to like it.
- What?
- Hey, a little bit of help!
- Okay.
- Should we just pull over here?
- No, keep going, keep going.
- What about here?
- No, not yet.
- Why not?
- Just keep going.
- I am going.
- Oh, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop.
Here.
While you were charming
Helms out of the key,
I was clocking where the
security cameras were.
Besides, cigarette butts.
This is where the staff
smokes so they can't be seen.
- Props to Brett.
You are revealing a criminal
mind I did not know existed.
Respect.
- Don't give me props yet.
Tried it, flopped.
- Yeah, I figured it would be.
One second.
I went through a
phase where I wanted
to be an escape artist as a kid.
I kept locking Ash
in the basement.
But I came away with a skillset.
- Now who's the
criminal mastermind?
Is it in there?
- Yep.
- Hi.
- I'm up from billing and
our copier is on the fritz.
I really need to get
these reports done.
- Sure, okay.
- Oh, thanks so much.
Great.
- Hello to you, sir.
- Still got it.
- Oh, sorry, just one second.
- Ugh, why so tiny?
- Hi, excuse me.
Yeah, hi, hello.
- Hi.
- Uh, Jocelyn.
- That's me, yep.
- You could stop
texting your boyfriend.
- Oh, he's not my boyfriend.
- I called housekeeping
20 minutes ago.
Those hampers are
practically overflowing.
- Right, yes, and
that is why I am here.
- And you should be there.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
That's really nice.
Wow.
- Anytime.
- Hey, just give him a second.
- Man down .
That's what-
- Come on, help me.
- Okay, okay.
- Are you all right?
- No, I'm not all right.
- Come on, get off it.
- Piece of cake.
Yeah, Dad, I got it.
- You gonna be okay.
- Yeah.
- And at least it's bandaged.
Okay.
- Ow, ow.
- No.
- Doing well.
- Your son hit me a golf ball.
- I know, well, what can you do?
It's just a little
more this way.
- Hi, there, could we get
medical to the clubhouse please?
It looks like there's someone
coming in off the golf course.
They appear to be
having a heart attack.
Oh, thank you so much.
Bye, bye.
- Okay, come on.
It's not a heart attack.
- He just sprained his ankle.
Did you order this?
- Oh, hi, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
- I was able to copy
90% of the towels.
Here, take these, take these.
- Go, go, go, go, go, go!
- I'm going, I'm going as fast-
- Go faster than you're going!
- Okay.
Have you seen a rat?
- You gonna be okay there?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Excuse me, can
you move your cart?
We're trying to get
in the locker room.
- Yeah, sorry, my
brake's broken.
I'm gonna need like a
second to fix it please.
- Oh, here,
here, let me help.
There you go.
- Oh my gosh,
you're really strong.
- The brake's fine.
- Thank you.
You have a great day, sir.
- You too.
- Bye, bye now.
- You're gonna be fine, okay?
- It's fine.
- I know you
wanted to get 18 holes in,
but wanna just change
and get outta here?
- Yeah.
- Okay, good.
Hey!
Could we get some towels?
These attendants
are crazy today.
- Yeah.
- Go, go!
- I'm going!
- Go, go, go!
- I can't
believe that worked.
- That was amazing.
- Oh, hey, Katheryn.
This is a copy of
Kennsington's Investors list.
Let's see what we can find
out about everybody in there.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- Tracey, hi.
- Hi.
- How's it going?
- Good.
I help with bookkeeping for
my dad's construction company.
- Great.
- These are account numbers.
The money from the
city and the investors
should all go into
an escrow account.
But here's the thing, the
account numbers don't match up.
- So, what's going on?
- We don't know.
Unless I like hacked
into the accounts.
- And see, that
would be unethical
and I could not
ask you to do that.
- So, I shouldn't?
- Tracey, come with me.
I would never ask
you to do that,
just like I would never ever
tell you that you should take
all of these things and
bring them to the basement
where Ash has the best computer
and the WiFi is very fast.
- Right, I'm not going to
hack these accounts at all.
- No.
- And yeah, you guys
have super fast WiFi.
- Oh, this is nothing.
When you get down there,
tell Ash that in the future,
WiFi speeds are going
to blow his mind.
He'll get it.
Hey, Tracey, your
shirt is really cute.
- You like it?
- I like it,
but my brother's gonna love it.
.
- What do we do if
the judge asks us
how the new information
was obtained?
- I find in that
case the best defense
is to get incredibly offended.
- Miss Hartman, we must
stop meeting like this.
People will talk.
- People always
talk, Your Honor.
We hope to give them
appropriate reason.
- Your Honor, I would
like to point out
that we have already
resolved this matter.
Miss Hartman is filing
nuisance motions as a means
of wasting the time of
the court and myself.
- This court assumes
that you are billing
your clients for
everything on this case.
So, our definitions of wasting
time apparently differ.
Now, it looks like the court
is being asked to invoke
a permanent stay against
demolition of the library.
So, have a seat, Mr. Baxter,
and let's hear what
Miss Hartman has to say
before we toss around
words like nuisance.
The floor is yours.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
Your Honor, we are asking
this court to reinstate
and make permanent
the injunction against
the demolition of the library.
- On what possible grounds?
- On the grounds
of new information
that has recently come to light.
If it'd please the court, we'd
like to submit into evidence
documents we have labeled
exhibits F through P.
- I move to disallow.
We haven't been informed
of any new documents.
- I'm sorry, Your Honor,
I'm sure that Mr. Baxter
knows as well as I do
that his is a hearing,
so the rules of
disclosure don't apply.
However, I have made copies
for opposing counsel,
although I feel
that their client
will be more than familiar
with the contents.
- Uh, Your Honor, we would
move to have this new evidence
excluded on a cursory
review it would appear
that this evidence is
unfairly prejudicial.
- Your Honor, we maintain
that these documents
have a highly probative
value to this case.
- Additionally, it would appear
that many of these documents
have been stolen from
my client's briefcase.
- Stolen, you say?
Miss Hartman.
- Your Honor, I'm outraged.
Is Mr. Baxter really accusing
me of theft in a court of law?
I mean, he of all people should
know that such outlandish
accusations without
underlying proof
are slanderous and
highly actionable.
- The young lady does
have a very valid point.
I'm assuming you would not
want to open yourself up
to that type of legal exposure.
So, what proof do you have?
Are the originals missing?
- No, they don't seem to be.
But these two pages are
wrinkled, indicating tampering.
- Wrinkles.
You would like me to throw out
evidence because of wrinkles.
I like to pride
myself on my patience,
but it has limits, Mr. Baxter.
It has limits.
Your motion is overruled.
Now, Miss Hartman, would
you care to explain
to the court what
we are looking at.
- Absolutely, Your Honor.
Michael Williams presented
document F to the city
as a means of securing funding.
That is a list of his
45 primary investors.
We did some research on this
list and it does appear that
29 of them are deceased and
11 are currently incarcerated.
- Mr. Baxter?
- Thank you.
Exhibits K through M show
a series of transactions
between escrow accounts
meant for construction funds.
However, you'll see that
the funds were transferred
to a subsidiary company,
Platinum Holdings.
And later used to purchase
property in Bahia, Brazil.
The sole proprietor
of Platinum Holdings
is Michael Williams.
- Whoa, dude.
- Your Honor, you last time
we spoke you asked for proof
that Michael Williams
intends to defraud the city.
I feel like these
documents connect the dots.
Thank you.
- I take your assertion that
these documents were obtained
illegally as proof that
they are in fact valid.
- We may not have reviewed them
closely enough, Your Honor.
- Well, perhaps I can help
in your review by turning
these documents over to
the State Attorney General.
And Mr. Williams, until they
have come to a conclusion,
you are hereby ordered
not to leave the state.
In light of this and the current
petition facing this court,
I am granting a
permanent injunction
against demolition
of the library.
Court is adjourned.
- You did it.
- Thanks.
Okay.
- Miss Hartman.
I'm not accustomed
to being bested.
Especially not by someone
I assumed was a novice.
- And yet, here we are.
- Yes, here we are.
- Hm.
- Give me a call if you need
a recommendation for law school.
And there may be a place
for you at our firm.
That is if you
can prove you have
what it takes to
swim with sharks.
- Oh, Mal, see the thing is,
I um, I think I just did.
- You were amazing.
- Thanks.
- Get a room.
- This is awkward,
I don't know him,
so it's really embarrassing.
- Well, all is right
with the world.
- Yeah.
Almost.
Okay, you ready?
- No!
- Okay, on three.
- This is my dad's truck.
- This is my dad's spine.
- What?
- One, two, three, go!
- Happy?
- Nope, back it up.
- Nope, one more time.
- Happy?
- Now I am happy.
- Hi.
Oh, you look beautiful.
- Aw, well, thank you.
Happy your parents'
25th anniversary party.
- Oh, thank you very much.
It's all about me.
Hey, where's Josh?
I thought you guys
were coming together?
- Yeah, he was supposed to,
but he is in love
with someone else.
- Ah, yeah, I'm
sorry about that.
- How does that
someone else feel?
- It's that obvious, huh?
- Hm.
- Okay.
I don't know, I don't know.
I, I, I guess I didn't
really expect it
to get this complicated.
- Hey, while we're on the topic.
- Uh huh.
- Can I have a look
at that complication?
- Mm hm.
- Wow.
- I know.
- Maggie.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Can we talk?
Somewhere quieter?
- Yes, yes, we can.
One second.
- So, my dad wanted
me to tell you that-
- Oh, it's, it's okay.
He doesn't have to thank me.
- No, he's furious.
His friend's getting
indited because of you.
- His friend?
His friend who was
gonna scam him?
He's mad at me?
- You don't know my dad.
He hates being proven
wrong more than anything.
But what I don't get
is I thought we had
put this behind us?
We were supposed to
conquer the world together.
But now you're back in court
going against all that.
Why would you do that?
- I mean, it was the
right thing to do.
That's gotta count
for something.
- I asked you to marry me.
That should count for something.
- It does.
It really, really does.
It's just, it's not enough.
I think that the idea of
you is just wrapped up
in somebody I thought
I wanted to be.
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- I know, I know you don't.
I'm um, I'm really sorry, Rick.
I'm sorry.
I don't want a
do-over, Josh Turner.
- I can't hear you,
Maggie Hartman.
Maggie?
Maggie, can you hear me?
- Sweetheart?
Sweetheart, are you okay?
- Honey?
- What?
What, what happened?
What's goin on?
- You must've hit
your head pretty hard.
You were out for
about 30 seconds.
- I was?
Oh, it felt way
longer than that.
You're going gray.
- Are you sure you're okay?
It's been coming
in for a few years.
- All right, it's a good
thing I am dating a doctor.
He's just grabbing
his bag from the car.
- Oh, gosh.
Um, Daddy, were you dancing?
- Well, what do you expect?
It's not everyday we celebrate
our 40th anniversary.
- Ash!
Um, I just uh, I just got back.
- What are you talking about?
- I just got back.
- No way, seriously?
- Yeah.
And you're here with Tracey.
You're here with Tracey!
- Yeah, sis!
We came in from
Palo Alto yesterday.
We have a couple more
months before I can't fly.
- Oh my gosh, I'm back.
I'm really back.
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- Sweetie, are you
sure you're okay?
I mean, that was
quite a bump you took.
- I'm fine, I promise.
I want you guys to
go enjoy your party.
I just need some rest.
- You're sure?
- I really am.
- Let's get you home.
- Okay.
- Where's uh, where's the car?
- Uh, honey, you guys
walked over here.
But I can drive you home if
you're not up for the 10 blocks.
- I think that's a good idea.
- No, no, I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I am.
- Aw, I love you so much.
- I love you.
- And you too.
- Put some ice on
that bump, okay?
- I will.
- You look after her.
- Will do.
Go have fun.
- We did all right.
- Yeah.
- Oh my gosh.
Oh, look.
The library, it's so beautiful.
- Library?
- Yeah.
- No one's called your
office that in years.
Are you sure you're okay?
- I just had the strangest
sense of deja vu.
I thought that, I thought
that we lived in Chicago,
and I worked at this big firm.
- Okay, all right.
We're definitely getting
you checked out tomorrow.
- No, no, no, no, it's okay.
I'm okay, I obviously
know that we live here,
and that is my office and you
are the school superintendent.
- And we're the
local power couple.
- Does anybody
actually call us that?
- I do.
- Do you?
- All the time.
- All the time?
- That's enough for me.
Let's go home.