Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
this party stop
this feeling stop
Okay, Charlotte,
I've got your outfit.
I'm just gonna put it
on the couch for you.
And your shoes,
and I just need
your opinion on
these two scarves.
Oh. This one.
This, thank you.
this party stop
Our guest today is
a Rhodes Scholar,
famed psychologist
and holds a PhD from Oxford.
But you all know her
as an author of three,
soon to be four,
best-selling books
on love and relationships.
Please welcome,
the one, the only,
Miss Charlotte Meyers.
Hi.
Aw, thank you.
So wonderful to see you.
So nice to see you.
Oh, sit down.
Thank you, wow.
So Charlotte,
tell us about
your new book.
Well this book is
very personal to me.
It's about how my
fiancee Doug and I
found each other again after
a particularly rough patch.
Want to read
us a snippet?
Sure.
Okay, let's see.
Oh, this is a good one.
I knew in my bones that
something was different.
I could no longer hide from
the piercing persistent truth
that was desperately trying
to knock down my door.
Doug and I had
fallen out of love
and I didn't think
we could recover.
So your strength comes
from your whole torso,
not just your arms.
What you're gonna do is
dig in with your shoulder
and then rotate
all the way back.
Just like that.
You're gonna have to
use the J stroke, Karen,
or you're just gonna
keep going in circles.
Please put the phone away.
Karen.
Whoa!
Perfect, just like that.
Sir?
Sir, can you dive in
and get my phone?
Yeah Mike?
Yeah we got another
phone in the drink.
Hey Mike, we now have
the owner of said phone
also in the water.
But like ships to
the lighthouse
we found our way
back to one another.
We found our way to
a love stronger,
better and deeper than we
ever could have imagined.
And to find out
how we did that,
you'll have to
buy the book.
Now rumor on
the street is
that you're getting
your own talk show.
Is that true?
You'll have to stay tuned.
And, uh, keep an
eye on my website.
Charlotte Meyers,
everyone, give it up.
Thanks for being here.
Thanks for having me.
So good.
Thank you.
Okay, well we got
your photo shoot
for the Chicago Daily
right now.
He's set up in the
lobby for us, okay?
Great.
Hi, hello, we have
Charlotte Meyers here.
And I'm Mallory,
her assistant.
You're late.
I know, I'm so sorry.
We were a little
bit behind.
You look amazing.
I've been trying to
get a hold of you.
I need to talk to you.
I know, today was crazy,
I'm sorry.
But let's grab dinner after.
Sit, now.
We're behind schedule.
Yes, yes, I know,
I'm sorry.
Oh!
Let's get you in here.
-Ah...
The book is about our
relationship after all.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Come on,
it'll be fun.
You're not
listening to me.
I need to talk to you.
Okay, well what
is it then?
It's just, um...
I'm not happy, Charlotte.
You're not happy,
what do you mean?
Is it your job,
do you need more exercise?
It's not my job, Charlotte,
it's not exercise.
It's us.
I think we should break up.
Are you serious?
You wanna break up?
Could you just
stop for a minute?
Five minutes.
Are you seriously doing this
the day my book launches?
The book about
our relationship
where we-we-we salvaged
it and got engaged?
The book that got
me my TV show?
I know the timing
isn't ideal.
Ideal?
Doug, we're getting
married in a month!
Why are you doing
this to me?
It's not you.
Really, it's me.
Sure.
Seriously, Char.
You're perfect.
You're brilliant,
you're beautiful.
My parents love you.
Yeah, great.
I should be happy.
But I'm not.
I think I loved the idea of us
more than the reality of us.
I'm sorry.
Just go.
Go.
I'll, uh, get my mother to
cancel all the wedding plans.
I could have died.
What kind of racket are
you guys running here?
He tipped my
canoe on purpose.
I lost everything!
Ma'am it's just a phone.
You're just a
little shaken up.
I'm hypothermic!
It's 75 degrees outside.
You just need to take
off your life jacket
and go stand in the sun.
I'm not paying for this.
I mean, are these
canoes even up to code?
Uh uh, you bet
your bum they are,
pardon my English.
They're brand new
and top of the line.
You shouldn't have been
taking selfies on the boat.
You think that's the first
time that this has happened?
That's why we have a
no selfies policy.
You will pay full price
or I will send you
to collections, mhm.
Now when you're
all settled up
join us for lunch
in the pub.
It's on the house.
Thank you,
have a nice day.
Enjoy your lunch.
Why are people always
trying to get out of paying?
'Cause they don't respect
our time or our work.
Or nature for that matter.
Ah, they're not all bad.
I find most people to have
a redeeming quality or two.
By the way,
there's another message
for you on the machine.
Sarah again.
Thanks.
Are you planning on
calling her back?
She's been trying
you for weeks.
No, I'm just not looking for
anything like that right now.
Hmm, when will you be looking
for something like that?
Hey Mike, do you wanna
hand me that ketchup?
Hey bro, long time no talk.
Hi Rob, I don't
wanna worry you,
but Dad's had a
bit of a fall.
I'll be on the
first flight out.
I can't believe it.
We've all been there, sweetie.
I'm sure you're devastated.
Who am I to give
love advice
if I can't even keep
my own fiancee?
But you're upset about
the engagement too, right?
Of course.
I'm just trying to keep my
entire life from imploding here.
I just got off the
phone with the network.
They somehow heard
about the breakup.
Well what did they say?
They wanna put the
talk show on hold.
But just until this
all blows over.
That's it, that
means it's over.
No, it's not over.
We'll revisit it
in a few months.
No, my career is finished,
I'm-I'm done!
I'm done.
Hey, we can manage this,
okay?
I pushed the interview with
the Chicago Daily 'til Monday
so that gives us a few
days to figure out
how to spin this.
In the meantime,
get some sleep, okay?
We'll meet with the
publisher in the morning.
Okay.
You're gonna get
through this.
You'll come out on top,
you always do.
Oh.
Dad?
Hey.
Dad, what happened?
I fell off the roof.
Dang gutters.
You know there's people you
can pay to do that, right?
Yeah, there's toilets you
can flush money down too.
Doesn't mean I'm
gonna do it.
Hey, Bro.
Well the surgery
went well.
I got 10 screws.
Oh.
But we got another problem.
Do I wanna know?
Dad doesn't have
health insurance.
Apparently he lost his
job a few months ago.
Dad, why didn't
you tell us that?
It's no big deal.
I was gonna retire
soon anyway.
Not a big deal?
Dad, your Medicare doesn't
kick in until your birthday.
I just got laid off
a few months ago.
I hadn't figured
that part out yet.
Well how are we gonna
pay for this surgery then?
Don't you worry about it.
That's my problem,
not yours.
He dumped you.
This is not a good look.
I know.
The book is about making
a struggling relationship
whole again.
- Right.
The engagement is
the selling feature.
Yes.
But you're not
engaged anymore.
No.
This is not a good look.
What do you
suggest we do?
Well I say we cut our
losses on this one.
Cancel the promos,
pull the marketing.
There's no sense
feeding a dying cow.
The book, not you.
So you just
wanna give up?
What if I still
wanna promote it?
Oh, oh honey no,
no, no, no.
Do yourself a favor,
stay far away
from that book.
It's a bomb.
Well, um, that's a bummer.
Maybe we should start to
think about the next book.
Use the Daily Article to,
to announce it
and distract people
from the breakup.
I started working on an
outline and I think it's-
Yeah maybe we should
put a pin in that.
What-what do you mean?
I mean, maybe,
you know,
lay off the relationship
advice for a bit.
Jane, what are you saying?
Look, Charlotte, I like you
but I run a business.
You can't pretend to be
an expert on relationships
when you can't even
manage your own.
Now you've always been
on shaky ground with Doug
but it's not like your
past dating history
was that much better.
And when you're
young and single,
it's fine,
it's relatable even.
But the older you get,
it'll just be the final
nail in the coffin.
So what are you saying?
You're not gonna publish
my books anymore?
Well, unless you can wow me with
something new and original,
and preferably having
absolutely nothing
to do with relationships,
probably not.
He's finally asleep.
A support nurse will
be here in a few hours
to wake him up for
his pain meds.
Good, good.
Well I'm glad you
hired some help.
I just wish I
could stay longer.
Well you gotta
get back to work.
It's fine,
I don't see enough
of you these days.
Yeah.
I've got a bit of time,
do you wanna grab a beer?
I think we could do
better than that.
Put me in
this straitjacket,
how am I supposed to
relax in this thing?
Don't take that jacket off.
You're already pushing
it in those shoes.
If you try to put those other
boats on me one more time,
I will leave right now,
I swear.
Relax, relax.
I won't,
you're so dramatic, Rob.
I-I forgot my
wallet in the car.
Bar's on the third floor,
go grab us a table, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
I just don't feel like
socializing, Mallory.
We're not socializing.
We're brainstorming the ways
to turn this all around.
Take control of
your narrative,
plot your comeback.
Yeah but I don't know
how to put a positive spin
on getting dumped.
We'll figure it out.
I have to use the bathroom.
Can you get us a table?
It's on the third floor.
Wait, hold it!
Thank you.
Sure.
Whoa.
Huh.
Ah, I'm sure they'll
fix it soon.
I hope so.
I'm a little claustrophobic.
Woo!
Is it hot in here?
Where are these people?
It's been like an hour.
Ah, it's been 30 seconds.
Hey hey hey, hey,
it's gonna be okay.
Just try breathing.
Close your eyes
and count to ten.
One, two, three,
four, five, six-
No, not working!
Help, somebody help us!
I'd hate to see
what you're like
in a real emergency.
Hi, is this
the front desk?
Hi, yeah, we're stuck in
your elevator right now.
Not moving, no.
Could ya? Yeah.
Great, okay,
thanks so much.
See you soon.
They're on their way.
Oh.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
First step in an emergency
is to keep your cool.
There's often an easy
solution within grasp
if your mind is clear
enough to find it.
I'll make sure to let my
nervous system know next time.
Thank you.
No problem.
So what are you,
an EMT or something?
Wilderness Guide.
I teach survival skills
and take people
on guided
wilderness tours.
Well that's fun.
Maybe I should take
one of your classes.
Eh, it's not really fun.
I'm not sure a city girl
like you would enjoy it.
Excuse me?
I don't mean any offense.
I just, I don't
think you'd like it.
Oh, here we go.
Have a good one.
There you are,
I was starting
to get worried.
I just met the rudest man.
I got stuck on the
elevator with this-
Total city chick.
Just like designer this,
high heels that.
I mean, sorry we're not
all wilderness guides
or whatever he said.
Like excuse me for having
an emotional reaction
to a life threatening situation,
you know?
I mean, she just lost it,
like truly lost it.
She was trying to pry the doors
open with her fingernails.
And then he said this.
He called me "a city girl".
Like it's some
sort of an insult,
like I couldn't hack it on
a camping trip or something.
I mean, come on.
I think I may have
offended her,
but I was just being honest.
I'm so sick of these
tourists coming in
and then crying when
things don't go their way.
Well aren't tourists
your whole business?
Yes.
Well now I need their
money to help Dad.
How hard could it
be to start a fire
or catch a fish?
My dad taught me that
when I was five.
The city girl and
the wilderness guy.
That sounds like a
great idea for a-
Book.
Oh my god.
"The City Girl's Guide
to Wilderness Survival."
That's my next book!
I love it, that's it.
I just need a
wilderness guide.
Hi, I don't think
we officially met.
I'm Charlotte.
Rob.
Ben.
Mallory.
I wanted to thank
you for your help
in the elevator back there.
I'm sure when
you insulted me
you were just
having a bad day
and taking it out on me.
And that's a thank you?
I actually wanted
to talk to you
about an amazing opportunity.
Yeah, we were actually just
thinking about leaving.
I don't think you
recognize me.
I'm Charlotte Meyers,
the author.
Lasting Love?
Growing, Together?
I have a huge
online following,
a podcast?
I'm sorry.
-No?
No idea.
Well, I'm writing
a new book.
"The City Girl's Guide
to Wilderness Survival"
and I need a teacher.
And that teacher
could be you.
What do you say?
You're writing a book
about wilderness survival?
I sure am.
No thanks.
We really gotta get going.
It was so nice to
meet you ladies.
Be safe out there and, uh,
watch out for those
elevators, huh?
It pays good money!
How much?
Thirty days in the wilderness
of Northern Minnesota.
I'll spend the first three
weeks learning survival skills
and the last week will
be a 30 mile canoe trip
through the
Superior National Forest
where I'll sleep under the
stars and catch my own meals.
And it has nothing to
do with relationships?
Nope.
No love, no feelings,
just straight up
survival techniques.
I love it.
Really?
Yes, it's dangerous,
it's different, it's fun.
I love it.
Now you have the Chicago Daily
interview tomorrow, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Use that to
announce the book.
Ooh, and really lean into that,
you know,
single girl in
the city thing.
Maybe we can use this breakup
to our advantage, ladies.
Yes!
Ah, ah, ah, ah-
That's the woman that
you're babysitting
for the next month?
I don't get it, why?
Trust me, I'm not
looking forward to it.
I need the money
to help Dad.
Ummm, still doesn't
make any sense to me.
Do you like her?
Absolutely not.
She is not my type at all.
Nah, I can't believe you're
letting some big city author
write a book about you.
No, no, no, no, no.
Under no circumstances is
she allowed to name me,
feature me,
talk about me.
I'm to be referred to
exclusively as "the guide".
Huh, so when does
she get here?
Any minute now.
You guys'll be nice
to her, right?
I have a feeling
she's gonna stick out
like a sore thumb.
Let's not make it
any harder on her.
Well, for sure.
We're Minnesotans,
we're always nice!
Mhm.
-Right.
Hello!
Wow!
Ooh!
Oh!
- Welcome.
Thank you.
How many bags
did you bring?
You know you're only
here a month, right?
Always be prepared,
that's what my
dad taught me.
You never know what
you might need.
Oh, this place is beautiful!
I'm looking forward
to a little R and R.
R and R, right.
Well, here it is.
It's quaint.
Um, there's extra
blankets in the closet
and I've stocked the
fridge with some basics.
If you want more food there's
a grocery store in town.
How far is town?
About five miles,
give or take.
I don't have a car.
Your legs work, right?
Yeah, I love walking.
There's no wi-fi and cell
reception is spotty at best,
but you're welcome to use the
landline in the main lodge
whenever you like.
There's no wi-fi?
Is that a problem?
No, I've been wanting
to "disconnect" anyway.
It's great.
-Perfect.
There's the bathroom.
You get a solid three
minutes of hot water a day
so use your time wisely.
There's no mirror in here.
And?
Just an observation.
All right you should
get some sleep.
We start early tomorrow.
Great, I'm an early riser.
Five a.m.
That's, uh, practically
sleeping in for me.
Okay.
Good night.
Basics, huh?
What can I make with
a tomato, an onion,
a cucumber and beef?
What about like,
I don't know,
something Greek.
Like a Greek salad
with beef in it?
That would be so good,
but the feta cheese
is five miles away.
Sorry, what's that?
I-I can't really hear you.
Ugh, you're kind
of breaking up.
Ugh, the service
here is terrible.
I've been using
my data plan
and it's gonna
cost me a fortune.
Can you send me
a wi-fi router?
Yeah, you got it, boss.
How's the cabin?
It's, it's cute!
It's-it's really cute.
And since I'm gonna
be here for a while
I was thinking
of going to town
and buying some stuff,
you know,
give it a little
Charlotte vibe.
Mm, that sounds fun.
Yeah, super fun.
What are you up to?
You look amazing!
Oh, tonight's the Children's
Foundation Gala, remember?
Ah, yeah,
Sasha's annual gala.
I can't believe
I'm missing that.
You're not really
missing much.
You know how
these things go.
Cocktails, auctions,
hors d'oeuvres.
It's pretty boring.
Yeah, sounds awful.
Well, I better go,
I can't really hear you,
but have a good night.
Enjoy the peace and quiet,
maybe you'll actually
see some stars.
Maybe I will.
Have fun tonight.
Okay, so, portaging is
when you carry your canoe
over your head,
traversing the land
between bodies of water.
Now, when you're
picking up a canoe,
you, um,
okay, I'm sorry,
I can't.
What is with the outfit?
What do you mean?
I mean, where do you
even get a hat like that?
Who are you,
Indiana Jones?
I like my hat.
And those boots,
you know we're getting
in the water, right?
I know, which is
why I paid extra
for the waterproofing.
Can we-can we
please continue?
Portaging, you were saying.
Yeah, so,
when you're lifting a
canoe over your head
there are three words
you need to remember.
Gunnel, hips and yoke.
You grab the gunnel
with one hand.
Bring it around,
grab the other side.
Bring it up to
your thighs,
and then you use your
hips to hoist it up
and over your head.
And you stand
under the yoke.
Just like that,
got it?
Sure thing.
Gunnel, hips, yoke.
Now you probably won't be
able to lift it on your own,
so we'll just go
into a two person-
Cool, like this?
Yeah, that was, uh, that
was perfect, actually.
Thank you.
You're pretty strong.
I hope so.
I work out six days a week.
Oh, okay.
Are we doing this?
Well, moving on then.
This way?
- Yeah.
Here we go!
Sure, lead the way.
I got this!
Okay, now, the J stroke
is when you-
Is when you want to
keep the boat straight
without losing speed, right?
Like this?
Yeah, how'd you know that?
I did a little research.
Couldn't help myself.
Let me guess, you were
a straight A student.
Valedictorian.
Not that it matters.
Good for you.
I'm getting the
hang of this.
I don't mean to be
rude or anything
but portaging and canoeing
isn't exactly
wilderness survival.
It is when you're a hundred
miles away from civilization
and your radios don't work.
Besides, we're starting
with the basics.
We'll work up to
the good stuff.
Mmm, exciting!
All right,
let's row it in.
You've had a long day
and you deserve a rest.
Um, and we're
actually throwing you
a welcome dinner
tonight at the pub,
so you can come out
and meet everyone.
A what?
That's so sweet,
thank you.
Great.
Why don't you lead the way,
J stroke?
All right!
Valedictorian.
Follow me.
Day one was a raging-
No, a roaring success.
Having successfully proved
that despite my city girl ways-
Nay, perhaps because of them,
I was a force to
be reckoned with.
Just a little snooze.
I am so sorry I'm late,
I overslept.
All that portaging.
It's okay, really.
Although we did
already eat, sorry.
Ooh, I feel terrible.
And all this for me?
It's okay, really, hi.
I'm Tina.
Mike and I, we co-own the
resort and pub here with Rob.
I'm Charlotte, it's
so nice to meet you.
Hi.
-Nice to meet you as well.
That is a gorgeous outfit.
I'll make up a plate for you,
there's plenty of food left.
Oh, thank you.
Can I get you a drink?
Ah, yes.
-Yeah?
A glass of wine
or something?
White wine,
thank you.
You got it.
Thank you.
They'll warm up to ya.
Might help if you try to
blend in a little bit though.
Blend in how?
Well, you could wear
less makeup for starters.
It's tinted moisturizer.
Lose the high heels maybe.
It's a special occasion.
There you go.
I'm so hungry,
thank you.
You know, I couldn't
help but overhear
your conversation
with Rob.
There are a couple of good
local clothing stores in town
if you wanted to get something
a little bit more comfortable.
I could take you tomorrow.
I would love that.
Is that okay
with you Sarge?
I know that you, uh,
run a really tight ship.
I think I can spare
her for a couple hours.
Excellent.
Get some normal boots,
would ya?
Yes, boss.
Is he always like that?
Yes.
Always.
Not a lot of variety,
but I assure you the
quality's great.
Oh, this is beautiful.
Only 30 dollars
and it's locally made?
Look at the quality of
this leather, it's insane.
Just because it
doesn't cost a lot,
doesn't mean
that it's cheap.
You know what,
you're right.
I'll grab a few.
Not sure why you'd
need more than one
but whatever
floats your boat.
I'll give them as gifts.
Ah.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Ask away.
What's the deal with Rob?
What do you mean?
Well, he spends a lot
of time on his own.
His family's in Chicago, right?
Mm.
You and Mike have
each other here
but who does he have?
He used to have
someone out here.
They were actually engaged,
it was a guide too.
But she had an
identity crisis,
broke off the engagement,
moved to New York.
I think she's in
finance or something.
Really?
Yeah.
Really did a number on him.
He hasn't dated much since.
I had no idea.
Yeah, I don't think he
likes to talk about it.
He's a little embarrassed.
Yeah, I can relate.
You know what,
you finish up here.
Okay.
-Okay.
I love these, I'm gonna
grab these three.
One, two, three.
You are just determined to buy
out this whole town aren't you?
The cabin needs sprucing.
Ah.
Is that for cooking?
It's a diffuser for
my essential oils.
Hmm, okay, let's go.
Hi.
Come in.
- Hello.
Thank you.
Wow, looks
incredible in here.
Yeah, I-I moved
some stuff around,
I hope you don't mind.
I see that.
No, I love it.
Oh, thank you.
Can I get you a
sandwich or anything?
No, I already ate,
but thank you.
Are you ready for
your next lesson?
Sure am.
What are we doing?
Haven't been fishing
since I was ten.
I used to love it.
Why does that surprise me?
I wasn't born in Chicago,
you know?
I'm from Idaho,
from a very
outdoorsy family.
You are from Idaho?
Yup.
How the heck did you
end up in Chicago?
After grad school
I got a job teaching
psychology at Northwestern.
And then I wrote
my first book
and the rest is history.
I could never
live in Chicago.
All the smog and traffic,
construction,
and it's so crowded.
I could never
live out here.
Don't get me wrong,
it's so beautiful,
it's just-
really isolated.
There's barely anyone here.
One restaurant and you guys
don't even have a movie theatre.
Hey, at least it's peaceful.
I can hear myself
think out here.
So it's like a,
like a meditation for you?
A what?
A meditation.
Hold on.
Soothing Female
Close your eyes,
imagine you are floating
slowly above a tranquil,
serene lake.
Why-why do you need an app
when you can get the
real thing for free?
It's pretty relaxing,
I'll give you that.
Please tell me you
rented out all 30 canoes.
Huh, what are you
talking about?
You didn't sent them
out for maintenance,
move them somewhere
else for storage?
No, why?
Hide them in the kitchen?
Where are the canoes, Mike?
You're from Chicago, right?
Born and raised.
How did you end
up out here?
My dad took Ben and
I on a trip up here
when I was 13.
It was just after my
mom passed away.
I guess you could say it
was a transformative trip
for a young city
boy like me.
After I got back,
it's all I could think about
and when I turned 18,
I moved up here and I
haven't looked back.
I'm sorry about your mom.
It's okay.
Thank you.
A country girl
turned city
and a city boy
turned country.
We're quite the pair,
you and I.
I guess you're right.
Oh!
I think I got something!
Reel it in.
- I think I got something!
Oh my god!
Reel it in!
Look at this thing!
Woo!
Here, here, hold it up.
I'll get a photo.
Wow!
It's so heavy.
Cheese.
Fish fry.
Thank you.
Woo!
You caught a beauty, Charlotte.
Enough for 10 people.
Thank you for cooking it.
Ah, my pleasure.
Hey Mike, can I
get a beer please?
Mike.
You all right?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I'm-I'm fine.
It, sorry, it's just
this canoe stuff.
What canoe stuff?
Someone broke into the shed
and stole all the canoes.
They were brand new
and top of the line.
What?
Who would do that?
A bunch of jerks,
that's who.
Can your insurance
reimburse you for that?
They were so new we hadn't
updated the paperwork yet,
so we're gonna have
to pay out of pocket.
With money we don't have.
Well I-I can raise money.
It's my specialty.
Oh no, that's okay.
We'll figure something out.
Seriously.
You need canoes to run
your business, right?
What other options
do you have?
Well we don't really have
any other options truthfully.
Then let me help you.
I-I'll start a GoFundMe
and I'll send it
to all my friends.
They love spending money.
Really, you'd do that?
Yeah, I'd love to help.
Thank you, Charlotte.
You really are the sweetest.
Anyone would do it, really.
And send.
Hey, Mal, what's up?
I got some bad news.
I debated even
telling you.
What happened?
It's Doug.
Is he okay?
Oh yeah he's fine,
it's just,
he has a new girlfriend.
What?
Yeah, he brought her to
Sasha's gala the other night.
It was their
"coming out" event.
Apparently they've been dating
for a few weeks already.
But we only broke
up three weeks ago.
And I'm not even sure our
wedding is fully cancelled yet.
I'm sorry, Charlotte.
Who is she,
do-do-do I know her?
What's her age?
She's your age,
minus 10 years.
Is she pretty?
Only if you like
traditionally pleasing
and symmetrical features,
then yeah.
Oh.
This is awful.
And debuting her at my
best friend's gala?
What was he thinking?
I know, he's not thinking.
No.
No, he's certainly not
thinking about me.
I'm sorry, Charlotte.
I wish I can be
with you right now.
Are you sure you're
gonna be okay?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
I'll just fish
my sorrows away.
I love you,
get some sleep, okay?
I love you too.
Gah!
Grr!
If I may offer
a small note.
Is everything okay?
No, no, everything's
not okay.
Not okay at all.
What's going on?
You wouldn't wanna
hear about it.
What if I do?
It's about my ex-fiancee.
The one you dumped?
How do you know
about that?
I may have read
the Daily article.
Yeah, that one.
Well, he's got a
new girlfriend.
Oh.
And he went public with her
at my best friend's
charity event.
I see.
Well, I mean, you don't wanna
be with a guy like that anyway,
right?
No.
No, you're right, I-
I just wish he hadn't
been so hurtful.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Yeah, I know you do.
I'm sorry.
Is there
anything I can do?
Do you want me to beat
him up or anything?
I can do that if you need.
I'll beat the
heck out of him.
No, it's okay.
Thank you for listening.
Yeah, of course.
That's what friends
are for, right?
Yeah.
There's also
something else.
What is it?
My publisher wants me
to go back to Chicago
just-just for the weekend
to discuss the book.
I tried to get out of
it but she insisted.
Is everything okay?
Oh, yeah, no,
she loves the pages.
She just wants to
talk about marketing.
Oh, it's great.
Yeah.
Do you wanna
come with me?
To Chicago?
Yeah, maybe you
could see your dad
and we can get Mike
and Tina to join us.
We can have a little fun,
a nice meal.
I just wanna
thank you guys
for taking such
good care of me
and making me
feel included.
Isn't leaving the
wilderness against the rules
for your little project?
I won't tell if you won't.
Hey, I ain't no snitch.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Mike and Tina
could use a break
and I am due to
check in on my dad.
So we're settled then?
Wow.
You live here?
It's like a museum.
Where's all your stuff?
It's called minimalism, Mike,
it's meant to look empty.
Why don't you guys
bring your things upstairs
to the guest bedroom.
I have a very
busy day for you,
full of relaxing.
And I made a reservation
at my favorite restaurant,
The French.
Sounds fancy.
I didn't bring
a fancy outfit.
I actually don't
own a fancy outfit.
Yeah, I'm not sure I have
the right clothes either.
No worries,
I anticipated this.
before I hit the wall
when it's so right for
been and I know what I got
place where to win inside
the knife falls steel
starts to shine
you feel change
the Wild West coast
so relaxing
off a new line
as I'll go
until I do shine
back the love
and the heat rise above
been and I know what I got
place where to win inside
before I hit the wall
when it's so right for
Oh wow, Charlotte,
what a day,
thank you.
And that massage,
it was more relaxing
than a midnight row
down the Minnesota River.
I can't believe how
stressed I was.
Well, you all deserve it,
you work so hard.
Thanks Charlotte,
you're so sweet.
Well I have to go
meet my publisher.
Are you guys okay on your
own for a little bit?
Yeah, I think I'll
go see my dad.
I'm gonna go
hit your pool
because I can't
believe you have one.
And I'm going
to have a nap
and try on that
pink dress.
Ooh.
-Oh.
Yes, take all the pictures.
Great, I'll meet you
back here at seven p.m.
Bye.
I love it.
I think we have a
hit on our hands.
Really?
-Oh, that's great news.
Oh, um, here are some photos.
I-I think it'd be fun
to include these.
Just disregard the
ones from today.
Oh!
Who's this?
Jane like.
That's Rob, my guide.
Not much about
him in the book.
What's his story?
He's just very private.
He went through a
breakup recently.
He was engaged actually.
Really?
Yeah, yeah,
she broke it off.
Weirdly, she's a financial
broker in New York now.
But like I said,
he is very private
and does not wanna
be in the book.
Sure, okay, well, uh,
send me these pics, okay?
I wanna get them
to marketing.
Sure thing.
Ooh, and your agent
wants to read a few pages,
get those networks
interested again.
Absolutely.
Yes!
I can't believe you let her
style your hair like that.
You clean up well.
You like this girl.
No, I don't, no.
Don't lie to me, son.
I'm not lying.
We're just-
We're just friends,
that's all.
Friends?
- Yeah.
Just go for it.
A little help here?
I'm with him.
You look happy.
I say go for it.
You can't stay walled
up forever, Rob.
Open up,
stop being so stubborn.
Hey, I got a suit,
that's a start, isn't it?
A suit?
What do you need that for?
Ah, we're going to some place
called The French tonight.
The French, oooh.
You guys look phenomenal.
You're our stylist.
So do you.
I feel a little exposed, but-
when in Chicago, right?
You look beautiful.
Well, shall we?
Yes.
Let me just fix this.
There you go.
-Thank you.
Whoa, I'll get that.
Oh, thank you.
And I'll have the steak,
thank you.
I think that, um,
Mike and I are gonna go up
front of the restaurant
and take some photos.
The flowers are
so beautiful.
We have flowers
at home, sweetie.
Not like this we don't.
See you soon .
Hurry back now.
We will.
Come on, sweetie
And then there were two.
Indeed there were.
How's your dad?
Well he's stubborn as ever
but I think he's doing better.
Good.
-Yeah.
How was your meeting?
Oh, it was great.
- Yeah?
I can't tell yet
but I think they wanna
turn it into a TV show.
Charlotte?
Hey!
I didn't expect
to see you here.
I thought you moved
out to the boonies.
Doug.
What a surprise.
Hi, I'm Lara.
I'm a huge fan
of your books.
I have been ever
since I was little
and found one on my
mom's nightstand.
Thanks.
And you are?
Oh I'm Rob,
her boyfriend.
Oh.
I didn't realize you
had a boyfriend.
Well I do.
This guy.
So what do you do?
Well I am a -
A prince.
I'm-I'm sorry.
A what?
A prince, yeah, yeah.
In, uh, Norway.
Yes.
- Mhm.
Wow.
So cool.
I know, right?
Yay.
Yes, well, um, it was so
nice to see you Doug, Lara.
Now if you don't mind,
we have to go speak
to his sister outside.
The Queen.
Wouldn't wanna be late
for that would we now.
Off with their
heads it would be.
Of course.
Don't let us keep you.
It was, uh, really
good to see you.
You too, Dougie.
Hey, it's Doug.
Sure.
It was so nice
meeting you.
Let's get
together sometime.
Sure thing, Lara.
Go.
Thank you.
Oh my god!
A prince, did you see
the look on his face?
Was it over the top?
I kinda panicked.
No, no.
- Okay.
No, it was great, thank you.
-Okay.
You're welcome.
I've never seen that
mischievous side of you before.
I like it.
Yeah well, I'm
loyal to my people.
I'm your people?
You know what I mean.
Well these two seem
to be having fun.
Yeah.
Tina hasn't gotten on my
case once about dating
since we've been here.
I heard about
your engagement.
I'm sorry.
Ah, whatever, it's fine.
No it's not fine,
it's devastating.
I should know.
Honestly, I-
I haven't been totally
truthful about that.
About breaking up
the engagement.
What do you mean?
Um, the truth is,
Doug broke up with me.
He blindsided me.
And I've just been pretending
that it's the other way around.
I'm sorry.
It's just so humiliating.
Especially when you're
a public figure.
I'm supposed to be a
relationship expert.
It's okay not to be perfect,
you know.
You're human,
you're not a robot.
Yeah, I know.
Can I tell you a secret?
What's that?
It kind of makes
you more relatable.
Really?
Yeah, you can be a
little intimidating.
So can you!
What?
You know, Tina's right,
you should, you know,
get back out there
and start dating again.
Stop spending
every night alone.
Put myself out there
and start dating, huh?
Yeah.
- Yeah?
What have you
got to lose?
Oh.
They're pouring
our champagne.
Great.
We should go, don't wanna
miss the first course.
Right.
My lady.
-Thank you.
And my gentleman.
Thank you so much
for inviting us
to the city, Charlotte.
I can't remember the last
time we had so much fun.
Oh, I'm so glad
you guys came.
It was nice to show you
my world for a little bit,
since you were so kind
to show me yours.
All right,
see you inside.
I should get
back to my dad.
Flight's at noon tomorrow?
Yes.
See you here at 10?
-Sounds good.
Uh, thank you again for
pretending to be my boyfriend.
It was really nice of you.
No problem.
I had fun.
Good.
Good night.
Okay, you guys hungry?
I could eat.
Ah, I-I'm sorry,
I should have bought food.
I'm not used to
having guests over.
It's fine, really, we'll
go explore the neighborhood.
Yeah, we'll,
uh, do brunch.
Oh, just one second.
Hey Mal, what's up?
I have some exciting news!
Go on.
Your publisher slipped a copy of
your pages to a network exec,
he loved it.
Are you serious?
Yeah, he's interested
in a TV show.
No, the show is back on?
Yeah well, with a
different spin.
Anyway, I set up a meeting for
10 a.m. back at The French.
Can you make it?
Yeah, yeah, it's a
little tight with my flight
but I'll make it work.
Okay, great.
Thank you.
Good news?
I think so.
I have to take a meeting.
Are you guys okay
on your own?
Of course.
-Get out of here, we'll be fine.
Okay, um, I will meet
you guys at the airport.
My keys.
Don't wait for me.
-Okay.
Good luck.
The book sounds brilliant.
Guaranteed bestseller,
it'll totally wash away
the stink of that last one.
Oh, thanks.
Now let's talk TV.
Yes, I was thinking a
fun tie-in to the book
would be a show where I take
people to the wilderness
and teach them survival
skills that they don't have.
Forget that.
Your publisher showed me
those before and after photos
of those lumberjacks.
From plaid to fab.
And that chunky woman
in the dress, incredible.
I think there's a
real show there.
Are-are you
talking about Tina?
You travel to those
rural remote areas,
you find these hopelessly
single men and women
who have no idea how
to dress themselves,
no idea how to eat
at a dinner party,
no culture, no class,
et cetera.
You get them cleaned up,
you teach them some
manners and voila!
You turn them into catches.
I don't know,
that kinda sounds mean.
Your publisher mentioned
that guide of yours, Rob,
I think his name is.
His fiancee dumped him to
be a banker in New York.
He should be our
first experiment.
Like maybe if he knew
how to carry himself,
he wouldn't have
been dumped, right?
That's not what happened.
I'll have my agent
send over the contract.
I think you'll
like the terms.
I gotta go, I gotta catch
a flight back to LA.
I'm really looking forward to
working with you, Charlotte.
I-
Charlotte?
Hi!
Oh, Sasha!
It's so nice
to see you.
Congrats on your
benefit last week.
You must have raised
so much money.
Most of it went to
pay the caterers
but we'll give the
charity a nice little sum.
Hey, did you get my email
with the GoFundMe for
my friends in Minnesota?
They got robbed and
they can't afford-
Send it to my assistant.
I never check my
own emails anymore.
Oh!
Well, do you wanna
hear more about it or?
If it's important to you,
it is important to me.
I'll make a donation
from my foundation,
AKA the tax haven.
Right.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I got you a little something.
Ooh, I love gifts.
Isn't it cute?
I got it in a little
store in Minnesota.
Aw, how sweet,
it's tiny.
Oh wait,
this is a joke, right?
Oh, you're too funny,
Charlotte, this is hysterical.
No, no, it's not a joke.
Come back soon, okay?
I miss you and your
sense of humor.
Bye.
The air is so
fresh here.
I can really
notice it now.
Ah, it was fun to
be in the city
but it's good to be back.
Okay everyone,
quiet please.
What's this all about?
I have an
announcement to make.
Thanks to the generosity
of everyone here,
and also some people
who aren't here,
I wanted to announce
that we have reached
our 30,000 dollar goal
for the new canoes.
What?
You're joking, already?
And there's more
pouring in by the day.
Well, we'll give the
rest to charity.
Thanks, Charlotte.
I don't know how
we'll ever repay you.
Ah, don't worry about it.
You've done more for
me than you know.
That's what friends
are for, right?
That's what
friends are for.
You know I don't think
I properly thanked you
for being my guide.
The whole deal felt a little
transactional at the time.
There is no need
to thank me.
This book is paying
for my dad's surgery.
It should be me
thanking you.
But still, it's taking you
away from your guide duties.
Believe me, I'm happy to
take a break from those.
You don't like
being a guide?
Sometimes.
But honestly we get a
lot of jerks up here.
They don't
respect the land,
they don't respect
the animals.
They certainly
don't respect us.
Sometimes I just feel like a
babysitter for rich people.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
-I didn't mean you.
I know, I know,
it's okay.
Honestly, teaching you
one-on-one has been great.
You're so focused and you're
serious about learning.
Half the time we
get groups up here,
they treat it like a joke
or an Instagram opportunity.
Maybe you could change
the business model.
Only teach people
one-on-one
or only teach people
who are really serious
about this kind of stuff.
The problem is,
the groups bring
in all the money.
I mean I only live simply
here but I gotta eat.
Yeah, no I-I get it.
Anyways, I'll figure it out.
Right now I need
to focus on you.
Only a few more days
until our big excursion.
Ah, a week in
the wilderness.
Do you think I'll make it?
I think you're
gonna be fine.
Plus Tina and Mike
will be there
to make sure we
don't screw up, so.
So what else do
I need to learn?
When starting a fire,
take your stick,
place it on the
dry wood here.
Here you go,
like so.
All the way down.
Okay, let me try.
Ooh.
-There you go.
It's hard.
I know.
This is hard,
it burns my hand.
Luckily I've got these.
Okay.
There you go.
-It's working.
You started your first fire.
Yay!
Go.
Oh!
That is unfair!
Oh come on, come on!
You ready for this,
you ready for this?
Ah, yes!
No, it doesn't count.
You're disqualified.
-I am the champion!
You can't push your
opponents over.
Show me your moves.
Come on!
Will you dance with me?
I don't know,
I think Mike needs my
help behind the bar.
I'm fine.
No excuses.
Come on.
Okay.
You old man.
Come on, show me
your dance moves.
Yeah?
Is that good?
Oh.
Oh we don't have to.
No, come on,
let's dance.
Look at these
two over here.
I can't believe this whole
thing is almost over.
Yeah.
You must be looking
forward to getting back.
Yeah.
Guess I'm excited
to go back.
I'll miss you
around here.
I'll miss you guys too.
And this beautiful place.
I know Tina
really likes you.
She's, um-
She's really enjoyed
having you around.
I like Tina too.
are dirty some
Well I-
-Yeah.
Better get back to, uh-
-Same.
Okay.
Tina.
What's up?
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
You like her.
Who?
And you may
even love her.
Hey, will you keep
your voice down?
What are you gonna
do about it?
It's complicated, Tina.
She lives in Chicago
for crying out loud.
I haven't seen you this
happy in a long time.
And Charlotte's
a good woman.
I know that.
But it doesn't
change the facts.
You have been making
excuses time and time again.
Look, I know
you've been hurt.
And I know it's
been hard.
But are you really gonna
let a good woman go
because your heart has
been hardened by a person
who didn't deserve it
in the first place?
She leaves in a week.
And since Mike and I
are going on this trip,
you really only have
tomorrow left with her.
So.
What you gonna do?
Oh boy.
Hi.
You're up early.
I'm just enjoying the view.
I was trying to get
some work done but
I can't stop looking
at this beauty.
I can't believe you wake
up to this every day.
Yeah, and it never
gets old either.
I didn't think I
was gonna see you
until later today.
Uh, you're not,
really, um-
I just came by to see what
you were doing tonight.
What we do every night,
go to the watering hole.
What if we did something
a little different?
Sure, what are you thinking?
Well, um...
It's a surprise.
Ooh.
Meet me at the lake,
at the drop in point, sunset.
What are we doing?
I just said,
it's a surprise.
Oh, okay, okay.
I will see you then.
Good, good, okay.
I'll-I'll let you get
back to your work.
Oh, yes.
Very important.
Yeah.
All right, uh,
see you later.
What's all this?
Oh, um, just thought we
could enjoy the sunset.
Just the two of us?
If that's okay.
Yeah, that's lovely.
Okay.
Um, right this way.
Wow.
Oh, thank you.
You good?
Okay.
Ready?
-Yeah.
So what's the occasion?
Oh, um...
Well it's our-
it's our last night in
civilization for a while
so I just thought we
could make it special.
That's very sweet,
thank you.
Sure.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah,
I'm totally fine.
Okay.
- Yeah.
Okay good.
Well the truth is, um-
Yes?
Well, what I
wanted to say was-
Go on.
I like you.
And I have for a while.
I know I misjudged
you and I'm so sorry.
Here I thought you
were this prissy,
stuck-up,
materialistic, rich-
Okay, I-I get it Rob,
thank you.
But...
You turned out to
be the most kind,
thoughtful,
well-meaning woman
I've ever met.
I know you live in Chicago
and I, I live out here, but,
I just couldn't
let you leave here
without telling you
how I felt because
if I did then I would
have regretted it
for the rest of my life.
Did I blow it?
I-I said too much,
didn't I,
I'm so sorry.
-No, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey.
-If you don't feel it's-
I like you too.
on a crooked line
space and time
I've been thinking of
are hit and miss
can't be fixed
I've been thinking of
The picnic was lovely,
thank you.
Well, Tina helped
me plan it.
Tina's a good friend.
Don't I know it.
I should probably go in.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, I'll see you tomorrow,
bright and early.
Bright and early.
Good night.
been thinking of
of the world and
my love
like the evening sun
like the stars in broken ones
Charlotte, I know what
you're gonna say.
I just got a pitch
from the network.
What is this?
It's horrible!
I know, I got the
same email too.
It's disgusting.
Where did they even
get that information?
I asked Jane to send over
a synopsis of the whole book.
She must have editorialized
on your notes.
Well this is awful
and offensive.
I would never say
these things.
Mal, these people
are my friends
and-and Rob is...
Rob is my friend too.
I'm not doing this show.
Yeah, of course not.
I will shut it down ASAP,
tell them you're out.
I prefer your
version anyway.
Thanks, Mal.
Of course.
Get some sleep and don't
worry about this at all, okay?
You got a big trip
in the morning.
You need to rest.
I will
I can't wait to see you.
I have so much
to tell you.
Me too.
Good night.
Night.
What is wrong with
these people?
Ooh, something
smells amazing in here.
Good morning.
What?
Well look who finally
decided to start cooking.
Well, I woke up early this
morning to work on my book,
and I was hungry,
so I thought I'd make you
guys a little something.
I actually forgot how
fun it is to cook.
Anyway, eat up,
I will finish packing.
Thank you.
I am starving.
Look at this!
What's this?
Is that me?
Oh, this must be for the book,
this is so exciting!
Overweight and mannish?
What?
What is that?
College dropout.
Can't afford the canoes
for his own business?
I don't understand,
I thought she
wanted to help us.
What are you
guys looking at?
It's a contract for
the show she's pitching.
Looks like you're
the pilot episode.
What?
Uneducated Lumberjack?
Are you kidding me?
Fianc left him because he
wasn't successful enough.
Is this what she
actually thinks of us?
Looks like she's
been using us
to pitch a show
this whole time.
I gotta go.
Ah, Tina, wait.
Alrighty friends,
who's ready for a
little surviving?
Where's Mike and Tina?
What's wrong?
Oh my god,
that's not what
it looks like.
I can't believe
I fell for it.
Rob, no, you-you
don't understand.
That's not-
You were just using us this
whole time, weren't you?
No, I wasn't.
Rob, please,
just let me explain.
And here I thought
what we had was real.
It was, it-it is!
I was just a project for you,
wasn't I?
Just a commodity
for you to sell
like everything
else in your life.
'Cause that's the world
you live in, right?
Everything's for sale,
everything's disposable.
I didn't
write that, Rob.
You're not a
project to me.
I guess you are
just a superficial,
fame-hungry
perfectionist after all.
Wow.
You are a terrible listener.
- Oh yeah?
And you know what,
at least I can say one
true thing in this world,
unlike you who can't
even say you like me
without having
a heart attack.
Well don't worry because
I don't like you anymore.
Fine!
I don't like you either!
Great! Oh-
And by the way in
case it wasn't obvious,
the trip is off.
You can keep your money.
I'll figure
something else out.
Rob, wait!
I didn't mean that!
Mike!
I didn't write any
of that stuff.
And I don't condone it,
please, believe me.
Have you seen Tina?
I don't think she
wants to talk to you.
Please, I can explain.
She's very busy, Charlotte.
I'm busy!
Being fat and mannish!
I think you should go.
Rob?
Rob.
Please just
open the door.
I-I-I need to explain.
Just
let me in, okay?
I'm so sorry for
what I said earlier.
I overreacted.
I was just
frustrated because
I've been trying
to tell you that
it's the network who wrote
those things, not me.
And I-I turned
down the show.
I would never say those
things about you guys.
If you-
If you could
just let me in
and I would explain everything
and you'd understand.
It's fine, Charlotte,
I forgive you.
Then why won't
you let me in?
I think you should
just go back home, okay?
You and me, we live
in different worlds.
It was never gonna
work out anyway.
You're a nice girl, Charlotte.
But I think you should
just go back to Chicago.
Go back to your life.
I've got some things I
need to do here, okay?
Goodbye, Charlotte.
I'm sorry you're
hurting, Char,
but I don't really understand
why you're getting rid
of all your stuff.
Well I just don't know why I
bought all this expensive junk.
I mean, who needs
fourteen scarves?
It's insane!
Are you sure you
wanna do that?
I mean, this was expensive.
You keep them.
What's up with you?
Why are you so happy?
I'm not happy.
No.
You look like you're
on cloud nine,
like you just met the
love of your life.
Wait, did you just meet
the love of your life?
Maybe.
Mal, that's great!
Tell me about him.
No, we-we don't have
to talk about him.
No, I want to.
Don't hide your happiness
because my life's a mess.
It's just, it's Ben,
Rob's brother.
Oh.
Yeah, he found me on Facebook
after that night at the Finley.
I'm sorry.
No, it's great.
Ben's great.
I'm really happy for you.
Really?
Yes, really.
You deserve it.
Do you want this?
Maybe.
I can't control
the wildlife, sir,
but we did see a moose
and a bald eagle.
You know what,
you should try joining one of
our one week long excursions.
I can't guarantee that
you'll see a bear
but it-it-it has happened!
You know what?
You, you don't deserve
to see a bear.
You'll probably get
yourself killed if you did.
And you know what else,
I don't care if you pay.
I don't care if
any of you pay.
'Cause I quit.
Rob Wilson, everyone.
Just practicing his
stand-up set for later.
He's not very funny.
And yeah, you have to pay.
How can I help you, ma'am?
I don't understand.
Why would you send
that terrible synopsis
to the TV executive?
It's not even what
the book is about.
Isn't it?
I'm sorry, Charlotte,
but I'm genuinely surprised
by your reaction.
That's what I got
from the pages.
I never called them names.
I never mocked them.
No, you didn't
use those terms
but it's pretty clear
you felt your way of life
was the correct way
and theirs was crazy.
These people have taught me some
of the most amazing things.
How to live life simply,
how to cook a
fish I caught.
They taught me how to
be less superficial
and how to just let go of
that need to be admired.
How to survive without
barely any belongings
and how to love deeply
and unconditionally.
Then that's what you
need to write about.
on more than words
of other things
different about this thing
in other places
things to say
leaps and beats
beats for me
acting differently
seen when to speak
little dancing fools
talk about it
leaps and beats
I love it.
Really?
Really.
And you know you never
have to be perfect
around me, right?
Yeah I know.
Aw, come here.
Thank you.
I love you and all
of your failures.
All of them?
Every single one.
I haven't had that many.
Is there a specific one
you're referring to or?
Wow, you did it.
You read the book?
I skimmed it.
You gonna reach out?
Hmm.
Wanna know
what I think?
What's that?
I think she loves you.
And I think you
love her too.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
And I think you
should go get her
and bring her back home.
You know what I think?
- Mm?
I think you're
probably right.
I guess I'm going
to Chicago.
Go get her, tiger.
I know you're upset
about Rob, Charlotte,
but it really is
for the best.
What makes
you say that?
Rob's the kind of guy
you date in college
when things are
fun and light
and you're looking for a piece
of eye candy on your arm.
But he's not the kind
of guy you marry.
Why not?
I mean,
what's the going rate for a
canoe instructor these days,
like seven dollars an hour?
Please, you wouldn't
be caught dead
marrying a
guy like him.
You know what?
A guy like him has more
class than you'll ever have.
Excuse me?
You heard me.
I'd be lucky to
marry a guy like him
but you wouldn't know that
because you're so shallow.
Hey!
What am I even
doing here?
I need to find Rob.
Okay, looks like
there's one seat left
on the next
flight to Chicago.
It's a little bit pricy
'cause it's so last minute.
Just book it.
I'll pay you back, okay?
Done.
Okay.
Thank you, Tina.
I really owe you one.
No problem.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
Ooh!
Do you think I
could get a ride?
Well, sure.
Come on, let's go
get your girl.
Thank you.
So the Watering Hole
is right here
and then the cabins,
are just down this way.
Want me to drive?
No, I'll drive.
Charlotte?
Rob.
Here.
-Yeah.
Can you hold this?
Charlotte!
Rob.
What are you
doing here?
I had to see you.
I was just coming
to see you.
I have been, I'm so sorry,
I've been such a jerk.
Oh no, I've
been the jerk.
I should have never
let you leave.
Hi.
-Hi.
I'm Tina.
-I'm Mallory.
Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
I read your book.
What'd you think?
I thought it
was incredible.
It was so honest
and raw and-
I love you so much.
More than I've ever loved
anyone in my whole life
and I wanna be
with you and
I'll shout it to anyone
who cares to hear it out.
I love you too.
I know you live in
Chicago and I'm here,
but maybe if we-
My heart.
Why don't we split
our time in both places?
I don't care.
As long as we
can be together.
Sorry.
-No worries.
Everything okay?
Ah, yeah.
Um, guys, hey, yeah,
sorry to interrupt.
I just got an email from
a different network.
They're interested
in a show
but more like the one
you originally pitched.
Seriously?
Yeah.
I'll only do it on
one condition.
Take your hands,
rub them together
like that.
Try to get some nice
friction on that log.
That's great.
You're doing great,
stay at it.
How's it going with that
tent over there, Charlotte?
Wow, this is super exciting,
isn't it?
To be honest,
Rob, not great.
Not great at all.
Yeah, not looking too good.
By the way,
when all
else fails,
use matches.
Just make sure you
keep 'em in a dry bag.
Oh, hello.
Hi.
How are we?
on your back
doors I will not crack
so you would know