Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Huh?
Happy Holidays,
my wild friends!
I hope you've been more
nice than naughty this year!
Aw, these lil' buds?
This is the best-behaved
foursome in all of Central Park.
Ah!
Oops.
C'mon, let's go. We've
got more luminaries to hang
before the Zoo Lights
ceremony tonight.
Aw, that moment
when all the lights turn on
at once...
makes me feel like
a kid again, every time!
Me too, Carlos.
Did ya hear Kate talk
about us being naughty or nice?!
Nobody panic!
We're not panicking, Melman.
Well... good!
Because I've been keeping
track of our Nice
and Naughty deeds all year!
Oh, like a chore chart?!
An organizational
tracking system with stickers?
Simple, yet efficient.
I'm impressed, Melman!
Thanks! And good news:
"Nice" is in the lead!
Hey, has anyone
seen Alex this morning?
Yeah! Woah! Wee! Woohoo!
Ah!
Ow! Oops...
There's another
one for the naughty column.
But the good deeds
are still in the lead...
just barely.
Beautiful work, Marty!
Merry Cave-mas to us!
Just wait for tonight!
That magical moment when
lights fill up the whole zoo?
Ah... Gotta be my favorite
holiday tradition!
My favorite tradition
is going to Dumpling Dan's
pop-up restaurant!
Ooh, and after dumplings?!
When we go to Cupcake Bea's
for Candy Cane Cupcakes!
The holidays
wouldn't be the same
without our annual traditions!
This will be the best year yet!
Not best enough!
Or should I say
not nice enough.
It wasn't
a strong year for niceness!
I thought
"Nice" was in the lead?
So did I!
But after Alex's train
fiasco this morning...
I double checked my work and
discovered a calculation error.
Nice and Naughty are tied!
How can I enjoy the most
wonderful time of the year now?
What does a sticker
chart have to do
with enjoying our traditions?
Isn't it obvious?
I can't have a good holiday
'til it's been a good year!
There's plenty
of time today to earn
stickers for the Nice column!
Looks like you only
need one more sticker
to put nice in the lead!
That's true...
and one more good
deed should be easy.
And quick!
Where are you going?!
To earn one
last sticker so I can enjoy
my dumpling, cupcake,
and zoo light tradition
in the nicest,
goodest way.
Ah!
Hola,Lucia! Looks like
you're in need of a good deed!
Here, let me help.
All done!
Guess I've earned this.
Hm... Guess I didn't
realize I was supposed to use
that much tape.
Oh, Odee!
- This is for you!
- Oh, for me?!
Uh... tape's a little sticky.
Woah!
So much for
earning that sticker.
It's okay, Melman.
It was the thought that counts.
C'mon, Melman,
we gotta go if we're gonna hit
all our holiday favorites!
Yeah, those dumplings
and cupcakes sell out fast!
But I haven't
done my good deed!
You can do one
on the way! We're heading
to the tunnels. Bye, Lucia!
¡Adios!
Maybe the chimps
need help with something.
Happy Holidays!
A special day calls
for a special toll!
Had a feeling
you might say that.
That's a beautiful tree.
But it seems like it might
be missing something!
Yeah, our tree is perfect!
But it could
be even more perfect!
This is going
straight to the top!
Bye!
Uh... That looks like
a good deed waiting to happen!
Need a tall friend
to lend a helping hoof?
- Thanks, Melman!
- No problemo!
Good deed done!
Ah!
There you go!
Well I gotta go!
I'm sorry, uh...
Happy Holidays!
Will ya look at that...
It's even more
beautiful than last year!
And smells even better!
How can anyone
smell at a time like this?
I know you wanted
to complete your sticker chart,
but is anything nicer than
a warm dumpling on a cold day?
Look! We beat the holiday lines!
Gotta love
a punctual celebration!
Huh! Looks like
I should've taken a left
at the dumpling.
Let's grab
our dumplings and cupcakes,
then we can kick
back at zoo lights.
Excuse me?
Gosh, I really don't
mean to bug ya, but...
can I bother ya for directions?
This map's confusing.
That's 'cause
your map's a menu.
Oh! How about that?
But! If you need
a good deed, I'm your guy.
Oh! Well, okay!
I-I-I'm lookin'
for a store, a big store
with a shmancy name and an even
shmancier holiday parade.
Whoa!
Fancy Fifth's?
That's the one!
Back in Canada,
the Fancy Fifth's parade
is world renowned!
Yeah! C'mon! Okay!
Well, Canada-renowned...
Whoa!
You came
all the way from Canada?
Are you here
with your family?
I'm afraid it's just me.
You're alone?
On the holidays?!
Well, yeah.
It's kind of a long story.
It's a good deed to
listen to long stories, right?
Consider these ears wide open!
Oh. Well, we were
passing over New York
on our way to Florida
when we got separated.
It was pretty cloudy
and the next thing I knew,
I was lost!
You're lost
and alone on the holidays?!
Yeah, I guess I am...
but I'd be a lot less
lost with those directions.
Well, then we can
do better than directions!
We're gonna help
find your family!
It'll be a little
harder than you think.
But if you could just
point me on my way.
Uh, is it an east/west kinda
thing or more of a north/south?
Will you excuse us a moment?
Reuniting a lost goose with
his family during the holidays?!
What's good-er than that?!
That's gotta be worth
a whole pack of stickers!
I guess we do
still have time before
Dan runs out of dumplings...
Yeah, and everyone
knows the last batch
of Candy Cane cupcakes
is the best batch, anyway.
And the Zoo Lights don't
come on until it gets dark,
so a little
detour should be okay.
That's the spirit!
We'll have plenty of
time for our traditions
once we help, uh,
did you catch his name?
Henry Herbert,
the Forty-ninth.
But you can call me Hank!
Okay, Hank.
What do you say we search
the city up and down
until we find your family!
You mean now?
Uh, ya wanna spend the day...
lookin for my family...
with me?
Yeah!
We can start at the park,
geese love
the Central Park pond.
I'm gonna
find your family, Hank.
'Cause nobody should
be alone on the holidays!
If I was
a tourist from Canada,
this is where I'd go, eh?
You betcha!
Open air, plenty of water, and--
Oh, people!
I love people watching!
New Yorkers at the holidays
are even more adorable
than I imagined!
I don't see it...
Did ya hear that?
That must be your family!
- They came back?!
Ugh!
What? It's allergies, Gina!
You said you couldn't hear it!
I never said
I couldn't hear it.
I said it didn't bother me.
Turns out it does.
Guess it's not my family.
Thanks for trying.
You sure are a nice bunch.
We are nice!
Which is why
we're not givin' up!
What about all
your holiday plans?
You oughta be out enjoying them.
Let's focus on
where those geese oughta be.
Hmm, if I were a goose,
where would I go...
I am a goose, and I wanna
go to the Fancy Fifth's Parade!
Then maybe your
family's at Fancy Fifth's
right now, looking for you!
Let's go!
Wow!
Whoops, sorry.
Fancy Fifth's...
Wow!
Would ya look at that!
- Wow!
- Wow, they're
setting up the parade!
Wow!
Oh, this window alone
is worth the trip to New York!
If you think
this is exciting,
you should see the Zoo Lights...
- Ooh!
- Ugh!
- Hey!
- Snowball fight!
This is so much fun!
Wanna know
what's even more fun?
Finding Hank's family!
C'mon!
Any luck?
Nothin' here!
This wild goose
chase is goose-less!
Places, everyone!
The parade's about to begin!
We roll out in five!
Nothin' better
than witnessing an efficient
and well-planned holiday event!
Except...
being in one!
Ho ho ho!
Merry Christmas!
Santa! Santa!
I was born to play Santa.
I went from lookin' for
the fancy parade to bein' in it?
Ah, I could pinch myself!
Please don't,
I wouldn't want you
to hurt yourself.
But if you do, let me know!
I'd be happy
to patch it up for you!
Any sign of your family?
Nope, but there's
a giant candy cane!
I'll get some for us!
Mmm-mmm-mmm,
not so fast, Hank.
We all want a Candy Cane,
cupcake, that is!
And the sooner
we find your family,
the sooner we'll get
a taste of ours.
Sorry.
I get easily distracted,
just ask my dad,
Hank the forty eight--
- Ooh, there! Look!
- What?!
Is it your dad?!
No,
but there's a giant dreidel!
And... one, two, three,
four, five elves!
I know you're excited,
Hank, but we're here for geese,
not for Santa's workshop.
Santa's
workshop's here too?!
Thank you! Ho ho ho!
Hear that?!
That must be--
Hey, Santa!
Love the new coat.
Ho ho ho!
Alex, focus...
I didn't know
you kids were in the parade!
Neither did we,
'til today!
How'd you spot us, Ant'ney?
Birds' eye view!
Second best holiday view
in all of New York.
First one's on top
of the Park Avenue Hotel.
Yep, you see
everything up on that roof.
Hm, you can see
more from the sky...
Oh, yeah!
Like that big ol' line
at Dumpling Dan's.
Bet ya see that one from space.
- I have a feeling we're
gonna miss our dumplings...
- Not if I can help it!
New plan: Alex and Marty,
go get in line for dumplings.
- Got it!
- Hank, Gloria,
you're with me.
Are we getting
the cupcakes?
Gloria and
I will get those after.
After... we try that
Santa-shaped bounce house?!
Nope,
we gotta do a good deed.
And we're gonna do it
like Santa would.
From the sky.
Mike to Mary Sue.
I'm in position.
This sure beats wingin' it!
Even my cousin Zeb
can't fly this fast!
Hank, look
on the horizon and see
if you can spot your family.
Oh, right, right!
Hank, look! Over there!
Those are definitely geese!
Wait, really?
Yeah-heh-heh!
Now you can spend
the holidays with your family
and we'll get back
to spending them with ours!
No, they're definitely not--
Here's to another
banner year of being nice!
Woohoo!
Guess I'll get
going then, to see these geese.
Who I'm definitely related to!
Thanks for everything.
What? This good deed?
It was a breeze!
Enjoy Florida!
See ya next migration!
Is that a thing that's said?
It is now.
It sure was nice to have someone
to spend the holidays with.
Take care!
Now let's get
our tails to Chinatown
and get this holiday
train back on track!
Hello, fellow do-gooders!
- Did we do it?
- We did it!
Told ya,
it always pays to be nice!
And patient. We're next!
It's almost dumpling time!
Do you think
twelve dozen dumplings
is enough for the holiday bash?
I sure hope so,
Millie, you bought every
last one in the restaurant.
Every last one?
There's always
next year...
I know stomach, I know.
I'm sorry, Alex.
I really thought
we could make it.
It's okay, at least
Hank found his family.
It was worth it.
And if we hurry, we can
still get our annual cupcakes!
Candy Cane
goodness here we... ugh!
Hank?
Oh, hi!
- Hey, there.
- Hank?
What's going on?!
I thought you'd be
halfway to Florida by now!
Is that a candy cane cupcake?!
Sure is.
The way you were talkin'
'em up, I had to try 'em!
Got there just in time too.
This was the last one!
Oh, you want some?
Huh.
Hank, where's
the family we reunited you
with in epicly nice fashion?
The truth is...
the birds we saw in the sky?
They weren't my family.
Oh, no,
so you're still lost?!
Oh, yeah,
I-I did lose my family.
But what I didn't tell ya is:
I kinda sorta flew away
from them first.
I always wanted to see
New York at the holidays.
But my dad always says,
"Florida's where we belong."
So, I don't know,
I wanted to get closer
to the magic, but turns out
I flew a little too close.
When I looked back,
all I saw was clouds.
Guess they didn't notice me
fall behind...
Your family's
not even in New York?
They gotta be
halfway to Boca by now.
Thank you
for letting us know...
that I didn't do the good
deed I thought I did.
If you'll all excuse me
for a moment...
So much for being good!
This very bad day's the perfect
end to a very bad year!
Ah, boy,
I sure messed this up...
I feel terrible.
And I made you feel terrible?
I guess I deserve
a naughty sticker for that.
I don't think
that's necessary.
C'mon, gang,
if we hurry, we
can still catch Zoo Lights!
What do you say, Hank?
Wanna join us?
Ah, I've overstayed my welcome.
But you enjoy
your holiday together.
- Bye!
- Nice Meeting you!
Happy holidays, Hank...
Ah!
Wow!
Just in time,
Kate hasn't turned on
the light display yet!
This'll brighten our holiday.
Uh... It's too bad
Hank couldn't join us.
Didn't we give
that goose enough
of our day already?
I kinda liked
having him around.
He reminded me how magical
New York is this time of year.
Yeah, the only thing
I like better
than the Zoo Lights
is watching someone watch
the Zoo Lights
for the first time!
Happy Holidays
and welcome
to the Tenth Anniversary
of the Central Park Zoo Lights!
May today be merry
and... bright!
Ooh.
Wow!
The lights are brilliant!
I can't stop smiling.
Even when I try.
Look at my face,
am I still smiling?
You're right,
Hank would've loved this.
Remember how his face lit
up when he saw the parade?
Nobody should
be alone for the holidays.
This sure was glorious!
But were there fewer
lights than usual?
Hm.
Sixteen luminaries are missing!
I count 'em, bit of a habit.
Oh, yeah, that's cause
of those geese who came by.
Geese?! What did they want?
They asked
about some luminaries.
Something about needing
extra lights to look for a honk?
You'd think they have
enough honks already!
'Cause they're geese?
Did they say a 'honk'?
Or a 'Hank'?
Hard to say. They had
very thick Canadian accents!
That must be Hank's family!
They were looking for him!
Did they say
where they were headed?
I think they were headed
for the Central Park Pond!
Geese love that pond.
We gotta
head back to the city
and reunite Hank
with his family...
for real this time!
You think that'll
earn you a sticker?
Sticker, shmicker!
We gotta do good
for goodness' sake!
But even
if we find Hank's family,
- we don't know where Hank went!
- Happy holidays, kids!
Wish you could see the birds'
eye view of the lights!
Second best view in the city,
and it was all ours!
But the first
best view is... Ah!
Grab your holiday hats,
we're goin' to the top
of the Park Avenue Hotel!
We made it.
My holiday crew?
What are you doing?!
You're here!
It's a holiday miracle!
I'm sorry, Hank.
We shouldn't have left you.
Especially not today.
Aw, Melman, it's okay.
You and your friends were
the best part of my holiday!
- Really?
- It was my dream
to see New York,
and thanks to you,
I didn't have to do it alone.
'Cause like you said...
Nobody should be
alone on the holidays.
Hey, shouldn't you be
at zoo lights?
Actually, I've gotta
feeling there'll be a pretty
great light show, right here.
I'd recognize
that honk anywhere!
Mom!
Dad! Debbie! Steve!
I thought
you left without me!
Oh, I told 'em
we should keep going,
but mom and dad refused!
I told ya, Hankie,
New York's too cloudy for
geese this time of year.
But that wasn't gonna
stop us from findin' ya, eh?
Ooh, thank goodness
a chatty pigeon tracked us
down at Central Park!
Nice one, Ant'ney...
Great pond by the way.
There were people
caroling there: so cute!
Whether
it's Florida,
New York or Winnipeg,
it doesn't matter where
we spend the holidays,
all that matters is
we spend it together, eh?
This is so nice...
Even nicer than a cupcake.
Or a dumpling.
Or a well-organized
and perfectly timed light show.
It sure is...
The holidays really
are better together.
Yep! Together-est
is even better than Nice-est!
And this one's been
the best holiday yet!
Are you thinkin'
what I'm thinkin'?
I think I am...
Melman! You know you're
not supposed to ride that train!
- It's naughty!
- It's okay, Marty!
We've got a whole year
to make up for it!