Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
The days are cold
Heavy mist that traps the snow
Just a metaphor of us
So many Christmases ago
We had our love so deep
Just like the joy the season brings
So let's fall in love again
This Christmastime
And every Christmas I'll be there
This time of year, we're both aware
We gotta fall in love again
At Christmastime
And all the angels in the sky
Shine down on us as we roll by
We gotta fall in love again
At Christmastime
In the candle's glow
I'm awake but no one knows
Just waiting patiently to hear
The sleigh bells jingle
There they go
And while the Northern Star
Lights the way
I dream of us
So let's fall in love again
This Christmas night
And every Christmas I'll be there
This time of year, we're both aware
We gotta fall in love again
At Christmastime
And all the angels in the sky
Shine down on us as we roll by
We gotta fall in love again
At Christmastime
Fall in love
Fall in love with the feeling
Fall in love, fall in love
Trust, believe
We can fall in love again
-At Christmastime
-Time
Help me sing it again
Fall in love, fall in love
'Tis the season
Don't forget there's a reason
We gotta fall in love again
At Christmastime
Oh, baby, we gotta fall
Christmas I'll be there
This time of year
We're both aware
Boy, we gotta fall in love again
At Christmastime
And all the angels in the sky
Shine down on us as we roll by
We gotta fall in love again
This Christmastime
-And oh, baby, we gotta fall
-We gotta fall
In love at Christmastime
Let's go.
-I say we pray
-Pray
Come on.
Pray that we will find
-We will find
-Pray that you find.
-Love for all mankind
-All mankind
-This Christmastime
-What the world really needs.
-We all need grace
We all need
-To heal our troubled mind
-Grace
-It's not that hard to find
-Not that
This Christmas.
-Not that hard to find
-This Christmastime
-Everyone together we pray
-Come on.
-Pray that we will find
Unconditional love.
Love for all mankind
We need it right now, y'all!
This Christmastime
We
We all need
Grace upon grace upon grace
To heal our troubled mind
It's not that hard to find
It is Christmastime
Listen. More than ever before,
-love needs to be something we do…
-Time
…not something we say.
-This holiday season,
let's give love away.
Christmas
Wow.
And now, walking offstage
after an incredible performance
of a brand-new single
for the holiday season,
"Fall In Love At Christmas,"
it is the global icon.
At home, she's a loving mother.
To the rest of us, she's
one of the world's greatest artists.
But this time every year,
she wears a different crown
as the undisputed Queen of Christmas.
It ain't official until she calls it.
So tonight, on Apple TV+,
we celebrate the season with the one,
the only
-Mariah Carey.
-Hey.
-Here we are again.
-Here we are.
-Merry Christmas. Merry magical Christmas.
-Merry magical Christmas, yes.
-Happy Holidays.
This is a wonderful queendom
you've created once again.
And here we are, just surrounded
by music and by creativity.
I kinda wanna remind both of us
where we were a year ago.
Well, I mean, it was really tough
trying to put everything together
for the Christmas special last year.
You put so much heart and soul into that.
Did you watch it last Christmas?
Watch it with the family?
Of course, we watched it. It was fun.
I mean, the kids were there.
It was a whole moment.
Even my dogs were there.
This year, we couldn't bring the dogs.
I don't know.
There was some drama with the permit
-or some nonsense.
-Right.
-The dogs liked me. I met the dogs.
-They love you.
Yeah. They like--
Zane, you couldn't pull through
for the dogs?
I tried. They wouldn't let 'em on set.
I wanted the dogs here.
Mutley is so mad.
He's not happy.
Cha Cha will never forgive you.
-They're so your dogs.
-They are.
So your dogs.
What are some of your fondest
memories of last year?
I ended up doing this project
called the Butterfly Lounge,
where I wrote this song,
"Fall In Love At Christmas,"
'cause my band was all based
out of Atlanta.
So we were there writing new songs,
and Kirk Franklin came in,
and he just kinda listened to it
and vibed with it
and took it home and did what he does,
which is his magic.
So, it's just a fun--
what I would call a love song.
-It's like a Christmas love song.
-Yeah.
-It reaches people.
-It's about this time.
I feel like it's about
what we're going through.
That lyric at the end
that Kirk says, you know,
"More than ever before,
love is to be something
-we do, not something we say."
-We say.
"This holiday let's give love away."
That's a beautiful sentiment.
It gave me chills when I first heard it.
And I was just so excited that we have
this moment to perform it together.
The single is out. You know,
sometimes these collaborations happen
and they're cool for the moment,
but sometimes they're meant to be,
and I really love the journey
the song takes you on
from love song to spirituality and world.
How was performing it tonight?
-Like, the band is incredible.
-Yeah.
I, personally, like-- The blessing
that I take from this moment
is that I was able to get back
to the singer-songwriter of it all,
rather than, like,
schlepping around the world.
-No offense to schlepping. But--
-You've schlepped.
And we'll schlep again, maybe,
in a fun way.
But no. This is--
So many Easter eggs in this conversation.
This is the best Mariah Carey
interview ever.
Within ten seconds you were like,
"I'm making new music."
Within five minutes,
"I may do some schlepping."
-This is the best.
-They know what I mean.
It's never schlepping when the fans
are there. That's the goal.
-One hundred percent.
-Know what I mean?
But it's been cool to sit back and go,
-"I wanna write something new."
-To create.
To create, to produce, to write, to do
all the things that I really love doing.
-Yeah.
-And with such amazing musicians.
I gotta ask you how the book
has influenced that.
Because when we spoke last year,
we talked about space, remember?
-Yeah.
-We talked about freeing up
a lot of the energy you hold on to.
To me, that would influence the music.
Influence the art.
-Yes.
-And has it?
I believe so, yeah. The goal is
to emancipate that little girl.
Little Mariah. My little-girl self.
And so, I think a lot of that
really did happen.
A lot of healing happened during that.
And it's been really cool because
we've been filming the whole time,
so it's like-- it's so not
this moment of glamour.
It's behind the scenes, writing, whatever.
Mutley and Cha Cha are there.
The kids make--
Sweatpants. Hoodies.
-You think I'm lying?
-I think you're telling the truth.
I don't know if I'm in sweatpants
and hoodies, but definitely pj's.
-That's been my COVID attire.
-All right.
I think this is the first time I've put
anything that clings on for 18 months.
-I was planning--
-I'm not used to the shoes anymore.
-Seriously, what are we doing here?
-I'm here to bring joy to the world.
And you do that.
One of the great moments
in the Mariah Carey
Magical Christmas Special
is this anthem,
"All I Want For Christmas Is You,"
and the performance that you did.
What was your goal
with that timeless song?
What did you want to
really bring out of it for the special?
Well, I feel like because we were all
just going through so much.
And I just wanted that song
to uplift people.
I really felt like
I was on a mission, like,
I can't not celebrate Christmas
with the world.
And guess what?
This year, "All I Want For Christmas
Is You" is now certified Diamond.
I don't know, the song itself matters
to me on a level that goes beyond, like,
the sales and all those other things.
Because I've grown to love it more.
I've grown to be able to be like,
"Okay, you know, I'm listening to it
for the love of the song."
-Yeah.
-I used to sit there and listen to it
when I first wrote it and recorded it
and pick it apart.
And go, "Ugh. Why did I keep that?
Why did I do this?" You know,
-I do that…
-Of course.
…but it's become a thing
where I think I appreciate it
in the same way that people
who aren't me…
-Yeah.
-…who like the song appreciate it.
How do you get yourself into a space
in the studio
where you're able to listen to these songs
that have been sung for generations
and do it in a way
that feels really authentic to you?
I have to have decorations.
So I had this room fully decorated
downstairs in the house.
Then, I don't know,
whoever was doing the tree, they were
totally bleak and took the tree down.
I was like, "Really?
They're gonna take my tree down?"
-Who takes a tree down?
-Some scrooge. Whatever.
And I was like,
"Now they want me to finish the song.
-How am I supposed to do it?" Luckily--
-Christmas is closed for business
-There you go.
You can start that one.
-I was just--
-But I had my blanket,
that's, my new Christmas merch, and I was
like, "Let me put that in there."
So I put it in the studio
and put it on my doggy
and my little plush toy and I was like,
"Okay, look, I guess I can look at that."
-These are beautiful, though.
-They are beautiful.
-Yeah. The whole vibe.
-I wanted to ask you whether
these meet your standard
of tree decoration.
-Absolutely. Yes.
-Right. 'Cause there are dos and don'ts.
Well, I would've had butterflies on it
if I had been able to come here
a day before with my art director's hat on
and just kinda tweak things.
-A little reverse engineering.
-Yeah.
I mean, I have no problem doing that.
But what can I do?
I can't put these thoughts
in people's minds.
You can come and take the tree away.
I have to ask a cheeky question
because, gosh darn it,
-you've dropped enough hints.
-Oh, no. Cheeky.
-You've dropped enough hints.
-Yes.
Are we hopeful we're gonna hear
something new
from you sooner rather than later?
Are we hopeful?
I can't speak for anyone but me.
-I'm working. I'm in the studio, yeah.
-Right.
I have another project
that I'm very excited about.
I don't wanna say, 'cause then people
are like, "Who is it?" and whatever.
But already some people that are just--
It's been a lifelong dream to work with.
-Wow.
-So, yeah.
This incredible event
that you've created for the ages,
it's gonna be around forever.
One thing always really stood out to me,
which was that you got to share
a moment in there with your kids.
I know.
-How special was that?
-That was the best. No, it was the best.
Because forever,
we'll have that memory together.
-Yeah.
-You know?
But, by the way, they are here
and they're very patient.
-So, they wanted to come say hi to you.
-Hey!
-Roc and Roe!
-What's going on?
-Here's Miss Monroe.
-Hi.
-Nice to meet you.
-And RocStar.
Nice to meet you.
Look at the back.
But we have to discuss this.
-Look at this!
-Come on.
You guys with the merch game.
The hoodies.
Wow, the fit is awesome.
-You're on-brand. They're oversize.
-Yes. Yes.
-It's great to meet you. Merry Christmas.
-Merry Christmas.
Your favorite time of year,
hands down, best time of year?
-Yes, yes, yes.
-Definitely.
-Yay!
-Halloween is, like, number two.
No, it-- Every year, I just have to say,
I enjoy it maybe more than them.
But I don't know. Do you guys have fun
every year or do I have more fun?
I think--
I think we all have
the same amount of fun.
Personally, I think I, like--
I love Christmas. It's my favorite.
-We all have fun.
-Yay! Come on.
-That is the best.
-Last year,
he woke us all up at 6:00 a.m.
to open presents.
-And I was still up from--
-Good man.
-Still working.
-I couldn't sleep. I was too excited.
-I don't blame you.
-Because I saw-- 'cause--
When I was trying to go to the kitchen,
I saw a bunch of presents and was like,
"Ooh! Ooh! I'm ready.
I'm ready. I'm ready."
I was like, "Guys, guys, I can't sleep."
And they're like, "Go to sleep."
Were you mad at your brother
for waking you up?
-No, I was like, "Thanks, bro."
-Let's go.
I love that you guys hung out with us.
-Thank you for helping us.
-Yes.
-Mariah, kids, great to see you.
-Thank you, Zane.
-Merry Christmas.
-Merry Christmas!
-Happy Holidays.
Happy Holidays.
Can I go off with these guys?
Yeah, please.
-You're kicking me out, right? We're done.
-Beat it.
-All right, yeah.
-Thank you, Zane.
-Thank you.
-Bye!
-Bye, guys.
Before we go, Mariah Carey has
something very special for us tonight.
She's returning to the stage to perform
a real fan favorite
for the holiday season,
"Christmas (Baby Please Come Home)."
Thank you so much for watching.
As always, it's so much fun spending
any time with the Queen of Christmas.
And you can too, simply by watching
Mariah Carey's Magical Christmas
Special right now on Apple TV+.
In our final performance of the evening,
once again, the one and only
Mariah Carey,
"Christmas (Baby Please Come Home)."
Oh, hey, yeah, yeah, yeah
Baby, baby
Ooh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Christmas
-The snow's coming down
-Christmas
I'm watching it fall
Christmas
Lots of people around
-Christmas
-Baby, please come home
-The church bells in town
-Christmas
-Are ringing in song
-Full of happy sounds
-Christmas
-Baby, please come home
They're singing "Deck the Halls"
But it's not like Christmas at all
'Cause I remember when you were here
And all the fun we had last year
Christmas
Pretty lights on the tree
-Christmas
-I'm watching them shine
-You should be here with me
-Christmas
-Baby, please come home
Baby, please
They're singing "Deck the Halls"
But it's not like Christmas at all
'Cause I remember when you were here
And all the fun we had last year
Christmas
If there was a way
-Christmas
-I'd hold back this tear
-But it's Christmas day
-Please
-Please, please
-Baby, please come home
Christmas
-Christmas
Baby, please
-Why don't you, why don't you
-Baby, please
-Christmas
Baby, won't you please come home
Merry Christmas, everyone.