Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Exhibited by TMS , Japan Co., Ltd.
Detroit: 15 years ago
Based on the original comic written by Gosho Aoyama, serialized on "Weekly Shonen SUNDAY" in Shogakukan
Screenwriter Takeharu Sakurai
What did I do to suffer like this?
Damn
WSG Boston will be opening soon
But the stadium is still under construction
Live broadcast of the Boston World Games Boston Stadium
I'm curious before opening day
Can it be solved smoothly?
Live broadcast of the Boston World Games Boston Stadium
If the stadium can't be finished
The whole country will be very angry, won't it?
I'm very sure of that
get out of the way
This vacuum superconducting fast train
Its maximum operating speed
Reaching 1000 kilometers !
Vacuum superconducting magnetic levitation train
It's amazing in the blink of an eye
It was incredible
People can't wait to ride
Tokyo World Sports Association Sponsors Shuanggui Asosiasi Association
Thank you so much for the warm applause
This newly developed vacuum superconducting fast train
From Shin-Nagoya Station to Tokyo Shibahama Station
Shibahama Station New Nagoya Station
It only takes 25 minutes
amazing
Experience the World of Tokyo
But where is Shibahama?
Don't you know Genta?
Experience the World of Tokyo
The elder sister said she would explain next
good then
Shibahama Station is located between Kawashin Station and Okamatsucho . Station
Stasiun Chuanpin
Okamatsucho Station Kawashin . Station
Shibahama Station is located between Kawashin Station and Okamatsucho . Station
Okamatsucho Station Shibahama Station Kawashin . Station
The design project is to be used as a
Dedicated station for vacuum superconducting fast train
Okamatsucho Station Shibahama Station Kawashin . Station
And the venue for today
Shibahama . View Hotel
Direct access to the station via the underground
Shibahama Station
Besides that
Main venue for next month's Tokyo World Expo opening ceremony
Stadion Shibahama
The same goes directly to Shibahama Station
Areas around Shibahama Station
After the opening of the Tokyo World Expo
Will be centered at the departure station of the vacuum superconducting high-speed train
Be the center of the crowd
What does WSG mean?
Ayumi doesn't know either
Etto if I'm not mistaken..
What are you doing ?
Ah, Conan is coming
You go to the bathroom for too long
We got lost while looking for the bathroom
Sorry to keep you waiting
Hei Conan
Do you know what WSG is?
of course i know
World Sports Congress
World Sports Games
Referred to as WSG
Experience the world
It's a sporting event held every four years
Athletes from all over the world
Will fight for the honor of the motherland
Vacuum superconducting magnetic levitation train
Will be officially opened to traffic
First car users included
Attendees at today's event
Tokyo World Sports Association sponsor representative
And representatives of the World Sports Association
Next let's see
Mr Alan Mackenzie, President of the World Sports Association
Alan Mackenzie Age: 64 Nationality: United States
FBI Director as representative of this event
Hello friends from Japan
I look forward to participating with you
Upacara Pembukaan Tokyo World Sport Games
And ride the world's first car with everyone
Vacuum superconducting magnetic levitation train
Mr. Alan, thank you for the speech
other than that
We have one more thing to tell our guests and friends here
It's good, I want to ride the train too
We ordinary people can't possibly be
Ride feel the fast train
Finally!
ara-ara
They are too happy
But is it too early to be happy?
Why ?
Did you not hear him say that there was a lottery?
How high do you think the chances of winning the lottery are
What the hell, stingy
There are still some possibilities
I remember several companies under the Suzuki Consortium
Is a sponsor of WSG
That's right
Let's ask sonoko nee-san for help
You think it's simple
this platinum VIP ticket
How can give it like so easily ?
Don't think about this world so easily
never mind, Sonoko
Let's talk
Right
How many children's tickets should not be a problem
Yaampun
You guys are too good with this boy
Please don't disturb
No problem, right?
Don't get in our way
you guys
You should be grateful to be here today
Okay
Sorry to bother you
Place to eat will be put here later
Can you guys go further to the side?
okay
We'll make room for you
Looks so delicious
children
After taking the food, you must gather in front of the main entrance
okay
Ready to eat
Let's eat more and refund the entry fee
Genta, Only those who pay should say such things
Their moods changed so fast
That's right, too
After all, they are younger than us
Younger
We're both just kids, right?
Then for children who are optimistic and innocent by nature
power outage
What has happened
What happened
Shibahama View Hotel Release Notification
What light is that?
Sorry Haibara
Help me hold the cup
Wait Edogawa
Yaampun
The light source should be here
Conan, are you okay?
Ran Nee-chan
lights on
Shibahama View Hotel Release Notification
I have to go to the other kids
Dad, Dad
If you are here, please answer
Sonoko, what's wrong?
Ran, my father suddenly disappeared
And the phone can't be connected
Wasn't he just with you?
That's right
But he disappeared as soon as the emergency lights came on
Where is he going
This is Mr John
Mr John
Sorry to interrupt your conversation
John Foyd (51 tahun) Chief Executive Officer Cod Japan
Can I spare your time?
You're busy
John Foyd (51 tahun) Chief Executive Officer Cod Japan
Sonoko-san
What happened
that
My father left, he was with me just now
Do you know where he went?
Mr John
I don't know English, Mr. John
This guest asks you not to run
careful
Ran, did I say something wrong?
Edogaw-kun
The blackout only lasts about 30 seconds, right?
The time is very short
Disappear from a place this big
That means it's our turn to perform
It's been a long time since we showed our skills
That's right, too
Our
Legendary teen detective team
Young Detective
Sonoko Nee-chan
Please send us the hotel
Shibahama . View Hotel
Sorry to make you wait so long
Inspector Megure
how is it going
We haven't found Chief Suzuki yet.
Oh it's like that
We use hotel broadcast calls
But no response
This might be a kidnapping case
The goal is for ransom
Conan and the others also attended the banquet
Also said that after the power cut
They saw something like a flash of blue and white fire
Let's hear what they have to say
I think that they use that
for seeing on TV series
The bad guys use it to let go
Something that can make people sting
Stun gun
Could it be?
Did President Suzuki also fall with the stun gun?
Chief Suzuki too?
But
To get the fainted out of here
30 seconds seems impossible
Have you checked the surveillance video?
Yes
Once the backup power is turned on
We didn't find anyone behaving suspiciously
This is very strange
How to take people out in the dark and crowds?
And what is the purpose of that person?
I should have
What has happened
What did you find?
There is a taste of eel rice
These kids
We were followed all the way from the room
Tell them to come back
Definitely smells like eel
But why no eel rice?
Turns out so
Everyone see here
The food urge seems to be missing one
There should have been food in this place before
let me see
Here it should be
Grilled eel with steamed glutinous rice and azuki bean rice in broth
Sounds so delicious
But this is weird
Why did the food just disappear?
Is it because it's so delicious?
So it was robbed by everyone
Wrong
Look, down here can hide people
Could it be?
President Suzuki brought with it
It's possible
That way, people can be moved in peace
If so
The culprit is most likely a hotel worker
Or dress up as a hotel staff
Go to the witness to see if anyone is there
Push the eating car out of here
Then check out the hotel surveillance video again
Well
You guys hurry back to the room
okay
Here
The smell of eel comes from here
Genta is so cool, like a police dog
I didn't know bell had such an ability
You guys don't know
I think I know
It's so close
The smell is getting stronger
hand soap
No any body here
Because the maids accept being interrogated, right?
How about it, Genta?
It should be in this room
I found it
Really? Haibara-san
Food push ahead
It should be the one that disappeared at the banquet, right?
Wow, found
Why is there a maid uniform here?
Edogaw-kun
President Suzuki is not on this cart
Okay
Great must be delicious
You can't eat it anymore
Kabayaki Sauce
Meet
Hospital
What about the suspect's appearance?
I dont see
There was a power outage
I see these children when I wake up
Our Junior Detective Team has done a great job
Yes
Inspector
President Mitsuka's testimony also says so
In other words
Did President Mitsuka have the same experience?
So was this incident really premeditated?
Father, what do you mean by this
The friend I met last week suddenly disappeared
Do you remember
He often plays golf with my dad these days
female president?
Is this the problem? My child's father
Mitsuka Eiko (48 tahun) Presiden Mitsuka Sugar
no
I don't play with him alone
Mitsuka Eiko (48 tahun) Presiden Mitsuka Sugar
But I remember when the police came
I found it in the stadium bathroom
That's right
But he didn't tell us at all
What happened then?
And he also didn't come to the banquet today
The female president surnamed Mitsuka
Is this also a sponsor of Tokyo WSG?
Right
Eiko Mitsuka
Isn't he president of Mitsuka Sugar?
Gula Mitsuka
I recognize this trademark
On Kamen Yaiba coklat chocolate packaging
There is this trademark
Yes
What I care more about than this is
see
There's a Kamen Yaiba Show
The maglev car opened to commemorate the Masked Rider Show
Really, it was the first day of a fast car
Audience recruitment has ended. Thank you for your enthusiastic registration!
Will be held at Shibahama Station
Oh my, I really want to see
right?
But, honey
Audience recruitment is long over
Why is it
Leave them for now
Experience the World of Tokyo
here he is
This company and Suzuki Chairman company
Is the sponsor of Tokyo WSG
The bosses of the two companies were kidnapped one after another
Could this be a coincidence?
hai
it's me
Even though it was a bit sudden
But the world experienced a serial kidnapping case 15 years ago
Do you still remember?
of course
Terrible case
Maybe it will be repeated in Tokyo this time
Yes
It looks so
Detective Conan: Scarlet Bullet
I'm a detective high school student Shinichi Kudo
With my childhood friend Ran
Ono Kefu's Music
When going to the amusement park
I accidentally witnessed
Ono Kefu's Music
The suspicious transaction activity of the man in black
Masato Sudo Character Design
Because they pay too much attention to transaction activities
I don't see their friend approaching
I was poisoned by that man
Direktur Seni Katsushika Sato Fukushima Takaki Ishigaki
When I wake up
Otoko in color design
My body is getting smaller
If they know Kudo Shinichi is still alive
Direktur Fotografi, Direktur Efek Khusus CG Nishiyama Hitoshi Matsukura, Oki Koiwa Kanman
It's not just my life that's in danger
The people around me will also be involved
Edited by Okada Sound Director Teruman Urakami Yasushino Urakami Keiko
On the advice of Prof. Agasa
I decided to hide my real identity
Edited by Okada Sound Director Teruman Urakami Yasushino Urakami Keiko
When Ran asked my name
I accidentally called myself Edogawa Conan
"Edogawa Ranbu's Complete Works"
To get directions to that organization
Detective agent Mori Edogawa Conan nicknamed Takayama Minami
I live in Ran's house where her father is a detective
I also have a good group of comrades
Who is also looking for the existence of the black organization
US Federal Bureau of Investigation Kogoro Mori voices Riki Koyama and Moriran voices Yamazaki and Kana
They are FBI agents
James Black
Andrey Camel
Jodie Starling
Shuichi Akai
Shuichi Akai Shuichi Ikeda Suara Voice Distribution
Akai is the FBI's ultimate sniper master
Dr. Akasa disuarakan oleh Kenichi Ogata, Aihara, disuarakan oleh Hayashihara Emi
now
He disguised himself as a graduate student under the pseudonym Okiya Subaru
Hiding in the house of the Kudo family, which is my home
Okiya Subaru is voiced by Ayu Ryotaro
Her sister Shuici, Sera Masumi
is a female high school detective transferred to Ran's class
Shiliang Zhenchun dubbing metode Hidaka
He lives in a hotel with a mysterious girl
And that girl
I think it's Mr. Akai, Mary
Marie dijuluki Tanaka Atsuko
He might have been forced to drink the same poison as me
Which caused his body to shrink
The man who called her "Mother Mary"
This is Sera's other brother, Hideyoshi Haneda
Shukichi Haneda Dijuluki Toshiyuki Morikawa
Now he is the sixth champion of shogi
In other words, these four people are actually family
And this incident
Produser Hidemine Kondo
Closely related to this family
Even though the body becomes smaller, the mind remains an adult
a famous detective who has to solve a case
the truth
There will always be only one
Sutradara Nagaoka Tomoka
Sonoko Nee-san
This toy from kamen yaiba
Can we really accept it all?
This is a scarf from kamen yaiba
There are also figures
All these gifts for you
As a thank you for helping to find my father
Asyiik
Thank you guys.
I don't have to
Me too
Actually, I also prepared a present
VIP ticket for vacuum superconducting maglev train
What's this
What's that
Who sent the letter?
Wrong answer
Tell us the answer directly
How about this
For the whole country is a Lottery
Able to ride the vacuum superconducting fast train
New Nagoya → Shibahama Maglev Train Opening Special Tickets
Platinum ticket
have
Alright, Sonoko-sama
thank you very much
Don't be too happy
No matter how great sonoko-sama is however
Can only get
Only six platinum tickets
Are there only six?
In other words
one
two
three
Four
lima
more
seven
We have seven people
No, no
With me it should be eight people
Professor is an adult, So it should be put aside first
Eh, how come
Keep going
We have to choose
Others who can't ride
How to choose this?
Of course it's determined by the professor's best guess
why
Because it's the fairest
you guys
Don't think the sky is always on your side
means
Duh, even though I want to go
But there's no way
I don't come for everyone
Okay, let's start guessing the riddle
Everyone will be first in the world
Passengers on vacuum superconducting high-speed train
But actually someone already took it
So, among the following three people, which one?
Lawyer
Lawyer (Chinese characters removed?)
Doctor
Doctor (Chinese script removed?)
missionary
Missionaries (Chinese book?)
This question is too simple
right
You guessed too fast
Ok I want to answer first
Sonoko, do you know the answer?
Confused
That's right
This question is too difficult
Give directions
I can't guess it at all
Alright here are the instructions
To make superconducting high-speed railcars
Floating on the track
Cars need to be equipped with super strong magnets
They are called superconducting magnets
Superconducting magnets (Chinese characters removed?)
If a lawyer
There is another way to say missionary
Lawyer = Lawyer
That's a lawyer
Tabib=dokter
Doctors and preachers, right?
Missionary = preacher
so be it
Professor
Tell me
The answer is
That's right
Very good
Ran
Sorry Sonoko
Okay
Now there are three tickets left
I won't lose to a bunch of brats
People riding the vacuum superconducting magnetic levitation train
It must be this sonoko-sama
But it's so hard to guess
A missionary is a preacher
missionary is
Preacher
Superconductor
so be it
The correct answer is preacher
It is
Third missionary
All answers are correct
Very good
Our luck is very good
Yes
It's nice to be able to take the fast train
And there are so many events around Kamen Yaiba
I have to hurry home
Show off with mom and dad
Oh no
Looks like I left my phone at the professor's house
I don't remember where to put it
You come back first
Goodbye then
Goodbye
We both also made an appointment with Sera
Let us go
By the way, would you like some bubble tea?
okay
What is it
I want to go for a walk with you
Do you want to ride it?
Boyya
ready to go
run
"Tokyo World Sports Tournament Guide"
Is the sponsor of Tokyo WSG
This is what they have in common
President Mitsuka who disappeared while playing golf
And President Suzuki who was kidnapped at the banquet
15 years ago
A similar incident occurred in the US.
I guessed right
After all, even the FBI was dispatched
That's great
I found it online
15 years ago in USA
Ahead of the opening of the Boston WSG
Boston's World Sports Association sponsors serial kidnappings
The sponsor's senior figures have been kidnapped one after another
First
Is an executive of a Japanese confectionery factory in Atlanta
Atlanta
second
Is a senior executive of a consortium in Chicago
Chicago
Third
Is an executive of an auto factory in Detroit
Detroit
Because this case is statewide
So the FBI is in charge of the investigation
but
After the third victim ran away from the perpetrator
He was shot dead at the station
Even though later
The first and second kidnap victims were rescued safely
Don't know why
They remain silent when asked about the suspect's information
Refusal to cooperate with research
There are rumors that the suspect is Japanese
Suspect is a sushi chef in Boston
Makoto Ishihara
Both he and the victim participated
Banquet for BostonWSG
And when the victim of the third incident was killed
He is near the scene
Also on the gun of the murder weapon found after
The database has been fingerprinted and the database is being retrieved
We also detected his fingerprint
Criminal Number: 7140202 Name: Makoto Ishihara
But when he was caught by the FBI
Ishihara refused to admit to the murder
I heard that the criminal motive
Is to protest the commercialization of WSG
That's why he committed this kind of terrorist act
High -level businessmen kidnapped
Then immediately stop sponsoring WSG
That's why there is such a saying
Companies that stop sponsoring
Under fire from across the United States
They are subject to terrorism
People don't forgive easily
and also
I checked the FBI director at the time
So this person
(Alan Mackenzie is 64 years old) Alan Mackenzie is an American attorney. The current President of the World Sports Association.
You should know Mr. Subaru
Alan Mackenzie
At that time he was still considered as the next presidential candidate
That's right
He is now the president of WSG
Coming to Japan soon
Are you curious?
After all, 11 years ago
A similar incident occurred in the US.
It's a crime imitating the case 15 years ago
I check again
Mr Alan was also the director of the FBI at the time
But before the case was killed
FBI arrests suspect
He didn't just confess to a crime by imitating a case four years ago
And confessed that he was this year's accomplice
FBI believe
What's happening in Tokyo now
Is it a further clone of these two cases?
This is the first time
Aimed at senior executives of sugar companies
The second incident was aimed at the senior executive of the consortium
Just like 15 years ago
So conclude
Third goal
Must be the top of the car manufacturers
Thank you son
Maori Detective Agency
Did any guests come to see dad?
By the way, where did that person seem to have met before?
Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, John Foyd, Japan
Mr John Foyd
What is the chairman and chief executive of Japan's Kod Corporation?
Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, John Foyd, Japan
He is a celebrity who often appears in various media these days
Father is the host for this big man
The so-called Japanese code
It was Takara's car that was on the verge of bankruptcy.
After being acquired by a British automaker
Established subsidiary
The next target might be him
VIP ticket for vacuum superconducting maglev train
I'm back
Completely innocent, I see
What
Tickets for fast cars
That's great my mom
By the way, I just heard what ran said
Conan and they will also ride a fast car
That little boy?
It's Brother
Hello brother
Is there any problem
It's July 24
I have work and I have to go to Nagoya
So just ask what souvenirs you want
Was brother also in Nagoya that day?
Is masumi too?
By chance
Let's meet in Nagoya
Please call again when you arrive in Nagoya
I don't have time to meet in Nagoya
Yaampun
Huft
No parking Here
Excuse me
Yumi
Deserves to be a Meijin celebrity
Hideyoshi called a new mistress again, right?
You bald mouse
no
Then who are you calling?
Who could let you hang up in a panic so I see you
in that case, okay
I will introduce it to you
Dinner is ready
Well
enjoy your meal
Tonkatsu is so delicious
Ran-neechan, can I watch TV?
Can
Very good
The most awaited news
Report on the vacuum superconducting fast train
The train was finally built
Conan, stop watching TV
The rice must be delicious too
understood
Trial operation announcement, one month before the opening of the vacuum superconducting maglev train
This is dimensional speed
And because of the train speed
Trial operation announcement, one month before the opening of the vacuum superconducting maglev train
"japanese bullet"
Almost comparable to the speed of a gun bullet
So it's also called "Japanese bullet" in the world
"japanese bullet"
amazing
We will ride it
Dad, are you okay?
Ran, sit down
Boy, turn off the TV
Okay
Are you going to take the fast train?
What's wrong with us coming?
Stop talking nonsense and change your clothes
When did you guys go?
Yaampun
On launch day
Tokyo WSG pembukaan opening ceremony
What
Dad raised his hand
You just got scalded, right?
Don't be stubborn
Sorry for soiling clothes
Uncle
Why ?
Mr. John will ride the train fast too, right?
The first car crew included
Attend today's event
Tokyo World Sports Association sponsor representative
Dan WSG
So Mr John
Is here to entrust uncle
Right ?
What has happened
uncle
My friend will also take the fast train
If there is danger
Will not
It shouldn't be so dangerous
I think so
Moreover
The two people who were kidnapped earlier have returned safely
In other words
Mr. John may have been kidnapped in a maglev car this time
That's bad we have to tell the police
and many more
I promised the client not to tell the police about it
Isn't it time to say this?
Those two people will be kidnapped
Maybe it's because of President John.
how could that be
He himself said it
He was drunk at the bar before
Accidentally playing golf with President Mitsuka
And President Suzuki attended the banquet
I told the male guest next to me
to be on the lookout
In this case published
His company reputation will surely suffer
Isn't it already broken?
Nowadays even foreigners who are not interested in forming cooperation
Chasing the nail in the eye
So, did he come to entrust father?
He asked me to investigate if it was his fault
I also want me not to worry the police until I find out the truth
I go to the bathroom
The good miso soup is a complete waste
I will heat it up again
Conan
Can't let the kids get on the fast train
But seeing them so happy
Really have to think of a way
Kamen Yaiba
Masked Superman (Chinese character removed?)
Japan World Sports Association Building
Friends who came to the scene today
We sincerely thank you all for your appreciation
Japan World Sports Association Building
The experience of riding the vacuum superconducting maglev train and the opening ceremony of the Tokyo World Experience Seminar
We sincerely thank you all for your appreciation
Now feel the experience of driving a vacuum superconducting fast train
The experience of riding the vacuum superconducting maglev train and the opening ceremony of the Tokyo World Experience Seminar
So many people come
After all, people all over Japan want to ride
We are so lucky
First of all, allow me to introduce myself
I am the person in charge of the promotion of the Japan World Sports Association
Ari Ishioka (25 years) Maglev train crew chief Inoue Osa (35 years) Maglev train engineer Maiko Shirato (29 years) Head of Publicity, Japan World Sports Association
Maiko Shirato, Head of Publicity, Japan World Sports Association
Maiko Shirato
I will explain the opening ceremony
Maiko Shirato, Head of Publicity, Japan World Sports Association
His name is Shirato
I remember that the pharmaceutical company where Haibara's father works is also called Shirato
It's called Baige Pharmaceutical
Not Shirato, right?
I am in charge of the vacuum superconducting fast train
Chief Development Engineer
Inoue Osamu
ito
Haru Inoue, Head of Vacuum Superconducting Maglev Train Development
How do you make everyone remember me?
My name is Osamu Inoue
Haru Inoue, Head of Vacuum Superconducting Maglev Train Development
Mister Inoue, hurry up and speak
okay
Haru Inoue, Head of Vacuum Superconducting Maglev Train Development
I am in charge of programming to ensure safe driving
I will do it for you then
Explain the applied technology of the high-speed train
Also good thanks for talking
The last one is me
Crew chief of the vacuum superconducting high-speed train
Magnetic levitation idol
Ishioka Ellie
Because my name is Ishioka Ellie
Vacuum Superconducting Maglev Train Service Department Crew Head
Everyone remembers me with "love you"
Where did the word "Ishioka" go?
As expected of Miss Ellie
He knows how to show himself
That's right
Okay
Let me explain to you the process today
July 24 schedule
10:00 a.m. on July 24th
The meeting place for everyone is here
July 24 schedule
Nagoya International Airport
The meeting place for everyone is here
The purpose of this car
This is the venue for the opening ceremony of the Tokyo World Sports Conference
Stadion Shibahama
From now on depart from Shin-Nagoya Station
Ride experience to Tokyo Shibahama Station
Vacuum superconducting maglev train Shin-Nagoya Station Shibahama Station TR Shinkansen
So we chose to start from Nagoya
And we will go to Nagoya International Airport
Meet with members of the World Sports Committee and sponsor representatives
Wait until all passengers arrive
Let's go to the airport hospital for a physical examination
Hei, Conan
Does the sponsor also have to undergo a medical examination?
I think so too
Moreover, we seem to be going from the airport to the stadium
Stay with them all the time
Mr. John not only
Is it dangerous on fast trains?
I don't think it should be taken lightly at airports and stadiums
Wait, Conan, do you want to go too?
Of course I have to go
Not at all
I just asked Sonoko
Prepare five tickets
But I also want to take the fast train
Alan Mackenzie Age: 64 Nationality: United States
He used to be a shooter in his school days
Photo of Alan Mackenzie from the Toronto World Expo (20 years)
Participate in Toronto WSG
Shoot?
Former FBI Director
Still shooter
Just seven years ago, Mr. Alan was experienced
Becoming president of the World Sports Association
Talking about seven years ago
Coincidentally that year Tokyo obtained the qualifications to host the World Sports Association
That's right
The relationship between President Alan and Tokyo WSG
Doesn't it look like it was destined?
One more thing
Everyone
Please pay attention to the high-speed train model
On the way the train will arrive at Shibahama Station
There will be 10,000 national flags flying like this
This surprise was proposed by President Alan
Wait Miss Ellie
We can't say this matter yet
This is supposed to be a surprise
On this issue
Please assume that you haven't heard anything
Also, please don't post it online
Okay
Please take it out now
Brochures distributed at the entrance
Dream from here, the vacuum superconducting maglev train from Shibahama Station to Shin-Nagoya Station only takes 25 minutes
Let's continue talking about the follow-up plan today
And the allocation of seats in the carriage
Dream from here, the vacuum superconducting maglev train from Shibahama Station to Shin-Nagoya Station only takes 25 minutes
Step by step to create a powerful and mobile experience The vacuum superconducting maglev train is undergoing trial operation and will be unlocked
And the allocation of seats in the carriage
so be it
We want to enter it's not so easy
You really care about the case in Japan
Now someone is copying the case handled by the FBI
Then we naturally have to advance
FBI headquarters has also issued a permit
Consent to the use of snipers by Mr. Akai
Using sniper
Do you mean you will kill the hostage?
Conan
The FBI has an FBI method of doing things
amazing
Masked Superman Show
Kamen Yaiba performance
We're going to watch Kamen Yaiba's show, it's a good thing
Their attention shifted from the fast car to the Kamen Yaiba show
But that girl is going to Nagoya too
That girl
Ran-neechan from detective agency
Wait a minute, shinichi
How do you know
Conan told you again, right?
Overall, don't go this time
Leave your father to me to protect
you protect
Shinichi, do you want to go to Nagoya too?
Then I should go together
Oi, Ran
Do not worry
Even if something
I can also protect myself
not like this
You are mine to protect you...
What's yours
Po
Ponoknya
You never go
Just a moment shinichi
Stupid
Don't let me make it clear
Nagoya International Airport
Passengers in a maglev car
Thank you to all of you
Able to work with us
In addition, sponsor representatives
Just arrived
That boy
Looks like Ran
Ran
Didn't I tell you not to come?
But I only rely on my father
How can I protect Mr John?
I want you to be nosy
President John also hired a bodyguard, okay?
Luckily, you didn't bring that bad boy with you
Conan and Ai-chan
Why are you here too
Because Haibara had to come and take a look
I'm not interested in Kamen Yaiba
I faintly hear a voice calling out to me
Everyone
Let's shout together this time
One two
Superman is masked
Save me Kamen Yaiba
I feel your heart
Debut Kamen Yaibaa
Cool
In the end, I still have to carry these brats
The Tokyo World's Fair is open!
Conan
it hurts
Danger
It's okay for a child
Are the kids okay?
Because it's decreasing
So I can't help but run
You are not hurt
Uncle, your Japanese is very good
I've been in Japan for a long time
Turns out so
This boy
The school teacher never taught you
Can't you not run around in the hallway?
Sorry this is the child of someone I know
Ran
Keep him tight for me
why is it like this
OK let's go
Conan
You should be able to return with Ai-chan by now
Can't do it
I am a child
Ai-chan should be able to go home alone
I can't go back
However, they are still children
Let's go
Is it all at the end of the team?
Right
Contact Okiya Subaru
Coffee cooler
I just arrived at Nagoya International Airport
I want to ask for your help, Boyya
so be it
This is the last option
I will try
Who are you calling?
Haibara
It's Genta
He said Kamen Yaiba's performance was amazing
Yes
Just waiting for you
I will go now
Be careful not to get lost, hurry up and follow everyone
okay
hai
Are you ok
By the way, I asked you to investigate?
According to the FBI report
Ishihara dies after being imprisoned
Ishihara always refuses to plead guilty, right?
According to the memoirs of the then FBI director
He keeps complaining that he is innocent
The director of the FBI at that time was
President Alan
How likely is Ishihara to be mistreated?
I'd rather believe that it's impossible
After Ishihara died,
Leaving his wife and daughter
Does he have a family?
After Ishihara died in prison
Wife and daughter return to Japan
Their names
Knowing that I will investigate the participant list
Uncle must have
Alan Mackenzie (64 years old) President of the World Sports Association
Chief Alan came to this place
Everyone
Let's greet him with a warm round of applause
Very fast
How about that?
They are not on the list
Yes
Then they might have changed their name according to the Witness Protection Plan
Is Ishihara a criminal?
How can his family be
Applies to Witness Protection Plans
As long as possible being attacked by the organization
Anyone can be the applicable object
On condition of ensuring personal safety
Mandatory request for other parties to cooperate in the investigation
This is what is called a judicial transaction
Can you tell if Ishihara's wife and daughter have become
Is it an object of protection?
If the procedure is carried out by the FBI
I'll find out soon
Federal Bureau of Investigation
But if it was executed by the US Marshals
Then it will take quite some time
US Marshal's Service
why
FBI dan US Marshals
US Bureau of Marshals, FBI
The relationship between the two sides is not very good
The international route reaches the exit
There is such a thing
By the way
The international route reaches the exit
If you change your name because of the Witness Protection Program
Can you change it to your liking?
Can not
Is that not possible?
Unless you can be sure that the pseudonym will not remind the real name
It may be
So
Ise Koyutsu
Tsukoi Ise
Owari Nagoya thrives in this city
It is indeed one of the three famous cities in Japan
Don't speak your mind proudly
Yumi kah
I also said I will pick you up when you arrive at Nagoya Station
Luckily you guessed that I was here
Of course I know
After all, you are a celebrity
Koalas are haunted by Taiko celebrities!
it's me
Don't talk about this
Going to Nagoya for a date
what do you think
Because I have work here today
And you have to wear kimono, you have to say at least
Luckily, I made a special dress
excuse me
Are you done with your work?
Um, I just finished today
look here
You can see Nagoya Castle
Being able to play against people in a place like this
A
Games?
Didn't I tell you?
Shogi Hall Construction Site Nagoya Aichi Konstruksi Construction
Here to build the Nagoya Shogi Hall
You also said that you are a member of the clubhouse executive committee
Shogi Hall Construction Site Nagoya Aichi Konstruksi Construction
I applied for it voluntarily
You can really find something to do
After all, I don't want other players to do this kind of work
Running to raise funds
No time to play shogi
People who experience this feeling
I'm enough
Tsukichi
Nagoya International Airport
Nagoya International Airport Hospital
Next, everyone will do a simple check
One examination room shared by men and women
Then I'll take everyone to the exam room on the second floor
Please follow me
What is wrong
I feel someone is looking at me
I’m here to work today, so I can’t be detected
OK, normal blood pressure
Next Mr Markenzo
okay
Is this an energy drink?
Similar
Here it is, Mr. Alan
thanks
I just bought it at the airport
I haven't slept all day
If I fall asleep at the opening ceremony
That would be bad
Do you both understand English?
How much has been taught in school?
me too
emergency stop
Friends please stay calm
Don't panic and run
Evacuate in an orderly manner
The door is closed, let's open the door
Damn this door can't be pushed at all
English is this for my life
You can rest assured that we will protect you
Father, I will find a way out
Ran
Ran-neechan
Listen to my answer
Ran
Edogawa, this isn't an explosion at all
This is superconducting cooling
Superconducting cooling
Edogawa
Quickly go escape
Haibara
You ran away
Keep consuming like this
Everyone here
Will die
Haibara
Shinichi
Ran, are you okay?
Can't move body
Moreover
What happened
hai
What's up, son?
who
This
What happened
Not ashamed to make it like this
What else can we do
The car suddenly came out and I almost hit it
But it doesn't matter
Because from the airport to the city
Panggil Jige
Just the way
Why did you hang up the call?
I found you Tsukichi
Who are you calling?
This is my family
nagoya
I would like to introduce you to my family
Say you're the boyfriend I'm dating
nagoya
Looks like they still don't agree
I told my mother beforehand that I waited until I got all the shogi titles
To propose to the girlfriend you are dating
One more title and one less
What is the difference?
You have earned the best title
That's my girlfriend Yumi Miyamoto
Yumi
Yumi, are you drunk?
I'm not drunk
Yumi is very dangerous. Let's go back to the shop.
Ran
Is there pain in the body?
It's fine without me, Ran, where are you
Ran
Shinichi
Not shinichi, it's me
father
Where are Conan and ai-chan
They haven't woken up yet
I will see President John's situation
You go and wake them up
Conan
Ran
nee-chan
Are you ok
Looks like it's no big deal
Conan, lost
President John is missing
He is not in front of us
Have you been checked by a doctor?
Don't know it's okay
Sender at Mr. John is still working
Ran-neechan, please take care of Haibara
Where are you going
bathroom
arah nagoya
What happened, boy?
Edogawa Conan
There is a small condition in the hospital now
Those people are safe
But Mr. John was kidnapped
What
Transmitter signal display
Mr John
On the only outside of the airport
I am afraid that I will cross Minggang Middle Bridge and go east
Can you catch up?
can
Noise
Where did he go?
Chasing the red car now
why
Don't talk, hurry up
The motorcycle has a helmet
not supposed to
Who is that
Don't ask too many questions, follow him
Okay
Coincidentally this time failed
Danger
Unlucky
Haibara
Are you awake Huibara
I was developed by Ran-neechan
Thank goodness it's fine, actually
You wait a minute I moved places
Can't get through
Mr. John's cell phone is turned off
Where are you
My tracking glasses are broken
It should have just happened.
You passed out and hit it
help me confirm Mr John's location
Location confirmation
How do you know I have spare tracking glasses on my body?
What makes you always want to get ready
wait for me a moment
Please Haibara
Nurse station
What happened to the explosion earlier
Please calm down, please let me
Maybe there was cooling just now
Hurry up and get an MRI technician
okay
Mr. Takahashi in charge of NMR
After Mr. John entered the island
Turn around from the Donghai exit and head south
In terms of speed, whether driving or riding a motorcycle
Go to the MRI room, hurry
Mr. Subaru, Mr. John now
i have heard
Donghae Conglomerate instructions, right?
find it
Haibara, Where is Mr John
now
Signal stops near East China Sea Joint Venture
I'm next
To enter the MRI room
The internal magnetic field there
May cause abnormalities in electronic devices such as tracking glasses
But because there is cooling
I think there should be no problem
What do you mean by quenching?
You, a detective, don't know
What is cooling?
Yes sorry
I will tell you
Inside the MRI machine
Superconducting Magnets
Superconducting magnets installed
To keep the working temperature at a low level
Superconducting Magnets
Liquid helium in the instrument
helium cair
But once the temperature rises due to several factors
Liquid helium will evaporate quickly
This is the cause
That's right
After cooling occurs
The oxygen content in the air will be quickly pulled down by helium
It will be life threatening in a few minutes
but
There must be a safety device to avoid this danger
why
This kind of drip station should not appear in the MRI room
emergency stop
And someone pressed the emergency stop button
How about this?
I think it's because
This thing is close to the superconducting magnet from the MRI machine
Someone pressed the emergency stop button in a hurry
That's why it leads to quench
But in general
If the emergency button is pressed
The pipes in the hospital have to be closed, right?
That's right
If there is smoke
The pipes in the hospital will be closed
divert
Only the ventilation duct to the outside will be opened
Why just like that?
Where are you going
Please follow me to the control room
The pipe to the second floor is open
And the exhaust equipment is set to full speed operation mode
You hear that?
Only the second floor was full of smoke
And it empties very quickly
MRI room
That's why we don't die from lack of oxygen
Did the prisoner do this on purpose?
It seems like
If so
Prisoners should have no intention to kill
so be it
That's why he targeted the kidnapping
Put it in an interesting place
I'm in company with Donghae
Where is the destination?
It's nearby
Mr. John doesn't move
That motorbike again
This feeling
Ini Jeet Kune Do
Who's he
amazing
I will be knocked down again
this child
is it possible
Really masumi
Mr. Subaru, where are you?
Is this all a disguise?
Who are you
Will be neechan
Conan
How will you be here?
I'm here to find someone
Do you go to this kind of factory to find someone?
I also have some situations here
From: M Subject: You go first
I haven't been able to meet that kid
I know mom
Will be neechan
The person you are looking for
Could it be Mr John
Your insight is very strong
That's right
I know where mr john
Come with me
a moment
Sera neechan, why are you here?
I saw her in the hospital lobby
What happened
Someone is driving the luggage cart
Pass through the confused crowd at ease
What does the driver look like?
He's driving too fast, I can't see clearly
But physically must be male
The perpetrator is a man
There
The dispatcher Mr. John is there
Is John Foyd near here?
That culprit used to take hostage before
Live in an easy to find place
This time it might be the same as before
I will try on Mr. John's phone
Do you know the cell phone number?
Why ?
by the way
Mr. John's cell phone
It seems dead now
will not
If the Perpetrator is the same as I thought
there is noise
Where
so be it
On top
Well
Meet
How can it be in such an interesting place
it is because
The culprit had no intention of killing Mr. John
I will start now
good to eat
Sure enough, if you come to Nagoya, you must try the triple eel rice
father
Shinichi called me just now
Said he found Mr John
Why was the detective man calling?
Don't ask, go and tell the person in charge
The bowl of eel rice is mine
You have to show it to me
Okay, okay
Thank you Shinichi
It's okay here
That's right
Don't tell me if you find someone
Mr John
Do you remember the situation when you were kidnapped
At that time, suddenly there was a burst of white smoke all around
Difficulty breathing
but
I woke up once in the middle of the road
It's in the car
I feel like there's someone else next to me
Is it a perpetrator?
do not know
Is it a boy or a girl?
food court
Can't you take the fast train?
why
The results of the physical examination are clearly normal
Ordered today
but
This very tasty. If something like that happens again
Ordered today
It's really delicious, it's troublesome
So I recommend you
Let's take the Shinkansen back to Tokyo
Miss Allie is in trouble
I have to go, Miss Allie, Mr Inoue
Did President Alan come here?
I have not seen it yet
I don't have either
I searched the hospital and the conference room
But Chief Alan is nowhere to be found
Aichi Prefektur Prefectural Police
Did you call 110?
It's me, you guys are too slow to get out of the cops right?
Sorry
Because of the explosion at the airport
Most of the police force in Nagoya City
Has been moved there
In any case, send this person to the hospital immediately
Thanks to you I was saved
thank you very much
You're welcome
Take care Mr John
Now my job is done
Tokyo
Important figures in the UK have been saved
Well done, Sera
Young Detective
We have to take the Shinkansen back
Does the train stop fast?
Saying that the carriage will still cooperate with the opening ceremony
Depart from the station
Only no passengers
Not even a passenger?
However, this is a fast unmanned car
It's not important
President Alan is missing
Mr John just said
There are still people in the car
That person is probably President Alan
I will answer the call later
I found the culprit's car, Boyya
Right at the airport parking
But I'm afraid I can only find out
Driver only male
The perpetrator is a man
Then the director of the FBI
Hello friends from Japan
How likely is Ishihara to be mistreated?
Akai san
As a last resort
Seems to have arrived
Let's go to Shin Nagoya Station now
so be it
Sera, let's go to Shin Nagoya Station
Hurry up
What is wrong
I don't mean that the culprit makes cooling.
Is the police force in the city mostly concentrated at the airport?
That's right
New Nagoya Station now when the police force is weak
15 years ago
World Sports Association sponsors serial kidnapping case TM company president shot and killed
Third person kidnapped
Shot at the station
World Sports Association sponsors serial kidnapping case TM company president shot and killed
So this time the prisoner
Will he kill people with a gun at Shin-Nagoya Station?
Not sure to use
"japanese bullet"
In other words, the decisive battlefield is in the fast cars
Akai has already rushed to Shin-Nagoya Station
Come on, quickly
good
Yumi, you drank too much
Please restrain yourself
How do I introduce you to my family?
What does this have to do with your family?
After all, the two of us are getting married
So cool
So you are willing to accept my marriage proposal
Of course
Yumi
I will make you happy
Tokyo World Sports Convention
Then let's go back to Tokyo too
Please follow me
I'm really looking forward to the fast car
Are you in trouble?
The child I brought is missing
Ran
Have you found President Alan?
Shouldn't be
However, the fast train will depart according to the original plan
The opening ceremony will also be held as usual
From: Edogawa Subject: Excuse me, Haibara
This is a decision made by the World Sports Association
It's basically impossible to change
How is President John now?
It should be fine
Don't you have to follow him?
I said that Mr John has bodyguards to follow
The commission I received was to investigate the incident
Let's go
Wait a moment
Conan isn't back yet
have you called?
I called several times
He didn't even pick up
You said Edogawa
He said he came home with his acquaintance
Departure ceremony of the vacuum superconducting maglev train from Shibahama to the Shin-Nagoya bagian section
After the departure plan is adjusted
Even on the vacuum superconducting fast train
No first passenger
But still attracts so many people
Come to see the style of the car
The fun time has finally arrived
Japan welcomes you
ten
Not only train fans nowadays
All of Japan
People from the world
Did everyone witness this historic moment?
one
Fast train now
Departure on time
what's this
The speed of the vacuum superconducting maglev train can be judged according to the color of the body
Everyone came to find out
How does the vacuum superconducting fast train work?
The speed of the vacuum superconducting maglev train can be judged according to the color of the body
There are a total of seven body colors, please remember!
How does the vacuum superconducting fast train work?
When the train starts, it will run on wheels
Then when the speed of the car exceeds 150 kilometers per hour
The train will depend on the attraction of magnets and coils
Floating on the track
After that, the maglev train will enter the vacuum tunnel
Reduces air resistance in tunnels
Cars run at speeds of up to 1,000 kilometers per hour
But the train can control the speed in the tunnel
Finally the train came out of the tunnel
After the speed drops to 300 kilometers per hour
Air brake system will start
Then the speed dropped even further to 150 kilometers per hour
The wheels that were originally stored at the bottom of the carriage will be released
Fast Train has no driver
So who's driving?
This problem
This question is good
In fact, we are in a vacuum superconducting high-speed railcar
Equipped with a manually controlled cab
Manual taxi
but
This cabin was used during the trial
Usually not used
In line with that
The main control room is located between Shin-Nagoya Station and Shibahama . Station
Will be responsible for operating the train
Then let's see
How is the situation in the car when the train is running?
Can you see inside the maglev train?
extraordinary
sadly
There's no one in the passenger compartment today
Conan
will be
If President Alan isn't in the car,
We didn't end up with a scolding
I said did you smell something?
This is President Alan
That's right
By the way, the culprit you saw at the airport
There are some suitcases in his luggage basket
There are two
And those are two identical squares
Two identical boxes
I remember to put Mr. box. John
It's a zipper
Conan
What are you doing now
Does it smell sweet and sour?
perhaps
This is the mark left by the wheel with a nutritious drink
Vitamin B2 added in nutrition drink
Is a fluorescent substance
Will react to invisible light
But it can emit invisible light
Your watch is too versatile, isn't it
After all, this is a detective tool developed by a trusted professor
Could it be the kids who missed me?
Just talk about me
It takes a little time to repair the car
Made me delay for so long
I hope they have fun at the kamen yaiba event
too weak
You are too weak, kamen yaiba
These kids are mine
Hentikan Which
The masked Superman is in danger
There are too many enemies
One two
Kamen steals, yes
Can the professor come quickly?
That's it for freaks
Whose voice is this
Where
Look at the sky
So two people in a fast car
excuse me
I am the companion
Sorry
I am very sorry
Not this
Please stop at the stop halfway
Drag them out of the car
I will pick them up
No
Today's plan is riding experience
The program is set to pass the station along the way non-stop
But the main control room can control the train, right?
But this way
The train can't take part in the opening ceremony
10,000 flag-raising activities on trains will also be stopped
That's President Alan's creativity
That's right
How can you consider the situation of the high-speed train and stop the activity in a relaxed manner?
But
We still have to contact the main control room
Leave it to me
Conan
will be
hai
Can you wait a little longer?
no
it's time
so be it
Go
We need to find Chief Alan as soon as possible
Conan
That was the shot just now, right?
And it's a bolt-action rifle
Who have you been with since then
What the hell are you doing
Do not worry
The one on the phone is on our side
Then it's up to the child, boyya
wait
I have another request
so be it
Send me the mobile numbers of all participants
July 24 vacuum superconducting magnetic levitation train/monitoring
What are you doing actually
good
what are you doing now
Lend me
Wait a moment
What are you doing now
That's right
Know that I was asked to do something
No more here
That's right
I will open the door
Could it be here
Wait a moment
Are you ok
He's still conscious
english where am i
In a fast car
How did you find me?
Thanks to the drink bottle you dropped
Totally worthy of being the former director of the FBI
This is President Alan
What
Mr. Native
What's this
Do you know what happened?
Everyone listen to me
When President Alan was fired,
Young Detective
Kidnapped with President John
What did you say
Then
Both of them were put in the prison car
Did Mr. Alan see the perpetrator's appearance?
Monitoring here
Too bad he didn't see
but
We already know who did it
"We" Conan also know?
no
The one who knows the prisoner is Shinichi-neechan
So who's the culprit?
Before revealing the real culprit
Conan wants to confirm one more thing
I said that's what Shinichi-niichan wanted to confirm
Then please
Good English
Unknown contact entered
Unknown contact
Hit my phone too
Halo
Who's this
No one will pick up who's calling
Impossible
Is everyone's phone ringing?
Conan and I also called
President Alan also rings
But only one person
The phone isn't ringing, is it?
That's right
Nona Maiko Shirato
Nona Shirato
Looks like your phone is not ringing
Because the phone is dead
There should be a battery in your phone, right?
According to me
It must be because of the MRI machine
Let electronic products damage
in other words
The person who caused the blackout
Nona Shirato
That is you
There happened to be a problem with the phone
Will you put the perpetrator on me?
Then you want to say
Did you happen to take this fast train?
The most important is Maiko Shirato
your name
And the shooting captive 15 years ago
Maiko Shirasu
Maiko Shirasu si ra ha to ma i ko Makoto Ishihara i si ha ra ma ko to
And the shooting captive 15 years ago
Makoto Ishihara's katakana is the same
Maiko Shirasu si ra ha to ma i ko Makoto Ishihara i si ha ra ma ko to
This shouldn't be a coincidence
Your father insisted that he was innocent but died in the end
You can't give his name
I'm not wrong
Alan
this weapon
I am very happy
You still remember
Correct
It's the same model as the murder weapon 15 years ago
This culprit
Which is your father?
Confessed innocence 15 years ago
But the FBI caught my dad
Do you remember?
Was that the first victim of that case 15 years ago?
i remember that
Is an executive of a Japanese confectionery company
When Japanese corporate executives are kidnapped
My dad is with me
In other words, he has an alibi
at that time
I said the same thing in my testimony to the FBI
But my father is still arrested
He screamed injustice until he died in prison
My mother came to Japan
But soon he was exhausted
Also died
That's why you always hate the FBI
So I listened to the US Marshals Office's suggestion to change my name and surname
Is it a witness protection plan in a judicial transaction?
you
Know a lot
Yes, to the people of the US Marshals
Don't understand Japanese katakana
So they don't find
I use my father's name
Then seven years ago
God is finally on my side
Seven years ago
Tokyo gains qualification to host this World Sports Association
yes, and
This man is also that year
Becoming president of the World Sports Association
This is the will of God
That's why you got involved in the Japan World Sports Association?
Yes
That's why I knew that this person was going to take the fast train
this "Japanese bullet"
That's why you planned the same case as 15 years ago
I do this to remind this person of his sins
But you didn't kill anyone else before
That's right
I just need to kill him alone
You're out of me
I want to wait for the "Japanese bullet" to arrive at the terminal
Take this person's life again
But thanks to your blessing, the plan has changed
I will kill him now
Looks like god
Still by my side
Stop right now
what you just said
As long as I die
That's right
I just need to kill you
Okay
Shoot here
Tuan Mackenzie
here
Shoot here
Shoot from a higher position
So even if the bullet goes through my body
It will only touch the floor
Aim for my chest
Shoot from a higher position
So even if the bullet goes through my body
It will only touch the floor
High-speed trains are designed to travel at high speeds
Use a very light material, right?
Of course
If the bullet hits a wall or ceiling
Dangerous train
Everyone present will be in danger
Even though the floor is quite strong
But shooting from very close range is also easy to penetrate
So you have to be at the farthest distance so that the bullet can hit the left chest
Shoot me from the highest position possible
That's what Mr. Alan said
Shut up and stop talking nonsense
Nona shirahato
I think you should know
Mr. Alan used to be a shooter
Also expert shooters who participated in previous experience events
Conan
father
here
Shoot here
Higher
Defeat
Return
Raise your hands up
take a step back
snow
Shot removal verification?
Conan
What is wrong
What has happened
who's this
Who shot him?
Yokohama Machida
The person who shot must be Mr. Akai
But shouldn't the show be?
Still in Nago?
Fast car
Tokyo
Just arrived near Yamanashi
Yamanashi
nagoya
Just arrived near Yamanashi
It's impossible to successfully become a sniper at this distance
nagoya
So Mr. Akai
Only customize special bullets
Not made of iron
It's made of silver
Silver bullets will not be orbited by magnetic levitation
Electromagnets hang on the sidewall
The electromagnetic induction effect between the electromagnets not only allows the train body to levitate
It can also make bullets fly in the trajectory
Current speed
Flying at a speed of 1,000 kilometers per hour
After entering the vacuum tunnel
Almost unaffected by gravity and air resistance
Chase behind a maglev car at a constant speed
This time
If the fast train slows down suddenly
And the slowdown lasts for a long time
The silver bullet will be during the slowdown period
Ultra-light car body that goes through the maglev kereta train
At this time, as long as the vital part of the perpetrator
Only in pre-calculated positions
Snipers can be successful
This requires the cooperation of someone in the carriage
Is that person?
That's right, Edogawa Conan
Nona shirato
Conan sera chan
Are you okay
Everyone is fine
Why did the perpetrator get shot
Did the gun explode?
Leave this alone
Hurry up let the fast train stop nearby
Call an ambulance
Taking into account the operating status of the high-speed train
Nearest station
What is the terminal?
Shibahama Station
I will now alert the police and ambulance to stand guard at Shibahama Station
Is this resolved?
Not yet
That's right
There are still accomplices who are not caught
And minions
Chicken wing
Yumi, are you okay?
I'm fine
Before seeing your family
I don't know how to vomit
Let's go back to Tokyo today
By the way, I'll take a taxi to take you to the station
That car really goes fast
Park me right away
Yumi
Is Yumi okay?
Yumi Yumi
Did you mean: accomplice
That's right Conan
It seems that Shirato's sister is also aware of this
new brother
Of course you would notice it if you saw that kind of thing
Obviously someone was operating the car from a distance
And when the perpetrator is in danger
In other words, there are accomplices who are secretly helping
The prisoner was carrying a large suitcase containing President Alan
Get on this fast car
After breaking free at the airport
Although the police force at Shin-Nagoya Station is insufficient,
It's not easy to ride a car like this
In other words, accomplice
Related to fast cars
And it's a boy
Really? Mr. Inoue
You can think of this cooling method and put it into practice
Eligible to be a magnetic levitation technology engineer
Talking about electric trains and nuclear magnetic resonance
Superconducting magnets are used
You are responsible for debugging
You can't be bothered with this little trick
Can use remote operation
The person who just made sudden braking like that
Only you can monitor real-time images in the car
Magnetic Levitation Engineer
Give it back to me
Don't you want to run away?
find it
The software connected to the main control room of the maglev kereta train
It hurts me back
Why are you doing this
Among the people involved in the case 15 years ago
Only two Japanese
One of them is the suspect Makoto Ishihara
The others are the first victims
The executives of that dim sum company
that person
Is my father
What did you say
After my dad stopped sponsoring world experience
Criticized in the US
He was finally dismissed by the company's board of directors
Newport Beach
Case 15 years ago
Taking everything our family has
Newport Beach
This car stops: Tokyo Chuanpin
Taking everything our family has
But the FBI
This car stops: Tokyo Chuanpin
But caught the wrong criminal and declared the case closed
Catching the wrong criminal
Four years later
The copycat was caught
Atlanta: 15 years ago
I recognize that person's face
One of the criminals who kidnapped my father 15 years ago
Like that
But my testimony
Hidden by the FBI
Just to beat people becomes a trick
That's why you hate the FBI
My father was accused of being unbearable in the US.
We really can't live in America anymore
That's why you came to Japan
After coming to Japan
I was investigating this case 15 years ago online
I found a woman who has the same hatred as me
Maiko Shirasu
He is your accomplice, right
Right
Go out
stop
bastard
father
Young Detective
What happened to Huihara
how is the situation?
Young Detective
Are you ok
Hurry up and answer me Huibara
Haibara
Perpetrators run away
At Xingangbin . Station
Unlucky
Halo
Sensei where are you
Okay, I understand
Go to Xingangbin right?
Camel
Well
Compared to when we met before
He looks like a different person
By the way, are you ?
I asked my brother to protect Yumimi
There is such a thing
Edogawa Conan
What's up son?
Shizuoka
Such a big man runs really fast
And even the escape car is ready
The world's first vacuum superconducting high-speed train
Ok everyone back
No, right?
Fast cars are coming
At least go to the platform and have a look before leaving
How do doctors?
Looks like I can only make one trip
Shouldn't be able to catch up
Unlucky
Ran
Help me contact the Megure Police Department
I will ask the teacher for help next
Talking to you on the phone
That's what you call yourself
There are two people
What did you say
One of them is the person you call teacher
The other one is the one carrying the rifle
Maybe from the FBI
Shibahama
The train will arrive at Shibahama Station in 10 minutes
Slowly now
The phone rings
Shinichi where are you
Dad called me and said
He was at the Gangbei Exit in Xingangbin
Loss of prisoners
Shinichi
cellphone
you brought two
Yes
guru
Where is the culprit now?
Near Gangbei Exit
If the prisoners depart from Xingangbin and take the Gangbei Exit
Xinganghama Third Keihin Port Northern Transportation Hub
Must ready
Let's take the third Keihin to Tokyo
He might as well just be hiding
Actually, I went to the beach area along the bottom line
What's the photo?
According to me
Don't think about things that are too complicated
For example
Industrial Avenue di depan Gangbei Exit
Stretches east-west
Gangbei Industrial Road Gangbin Transportation Center Gangbei Overpass
If you go west
Tsurumi River
Will cross the Kamoike Bridge across the Tsurumi River
Jembatan Kamoike Sungai Tsurumi
Now this time
You should be able to see the fast train on the bridge
Vacuum superconducting magnetic levitation train
Could it be?
Did the perpetrator chase the fast train?
I'm afraid so
Jodie
I understand
Camel
Yes
Go to Yachi Bridge now
good
Conan, your two cell phones
Can you show me
I also want to know who I am
Who's this
Or are you saying that for a reason
Can't let me see
plan
Notice: Five minutes before the train arrives at Shibahama Station
There he is
Beginning
what sound
is it possible
The train is going fast
Shibahama Station is almost there
Gotta start slowing down
Does he still want Mr. Alan's life?
He really intended to use this "Japanese bullet".
find it
Black German car
It should be that one
careful
Well
What's with that car?
Do not dare to show up?
Start chasing
At this speed, the wheel cannot be lowered
The magnetic pole of the track cannot be reversed
Is there no way to solve it?
There's no point if you ask me
In a fast car
There are manual taxis, right?
Connect to main control room to receive signal
Maybe they can fight together
no
How can ordinary people drive?
Besides, it's still a child
Less bullshit and hurry up
No brakes not responding
unlucky
Haibara, we did it according to the requirements of the main control room
But the train still doesn't slow down
Current speed 1000km/h
Why doesn't the speed change at all
Can't find the reason
Current speed 1000km/h
It is said that even the main control room cannot be controlled
how
Unknown programs take control of the system
That's why I can't stop
In other words
Perpetrators set up other systems first
What will happen like this?
After the track is completely turned off
The buoyancy of magnetic levitation will be lost
The train slows down gradually
finally
The body of the car will touch the ground
Emergency landing
It does not matter
As long as the train's superconducting magnets don't fail
The car will not slip
Even if the speed drops
The train can still
Landing in a relatively balanced position
Who are you
Just an elementary school student who really likes science
What has happened
camel
Is it okay with your car skills?
of course
But I'm not used to the road conditions in this area
No problem
I'll show you the way
Shuichi Akai
Don't leave it to me
I already remember all the maps in the area
Well
Um I thought about it
Trick win
First, the offensive must be divided into two groups
Joed, Camel
You are divided into two groups
Akai, we are divided into two teams
What to do next show
The first way remains the same
Camel kept chasing
The second way is standby at the next location
Standby
This is an irregular cover layout
It only takes five steps for the public
Too slow
Let's go after the culprit
We got the news
Fast train speed out of control
it will hit Shibahama station in five minutes
What did you say
Everyone
Please keep calm and don't stop
Everyone is behind me
Don't worry, professor
What happened
What
Was it an earthquake?
The body of the carriage is too vibrating and can't stay still
car door
Why the car body becomes so unstable
Okay, I understand
I just checked with the main control room
Liquid helium in the car quickly leaked
Is that a quell again?
Nothing happens wherever you press
Edogawa
The superconducting magnets of the high-speed train have cooling
so be it
No wonder there was an explosion just now
I will slip if I don't want to find a way
How to do
see
Bad situation
Conan
Ran
Edogawa
The location where you were just now was the sub-control room
Maybe in the car cabin
Brakes can still be used
I understand thank you
As soon as possible
The first step
Attacker leaves
Gusei Station near Hachioji . Street
Hideichi Akai James Black dan Judy Stylin
Camel, you go to Guxi Station
if that's the problem
Wasn't it getting further and further away from the prisoner's car?
Stop talking nonsense and go to Guxi Station
okay
Isn't that car chasing me?
The second stage
Defenders drive along Route 109 to Umenoki
Just in front
what's that
How to do
Continue like this
Calling Yuanzi
Sonoko
Ran
Shibahama Station is in chaos as the fast train goes out of control
WSG forced to postpone opening ceremony
Even an evacuation warning was issued
Impossible
You are on the Shinkansen
It should be fine
I'm fine
But the problem is
We called ai-chan
But he didn't answer
We are still afraid of the accident
Ai-chan with me
But Conan
haibara right next to you
Then tell him quickly
new kamen yaiba
It was from the sky
Get off with a parachute
very cool
parachute
no
The brakes here don't seem to work either
At a loss
Conan what are you doing?
Nothing I thought about what this is for
Can Edogawa hear it?
Caught
Umenoki
unlucky
What is the origin of the car?
I will go after
third step
Attacker heading to Loop Line 2
Go to Carmel on Loop Line 2
But
I finally caught up with that prisoner
camel
I go
Xingangbin Third Keihin Loop Line 2
This is a car that really humiliates the perpetrator
wrong
He's still here
Understand?
Even if the brakes really fail
Other devices may still work
so be it
When everything is ready
Just press the blue button
thank you
Then we will listen to Rans suggestion
Move to the driver's seat in the back
I want to live here
In terms of
We'd better split up
If you hear my voice there
That's the signal of the action
good
Tamachi Loop Route 2 Shinkohama Ketiga Keihin Tokyo terikat
What has happened
how
fourth step
The defender changes lane to the side of the road
This guy
Not anymore
We can't catch up
mission fails
There is no fifth step
Attacker walking under the Xingangbin Earth Bridge
General
Jodie
Really coming
parking
What is this man doing?
There should be some distance from the front of the car
Okay
Tie this end
My work is done
I will wait for Conan's next signal
finally achieved
now
will be
What a big parachute
Stop for me
Conan
Damn how can I die here
how
Monitoring on the car is restored
get out of the way
Not here
Sorry to let me
Conan
will be
Please answer me quickly
Edogawa
Young Detective
Haibara
Ran-neechan
Young Detective
Do not worry
Everyone is fine
The perpetrator took the initiative to shoot the gun
What kind of magic show do you use
This is not magic but shogi
Shogi
I have the best in Japan
wrong
It should be said to be the number one mind in the world
FBI
Federal Bureau of Investigation
Lying on the ground with head in hand
Turns out it was from the FBI
FBI
Is the FBI hiding my confession?
15 years ago
I witnessed the incident with my own eyes
But you caught Ishihara
Call a person named Makoto Ishihara
Slander as a criminal
Detainee 15 years ago
Makoto Ishihara
Nonsense
He doesn't talk nonsense
The impersonator was arrested four years later
Confess yourself
The person you see
Actually a copycat
In that case 15 years ago
He is Makoto Ishihara's partner
you're lying
Then why are you
When that man was arrested 11 years ago
Not announced to the public
He was also an accomplice in the case 15 years ago
James Black |
Due to judicial transactions
We no longer hold him accountable for his past crimes
The condition is that he must acknowledge the names of his accomplices
so are we
not holding him accountable in the case 15 years ago
That's why we didn't announce it to the public
Ayah Shirato Maiko
Makoto Ishihara
He's an accomplice to the prisoners who kidnapped your father
You actually became an accomplice of this kind of person
For unnecessary revenge
Become a criminal
no
Everything is to blame for your assertive judicial dealings
Is this a self-serving judicial transaction?
That's right
This is the dirty trick you are the best at
So our talented family will
Then your family
Why can we get away with US accusations?
What's the matter
Able to pull ridiculous revenge jokes
What do you want to say
Precisely because you have been able to change your name and surname through the Witness Protection Program
Isn't that?
Isn't this what you call it?
Part of that dirty judicial deal
Where is the culprit?
it's here
Let's leave it to the Japanese police.
Conan
will be
Tokyo Fire Department
Are you okay
How was the injury?
Tokyo Fire Department
I only got a few scratches
me too
are you okay
Who is it?
That's the suspect, Maiko Shiraito
I leave it to you
Yes
Pay attention to slow down during construction ahead
He is still alive
Worth the show
Really can use magnetic levitation path to hit tough snipers
Also accurately dodge the fine points
No one can do it except you
No, this is not my credit
It was all that kid's idea
Is everyone's cell phone ringing?
I sent an email to Mr Alan then
Beg him when the situation is critical
Bring the prisoner's shoulder to that position
Please help if necessary... Avoid hitting the prisoner's vital organs on the shoulder... the center of the roof
Higher English
Defeat
Return
It turned out like this
No matter how cruel the prisoner is, he can't kill him
It seems this is the boy's principle
Different from our FBI
I love that jacket
forget it
Come back
okay
When you pull the trigger
Pale and sudden emptiness
Chaos and glare obscure the truth
Baptism that brings endless darkness
I parked the car there
Come and get it
good
other than that
There are two other guests in my car
I hope you can send them home safely
Troublesome for you, Camel
FBI kid
I don't know where you come from
All because of you
An important figure in our country is almost in trouble
Luck this time
I'll let you go if things don't become a big deal
Don't think there's another time
Child?
Don't you remember
You clearly agreed to my marriage proposal
do not remember
I fainted, I have no impression at all
how
I remember apparently throwing up in whose car
Drive safely, slow down
What smell is this?
Hi guys
It's time for you to play
Oh!
GW public decision in 2022