[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Mid-tempo jazzy introduction
plays ]
**
>> * I'll have a blue
Christmas without you *
* I'll be so blue
just thinking
about you *
* Decorations of red
on a green Christmas tree *
* Won't be the same, dear,
if you're not here with me *
* And when those blue
a-snowflakes
start fallin' *
* That's when those blue
memories start callin' *
* Yeah *
* You'll be doin' alright
with your Christmas of white *
* And I'll, I'll have a blue,
blue, blue, blue Christmas *
>> * Aah-aah-aah-aah *
>> Hey.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
"Christmas in the City."
My name is Michael Bublé.
And we are here at
Rockefeller Center, coming
direct into your home, wherever
you are, coast to coast,
worldwide, from the North Pole
to the South.
Hey, what do you say we get this
party started, huh?
[ Cheers and applause ]
Hey.
J-man, J-man, let's go.
Let's go, man.
**
>> * Oh *
* Oh *
**
>> * And when those blue
a-snowflakes start fallin' *
* That's when those blue
ah, those memories,
they start callin' *
* You'll be doin' alright
with your Christmas, babe,
of white *
* And I'll, I'll have a blue,
blue, blue, blue Christmas *
>> * Aah-aah-aah-aah *
>> * Yes, I will *
* I'm gonna have a blue *
* Ah-ah-hey *
* Christmas *
**
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> From Studio 8H in
Rockefeller Center, it's...
With...
...and your host, Michael Bublé.
We'll be right back, after this
short break.
year.
>> I love you!
**
>> * Ooh, ooh-ooh *
Give it up -- Jimmy Fallon,
everybody!
[ Cheers and applause ]
**
>> Thank you.
>> Thanks.
**
"I'll Be Home for Christmas,"
is now available to stream and
purchase only on Amazon Music.
admired my whole life.
>> Give it up for Leon Bridges,
everybody.
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> * Do-to, do-to-do *
>> * Ba-boom-boom,
boom-boom boom-boom-boom *
[ Cheers and applause ]
>> I want some more singing
lessons.
>> The Nintendo Switch.
Dude, dude, dude, dude.
Give me a hug.
[ Cheers and applause ]
* Sleep in heavenly peace *
>> * Ahh-ahh ahh-ahh *
[ Cheers and applause ]
**