How did I survive that?
It was some damn fall.
Oh shit. My comms busted.
My thermals busted too.
I should have got snapped in
half and died on the way down.
Instead of slowly turning
into a meat popsicle.
Seymour!
Seymour! I'm down here!
Mickey?
Seymour!
Seymour, I'm down here!
Mickey! Whoa!
You haven't died yet?
No!
Hold on.
Oh shit!
Your flamethrower's still good.
Not a single scratch.
It's a good thing I thought
to come down here.
Weapons will be happy to see this.
Yeah, I'm gonna turn this in, okay?
I can take it.
You're not mad, right?
That I'm just taking this?
I mean, it's not looking
very good for you, right?
Also, line only goes this far.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I know.
We're cool.
You shouldn't have to take the risk, huh?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Plus, they're gonna reprint
you back out tomorrow anyway.
Yeah.
Hey, Mickey.
Yeah?
What's it feel like to die?
I'm sure you're used to it by now.
Still.
How many times is this?
You're Mickey 16?
17.
Jerk.
18 after this one.
Well, it's nice knowing you.
Have a nice death.
See you tomorrow.
Oh, great.
Why not?
That's a pretty big one.
Hopefully, I'll just get
swallowed in one go.
It's gotta be better than
slowly freezing to death.
I guess.
Or maybe not.
But they just printed me
out again every time I died.
All my data is saved and I
just get a whole new body.
They do all this kind of regular
uploads of memories and
my personality traits and
re-implant it back in my brain.
That's some crazy technology, man.
Let's just say it's advanced.
It's very advanced.
Come on.
Wait.
Just hold on a second.
Just like, you know, calm down.
Just relax.
Breathe.
That's right.
The whole body printing and memory transplanting thing,
to be honest, was so ridiculously ahead of its time
that it caused so many, like, ethical fights and religious
blah blah blah that it was actually banned on Earth.
And they only allow it now in
outer space for expandables like me.
So from the second we
left the atmosphere, they
made me work my ass
off all the way to this planet.
Gave me one mission after another.
Uh, Tech?
What's going on?
The extra cable's here already.
Um, the thing is, Mickey...
Hey, Medical, you wanna tell him?
Tell me what?
Hi, Mickey. How you doing? Um...
Are you experiencing any
vertigo, nausea, or dizziness?
Uh, I guess I am feeling a little dizzy.
It's only gonna get worse from
here, Mickey, with a nice fever, too.
Truth is, you're exposed to
unthinkable levels of radiation
right now, which is why we
sent you out in the first place.
Okay.
If you could give us a full
description of your symptoms.
So, a couple things I wanna go
through on our cosmic radiation checklist.
First, how long until
your skin starts to bleed?
Then, how long until you go blind?
And of course, how long until you die?
That's the real nut we're after.
There was this one time in my fourth grade
science class, I messed with a lab frog.
I just figured this all
must be my punishment.
Mickey, take off your glove so I can see
what's happening under your space suit.
Oh! Oh!
Wow! Did you see that?
Good morning.
Keep yourself hydrated, Mickey.
You'll start to feel extremely parched.
Arkady, I think the dose was too high.
Who cares, Dorothy?
He's gonna be dead in ten minutes.
Just focus on getting
all the blood samples.
He's gonna bleed through his
eyes, nose, mouth, ears, and rectum.
Make sure to collect separate
samples from everyone.
Okay? And keep the memory
upload going at the same time.
This Mickey's special.
You know that, right?
Out of all the Mickeys, you
will have the shortest life span.
I heard.
Terminus.
Well, aren't you any good news?
Smaller than 15. Much better, isn't it?
I would have been filthy rich
by now with life insurance,
except I have obviously
expendables or uninsurance.
There's no workers' comp,
no unions, no pension benefits.
Now, I wouldn't be surprised
if you were thinking at
this point, well, then why
did you do this to yourself?
Well, because I had a
friend who told me that
one day macarons would
sell better than burgers.
And because I trusted
this shitty friend and I
got an enormous loan from a wonderful
gentleman to open a macaron store.
All right, all right, calm down.
I'm well aware that
you have four weeks left.
Just think of this
as a little field trip.
Taste of what may unfold should you
fail to reimburse us in a timely manner.
Besides, you two have a
lot of time on your hands.
With your little macaron shop gone under.
Woo! This is, uh, this is quite a show.
You got on here for me. Quite a show.
The message is clear. I hear you.
I hear it loud and clear. I'm late.
I'm late. The money is late. It's coming.
Darius Blank.
A name I wish I'd never heard.
Mr. Blank is no less concerned with money.
He has plenty.
This building is just
one of his many assets.
Watching his delinquent
borrowers die, savoring
the details of death,
that he truly enjoys.
The message is clear. You can stop now.
We can stop. You know, it's, it's, it's...
I hear you. Two, you
know, two weeks, uh,
two weeks is all it
takes. All it takes now.
And, and, and, and, more time.
More time. More money. More money.
Who caught that gentleman four
days ago at Ulaanbaatar? Mongolian?
Looks expensive.
Best assured, anyone
who misses the deadline,
we chase them to
the ends of the Earth.
So we decided to get off of Earth.
Nothing was working out,
and I got no family lying on me.
So I applied to the colony
expedition, but there's,
like, a million other
people with the same idea.
Seems like the whole of this rotten
planet was running away from something.
I guess everybody's got money problems.
But anyway, we had to get on this ship,
because it was the last one of the season.
Waves upon waves of people
desperate to leave Earth.
It's clear anti-migrationists are
talking to a brick wall when they insist...
...on fixing up the Earth instead of risking
lives by migrating to another planet.
It feels like these passionate
applicants are already off in space.
More importantly, this
is the expedition led
by former Congressman
Kenneth Marshall...
...who lost his last two elections.
Is this failed politician now trying to
establish a kingdom beyond the stars?
Is it his fanatical supporters who
won him a generous sponsorship...
...from a particular religious
organization and corporation?
So many questions left unanswered.
Let's go and talk to the crowd.
Excuse me, are you a
Kenneth Marshall supporter?
I am. I am. Big time.
I am a full-on supporter.
I basically am the one and only.
Are you from Marshall's official channel?
No way!
So Marshall's watching this right now?
Oh, my God!
You need to pick me.
I swear. Please, pick me.
You need people young and healthy...
...and gentlemen, we have
another wild sandstorm today.
Access is now restricted to game three.
Please visit our stand for
discounted goggles and masks.
Additional 5% off with
Marshall Pay, as always.
The other expeditions wouldn't
take me, but they're wrong.
I promise I can fix toilets.
I make gingerbreads.
You've got to take me, Commissioner.
Expendable.
You're applying to be an expendable?
Seriously?
You read through the whole application?
Uh, yeah.
I should have read through it.
I mean, I didn't have too much of a choice.
I don't have any bona fide certifications.
I don't really have any skills whatsoever.
But then I find out
Timo's already called dibs
on a position for
himself as a flitter pilot.
He only just got his learner's
permit a couple of weeks before.
No idea what he had to
come up with to pull that off.
But you've got to give it to him.
Excuse me.
Is there, like, some construction going on?
Sorry, what?
I don't hear like a...
like a chainsaw.
Uh, no.
I want it to get the hell out of there.
Somewhere where the
sound couldn't follow me.
Far out into space.
You read through the paperwork?
Yes.
You read it, so you know, right,
this is gonna be a pretty extreme job.
But it's also gonna be... fun.
I'll explain all the details.
I got so distracted by that smell.
Uh, the smell of this woman's hair.
It was like it brought back some
faraway memory or something.
That giant tank downstairs
is called a cycler.
It takes organic waste
produced in the spaceship.
Apple peels, chicken bones, rotten eggs,
dead bodies, human waste, you name it.
Then it combines,
refines and recycles them.
And sends a portion to this printer.
Raw materials for a human body.
Once you die and the
committee approves, it'll
print a new version of
your body within 20 hours.
Take your clothes off.
Change into this.
I couldn't even hear
anything she was saying.
It was like all my senses
were focused on my nose.
Like real deja vu, but for a smell.
We're going to do a
full scan of your bio data.
That means you'll be reprinted
exactly as you are right now.
Forever.
I better pop this.
Otherwise it'll be there every time.
Well, I'm glad she didn't
know about the one on my butt.
So after she does the body
scan, she uploaded my memories.
Call it a personality backup.
And I gotta do this
once a week so I don't
have any big gaps every
time they print me out.
In the past, you would have
needed a hard drive the size
of a commercial refrigerator
to copy an adult brain.
Now this little brick.
Clever, right?
So I was injected with
some special solution.
It brought back a flood of old memories.
Too many memories.
We were heading home from the supermarket.
And I asked to sit in the front seat.
I said, I'm big enough.
And that's when I saw the red button.
And I just pressed it and she crashed.
Put it to your head and pull the trigger.
This is the final requirement
to become an expendable.
Prove to me you have faith in this system.
From now on you need to get used to dying.
This is your job.
I began the four and a half
year journey as Mickey One.
When you're stuck in a spaceship
for that long, food is everything.
Warning, Mickey One.
Seven calories over the
current ration allocation.
On that first day in the cafeteria,
I think I might have started thinking,
what have I done?
A little.
The whole room was full of
people eating this crappy food.
And there's total silence.
Like you could hear a pin drop.
Until Kenneth Marshall...
and his wife, Ilfa, walk in.
And a whole bunch of
people just started going nuts.
I was thinking, what
the hell am I doing here?
But that's when I saw her.
Nasha.
That was the first time
I saw Nasha Barrage.
On day one of this long journey.
Keep that up for one...
That's two percent of the precious
meal you're eating right now.
As you know, our number
one priority is to conserve
food resources until
our arrival at Niflheim.
So that we maximize our survival rate.
So listen up.
Sexual intercourse, for example.
Each session consumes
a whopping 100 calories.
At least.
Depending on the participant's
duration times friction equals...
The point is, Kenneth is
talking to the committee
about banning all
sexual activity on the ship.
Are you sure this is the
right time to bring that up?
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
I was just trying to help you.
It's okay, Ilfa.
Am I doing okay?
Should I go harder?
Yes, yes. Go hard.
All right.
Fellow pioneers.
Once we've arrived at Niflheim and
we've secured our food production,
we will launch the greatest sex
encouragement campaign in history.
You will spread your
seed across the planet.
Even when it's restrictive,
you will always seafood.
NOW.
Formigating.
calidad to you.
Início.
God bless um...
God bless...
Those four years would have
felt like 40 if it weren't for Nasha.
She stayed with me in the best of times...
and kept by my side in the worst of times.
Not everyone gets lucky
enough to find a soulmate like this.
None of this would have happened
if I'd never boarded this spaceship.
So all hail the great
loan shark, Darius Blank.
Thanks, Darius.
But it wasn't like I was slack, you know.
I was super busy every
day taking care of Nasha.
She's an all-in-one elite agent.
And it's not easy
supporting someone who's a
soldier, a police
officer, and a firefighter.
But what she sees in me, I got no idea.
I'm just grateful.
But as soon as I step out the door,
the ship was filled with mostly dickheads.
Hey, Mickey, right?
Can we just ask?
What's it like to die?
You know, when you're reprinted?
Now, how does that feel?
Oh, come on, just tell us.
We really want to know.
Imagine spending years
elbow to elbow with these bozos.
It was enough to push anyone over the edge.
Sometimes even if
Nasha, who is a model
citizen, would have to
step in and remind us...
...that we were all one big happy family.
There to help one another.
There to have each other's backs.
A tight-knit, harmonious community.
...and the committee
has written about this.
Hey, Mickey.
You must be hungry. Have some more.
Uh, thanks, Kai.
Can you change your shampoo?
Shampoo?
There's only one shampoo in
this entire space. Thank you.
It was a very long trip
in a beautiful community.
Hi.
But, uh, Nasha was obviously
my one and only, you know.
For real.
And as for my one and
only job, I was proud of it.
I felt like I was part of the team.
Be careful.
Patty!
Travelers... And
sisters... And sisters...
It is long that we have caught
four years together in this ship...
...and that we love you
like our very own family.
And here we are right below us
awaits our very own planet of purity...
What's fucking wrong with him?
It's fine, aren't it?
Maybe we have some glue or something.
Like a virgin vanilla ice cream.
Touched for the very first time.
It's gonna be really cold.
Whoever's gone down there
first is gonna freeze to death.
And then, make easy
breaths, fill your lungs,
and you're sucking in every single
microscopic particle floating around.
All the viruses.
Fill every avioli.
So good?
Oh, so good!
Brilliant.
There really was an
unknown virus in the air.
A lethal one.
So fucking warm.
I'm fine.
In the end, thanks to the lab
rats Mickey 12, 13, 14, 15, and 16
getting stabbed, gasped, dumped,
and burned, we got the vaccine.
My great gift to mankind.
And so, we didn't need oxygen masks,
and we could see our
breath as much as we wanted.
Look at that, Jennifer. Ridiculous.
I can't believe we
still live in that thing.
I know, right?
Planfall was ages ago.
And we're still eating the
same crappy in-flight TV dinner.
Precisely why we ought to
build residential complexes.
You know, grow crops as soon as possible.
Yeah, sure.
You know, spread the seed.
Infest the land.
Propagate the species.
It's freezing.
Whoa.
Look at that color.
Yeah.
It's beautiful.
Oh.
He's such a klutz.
You should learn some Breakfall moves.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Come on.
What's Breakfall?
What is it?
Come on, Mickey, let's go!
Go, go, go, go!
Mickey, Mickey, it's Marshall.
You fucking useless little asshole.
You're an expendable.
You're here to be expended.
Damn it!
I'm so sorry.
And why is Jennifer Chilton, a
precious, fertile female, dead and not you?
How do you train us?
You know?
Fuck you.
That's what I want to know.
Disgusting.
Really?
You don't like my sauce?
No, no, no, no, darling.
Those things.
Look at them.
What the fuck's going on?
They're delicious, aren't they?
Oh, for some reason, I like it.
Hey, you.
Stand still.
Don't move.
They lust.
For humans.
God.
You're a body of flesh.
Creepy.
Oh, honey.
That's perfect.
We should call them creepers.
I'll call them creepers.
I'm calling them creepers.
Preston, are you listening?
Expendable, I've decided
in the committee that
going forward, your
rations will be halved.
So, my shift doubled,
14 hours every day, seven
days a week, until I brought
home a creeper sample.
How did I survive that?
What's it feel like to die?
Even on my 17th
go-round, I really hate dying.
Still. Always.
Bon appétit.
Where am I? What's going on?
I'm not coming out of the printer.
I'm still 17.
Why didn't that thing eat me?
I was passed out.
Did I not look tasty enough?
Oh, I've got it.
They're saving me for their kiddos.
What a great mom.
Oh, please just make it quick.
Come on, guys. Big bites. Big bites.
Ow!
Where are you taking me now?
Has my meat gone bad
after all that reprinting?
I'm still good meat!
I'm perfectly good meat!
I taste fine!
...
... ...
...ditching me out here
in the middle of nowhere...
...it's not cool!
...that rock is, are you blind? You can't
just have the other bat feuds through here!
Science requested it, so
don't give me shit about it!
You try to jam it in and scratch anywhere
on this date, my date, it's on you!
On me? How? Blame the
guys in science. They cut into
this site, but I got specific
orders to bring it as is!
I don't fucking care, okay? Through the
meeting over there, I can't reach them.
I'm not taking the fall for
this. Every time you come in
here, my gate, gate 3, you
act like you own the place.
Why would I wanna own this shit already?
You should shut the fuck up, okay?
You know what? You need to get laid.
Fuck you!
...you need to get laid. Fuck you!
Oh damn, Nicky!
Didn't expect to see you out there today.
Wait, is that the time?
It's 3.30?
...it doesn't really make any sense.
...Do you remember what?
Do you remember when I left?!
What did you say?
...razón!
...shut it off!
...the maze!
...the switch!
It's that time again, the
dinner of your dreams,
with Kenneth Marshall,
who will be this month's
lucky guest of honour.
A grand surprise awaits.
Hang onto your ship,
because the dove of luck
just might come fluttering its wings with
an invitation for you. From Dove with Love,
over and out.
What is this?
Why aren't you dead?
Oh God, oh God, oh God. No, no, no, no.
18? They printed you out today?
What the fuck is going
on? According to Timo, you
should be sliding out on one of those
creeper's assholes right about now.
You have to put it like that?
Oh God, I'm completely fucked.
What do you mean?
We're multiples.
I gotta kill you.
Kill me?
I mean, you should probably
kill yourself if one of us has to die.
It's been, like, two hours since I
was printed. I've barely had a life.
Well, I was never dead. So you don't count.
Go back to the cyclone!
Multiples. Where do I even begin?
Mankind is not equipped to
deal with the legal and ethical
implications of adopting this
human printing technology.
Please tell me.
Can any of you honestly guarantee
that the technology will not be abused?
No one in their R&D department
could come up with a convincing answer.
But the real problem was
that one of the brains behind
human printing turned out
to be a certified psychopath.
Helen Manikova.
I think it's him.
Are you sure?
There was this series of particularly
brutal murders targeting homeless people.
And only one eyewitness account.
But it matched Alan
Manikova's appearance to a tee.
The cops thought they had their man,
except Manikova had a surefire alibi.
At the time of the
murder, he was getting his
makeup done for a
children's science show.
But the cops had his number.
When they raided Manikova's house, they
brought two sets of handcuffs and warrants.
They were on to him.
Or rather, they were on to them.
Which one's Manikova Prime?
You?
Or you?
Yep, there were two.
One for the murder, and one for the alibi.
Manikova had printed another
Manikova without the company knowing.
So here's a question for you.
Are they accomplices, or did
one act under the other's orders?
Are these separate and independent crimes,
or were they one person from the get-go?
They only get half portions in jail, or...
they get a full meal each.
Police, legal experts,
philosophers, everyone was stumped.
But while Manikova One and Two were
both locked up in an interrogation room,
another homeless man was brutally murdered.
Lo and behold, Manikova Three.
I think it was some cheap
tabloid reporter who called
them multiples, or some
professor or something.
Whoever came up with it, it stuck.
And pretty soon the word
multiples spread fear and contempt.
So multiples are an abomination.
They destroy the natural order.
Each soul shall only have one body.
Right?
One soul, one body.
The Lord, he only blesses
this one-to-one union.
But former Congressman Marshall
does have a point worth considering.
It would be a shame.
Not to explore the potential
application of this advanced technology.
I was happy to receive an
invitation from this committee.
You were subpoenaed, Mr. Marshall?
Sure, sure.
In any case, I want to take this opportunity
to speak as an expedition commander.
Human printing is a sin.
Multiples are Satan's work.
However, I've been
contemplating how can we use
this abomination for our
common economic benefit.
I propose a trial run of human printing far
from Earth under the strictest oversight,
limiting such individuals
to one per expedition
per planet under the
designation expendable.
Multiples, in the case of multiples,
we exterminate every offending individual,
in totality, mind and body, all
for the sake of public service.
On this Niflheim
expedition, all multiples will
immediately be arrested,
executed and permanently deleted.
Oh, man.
What the hell is this guy?
Nasha told me that Mickey
3 was whiny and clingy,
5 was indecisive and apparently 8
was pretty annoying and kind of stupid,
but none of them were complete nut jobs.
Even this lunatic is scared
of being a multiple, though.
That's permanent deletion.
Trying to trash me in the cycler.
If one of us has to go...
it ain't gonna be me.
We can split the workload, too.
And we can take turns dying.
You're 18, so you can take even numbers,
and I'll just cover 19, 21 and odd numbers.
Are you afraid to die?
Kinda, yeah.
You've died plenty of times.
What are you so scared of?
Until now, I died
and... I was just...
born again.
You know?
It felt like it was me, continuing on.
But now...
once I die...
it'll be over for me.
It'll be you living on.
You get what I mean?
I don't like you.
You're such a little bitch.
But I'm you.
I'm not you.
I'm not gonna live like you.
I'm gonna kill you!
What the fuck, man?
Are you trying to get noticed?
They don't even have cameras.
Take that off, you dumbass.
Amateur.
Your first time.
No, no.
This is the pure stuff, right?
Undiluted?
Who do you think you're talking to?
This...
is pure uncut oxy.
It's fucking rare.
You only get two oxyzulfocapsules
and one flamethrower, man.
... ...
...
... ... ... ... ... ... ...
... ... ... Wait. Fact-checking.
Have fun, man.
Let's kill him.
Are you crazy?
He's like my only friend.
Forever.
Same warfare as this meat shit.
Wait, wait, wait.
Demo!
Mickey, what?
Looks like business is blowing up, huh?
What are you talking about?
Another junkie coming in.
Hey!
Are you mental?
Wait till I get out of
here or I'll kill you!
What the fuck is this?
Come down lower!
You fucking idiot!
Mickey, help me.
What is that?
Why is it so red? That looks hot.
What are you doing?
I want you to have a car dying.
You son of a bitch.
What?
Come on!
Stop!
Shh, shh, shh.
Who's that, Mickey?
Hey, what's going on?
Mickey, what are you doing here?
Uh, Demo accidentally fell in.
But, uh... he's alright now.
I wanna keep dealing, motherfucker.
Watch what you say.
What happened?
You okay?
What's up with your hand?
Uh...
I was taking out the trash
and I tripped into the hole.
I would have been a
goner if not for Mickey.
I almost became a cyclodust.
Hey.
You alright?
Don't you stay in bed. It's only been
a few hours since you were printed.
Yeah, I should have died.
You heard the rumor?
Huh?
Some guy out there is
dealing undiluted oxytocin.
What?
That's crazy. That's pretty messed up.
Between us, Timo?
A drop here and there before
bed to take the edge off?
I get it.
But the pure uncut
stuff is crossing the line.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
That's... bad.
Nasha, take Mickey home. I'll wrap up here.
Yes.
Thank you. I'll see you tomorrow.
Today I feel like... B6.
B6?
Yeah.
Flying Nasha.
It's definitely my place for now.
It's alright.
B6.
B6 was ours, Nasha.
Mickey?
Hey, brother.
I was just headed to your room to catch
you, but here you are. Looking good, Mickey.
Yes, sir.
Stand there.
Arm around, please.
Great.
Big smile, Mickey.
Sorry. Could you just stand there?
Great. Thank you.
And action.
Congratulations.
This month's lucky winner,
the fortunate soul who will have the
privilege of a private dinner at the camera,
will have a private dinner with the
one and only Kenneth Marshall is...
Is that the barrel?
It's Mickey.
Great. Big smile. Smile.
Yeah. Amazing.
Okay, cut.
Now, Marshall wants you to come ASAP, okay?
He's got a whole feast
prepared just for you.
The Lord is truly blessing
you today, Mickey.
I need to go back to my room.
You get to stuff your fucking face, Mickey.
I bet that freak is probably
drooling all over my
beautiful Nasha already.
It's disgusting.
What's even more
disgusting is that I'm drooling
at the thought of the tenderloin
steak I ordered for Marshall's dinner.
This is so wrong!
So glad you seem to be enjoying it.
How's the sauce?
Oh.
Oh, sorry, sorry. Please.
Continue.
Yeah, yeah, Mickey, uh,
listen, going back to everything that
happened with, uh...
Jennifer?
Yes, Jennifer.
Jennifer, uh...
I know, I know.
When we lost our
dear Jennifer Chilton,
I may have gotten a little
angry and said some
terribly unkind things.
I know it's late, and
I want to apologize.
Oh, he's always like this.
Such an adorable
man, and then suddenly he's all cutthroat.
Sorry.
You're still squishy,
fresh out of the printer.
Continue feeding him.
Oh, anyway, we have
another special guest here.
Hi, Kai.
Sorry I'm late.
You look very nice.
Thank you.
Come, come.
It's good to see you.
Sit.
You okay, emotionally?
Yeah, I feel fine, sir.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear it, Kai.
I'm so sorry about Jennifer.
I hear you were extremely close,
your best friend.
But I knew you'd stay
strong throughout the long.
Thank you, ma'am.
But we didn't invite you
here simply to comfort you.
We've had our eyes on you, Cass.
Me, sir?
May I ask why?
You're one of us.
With your impeccable
genetics, you are the perfect
specimen for the
colony I envision.
Thank you, sir.
That's why the church,
I mean, um, company,
has chosen me to lead this expedition.
The Earth's beyond saving
with all its muddied people.
But you,
you're something special,
and I'm creating a world
on a pure white planet
full of superior
people like you and us.
Isn't that right, darling?
Yes. It's his vision,
his sensibilities.
But let's be honest.
With your medical records in hand,
you ran to join our expedition
instead of one of those pathetic
planets where they plant microchips
in their artificially
inseminated baby embryos.
You really are the perfect candidate for
Niflheim's natural child birthing program,
aren't you, dear?
Mr. Marshall,
am I just a uterus to you?
No! No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, it's nothing like that.
Kai, no.
This man is not one to objectify women.
All my husband means to say
is he has very high standards.
His only dream is of a planet
exclusively for a pure human race.
That consumes real crops
and real meat
and dinners with delicate,
delicious sauces.
Oh, sauce is the true
litmus test of civilization.
People who devour
burnt meat are barbarians.
Do try the sauce, Kai.
Here, I made it myself.
Oh, thank you.
But first, I'd like to say a few
words in Jennifer's memory.
A prayer.
Always ready for a prayer.
Jennifer,
when I first met you at
the cafeteria four years ago.
..
You were...
Dear Lord, Jennifer Chilton's
one and only soul
was taken from her
wonderful friend, Kai.
Dear Lord,
Jennifer Chilton... Rejoice
in the Lord our one and only
Almighty Let us
sing for our Father's
grace
Thank God for our Father's
grace God almighty free at last
We're going to the
promised land A sea of light
in your light Your kingdom
in front of our eyes Hallelujah
Hallelujah Your servant
at the top has died Let's go!
Let's get up now
Forever and then
Come again Come again
For ever is your kingdom God Almighty
God of glory Christ has welcomed us Who HD
is God This peace
You are perfect
No, no, no, not at all.
I mean, artificial meat is crap.
How are we supposed to improve it
unless we fail upward to perfection?
No. Arkady, stand tall in
your failures like me, my friend.
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
Commander, so you were testing
out your in-flight TV dinner on him?
In-flight TV dinner?
Is that what the young
troops are calling it now?
Excuse me.
Are you in a lot of pain?
I'm being punished.
What?
It's my punishment.
I should have gone to
Nosh and not come here.
Dorothy, bring me Purple Joe.
Sir, you remember the special
painkiller we've been developing?
Yeah, Purple Joe.
It's a quick-fix turn to the agents, right?
Yes, since...
Since Mickey here is
in such awful pain, it's
a perfect opportunity
to try a little test.
So give it to him.
Oh, great. All right.
Don't touch him, please.
Mickey, can you see me?
Mickey?
Mickey!
Get back down there.
Mickey?
Oh, God. Oh, God.
What did he do?
Ah!
Apologies, sir.
The painkiller's not working.
Don't film this, Preston.
Please, turn it off.
This is better, right? More humane.
Yes, sir. More humane.
No, no, no, no, no, no! What are you doing?
Huh?
You can't tear a hole in my fucking carpet!
Well, we'll just shoot him from the side.
But what about the blood?
This is a Persian tavern!
Honey, calm down.
Shoot him now.
What the hell is going on?
This was supposed to be a fucking dinner!
He's your guest!
Agent Guy Katz, what the
hell's going on with you?
He's a meat matrix.
It's a goddamn print job.
Inexpendable.
He signed up for this.
Yes, sir.
This is for our planet, Agent.
I'm sorry, sir.
Come on, guys.
Please don't shoot him.
I'm okay now.
I don't think so.
He still seems like he's in a lot of pain.
Of course he is.
Are you really okay?
Just thank you for dinner.
Huh.
My room's just there.
You need to clean up and rest, Mickey.
Don't worry about me.
I can walk.
I just need to get back to my room.
No, I'm just about to...
Actually, we're going to mine.
Here.
It's dry.
I drink this whenever I have a stomachache.
It's from Earth.
It's precious.
So I've been saving it.
But I made some for you.
Thanks.
Sit.
You know, Mickey...
I didn't want to ask you this.
But just this once, okay?
And I'm so sorry.
What's it like?
Dying?
You're asking because of Jennifer?
Yeah.
We locked eyes...
in the last moment.
What did you feel?
As all that ice came crashing down on her?
I can't stop thinking about it.
I don't think it's what I usually feel.
It's...
I die so often.
Because you know you're
going to wake up again, right?
Because you die knowing that.
Oh...
Well, I always feel scared.
It's terrible.
Dying.
I hate it.
No matter how many times I go through it.
It's scary.
Still.
Always.
Every time.
But you're here.
And Jennifer isn't.
Out there.
The entire universe.
She's nowhere.
You don't look like you're printed out.
You're just a person.
Are you and Nasha open?
I have to go.
Nasha.
Please forgive me.
The guy that you're having sex with.
That's not me.
You motherfucker.
How dare you touch her.
Seventeen.
I knew this would happen at some point.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Stand, stand.
Stand next to each other.
Wait, take this off.
What?
Yeah, I want you to look the same.
Oh, my God.
Nasha, how can you laugh right now?
This is a multiples violation.
I'm as good as dead.
Oh, come on.
When else am I going to get these shots?
I mean, think about it.
It would be so psyched
if there were two of me.
This is mild Mickey.
And this is habanero Mickey.
This is so exciting.
This is so different.
Nasha, you're different, too.
You don't seem like yourself.
Oh, Jesus.
You just did oxyzophil with him?
Just a teeny tiny bit.
With a ton of water.
What?
Do you want some?
Yeah, yeah.
Relax.
Just take it easy.
Nasha.
This piece of shit just
tried to kill me earlier.
Right here in this room.
Look, I was bleeding.
Like you weren't thinking
of trying the same thing.
I saw you sneaking up behind me.
Hey, hey, hey.
Shut up.
And sit down.
Oh, hey.
Attention.
From now on, I'm going to
feed you both as often as I can.
So be good boys and don't fight.
Now, 18 tells me you guys
have sorted it out already.
E-Huff.
Work off.
Alternating deaths?
Even so not.
It's a great system.
Negotiation time.
So everyone just chill.
Okay?
You leave us alone for a sec.
Why?
What's the problem?
I'm leaving.
Oh, you're such a baby.
I'm scared.
This guy needs some oxyzole for him.
Relax.
Talk about what?
I don't care about your private life.
Okay, fine.
But what's up?
What's the rush? Where are you going?
I just witnessed the multiples
violation with my own eyes.
As an agent, I have a duty to report it.
Since when have you been
coming to Mickey's room?
This is your first time, right?
What's up with you and Kai, bro?
Why was she here?
What are you supposed to do now?
She's gonna go straight to
Marshall and report us, isn't she?
You need to relax.
Nosh is handling it.
She can convince anybody of anything.
Phew. Oh my God.
Besides, this moron is
busy with his clown show.
This fucker.
Such an attention whore.
And what did that asshole serve for dinner?
Was it good at least?
You really wanna know?
What went down at that dinner?
So...
the one with 17 on his chest...
that's the Mickey that
was in my room just before?
Mm-hmm.
And the one you were grabbing...
he's 18, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
You can have 18. I'll take 17.
Whoa.
There's two of them.
Why not share?
All right.
So you get this straight.
You were shitting your pants on the floor.
And he comes up and stabs
you in the neck with a syringe.
That's what happened.
I wasn't, like, shitting my pants.
I was just puking up a little.
That's not the point!
I've seen you rubbing up on Mickey
every chance you get, you fuckface.
You know, I've always wanted
to kick the living shit out of you.
Oh, Masha, come on.
I'm trying to be considerate.
Mickey, 17...
was about to double dip,
if you know what I mean.
Move on from you to me.
In fact, we almost...
Double dip?
Shut up!
Oh.
Mickey is not some
cookie you can split in half.
17 and 18 are both Mickey.
Both my Mickey.
So then after Marshall fucks you sideways,
you really let him have it, right?
Right!
What did you say?
I said...
I said I said thank you for dinner.
You said what?
I said thank you for dinner.
Thank you for fucking what?
God!
You son of a bitch!
Fucking loser!
Mike...
I guess I am kind of a loser.
What?
Is that what you are?
Huh?
Is it?
Free Atlanta!
The floor to the promised land!
And free Hawaii!
God!
Gah!!
It's not your fault.
Let's kill that fucker.
This guy would be killing each...
Kill this, kill that!
Why don't we kill everybody?
She can stay here and watch TV if you like.
You can stay here and watch TV if you like.
W. wait!
You can't negotiate
shit with that attitude.
Hey Jesus. You're hot on oxyzole foam.
Mickey!
He has your gun.
Gun?
We have to stop him.
What? Where's he going?
Why? Why? Why is Commander Marshall cutting
into that big beautiful handsome rock?
It's sleek, hot, exquisite.
This is where our names will be etched.
Mine and yours.
And you! And you! And you!
And you, my beautiful Eoclid.
Almost every single one of you will
be remembered throughout history
as the proud founders of Eoclid.
The land of Niflheim's first generation.
Our cornerstone. Black diamond.
Beautiful and shimmering in purity.
This rock will become the
symbolic monument of Niflheim.
The one and only pure colony planet.
The one and only Niflheim!
The one and only!
God, don't touch it, sir!
Maybe it's contagious!
It's contagious!
You touch it, you die!
Damn it!
I say it's contagious!
Stay calm! God damn it!
Scalding!
Initiate stay calm!
... ... ... ... ...
...
... ... ...
... ... ... ...
... ... ... ... ... ...
... ... ... ... ... ... ...
...
Don't shoot!
I'm not about to control! Don't shoot!
Yes? Calm down. Calm down.
We have everything under control.
You have, Marshal!
Those low-life multiples have
ruined our precious symbology.
Kill it! Get down, sir!
Open fire!
Kill it!
Arrest him, fucking multiples.
Tell the committee you are aiming
at the Creeper behind Marshal.
Otherwise you could
get permanently deleted.
Fuck that shit.
You really think Captain
Crane Pie is going to let us live?
He's probably going to shoot us himself.
He's a nutjob.
He doesn't listen to anybody.
He's the biggest, dumbest
nutjob out of all the Mickeys.
And that's saying something.
You screwed my entire life up.
Oh, really? We all got
fucked the minute you
decided not to die and
came crawling home to me.
That wasn't my fault.
That was the Creeper's fault.
Creeper?
Well, if that Creeper
is eating me like it's
supposed to, then we
won't be in this situation.
But they all kicked me out,
and I'm a goddamn multiple.
They kicked you out?
Yeah.
You're all pushing me and pulling me,
and they all threw me back into the snow.
Maybe I didn't look tasty enough,
or smelled off. I don't know.
Maybe I was in some kind of sauce.
Hold on. You're telling me they saved you?
Think about it. You shouldn't have died
in that crevasse. The Creeper saved you.
Uh, I guess if you put it like that,
uh, they were sort of saying me off.
I mean, maybe I should have said thank you.
Yeah. I don't think they
were going to eat you. Right?
Oh, my God.
We have to report this to science.
They saved humans.
Yeah. People need to know this.
They saved me.
Where's the fucking ladder?
You're supposed to bring a fucking ladder.
I don't know.
Here. Let me help.
Stop. Stop, stop, stop.
Stop. I'll do it myself.
I'm coming down myself. Get the fuck off.
Come on.
Hey, Timo. What are you doing here?
Oh, wow. You two really are multiples, huh?
But it's you.
Yeah, I see it in that
schmuck face of yours.
You're the one that
gave me this. Right?
Oopsie.
Here you go, guys.
You guys must be starving.
Thanks, man. I knew you'd be coming for us.
What are you up to?
What's all that?
So, um, here's the thing.
I need to shoot a video
and send it to Earth ASAP.
Video? To Earth?
Yeah. Um, it's for, uh...
Darius Blank.
Darius Blank? Who's that?
I found this at my door today.
It's written by hand.
It's a beautiful handwriting.
It's from Darius Blank's associate.
Yeah. His associate.
I'm not kidding. His associate.
You know what I mean? Like, of course.
Of course the loan shark
of all fuckin' loan sharks
would figure out a way
to send one of his guys
to follow us all the way here to Niflheim.
To where we are right now.
That's like a million fuckin'
miles from the world out there.
You know what I'm talking about?
Do you know how far that is?
No matter what pittance you
manage to scrape together,
we've found that
sending it to Earth will cost
you an intergalactic
transfer fee more than...
half the total sum.
God fucking associate!
I have no idea who that is!
I don't know who that is!
Isn't that fucking crazy?
Send a visual work of art.
That's fucking crazy.
A video file that captures
the details of death.
Read the back.
It says, chop up into a
minimum of 13 pieces.
Chop up?
Is that it?
What the fuck is this?
Hey! What did I say about the close-up?
Close-up is more important, okay?
So take the 32K camera
and put it over here for Mr.
Darius Blank.
You understand?
I'm sorry, Nicky.
It's all there.
Right? In the letter.
If I shoot this video and I
send it to him, he'll let me live.
If I don't,
I'm gonna send that guy in.
He's gonna kill me first.
What am I supposed to do?
Come on, dude. If I die, that's it for me.
But you're expendable.
They'll just print you right back out.
Please.
Nicky.
I'm your friend.
Okay?
Please do this for your friend one time.
You gotta do this for me, man.
I'm your brother.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, shit.
I should've killed this guy
when I had the chance.
You guys just do this for me this one time.
That's all I'm asking.
I'm so sorry.
Stop crying, you prick!
I'm getting on my fucking nerves.
Why don't you guys do
rock, paper, scissors, okay?
And then we'll just shoot the loser, yeah?
No.
All right.
Shoot him.
Him?
Yeah, him.
I wasn't expecting that.
I thought you'd choose him.
Yeah, you'd think so,
but the soft one's easier.
Come on.
You're a dumb fucking bitch, Timo.
If you do this and what space lets you
live, you think that'll be the end of it?
You don't think I'll tell you
to fuck in pieces myself?
Oh, my God.
What is the big deal?
All right, just take me instead.
What?
Just chop me up, not him.
Look at him.
You shot him one time with the tager,
it's like you just boofed a
fucking electric eel, man.
But you can chop my whole
body up into ten mickey chunks,
and I'll still be fresh as the
freshest sashimi, head held high.
Theorists will love that.
I just need a little of your help.
My help?
Can't I need more of that?
Oxy's hopeful.
Yeah, I got some oxy.
But undiluted.
You want...
You want undiluted oxy right now?
Yeah.
Just think of it as the, uh...
Think of it as the final
cigarette before execution.
It's the least you could do for a friend.
Give him yours.
What?
Come on.
No.
I'll give you a freebie next time.
You know me.
This was expensive.
The keys!
Nasha!
It's all mine.
Do it!
Nasha!
What are you doing?
What's going on here?
Nasha!
Stay put.
That did kind of shock me a bit.
I mean, she literally was gonna
cut his head off with a chainsaw.
Uh, but then I thought
about it and I was so touched.
She's the only person who'd
ever lose it like that over me.
And it wasn't the first time either.
Nasha.
She's the only one who's
always been there for me.
She's always loved me.
Every me.
Even him.
The me I don't understand at all.
What is this?
Oh, you don't know about this.
They've been circling the whole night.
And still more coming in.
What are they doing?
We don't know.
They can break through solid ice and stone.
Imagine if they all come from this ship.
Terrifying!
But you couldn't even tear
through the sack at the cafeteria.
You hear that?
It's coming from the one
we captured yesterday.
Keep going, keep going.
Wait, you mean the baby?
Well, yeah.
It's been screaming and crying like one.
And that's when they all started gathering.
That was... That was the
one that I... Keep going.
Never mind.
Hi.
How you doing?
Excuse me!
Come up.
Somebody passing through?
Hey.
Why did they set up
the situation room there?
Beats me.
I was just told to bring the prisoner.
Apparently, Otha made a big scene.
She wants the creeper now.
Darby, I have crucial
information about the creepers.
McGee needs to file an official
report with the head of science.
Oh, wait.
Yes, I knew it.
Yesterday, at the cafeteria when
you held on to the baby, I saw it.
You saw that?
I don't know what it means, though.
Oh.
What?
So you were just imitating?
Well, originally... No offense.
What's the matter?
It's really hectic right now.
Let's talk later.
We're recording the sounds to see
if we can analyze any kind of pattern.
The committee is declaring
a level three emergency.
Sole command and
control has been granted
to Commander Marshall
by a vote of 36 to 21.
Thank you.
What an event.
This is a truly novel ingredient.
This opens up a whole new
world of potential sauces.
It's such a great... how should I put it?
Opportunity, ma'am.
Yes, quite the opportunity.
Just super.
Yes, it is a super opportunity.
Oh, wow.
It's such a godsend, too.
It is free from harmful pathogens, correct?
Yes, ma'am.
Sure.
Which dickhead is it, Mickey 18?
Keep his head still!
Now I can tell you to a punch.
Filthy multiples.
Oh, yeah.
That does seem fair.
Oh, goodness.
Bright meat.
That's nothing, honey.
Wait till these two are
scorched sausages in the cyclo.
How are you going to handle that stench?
Mickey.
I'm so sorry.
You too.
This brick stores your memories, right?
Now you'll watch as I permanently
delete your being from it.
That way you'll understand
the meaning and terror of finality.
No more reprints!
That's what you both should
be thinking when you die.
Dead forever!
Now that the memory is
gone, which body goes first?
One of the times, twice the fun.
Creepy.
Commander Marshall, sir.
May I say a few words?
Regardless of who burns
first, the simple fact is...
we currently have two
Mickeys here before us.
Due to no fault on their part, I might add.
One of them is being falsely
accused of firing his gun at you.
But the truth is...
he was concerned for your safety.
He was the first to notice the second
Creeper coming out of the stone behind you.
And as you are well aware, the day
an expendable is printed... Enough!
You, defending these idiots,
should be mopping up your own shit.
Illegal possession of oxyzophil.
Concealment of a multiples violation.
It's disappointing.
An attempted murder
without... fucking chainsaw?
I mean, it's quite the colorful rap
sheet, don't you think, Miss Barrage?
The clouds of war are billowing.
Look at those vermin swarmed.
Mankind must unite
at this critical juncture.
Why are we wasting our time
with these dregs of society?
Spoken like a true wartime commander, sir.
Very impressive.
And a fine entry to add to your
collection of battle quotes, if I may.
You like that?
I do.
More of that?
Please.
You keep mentioning
that we're in a state of war.
May I be so bold as to
offer two observations, sir?
Be my guest.
Firstly, fighting a war requires a
huge amount of energy and calories.
Seeing as we're in
the early stages of
settlement and our
survival is in the balance,
I wonder whether this
expenditure is prudent.
Secondly, our apparent
enemies are the Creepers.
But do we know whether they
actually want to engage in war?
For hours they've been swirling
in circles doing nothing but wailing.
My God, Agent Verge.
You used to be a five-time
Marshall Cup champion.
Agent of the Month.
And now you're sweating
over these alien insects?
How far you've fallen.
What are you going to do when they tear
a hole in this ship and tear off your ass?
These grotesque shit gibbons.
Grotesque or not, they are the
native inhabitants of this planet.
And we have proof that
they saved one of us.
They didn't eat him or attack him.
Saved and not eaten who?
Uh, me.
They saved me.
Of course they didn't eat you.
You're crap food.
You're recycled spam, baby.
You get chewed up and shit
out over and over and over again.
Well, I guess they aren't
just stupid bugs, honey.
I mean, they knew to pass on crap.
Junk.
They must have some cognitive ability.
Exactly.
Actually, they exhibit
signs of high intelligence.
They may be able to engage
in meaningful conversation.
And we're analyzing this and...
Sir?
You must try communicating
with them yourself.
We're developing a sort of translator.
Like that, you mean?
You think I'm an idiot?
Oh, fuck.
Four and a half years
across the fucking galaxy
just to hear these
goddamn alien squawks?
Tell me how the fuck that
makes any sense, somebody?
How does this make any sense?
How does your bullshit make any sense?
You know, your fucking fuckface is what
really doesn't make any fucking sense.
You fucking...
IDIOT!
You call them aliens?
We're the aliens, dumbass!
They would have been here before us.
And Mickey...
Mickey was always just Mickey Barnes.
Do you even understand what that means?
They were just living their lives
before you came in with your bullshit!
And you think you get to
decide who lives and who dies?
You are a dumb fuck!
No wonder you blew the
elections, you fucking moron.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
God, hang up!
Bite.
What?
Falling in three, two, one.
Fine, as you shut the fuck up.
This is clearly abuse,
one kiss after the other.
Rolling.
In the 32K.
Make sure you get everything.
Impressive teeth.
Yeah.
We need more of our guys.
Sir, now might be the prime
time to initiate total extermination.
The ones out there alone
would be more than enough.
What are you talking about?
We're gonna gas them,
we're gonna gas them all.
What's that look for?
Still not confident in your failures?
No, no, sir.
Arcadi 3.0 has gone through
several meticulous stages of testing.
Arcadi 3.0 is the ultimate nerve gas.
I have every confidence in it, sir.
As you should, Arcadi.
This has to succeed.
I'll put it in my prayers.
This is the day we've
been waiting for, sir.
Future historians will
mark today as error-defining
for cleansing dangerous
species on colony planets.
Why don't you board
the flitter yourself later?
You mean when we spray the gas?
Yeah.
I pull the trigger?
Exactly, sir.
If you write the leaf flitter and
appear to commandeer the operation,
the footage I get, it will be historic.
And the members, the church
members back on Earth, they will adore it.
Yes, yes, the company.
All right.
It's time we initiate
Operation Total Extermination.
Honey, can I have a word with you?
Yes, my love.
I've got an idea.
I hope you both can appreciate what a
great honor my wife has bestowed on me.
I'm going to be storing
on your shit stains.
And so I can press both
buttons simultaneously?
Yes, sir.
Press them and they'll
go off at the same time.
They'll also explode automatically if
they exit the range of the remote control.
You hear that?
I have you by the balls.
Don't even think of running off.
You'll each be given a primitive
weapon as you head out.
You cut off as many creeper
tails as you can, and the
first Mickey to bring back
100 tails is the winner.
And the winner doesn't die.
But the loser goes...
Boom!
Boom.
A world keeps going from here.
Your job is to make
them scream so loudly that
every last creeper comes
running in to save them.
We'll kill two birds with
one stone, right honey?
Oh, absolutely. 100 tails is enough to
make enough sauce to last a couple years.
Better be on your toes.
One false move and you're man burger.
It's all punishment.
What was that?
My entire life's a goddamn punishment.
All for pressing that
button when I was five.
Oh, this again.
Accident was caused by a
car defect, you know that?
I don't know.
Well, it wasn't pressing
that stupid button.
It wasn't while I was driving either.
How many times I gotta tell you?
Sorry, Mickey.
Mickey, you need to move. Like, now.
Can you at least put the ramp down?
We can't do that right now. I'm sorry.
You're gonna have to drive.
What?
Mickey!
Take this.
It's not finished, but it might help
you communicate with the Creepers.
Let's go.
Is this like a translator thing?
Yes. Good luck.
For what it's worth, I doubt
Marshall will kill both of you.
Come on.
Well, I... Go.
With this device, I got a job to do.
All right.
They saved me. Now I save them.
What are those fuckers doing?
Even I can count.
Dozens of fresh tails
they're leaving behind.
Are they out of their minds?
Oh, honey.
Should I just press the button?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's sit back and watch.
They'll start chopping
tails as soon as they
realize one of them
has to outlive the other.
Hey!
It's me!
You gotta run away!
You gotta get them all out of here!
You gotta go back to your cave!
Go back to your cave!
Or you're all gonna die.
What?
Oh, hello.
Um...
Yes, I just... I wanted...
About last time, I...
Uh...
I...
I wanted to say...
Thank you.
Um...
Do you remember me right?
Mickey.
Uh...
How do you know my name?
Cigarette.
Wait, are they having a conversation?
Yes.
We already explained it just now.
How?
How is this possible?
Oh, well, it's still a prototype,
but it's like a translator device.
Dor... Dorothy?
Oh, no, where's Dorothy?
I can't hear a thing with all the static.
I mean, even the video is shit!
Apologies, sir. The snowstorm is exacerbating
the absorption... What about this?
Will this detonator work?
Yes, sir. That is a special
shortwave signal, so it'll be fine.
And who's that big one there?
Is that the queen bee of the bunch?
Hmm, looks like a croissant dipped in shit.
Uh, official reports
are still being finalized,
but we think everything
revolves around that one.
The mama creeper.
So that one's the boss. Like you.
Say what?
We gotta get out of here, or they're
gonna kill you all with this death gas.
That gas, Arcadi 3.0,
I got blasted with that.
It's seriously...
...insanely painful.
Do you know what gas is? Gas?
Like...
...like gas?
Mind your own business, stupid.
Mind my own business? What about you?
Why'd you save him at the cave?
Should kill him?
No!
I'm... ...we're very
grateful. That's all.
Then why?
Why kill Luko?
Uh... ...Luko?
Baby...Luko.
Oh.
You grew.
Shattered.
Blood.
Yeah, uh...
...oh, that's, uh...
...that's Luko.
We save you.
You kill Luko.
So what's the name of the other baby?
The one on the ship?
Zuko.
Kill Zuko, too.
What if Zuko dies? What will you do?
Death.
All.
You mean all humans.
Extinction!
How?
Easy.
Unless somebody
wants to kill me.
Desperate.
Dusko.
уль What's wrong with them? What's wrong
with him? And they're saying something.
What is that idiot saying?
It's not sign language.
C3? C3? What's C3?
Bring the baby! Bring the baby!
Honey, this doesn't sit
well with me. Why are those
two losers chatting with
the boss of the bugs?
They think they're negotiating
on behalf of mankind, humankind?
You should be standing out there, sir.
Ushering in this historic moment.
You're seeing two bosses meeting
face to face in a climactic snowstorm?
A moment of destiny?
All you have to do is go out there.
I know I can create an iconic scene.
A decisive moment in the
history of the Niflheim settlement.
Oh, I can picture it now.
Adorning the ceiling and
the walls of the Grand Chapel.
Yes, ma'am. Yes.
One final touch, sir.
I think it would be great if you give
them a message before spraying the gas.
A message?
Without such poignancy,
today will be a third-rate
carnival where we spray cheap
pesticide over cockroaches.
Yes, they are disgusting, filthy, evil
insects, but it will be their last moment.
And you could offer them a few
merciful words as a proper farewell.
Like a wise, benevolent priest.
Get me a camera crew. Tell the
first squad to meet me fully armed.
Yes, sir.
My love, the Situation Room is yours.
Till we meet again?
C-3!
Not who you want to meet.
It's the wrong thing.
I want to get Sokol back safe.
I mean it!
Not enough.
But what else?
We lose Luko.
One.
Be fair.
Be fair?
And we have to contribute to death?
Yes.
Fair.
One of yours.
Die.
So if we bring back Sokol
safe, and a human dies?
Peace.
Do you copy?
Okay, the radio signal is
a little patched right now,
so the comms speaker will
be on the right line of comms.
Units, who do you copy?
Our orders are to send you a
score for under-martial... Die!
I'm not going to dance!
Do not entertain the queen!
Die!
I'm down.
Okay, right after your speech,
sir, we'll close the canopy
at once, and that will be
the signal for the air squad.
Spray that gas.
Glorious annihilation, sir.
You.
Yes, you.
Come here.
What's your name?
Matthew?
Oh, Matthew.
You have the face of an angel.
Here.
Try my socks.
Here you go.
Tell me what you think.
No!
Take it easy.
One snap and it's instant death.
Nasha Barrage, what do you want?
The baby.
We have to take it to the moment.
That's all?
Yes.
Guarantee us a safe exit.
Unless you want to see me break her neck.
No.
Nasha, please don't.
Look, we secure Nasha's exit as negotiated.
Nasha, can you release her carefully?
Let me get the baby.
Be careful.
Nasha, are you okay?
I need to hurry.
Can I get a flitter?
I doubt it.
You'll have to run.
Ma'am, today you and the
commander have displayed
an impressive range
of verbal and physical
abuse and acts of cruelty that
far exceed your granted authority.
You want to be executed for mutiny?
All video evidence of abuse will be
presented to the committee for review.
I suggest you have answers
prepared for your hearing.
Thanks, Zeke.
Maintain control on site.
Here!
We'll start slowly circling
the creature from the outside...
Making the scene
absolutely spectacular, sir.
I'll keep my speech short and tight.
A marvelous address, no need to add it.
And then I'll blow off the mickeys.
Pokemon Go!
You can do this, Nachi.
We'll get things under control inside.
Okay. See ya.
Good luck!
Nachi's gonna figure this all out.
His own will be back, you see.
Who is that?
Who's coming?
Wait.
What is this bullshit?
Which one's your mama?
What the fuck am I supposed to be
looking at when I make my speech?
I was gonna send them off with some dinghy!
Now a barbarian can fuck off!
Is that bazooka ready?
Yes, sir. Loading now.
We're gonna blast that
mama bitch into oblivion.
We need to fucking speed.
I'll go hard.
That's the mama there, sir!
Can you see it?
That's a different shit!
Yes, it's her!
It's not her death!
Sorry, sir.
McKay!
Naza!
Come to say goodbye.
What?
Jesus Christ!
I knew you would make it!
Is the baby okay?
Look!
You're also afraid.
Yeah, I'm afraid.
I need you, human.
You're important.
Come to me, my boy.
Okay, guys!
Guys!
Don't be shy.
Sit down, take your seats.
The groundbreaking
ceremony will come later.
But we'll start with the expendable stuff.
Mickey, come up to the front, mate.
Can someone please sit on the
front row, you fucking introverts.
Hello everyone.
I'm Nasha Barrage, member of the committee.
After weeks of debate, we have
finally come to this momentous day.
The day we abolish the
Expendables Programme.
I would like to thank my fellow
committee members for their support.
I've been really feeling the love.
And especially for
fighting right to the end
and persuading the committee to
permanently abolish human printing.
I would like to thank our
very own Mickey Barnes.
And to be fair, I'm just so fucking
happy I get to grow old with Mickey.
I was really stuck in
getting old by myself.
Okay.
Alright.
So you hit the button.
Wait.
Nasha will give the signal.
You hit the button.
Wait.
And then over there...
Do I get up and press it or...?
No, in my seat, right?
I honestly couldn't give a fuck.
Henceforth, on Niflheim, as on Earth,
human printing is now
permanently abolished.
Here today, the human
printer will be burnt to ashes
and erased from memory.
Nasha's such a natural.
I think she could even run for
committee chair next election.
It blows my mind still to
think that this amazing woman
just six months ago was riding
with the rest of us in that shitty prison.
The day Marshall got blown to dust,
Ilfa went into shock and
was taken to the psych ward.
Rumors went around that
she slit her wrists there.
And everyone else
involved was shoved into jail
and somehow lucky Timo
squeezes out on parole.
But as soon as he got out, he
spent every day dreading the moment
he'd come face to face with
the man who delivered the letter.
The associate of Darius Blank.
Who one day finally jumped him.
It was a fight to the death.
In the end, the associate became a...
cyclosoup.
Except for one ear.
Even at the trial, Timo
chooses to represent himself.
As he had his grip on me, he brought his
knife around to my midsection right here.
And he sliced...
And he got released.
...took him...
...on self-defense.
Classic Timo.
But our trials, on the other
hand, were never-ending.
It became a whole political
fight between all the pro-marshals
and the anti-marshals.
But by then, Nasha had made up her mind.
She'd overhauled the
committee and changed it herself.
So after she got out, she
really did run in the election.
And she won in a landslide.
On her first day in the assembly,
Nasha was so cool about the whole thing.
I was very, very nervous.
I don't think she really noticed, though.
Nikki?
I got the upgraded translator.
It just came out.
Okay, let's be fair.
Can I ask you a question?
Go.
You said before about
extinction and all that.
When you're all like...
...and, like, screeching and everything.
Mmm...
...would that really
make our brains explode?
From, like, the pitch?
Explode.
But you said that our
eyeballs would explode.
Mmm...
...why not our eardrums?
Because it's, like, sound.
All I explode.
Really?
Can you try it right here?
Right now?
Who said bluffing was only for humans?
Gotta love that, uh, poker face.
Yeah, and, uh, nice burp, too.
Uh, hello?
What are you doing here?
In the middle of the night?
Well, I just, uh...
...I thought you were in the hospital.
Hey, watch it.
Look down.
Don't step on it.
It's a priceless delicacy, Bab.
Go on.
Take a dab.
Have a taste.
A what?
Now you're too good
for sauce off the floor?
You think anyone else would allow scum
like you to taste something so refined?
What is...
...what is it made of?
Rude.
Not how it works.
A taste of faith comes first.
Then I tell you what's in it.
Mickey, you don't think
I'm letting you taste this
out of some high regard
for your palate, do you?
It's the opposite.
A true masterpiece would
be a sauce that could
appeal to even an
ignorant cretin like you.
Whatever.
Fuck it. Taste it. Waste it. I don't care.
You're worthless now.
Much better to bring back my usual taster.
The supreme one with
an actually refined palate.
Wait. That's...
Even his kidneys are
more handsome than you.
Not this. It can't be.
Of course it can.
Admit it. It's what you want.
It's what everyone wants.
Hey, Ilfa.
I just remembered.
You died...
...the day after Marshall.
Go ahead. Touch me.
See if I'm ghost or human.
Ever since I was a kid,
I've had scary dreams.
This time I wasn't scared.
I just thought to myself, what would 18 do?
Fuck off.
What are you doing? Press the button.
Mickey, press it.
I am glad the printer's gone.
But a part of me can't
help feeling guilty that I
didn't let all the other
Mickeys have a chance at life.
But I have to stop feeling guilty.
It's okay for me to be happy.