Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[dramatic music plays]
[man 1] Looking at a horse
when he's standing still looks magical,
but when he's running,
you know, it's like,
they should have wings.
[dramatic music continues]
There's a lot of horses
I've been given, um, on this ranch
that, uh, were problem horses
that other people couldn't handle.
Line up, boys!
Once you start working them
and you find their niche,
what they're gonna be
and what they can do…
Good girl.
…you know, they fit in quite well.
[man 2] No one can classify
themselves as a horse master.
My father can classify himself
as a horse trainer,
'cause he's trained horses
to do incredible feats.
-It's not just someone doing a trick.
-[clicking tongue]
It's like they become really good friends.
[man 1] Smile, guys. Smile.
Yay! Good!
[woman] But you lose the Robin
that I married for a little while.
But it's… it's worth it to see what
the result is, the magic that he creates.
[whinnies]
[tender music plays]
[Robin] When you get a new horse
and you don't know
what his history was…
sometimes it takes a little bit to get
across that edge.
[whinnies]
[Robin] Some of the… the wildest horses
that you come across,
and you get them, and you see
that spark in their eye, and they're wild.
You know deep down,
you can see it in their eye,
there's a better side to this horse.
[man on TV] Hang on, cowboy! Yeah!
[Robin] I grew up
with horses always around me.
I was raised in a little country town
in Australia.
I wasn't small, but I would be called
the runt of the litter.
I didn't speak that well. I couldn't read.
I was a loner.
I was happy with a horse.
When you can't communicate
with other people,
you're ostracized a little bit.
That's why I was pushed
to my grandparents,
to try to change my life,
which it changed my life.
I looked up to my granddad,
and he had a stern voice.
And, you know,
he was a highly decorated war hero,
and he'd been in the Light Horse Brigade
in Australia, you know.
And that's such a… a huge honor
to fight for your country on horseback.
But… I've never seen
love in my… granddad's eyes.
We always ate at the table together.
And then he'd look straight down
at his food,
and then he'd look up again
and just look straight through you.
That stare.
Just before he passed away in hospital,
and… and he'd still give me that look.
[announcer] What did you think
of his efforts tonight?
[Robin] That's always been
at the back of my mind,
you know, what my granddad
had said to me, you know?
"You'll amount to nothing."
My grandma was very soft-spoken.
When I was young, I would look at a book.
Instead of opening up
and going from the top,
I would start from the bottom,
and she said,
"Now start from this side here
and then follow it down
again and again and again."
And I think that's what's helped me
pass this on to my training.
You know,
it was that repetition of doing it.
She said, "Believe in what you are."
"And if you want to do it
through the horses, do it."
Just be very gentle with them,
and they will give back
a lot more love to you.
You know, I… I like a man
who watches things going around.
It means he'll make his mark someday.
[Robin] I would say I was about 10 or 11.
I went into this movie theater,
and… I was mesmerized.
You know, it was so large, the screen.
It's just wide,
and… the animals running towards you.
And the whole attire,
I mean, the hat, the boots, and the scarf.
Especially their mannerism
and how they got on a horse, you know?
It's just like, "Oh, wow."
I went back the next day.
Every time I watched a western
with a horse doing something unusual,
you know, I'm gonna copy that
and just see if I can do it better.
My first trick was the lay-down position,
because I wasn't that big
to… to get on the horse.
So I had to teach him to lay down
so I could get on him.
Good boy. Whoa.
I wanted to get into the picture business,
because I wanted to train horses.
But all the lots in Hollywood
got rid of all the horses,
because it was just after Star Wars.
Westerns were done.
[dramatic music plays]
Moving 10,000 miles across the world…
[chuckles] …to America,
it felt like you just had a brick dropped
right on the back of your neck.
I'm not gonna make it.
It's over.
There was still a desire to stay here
and work it out.
Once I got to Wyoming,
I knew this was home.
[wind gusting]
Getting up early in the morning,
and I… I think it was the first morning
after pulling the chuck wagon in
on this little lot.
And… seeing the horses
right there with me,
there was no going back.
It was my dream to train.
My, uh, third horse
was Juniper,
and which… changed my life completely.
When I looked in Juniper's eyes,
there was a little bit of a sadness there.
Even though it might
have been in his past,
I'd seen something bigger.
That horse was so smart.
He had that gift.
Juniper had this wonderful rear.
He had great balance. Unbelievable.
A horse like that,
it only comes once in a lifetime.
You like Robin?
Hey, do you like me?
-[whinnies]
-Of course you do.
[mellow music plays]
[Robin] When I got here,
even though the westerns had finished,
but these old cowboys still were alive,
it was about two years later,
I run into Darrell Winfield.
Wow, that's the Marlboro Man.
He was the real deal.
Darrell said, "Robin, I've heard
you've got a horse that can rear."
"Can you put a rider on him,
and can you cue him
behind camera to rear?"
I said, "Well, I've got,
uh, Juniper over here."
It was definitely my first audition.
I got the part.
I got a job.
[upbeat music plays]
[projector whirring]
[Robin] When you get storyboards,
you look at them, you go,
"Wow, okay,
I think I can do better than that."
[director] Ready, Robin?
And action!
[Robin] Hup!
Good.
Good boy.
I know, especially my horses,
and… they all enjoy working.
You know, they find their niche.
I think, when you get on set, you know,
you know where you started from
with the horse.
The building blocks that went into it.
And that's when the orchestra comes out.
He's performing in front of you,
and he's performing
in front of that camera.
He's showing off his art.
Good boy!
Good!
Kick! Good boy!
First lesson's pretty good.
Smart horse.
[tender music plays]
Come on, young lady.
Come around.
One second on camera,
when you look into it…
-[clanging]
-…it's weeks and hours of training.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Good, kids!
I use a… a whip or pointer,
and it's not there
to, um, touch the horse.
I'd use a pointer, or I would use
a lunge whip as a sound.
All right, here we go, guys!
It's just to guide him
to go away from you…
Good, kids!
…or come to you.
[whistles] Come to me.
Eye contact is very important
with everything.
It's just like a human.
You know when you first meet a person?
[smacks lips]
Good. Good.
Okay, you found your mark. Pirouette.
Come.
You might be right-handed.
I'm left-handed.
And that is exactly the same
with a horse on each side of his eye.
You got to train with one side first
and then go to the other side.
Good!
Once you got both eyes,
then you can cue them
from anywhere around the camera.
Pirouette.
And… good gal!
Bravo! Bravo!
That was beautiful, Em.
A pirouette is so graceful,
and they can hold their front feet,
where she'll pivot all the way around.
And it's just…
it's like going out into a waltz.
[gentle piano music plays]
[Robin] And when you've got
both eyes in sync,
it's just like playing the piano,
'cause they're playing their music
in front of you.
[whinnies]
Imagine the power you'd feel
if you had 50 horses
charging towards you.
Whoa! You're a big girl.
I seen this, uh,
in a circus book when I was a kid.
A Clydesdale standing
on top of a… a teeter-totter.
And I always wanted to recreate it.
I just want to get her to balance it now
and just hold the weight.
Steady. Nope.
Steady.
You have to gradually let them
feel,
smell you…
and then you've got that touch with them.
[uplifting music plays]
I'll look back
on some of the magical stuff
that I put together with horses.
You know, if it's not on film,
it's like it never happened.
Oh, that's--
Look at that balance! That's balance!
Yes!
[claps]
[thunder crashes]
[dramatic music plays]
[inaudible speaking]
[Robin] A paragon pioneer
is a person that's living in the present
but… believes in the past as well.
Sometimes you feel like
you've been there before.
[dramatic music plays]
Welcome! Welcome!
Little bit of history here, guys.
[woman] Robin is very passionate
about recreating the old Wild West.
And we're all proud of it,
because we all participate in some way.
[man] The cowboy dream is dying off,
but for my father, no,
he's definitely a full-blown cowboy.
[Robin] It makes me feel like
when I first got to America.
Just want to keep it alive.
Welcome, boys! Welcome!
♪ Paint your wagon
Come along ♪
♪ Gotta dream, boy
Gotta song ♪
We're going home, baby!
[calming music plays]
[whinnies]
[Robin] My horses,
when I… talk about them…
I say, "The kids are out together,"
because they are kids.
They're my children,
even though I've got Patrick.
[whinnies]
When I first got Juniper,
that horse taught me so much
of being patient and being humble
and excited.
We'll camp here.
He would do better than I had ever thought
an animal could ever do.
And you'd only have to show him once,
and bang, he got it.
Good boy, Jun.
He built me, and he built this ranch.
Juniper was getting old.
He was in his thirties.
The young man that I had here
signaled to me.
He said, "You know, you'd better come in.
I think Juniper is really, really sick."
And he must have hung on till I got home.
And I got there and put him in my arms
and just… knelt down there with him,
and, you know,
he gave that last little whinny
and then was gone.
[wistful music plays]
[gunshot on TV]
[boy on TV] How'd you know
when he was gonna draw?
[man on TV] By watching his eyes.
-Remember that.
-[boy on TV] I will.
Come on, guys. Line up.
Come on. School time.
Mrs. Parker loves to give smiles.
-Mrs. Parker.
-[clicking]
Good girl.
Once the horse gets the spark,
I'm the flint.
And all of a sudden,
the animal just comes alive,
and he's got it.
[horse whinnies]
[uplifting music plays]
[whinnying]
[wind gusting]
[nickering]
[Robin] As much love
as you can put into them,
they're gonna give it back to you.
But if you can stand there and hold that,
like… [gasps]
…it's a world.
[mellow music plays]