Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Woohoo!
Ya-haa!
Hurry, friends!
Time for another adventure!
Adventure? I'm in! Yee-hoo!
Let's go, ponies.
Earth ponies, take the lead!
Pegasi, fly beside me!
Unicorns, horns at the ready!
ALL: For Equestria!
What fantastical foe awaits us,
Princess?
Is it something scary?
Or is it something awesome?!
No matter what it is,
we'll face it together.
For we are
the Guardians of Friendship.
With the power of our friendship
and magic, we will...
- Spread love!
- Give hugs!
- Fry brains!
- Huh?
Wait, what?
Yeah, I'm a unicorn, and we're evil!
I'm gonna zap everypony
with my horn lasers!
(ALL SHRIEK)
No, no, no. It's all wrong!
The ponies are all supposed
to get along, remember?
Boring!
It's like in the olden times when
all three ponykinds were friends.
Uhh! Here we go again.
And they never used their magic
against each other.
- You're wrong.
- No, I'm not!
My mom says the pegasi and unicorns
tried to eat up all the earth ponies
by zapping 'em with lasers
and frying 'em to a crisp.
They wouldn't do that.
So the earth ponies kicked
their butts in an epic battle.
And if they ever try to come back
to Maretime Bay,
we'll kick their butts again!
Those are lies. Hitch, tell him.
Well, that is kind of what our
teacher said in history class, but...
But, hey, we can play the game
your way if you want, Sunny.
- I don't mind.
- Well, I do.
It's a boring game. Let's play
Pegasus Barbecue instead!
Sprout, stop it!
- SPROUT: Earth pony burgers!
- I'm going to tell my dad!
(CLOCK TICKS QUIETLY)
- Horn fight!
- You're going to break them!
Take that, earth pony! Pew, pew!
Dad, tell them
that's not what they do.
Time to head on home,
don't you think, colts?
Uhh! Fine!
Pew, pew!
Oh, no! My brains are melting!
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
- Mom?
- Hello, Mrs Cloverleaf.
How many times have I told you?
You cannot just go trotting off
without my permission,
especially not here.
And why is that again, Phyllis?
Because you are brainwashing
their minds
with all of your...nonsense.
It's called research, Phyllis.
And by the way,
I leave all the brainwashing
in Maretime Bay to you.
Unicorn cupcake?
Freshly baked.
Uhh! You know,
you're an earth pony, Argyle.
You should really start acting
like one, at least for her sake.
(GIGGLES)
PHYLLIS: Who does he think he is,
talking to me like that?
That pony is trouble!
Don't worry, Mommy.
When I become sheriff,
I'll keep everypony in line.
Hmm...Sheriff Sprout. Oh,
it does have a certain ring to it.
(SIGHS)
What's the matter, Sunny Bunny?
Hitch and Sprout
still don't believe me.
Maybe one day they will.
But the important thing is that
you stand up for what you believe in.
OK?
Well, when I grow up, I'm going to
show everypony that we are right.
- Oh?
- Yeah.
And someday the both of us
will meet unicorns or a pegasus
and we'll be best friends forever!
Well, maybe today is that day.
Look, a unicorn!
(GASPS) Where? Where?
Over here.
(LAUGHTER)
- Hold on.
- Whee!
- I'm soaring through the sky!
- Yee-ha!
Wait. Dad, I have an idea!
(CLEARS THROAT)
"Dear unicorns and pegasi,
"you have friends in Maretime Bay.
Come visit us."
Can we send it?
DAD: I think it's our duty.
(GIGGLES)
- Can you tell me the story?
- Again?
- Please.
- (CHUCKLES)
Once upon a time, many, many moons
ago, in ancient Equestria,
- there lived a very special...
- Unicorn!
(DAD CHUCKLES)
DAD: The unicorn was very bright...
SUNNY: As bright as the sun.
DAD: One day, the princess
summoned her to the castle
for an important assignment.
- To learn about friendship!
- Mm-hm.
She soon made lots of new friends.
SUNNY: Earth ponies, pegasuses
and unicorns.
Together, they showed everypony
the magic of friendship
and how to live in harmony.
Wow. You finished it.
Pretty neat, huh?
Earth ponies watched in wonder
as pegasi painted rainbows
across the sky.
The nights were lit up
by 100 unicorn horns.
It's beautiful.
I wish I had a friend
who could fly around or float things.
(YAWNS)
Why can't we be friends any more?
(SIGHS) That, my darling,
is a big question,
and maybe one day,
we'll figure it out together.
We'll do our part...
BOTH: Hoof to heart.
Goodnight, Daddy.
Goodnight, my little pony.
Goodnight, friends.
(SNORES)
(ALARM CLOCK BEEPS)
(YAWNS)
(SNORTS)
Perfect.
Today's the day, Dad.
I actually have a plan this time.
Wish me luck!
# Good morning, sun
# No time to chat, I gotta run
# Cos I got places to be
# So much to do
# Excited, yes, and nervous too
# A change is starting with me
# I never worry 'bout
upsetting carts, hardened hearts
# Or wonder, "Will I belong?"
# I’ve heard it enough!
# I’m calling their bluff
# I’ll never get lost in the grey!
# There’s something inside
burns bigger than pride
# Shines out of me, lighting the way
# Gonna be, gonna be, gonna be
my day
# Be my day
# Gonna be, gonna be, gonna be
my day
# Gonna be my day!
# Gonna be my day
# Hey there, hello
# The friends I make
The friends I know
# Today you answer my call
# Instead of hide
Instead of staying stuck inside
# Instead of building your wall
# Come on and party with me
# Join the band
# Understand
# We'll all be singing the song
# I’ve heard it enough!
# I’m calling their bluff!
# I’ll never get lost in the grey!
# Go big or go home!
# Get real or get known!
# Get ready and raring to say...
# Gonna be, gonna be, gonna be
my day
# Be my day!
# Gonna be, gonna be, gonna be
my day
# Everyone’s afraid
(ALL SHRIEK)
# Always judging
# Never budging
# Ain’t it time we made the team
# The dream?
# Oh...
# Let’s open our eyes
# Sun starting to rise
# And finally able to say...
# Gonna be, gonna be, gonna be
my day
# Gonna be my day!
# Gonna be, gonna be, gonna be
my day
# Gonna be my day!
# Gonna be, gonna be, gonna be
my day
# Be my day! #
Aha, there you are, Sunny.
Just the pony I was expecting.
Morning, Sheriff Hitch.
I see you brought the whole squad
along again.
(ALL SQUEAK)
(SIGHS) What is it with me and
critters? I'm like a magnet to them.
Guys, come on.
Give Hitch a little space.
(SIGHS)
- So, what's up?
- Oh, please, like you don't know.
Today is the annual presentation
at Canterlogic.
- Hey, I'm headed there right now.
- No, you're not.
Listen, I know that you have come up
with some hare-brained scheme
to sabotage it, and if you think
I'm just going to let you walk in...
Hey, Hitch...
- No.
- Come on.
Good morning, Sheriff Hitch.
Morning, Mayflower. Dahlia.
(CHUCKLES)
Sunny, I'm on duty.
(GROANS)
BOTH: Up high! Down low!
Hitch it to a post!
Flip it sunny side up
and on a piece of toast!
OK?
(GASPING) I did what you asked for,
Hitch.
She never left my side,
not even once.
Oh, hey, Sprout. You OK?
You seem kind of wheezy.
That's Deputy Sprout to you.
Hey, wait up! I'm not finished!
Sunny! Sunny, we both know
how this goes.
Every year you try to sneak in
and every year I stop you.
Look, you have nothing
to worry about.
I'll just go into the factory,
deliver my smoothies...
Uh-uh. You can't even step
a hoof in there.
My mom had you banned.
- But I...
- (SIGHS)
I'm asking you as your friend, Sunny,
not as sheriff.
Just please try not to pull
any stunts today.
OK. OK.
I'll try.
Thank you.
Now, give your delivery to Sprout
and go home.
Hey. Hey!
That's a violation of Code 33.
Bye-bye.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, watch it!
Welcome, everypony. Got any questions
about the Canterlogic factory?
Happy to answer them.
MARE: Where are the free smoothies?
(SIGHS) You know what, Sprout?
I think I finally got through
to Sunny.
ANNOUNCER: It's the moment
you've all been waiting for.
As the founder of Canterlogic,
she's been keeping us safe
and stylish for the last 20 moons.
Please go wild for the one and only
Phyllis Cloverleaf!
- (APPLAUSE)
- Thank you. Thank you.
How are you? Thank you so much.
We here at Canterlogic
are so thrilled
to create perfect products
that protect ponies like you...
...from ponies like that.
(BOOING)
And like I always say,
to be scared is...
ALL: To be prepared!
Oh, I love it. That's right.
- Ya-hoo!
- So let's start the show!
(MUSIC)
Up first, we have Sugar Moonlight
looking absolutely stunning
in our high-tech
Anti-Mind-Reading Hat.
All those psychic unicorns out there
are going to be out of luck
when you wear this little number!
Now let's welcome Sparkle Chaser
in his Pega-Periscope Goggles -
the easy way to keep
your eye on the sky.
Oh!
It's all part of the show!
Next up, the Earth Pony
Balloon Escape Pack.
Whoa...
Uh... Whoa!
Argh! Arghhh!
Yikes. That's going to be
a lot of paperwork.
We take great care
here at Canterlogic
to ensure the safety of you,
our loyal customers.
ALL: Aww!
Now, please, stand back.
This product-testing demonstration
is fully automated.
(GASPS)
Earth ponies of Maretime Bay,
fear is not your friend!
But the unicorns
and pegasi can be.
Let's extend the hoof of friendship.
That is not what I meant.
Turn it off, turn it off!
So now you can prevent
an aerial abduction
with a set of our new
Anti-Pegalift Boots!
Peace with pegasi!
Unity with unicorns!
Whoa! Give me that back!
(SIGHS) Sunny!
Peace with...pegasi!
Uh...everypony take a look at
our Unicorn Entrapment Device.
Whoa!
Toots, Sweets, shut her down!
- Sheriff's orders!
- We're trying.
Fully automated means
it has to go through the whole cycle.
Oh, no. Ooh!
Peace with pegasi!
Unity with unicorns!
PHYLLIS: And this
is the Splat-a-pult!
Ohhh!
Cease fire!
ALL: Ooh.
PHYLLIS: Let's hear it, everypony.
Come on!
Uh...
(ALL GASP)
(PANTS)
Aren't you tired of being scared
all the time?
The truth is, we're not in danger.
It's all a lie.
We don't need any
of this Canterlogic junk.
Oh, we don't, do we?
How do you suggest that we defend
ourselves? With hugs and cupcakes?
(LAUGHTER)
Just imagine...if you had
a friend who could fly
or a friend who could...
Fry your brains
with a single horn zap?
Or swoop down and snatch you away?
(ALL GASP)
Sheriff, do your job.
All right, Sunny, let's go.
No. Everypony needs to hear this.
Everything you believe about
pegasi and unicorns is wrong.
They used to be our friends
and can be again.
AUDIENCE MEMBER: Hey, we don't need
any of them round here!
Come on, let's go.
Show's over, Sunny.
AUDIENCE MEMBER: Sunny,
you're just embarrassing yourself!
PHYLLIS: It's quite sad, really.
Now, where were we?
Do you have any idea how many
bylaws you broke in there?
I'm sure you're about to tell me.
Actually, for once I can't,
because there's so many!
I tried to warn you. I can't keep
associating with some pony
who breaks every rule and
causes chaos wherever she goes.
I'm the sheriff!
Exactly. Other ponies
look up to you. You can help.
The law is the law, Sunny,
and I'm here to uphold it
and keep everypony safe.
Aha, you just said everypony.
That includes pegasi and unicorns.
Come on, Sunny, what did you think
was gonna happen?
You give a little speech and what?
Everypony just magically welcomes
unicorns and pegasi
into Maretime Bay?
You keep saying there's nothing to be
afraid of. Well, then, prove it.
(SIGHS) All of that pony unity stuff
was just a foal's bedtime story
made up by your dad.
Like it or not, this is the way
it is, and always will be.
I'm the last real friend
you got in this town.
You really want to lose me too?
(SIGHS)
(GIGGLING)
- Rarrgh!
- Argh!
(GIGGLING)
- Rarrgh!
- (GIGGLING)
I wish you were here, Dad.
(GALLOPING)
Uh...argh!
(SHRIEKING)
What the...?
What's going on? What's happening?
(SQUEAKS)
Argh!
(BRAKES SCREECH)
(GASPS)
Hi, new friend! My name's Izzy.
U...U...
Unicorn!
(SHRIEKING)
Ooh, is everypony
playing hide-and-seek?
I see you!
Argh! It's a unicorn!
Hey, what's going on?
(GASPS)
Unicorn attack!
- (ALARM BLARES)
- This is not a drill!
I repeat, this is not a drill!
A vulnerable young pony.
Your son is safe now, ma'am.
- This isn't my kid!
- You're welcome.
Man the Splat-a-pult!
Activate the unicorn trap!
Pick up that litter!
Wow.
Is that the sea?
I've never seen the sea.
- (ALARM BLARES)
- I've got to get you of here!
Earth ponies are serious about games.
They're not playing,
they're terrified.
- Oh, no. Of what?
- You! You're a unicorn.
Earth ponies hate unicorns.
Really? That seems a little harsh.
Let's go!
(HUMS)
Oh, I haven't seen this one yet.
(ALARM BLARES)
(GASPS)
All right, citizens, calm down.
The threat has been neutralised.
The unicorn has been captured.
You may now cheer.
(CHEERING)
Sunny!
What are you doing?
Don't even think about it.
No, don't you dare.
No, no, no, no. Sunny!
So, your name's Sunny?
(ALL GASP)
Argh!
Bye! It was nice to meet you all!
Deputy, to the lighthouse!
Uh...
- Oh, no, I appear to be trapped.
- (SIGHS) You gotta be kidding me.
Do earth ponies
also like staring contests?
Hmm!
You win. I blinked.
There's a unicorn in my house.
This is so cool!
Wait, no, it's bad, very, very bad.
What have I done?
Wow! I've never seen
an earth pony before.
We look exactly the same,
except for this, of course.
Oh, hey, be careful
where you point that thing.
- Why?
- Well, I...um...
...sort of don't want to get zapped
with a wayward laser beam,
but of course you know that already.
You've probably been reading
my mind this whole time.
Isn't it supposed to glow,
by the way,
or does that only happen
when you levitate stuff?
Well, actually...
Wait, don't answer that yet.
Let me get my notebook.
OK. Wow.
OK, 142 questions for a unicorn.
Question number one.
Where do you live?
- Bridlewood.
- I knew it.
Do unicorns really live in trees?
Do they eat pizza?
If so, what toppings do they like?
If not, why not?
Can you actually fry pony brains
with a single horn zap?
(GASPS) Can you make this float?
No, but I can do this.
Ta-da!
Wait, you don't have any magic?
- HITCH: Sunny Starscout!
- (FEEDBACK WHINES)
Argh, that hurt.
Sunny Starscout, I know
you're in there with that unicorn.
Come out with your hooves up
and surrender.
Yeah, you're completely surrounded.
Will you let me do my job?
- You are under arrest.
- This is bad.
- How sneaky are you?
- Er, medium sneaky.
I can work with that.
OK, I'll distract them.
Pff! Relax!
- I'll talk to him.
- No, no!
Hi, guys.
Now, I know what you're thinking.
Argh! She's already reading
our minds!
Quick, before she fries our brains!
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
- To get reinforcements!
- We have reinforcements?
Huh?
Oh, come on!
- You don't have any magic?
- No.
(GASPS)
No magic?
If it makes you feel any better,
we did have it,
but that was many, many,
many moons ago.
It just, poof, disappeared.
Everypony thinks the pesky pegasi
had something to do with it,
but, oh... Oh, hey,
you look kind of woozy.
Are you OK?
Huh... I am on the run with a unicorn
who has no magic.
What are we going to do?
(SNIFFS)
What are you doing?
- You don't smell.
- Thanks. Wait, what?
I was told all you earth ponies smell
like rotten sardines, but you do not.
Hmm!
What else do unicorns say
about earth ponies?
Oh, just that you're lazy and not
the brightest crystals in the forest.
- Charming.
- No, just those three.
So, what's the plan?
Wait, I've got it.
Izzy, we're going on a quest -
to Zephyr Heights.
- The pegasus city?
- Yes. We need to find out
what happened to your magic
and bring it back.
They have magic. Maybe they can help.
But the pegasi are bad news.
What if you're wrong about them?
Earth ponies were wrong
about unicorns.
They could welcome us
with open wings.
But what if they don't?
# Up ahead, is the sky growing dark?
# Where it leads is
a big question mark
# And I'm scared that I'll end up
a pony gone missing from pegasus-ing
# But you're not alone
# You got a pony in your crew
# I do? Who?
# I'm lookin' out for you
# When you're off track
# I got your back
# You can rely on me
# I'm lookin' out for you
# Back at home
it was earth ponies first
# Heard it so many times
I could burst
# And I fought for a change
but it's lonely
# Cos, you know, party of uno
# Well, if you need a friendly steed
like you-know-who
# I think I do
# I'm lookin' out for you
# When you're off track
# I got your back
# You can rely on me
# I'm lookin' out for you
# Lost in the hills
# I got the skills
# Pony, let's get going
- # Get going
# I'm lookin' out
# I'm lookin' out for you
# I'll go where you're going to
# It's all I ever want to do
# I am lookin' out
# For you! #
(SNORING)
I told her. I told her. No more
favours, no more bailing her out.
She gave me no choice. No choice.
All right. We need to arrest her
and bring her back to face
the full force of the law.
Question. When you say we,
you mean...?
You and I.
Uh, I'd...I'd love to,
but, um, I just gotta clean up
my workspace,
get my papers in order and...
You know what?
I think you're right.
This one's a job for Hitch,
and Hitch only.
All right. Sprout, you stay here
while I'm out dancing with danger.
Keep everypony calm, maintain
the peace, be a pillar of strength.
Who am I kidding? Just try not
to start a war while I'm gone, OK?
Oh, everypony loves Hitch!
What does he have anyway?
Sure, he's got a perfect mane,
shredded abs,
paid-off mortgage.
So what? I've got stuff. I can do...
...um, things.
Like that. And that.
And that.
Ugh!
Where's Hitch? Ponies all over town.
They're terrified.
They want answers.
He went after Sunny.
Another solo Hitch mission.
Sugar cube, why the Sprout pout?
That's great news.
- It is?
- Yes.
It means that you are the sheriff,
at least for now.
I am!
Hey there. The name's Sprout.
Sheriff Sprout.
What's the problem, filly?
Don't worry. Sheriff Sprout is here.
Pick up that litter!
Sheriff Sprout's orders!
You know, not to freak you out
or anything, but you do know
pegasi can steal your luminescence,
don't you?
- My lumi-what?
- Luminescence.
You know, like your sparkle.
Yours is...lavender.
- Huh?
- And the happier you are,
the brighter it shines!
(WHOOSHING)
- (WHOOSHING)
- Ooh!
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
(BOTH SCREAM)
Hurry!
- Argh!
- Sunny!
(BOTH GASP)
(BOTH SIGH)
(BOTH SHRIEK)
- (GASPS)
- A real pegasus.
Whoa, a unicorn and an earth pony?
Together?
OK, well, this day just got
a whole lot more interesting.
- (FAINT CLANKING)
- (GASPS)
Don't tell them you saw me.
There's no way we could!
We don't even know your name!
- She seems nice.
- (DISTANT SHOUT)
(GASPS)
Thunder, get it together!
- But-But that's an earth pony.
- They're harmless.
- They have very tiny brains.
- THUNDER: What do we do about that?
- Well, did you bring the shield?
- What shield?
- Didn't you read the guard guide?
- Yes.
- OK, no.
- Oh, fine!
I've got this.
(POP)
- That's creative.
- What's it like to fly?
Is your wingspan
the same as your height?
- Well, I...
- Do you need a licence to fly?
- How far can you go?
- Can you fly to the moon?
Do pegasi wear horseshoes
or do they just weigh you down?
Well, I-I do collect sneakers.
Hey, don't answer anything!
They could be spies.
(BOTH GASP)
Wow!
PRESENTER:
Good morning, Zephyr Heights!
It's another beautiful day
in the big city.
Looks like warm breezes
and clear skies
for tonight's royal celebration!
Royal celebration?
Ha! Talk about great timing!
PRESENTER 2: Tonight's royal bash
for Queen Haven will be stunning,
but the real jewel in the crown
will be Princess Pipp's performance.
Isn't that right, Skye?
Oh, my, yes, Dazzle.
And this just in -
an exclusive vid from Pipp
for all you loyal fans out there
in ZH.
What is up, everypony?
Big shout-out to all my fans,
the PippSqueaks.
(BOTH SQUEAL)
So tonight's the night.
I can't wait to debut
my new song later.
It has a very special place
in my heart,
but not as much as you guys!
- ALL: Aww!
- We love you so much, Pipp!
OK, guys, I love you lots.
Got to go. Pipp, Pipp, hooray!
- Pipp, Pipp, hooray!
- Move it.
- You betcha.
Do you see anypony flying here?
Oh, they have a castle!
Oh!
- Wow!
- Bow before our queen!
(FANFARE)
Your Majesty.
(YAPS)
(GASPS)
(MUSIC PLAYS)
(YAPS)
- (GASPS)
- Hi, new friend!
Guards, state your business,
and please make it quick.
We're on a very tight schedule today.
Before the celebration,
Cloudpuff needs his pedicure,
Pipp needs to rehearse
and I need to practise my laugh.
(LAUGHS LOUDLY)
Hmm. Still not right.
Your Highness, we found
these intruders in our territory.
(GASPS) An earth pony and a unicorn
in Zephyr Heights!
We have them under control,
Your Highness.
And we deployed the shield.
Is this an attack on the night
of our royal celebration?
Why are you here? Who sent you?
Nopony must know they're here.
Check it out, PippSqueaks,
live from the castle...
...i's a real unicorn and earth pony.
- I know, right?
- (ALL GASP)
- This is so not a filter.
- Pipp!
There's nothing to fear.
Those nasty little ponies
have been captured.
- Your queen will protect you.
- (ALL SIGH)
Shut it off.
(SIGHS)
Excuse me, Majesty?
We only want to ask you
a few questions about magic.
- We...
- Guards!
Please escort these ponies
to the dungeon
until I can question them properly.
And confiscate the book.
What? No, no.
But-But, Your Majesty,
I just wanted to ask you
a few questions, please.
Did she just say dungeons?
What else could go wrong today?
(LICKS)
(CLAMOURING OUTSIDE)
Mom?
My, oh, my. Aren't you
the handsome sheriff! Look at you.
Yes. Yes, I am, Mommy.
Well, this is it.
It is your time to shine, dear.
Everypony wants to hear from you.
- They do?
- Of course.
You are in charge now.
It's your destiny.
Citizens!
Ow!
It is I, Sheriff Sprout.
- Sheriff? Where's Hitch?
- We need a real sheriff.
- Tell us what's going on!
- Hitch would know what to do.
Come on, now, everypony.
Let's listen to what
our new sheriff has to say.
That's you, sugar cube.
Oh, yeah, it's me.
OK, folks, calm down.
There's no need to be scared.
We're scared
and we want to be prepared.
The unicorns are coming!
(CRASH)
- What do we do?
- What's your plan, Sheriff?
What if the unicorn comes back?
Actually, what if you're all right?
The unicorns could come back.
They could even bring the pegasi.
We are all in danger!
(ALL GASP)
Now is not the time
to be complacent.
We should do something.
# Something is lurking
Something is here
# Something is feeling stranger
Stranger
# Stirring up discord
Whipping up fear
# Whispering softly
# Danger, danger!
# Outsiders creep up slow and steady
# Wings glistening
Horns at the ready
# Think what they could do
to the status quo
# Oh, no
# They're gonna steal, plunder
and pillage
# They're going to
take over the village
# Don't just sit on your butts
and do nothing and wait
# Let's enter
a blind irrational state!
# Better get nervous
Better get tense
# Better not let them
catch you blinking
# You don't need a reason
Fillies and gents
# This is no time for sober thinking
- # Mob!
- # Mob?
- # M-M-Mob!
- # Angry, angry
- # Mob
- # M-M-Mob
- # Mob, mob
# Angry, angry!
# Fight
# See in black and white
# That's your pony right
# Time to lift your manes
and proudly
# Throng
# Numbers make you strong
# Millions can't be wrong
# Specially when
they're screaming loudly
# You might not have
a bale of hay to borrow
# Are you saddled with your sorrow?
# Are you scared about tomorrow?
# Well, it's all gonna work out
painlessly
# If you follow my orders
brainlessly! #
- Who are we?
- We're an angry mob.
- What are we?
- Look at this corn.
- It's on the cob.
- Look at that guy.
- My name's Rob.
# Mob, mob
M-m-mob mob!
Angry, angry!
# Mob, mob
M-m-mob mob!
Angry, angry!
# Mob, mob
M-m-mob mob!
Angry, angry!
# Mob, mob
M-m-mob mob!
Angry, angry mob! #
(CLAWS CLICK)
(GENTLE MUSIC)
(FRENCH ACCENT)
This princess smells.
So could you.
Parfum La Pipp.
Something is not right.
We haven't seen a single pony flying,
except the royal family.
Izzy? Are you listening?
- (CHAIR VIBRATES)
- This isn't dungeony at all.
- Uh-h-h-h...
- Hey!
I'm sorry you two got thrown in here,
but I have to talk to you.
Princess?
Your Majesticness.
Y-Your Graceful Highness.
Zipp. Just call me Zipp.
OK, Zipp. I'm Sunny.
And this is my friend.
Izzy Moonbow.
Sunny, Izzy, I really need to ask you
something important.
- (WHISPERS) About magic.
- That's why we're here.
Maybe you can tell us
how yours works?
Izzy has no idea how the unicorns
lost theirs. So we thought maybe...
Whoa, whoa, wait.
Lost theirs? As in no magic?
Well, that changes things.
Listen, I might have
some information that could help,
but first, you need to tell me
about this.
My journal! Thank you, Zipp.
I never thought I'd see it again.
Yeah, I can be pretty sneaky
when I want to be.
Nice!
I'm only medium sneaky.
So where did that come from?
It was my father's. Why?
That star...
(FANFARE)
Zipp, what are you doing here?
Mom said to stay away.
- Right. Then why are you here?
- For the content.
Princess?
- Why isn't anypony flying?
- (GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
Everypony knows that
only royals can fly, of course.
BOTH: What?
I know, it's not fair,
but that's just the way it is.
If there was some way we could
teach the citizens to fly,
you know we would in a wing-beat.
Right, Zipp?
Yeah. In a wing-beat.
(PHONE BUZZES)
Oh, dress rehearsals. Gotta go.
And so should you.
# Me-me-me!
# Red feather, yellow feather
Red feather, yellow feather... #
(PIPP TRILLS)
I have to show you something.
(BOTH GASP)
You coming or what?
(GIGGLING)
(WIND WHISTLES)
(GRUNTS)
(BUNNIES SQUEAK)
Litter.
- I mean, a clue.
- Oh!
Hmm. Unicorn hair.
Pegasi.
Track's gone cold.
Sunny, Sunny, Sunny, Sunny.
You think you've escaped?
Well, think again.
I will not eat, I will not sleep...
Well, maybe a quick nap and a snack
if I can't find you
in the next few hours.
But after that,
nothing will stop me!
(HIGH-PITCHED CHEERING)
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
No, no. You're too kind.
- Also...
- Shhh!
I'll follow you wherever you go.
Whether harshest deserts,
the coldest tundras,
no trail too dangerous,
no clue too small.
(BUNNIES EXCLAIM)
The past matters not! It's justice...
Oh, what? What?
(BUNNIES SQUEAK)
Gotcha!
Watch your step.
Argh!
(BOTH GASP)
- Where are we?
- It's amazing, right?
I'm pretty sure it was
some sort of station
for when earth ponies and unicorns
used to visit Zephyr Heights.
It's like everypony just forgot.
This is proof. All ponykinds
did used to be friends!
My dad was right.
Must be really weird,
being the only pegasi that can fly.
(SIGHS)
The truth is, we can't fly either.
We've been faking it.
Faking it? But-But how?
You'd be surprised what some wires
and good lighting will do.
But I'm just so tired
of living that ridiculous lie.
That's why I come down here -
to get away from all of that, and...
...well, to do this.
(WHOOSH OF AIR)
- Wow.
- Whoa!
Her sparkle is so bright right now!
But that's not why
I brought you down here.
This is what I wanted to show you.
Oh, my stars.
This was made a long, long time ago,
when we still had magic.
It's beautiful!
- SUNNY: What is that?
- ZIPP: That's the pegasus crystal.
It's part of my mom's crown.
Hmm. Where is the unicorn crystal?
Look.
They fit?
These two crystals belong together.
United.
So, what are you saying?
Maybe you lost your magic
because the crystals were separated.
So if we put them back together...
...magic will return?
And all three ponykinds
will get along again!
- All right!
- Oh-ho-ho!
But what about the unicorn crystal?
Well, if you're looking for crystals.
we've got, like, a gazillion of them
back in Bridlewood.
Then that's where we'll go next.
After we get the pegasus crystal
from your mom, of course.
Ooh, that'll be tricky.
She never takes her crown off.
(SNORING)
# Keeping the queen clean! #
So, what do we do?
I got it! Pipp's performing
at tonight's royal celebration.
All eyes will be on her,
especially my mom's.
She'll be distracted.
So we just need to swap
the real crown with a fake.
Ooh, I can craft a decoy!
But I will need a box of macaroni,
a tube of glue, 14 gooey bunnies
and three jellybeans.
Oh, and glitter. Lots of glitter.
ZIPP: I'll get the supplies.
I'll pass them off to Sunny,
and then she will get them to you.
Once you produce the decoy,
get your flanks to the palace.
Everypony who's anypony
will be there,
so security will be tight.
(REPORTERS CLAMOUR)
I'll distract them,
so you can sneak in.
IZZY: Maximum sneaky.
ZIPP: You'll need to be stealthy.
Carefully make your way
to the Grand Hall,
but watch out for the guards.
- Oh!
(CLINK)
ZIPP: I will open the door
to the back stage of the Throne Room.
And once Pipp starts singing,
my mom will be so caught up,
that swapping the crowns
will be easy-breezy.
SUNNY: Easy-breezy.
Sure.
I hear you paid our guests a visit.
Pipp told you?
Oh, you know she tells me everything.
I wish you would tell me more.
You're going to be queen one day.
You'll wear this crown.
And trust me,
it is heavier than it looks.
Actually, there is something
I wanted to tell you.
The unicorns don't have any magic.
I think it's tied to
why we can't fly...
Zephyrina!
I don't know what silly ideas
that unicorn put into your head,
but we have a duty
to protect our citizens.
Pegasi are happy enough
knowing that we royals can fly.
Why would you want
to disrupt things?
Because it's a lie.
It makes them feel safe.
Oh, one day you'll understand.
Your sister does.
- Oh, and here she is now.
- # Me-me-me! #
Showtime!
We are go for launch.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Remember to smile!
Ugh.
# We got the light
We’re coming in stronger
# We’re in it together
# If you want it
It’s all inside your mind
# We got the light
We won’t wait any longer
# We’ll get it together
# If you want it
Then you can paint the sky
# Used to care what they’d say
Let ‘em into my brain
# But I found a new way
Oh-oh-oh... #
No, you hang up.
No...
(GROWLS)
Argh!
# We don’t fly like we used to
We take what we’ve been through
# And we can feel brand-new... #
Aah!
Sunny Starscout,
you are under arrest...
(BARKING)
Oh!
# I’m shining brighter
Ooh-ooh
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# Dip and slide
Through the cut
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# Dip and slide
Through the cut
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# We say high
You say what?
# Everywhere that I’ve been
Yeah, they say I’m different
# But I’m good in my skin
Ooh-ooh
- (GRUNTS)
- # If it doesn’t feel right
# Break it in with tie-dye
# And don’t you stop till sunrise
# We don’t fly like we used to
# We take what we’ve been through
# And we can feel brand-new
Ooh-ooh... #
Oh! It's the prisoners! (WAILS)
- Shh!
- Quiet!
# I'm shining brighter
Ooh-ooh-ooh
# We got the light
We’re coming in stronger
# We’re in it together... #
It's OK - don't be scared.
I'm not going to fry your brain, OK?
Argh!
What the...?
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Uh...
# Throwing up
Find a glove
# Fly around, bup-bup-bup
# Doing stuff that I love
# You're like, why?
I'm like what? #
What is happening?
# Crisp and dry
Eat some mud
# Glowing up
Lovey dove... #
(SCREAMS)
(ALL GASP)
Aaah!
- I got it!
- Yes!
Let's go!
Freeze.
PEGASUS FAN: It's the prisoners!
Another earth pony!
(CROWD GASPS)
- She's a fake!
- Fake!
The royals can't fly either?!
- Zipp?
Zipp! Hurry!
FAN: They can't fly?!
She's faking it!
She's a fake!
(SIRENS)
Quick! This way.
- (THUMP)
- OK, I think we lost them.
(SQUEAKING)
Hitch, what are you even doing here?
Arresting you. And saving you.
So, you know, a little bit of both,
actually.
You're welcome.
Oh, gee, thanks.
But we don't need any saving. OK?
And you are?
Her mom is the Queen!
Wait a minute.
So that means you're a princess?
Huh, look at that. The sheriff
just became a detective.
- What?
- (TV JINGLE)
Breaking story.
Zephyr Heights is in turmoil tonight
after the shocking revelation
that the royals cannot fly.
Pipp used to be my favourite.
If we can't trust our own royalty,
who can we trust?
I blame the unicorns
and the earth ponies.
They ruin everything!
This just in. Queen Haven has been
arrested for being a phony pony
- full of baloney.
- (GASPS)
No comment, and no photos!
OK, one photo.
Anypony care to explain?
We had to get the crystal!
Look.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
- It's not here!
- Seriously?
On the bright side,
we had so much fun losing it.
We have to go back.
But it could be anywhere!
(CLATTER)
Somepony seriously needs to explain
why this thing was so important
that you had to ruin
my whole show over it.
Trust me, it was.
You left me hanging there
in the spotlight.
Now everypony knows we can't fly.
(PHONE ALERT)
A warrant is out for the arrest
of the princesses.
Pipp! Zipp! Save yourselves.
What?! This isn't happening.
- This is so not happening!
- Pipp!
Forget about all that. We think
we can bring back magic,
but we need that crystal.
Have you lost your mind?
Please. This might be
our only chance.
Oh, fine!
I know a way out.
Come on.
What? Wait! You can't just...
But I'm a sheriff!
(SIGHS)
- Hey!
- (YELLING)
(RASPY BREATHING)
(SLURPS)
Why aren't you finished yet?
We're working as fast as we can,
but we've run out of rivets.
Riveting story. (LAUGHS)
(SIGHS) Just make it work, OK?
(YELLS)
Sugar cube,
I know your little top-secret project
is important and all,
but when do you think my workers
can get back to making
Canterlogic products?
(YELLING)
(THUMP)
Back to work, Glitter Cupcake!
It is my factory, after all, dear.
It's my town, Mommy.
Your son's now Emperor
of Maretime Bay.
Emperor?!
But yesterday
you were only the sheriff.
Well, see how fast
I'm climbing the ranks?
This defence factory
is going on offence,
and it's all thanks to your love
and encouragement.
Break's over, Bubblegum McGinty!
Oh, dear.
Somepony's getting a big head.
That's the tree from the map!
That means...it's this way.
What am I even doing here,
hoofing it across Daisy Fields,
looking for a magical crystal
that doesn't even exist!
It was supposed to be
my best show ever.
Now it's all over.
I'm a criminal,
- and it's all because of them.
- Them.
And that is so not cool.
No, it is not.
Did I just agree with a pegasus?
Hey, are you sure she even knows
where to find this other crystal?
Don't you trust me at all?
I don't know.
You are the one that just got Mom
thrown in jail.
Look, once we get our magic back,
the whole kingdom will be so excited,
they won't even remember
what happened back there.
You'll be a hero, Pipp.
Let's get one thing straight.
We're almost to the river, everypony!
After this whole escapade
is over with,
you are going to march back home
to Maretime Bay with me.
- Is that clear?
- Crystal.
Great. Because this badge
means that I'm the sher...
Argh!
No, no, no, no!
Where's my badge? Hey!
- You.
- Hmm?
I know unicorns like shiny things.
Oh, you know, I think I did see
a shiny badgey thing on the ground
- a few hours ago.
- What? Hours?!
Well, maybe it's for the best.
Between you and me, buddy,
that badge was creating
an unhealthy power dynamic.
(SINGS)
(GASPS)
Where are we going to do?
Any ideas, Zipp?
You know what would be great
right now? Let me think.
Maybe something like
the ability to fly?
You know what would be even better?
Not being stuck in the middle
of nowhere...
Oh, well! That's the end of that.
Time to go home.
I wish I could say it was nice
meeting all of you, but it wasn't.
- Come on, Sunny.
- I don't think so.
Everypony stop.
We're gonna get to the other side,
find the crystal,
and bring back magic.
And once we do, you'll get to fly,
you'll get your fans back,
and you'll have me in custody.
Everypony happy now?
(CRASH)
Ta-da!
- All right.
- Ah, great.
Come on, everypony.
(YELLING)
Oh, yeah! Nailed it!
Come on, stupid stick.
You need some backup, Sheriff?
No, thank you. I've got it.
Come on. If I only had a match.
Ah! Oh.
- Oh, well, that was sad to watch.
- Come on, don't be a hero, dude.
Come get warm.
Are you sure about all this?
Because if we just go back
to Maretime Bay...
What have we got to lose?
By giving magic back to our enemies?
Uh, let me think.
- I know - a lot!
- Come on.
Do they look like enemies to you?
My sparkle is aquamarine?
That's like
my sixth-favourite colour!
(SIGHS) I don't know.
Maybe I should just go back
to Maretime Bay, where I'm needed.
If that's what you want.
But you should know
I'm actually glad you're here, Hitch.
We all are.
(SNORTS)
(SIGHS)
So, I think we should set off
at first light.
Last stop, Bridlewood.
What's wrong, Izzy?
It's just that being with you ponies
has been the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
I guess I just don't want
our adventure to end.
But, Izzy, you'll get your magic.
Can I ask you a question?
Why did you come to Maretime Bay?
I always wanted to visit.
When I was a filly,
I found this pretty lantern.
It had a message inside.
It said I had friends
in Maretime Bay.
It... It was you!
I made it with my dad.
We always promised each other
that someday we would prove
that all ponies
were meant to be friends.
We'll do our part. Hoof to heart.
Hey, um...
I want to do my part.
What have we got to lose, right?
- Whoo!
- All right!
I have to admit, a unicorn forest
does sound kind of magical.
Or not.
IZZY: Come on!
My house isn't far from here!
(SINGS TO HERSELF)
(IZZY CONTINUES SINGING)
Well, here we are, guys.
La Villa Izzy.
ALL: Wow!
(PLAYS TUNE)
- Did you make all of this?
- Yeah!
Unicycling. Isn't it funky?
It is gorgeous!
- I also make friendship bracelets.
- Oh, cool.
Wait, wait, watch this!
Hold everything!
Ha! I've never gotten to use it
with actual friends!
- Ta-da!
- Oh!
I so wish I had live-streamed that.
We don't have time for that
right now.
If we're going to get
the information we need
on the unicorn crystal,
we can't stick out like sore hooves.
We need to look like unicorns.
Yay! Makeovers!
I love makeovers.
No... No, this is not...
this is not what I signed up for. No.
So, Izzy, can you do it?
A glow-up?
Honey, you came to the right cottage.
# I thought earth ponies were
the pony ladder’s bottom rung
# I heard that pegasi were brutes
you’d hate to be among
# You smell like fishes
You’re vicious
# I bet you eat your young!
# Meet any one of you
The thing to do is run away
# But although I know we’re all
a bunch of different breeds
# Take away our wings and horns
and we’re just frightened steeds
# So let’s put aside our differences
cos what we need’s a win
# Oh-oh-oh
# Come on, rip out all the pages
of your history books.
# Just because we’re undercover
doesn’t mean we’re crooks
# When we walk you through the crowd
and give your brand-new looks a spin
# You’re gonna fit right in! #
This is a new low.
# You're gonna fit right in... #
It's never gonna work!
# They taught us unicorns
were super-scary maniacs
# With horns like razors and tongues
like Tasers and teeth like tacks
# They take your hooves and then
they grind them into midnight snacks
# The basic gist of it
is unicorns are not OK
# Look, I know we’re risking
everything for this endeavour
# But look at us - we’re brave
and strong and weird and clever
# We’re running out of options
and we’re desperate to begin
# You’re gonna fit right in! #
If you say so!
I know you will -
now watch and learn.
# This is how a unicorn walks
# Walks
# This is how a unicorn talks
# Talks
# This is how a unicorn hoops
# Hoops
- # This is how a unicorn... #
- Oops!
Stop!
# This is how a unicorn struts
# Watch us shake our unicorn butts
- # Now you're in the unicorn know...
- # Whoa
# Soon you'll make a unicorn pro! Oh
# A unicorn horn
makes a unicorn stride
# It's the more-head on your forehead
It's the source of your pride
# Every unicorn who's born
has worn a horn that's unique
# So we'll whip them up as we speak
You'll be looking très magnifique
# And with those rocks in our pockets
We'll reap the reward
# And folks'll be floored
We'll strike a new chord
# Our magic restored!
# Lately, all Equestria
has lost its heart
# But if we can help to find it
we should play our part
# If we fail, we’ll go to prison
# But if not, we’ll start to grin
# So let’s begin!
# We're gonna fit right in!
# This is how a unicorn walks!
# This is how a unicorn talks!
# Now you're looking unicorn strong
- # This is how a unicorn
- # Ends this song. #
(GIGGLES)
Ta-da! Crystal!
Crystal! Crystal!
Crystal!
She does know we're just looking
for the one, right?
Crystal!
Crystal! Crystals!
(GIGGLES)
Ow.
- Hey.
Well, this is...cheerful.
These other unicorns
seem so different than you.
Yeah, I get that a lot.
My sparkle is a bit too sparkly
for Bridlewood.
How can we tell
which ones are magic?
Ooh!
- You said a bad word!
- Huh?
Hurry, before we get jinxed!
ALL: Ah!
(ALL BLOW AIR)
# Bing-bong-bing!
Bing-bong, bing-bong!
# Bing-bong, bing-bong! #
O...K.
I'm going to need some context.
Unicorns are very superstitious.
If a pony ever says
a forbidden word,
we have to do a ritual
to ward off the jinxies.
- Jinxies?
- Bad luck.
Forbidden words?
Magic, wing, feather...
Oh, and mayonnaise.
- What's wrong with may...?
- Ah-da-da-da-da!
(CUCKOO CALLS)
- (GASPS)
- Come on!
There's something I want to show you.
The Crystal Tearoom?
There's a pony inside
who collects crystals.
Maybe he could help us.
That's great, Izzy!
- Oh, and, Hitch...
- I know, I know.
No forbidden words.
Earth pony jinx.
Something stinks.
Pegasus neighs...
That's the pony I was talking about.
So word in the forest is
you collect crystals.
Yes, I do.
Well, I mean, I did.
I lost them all in a limbo contest
with Alphabittle.
Oh, no.
- Who's Alphabittle?
- (BELL CLANGS)
Time's up! Pass it over, Jasper.
Ohhh.
Guess that makes me the winner -
again.
Pay up.
Oh, fine.
You could always try
winning it back!
All right, suit yourself.
There it is!
I've got an idea. Maybe I can
beat Alphabittle at his own game.
Wait! Alphabittle can smell fear.
Got it.
OK, be cool.
Oh...
Tea.
(CRITTER SQUEAKS)
Hold the milk.
Quite the game player, I see.
It passes the time.
Why. Do you play?
I don't play.
I win.
Is that so?
Yeah, it is.
And I challenge you for that.
You think you can beat me?
Only one way to find out.
Big talk for a little pony.
I think you'll find
I'm average height.
Tick-tock. What do you say?
Whatever you're betting,
it better be special.
Special enough for you?
(ALL GASP)
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Um...what are you doing?
Don't worry! I could solve
that cube puzzle in my sleep.
But if he wins,
we'll lose both crystals!
- We won't. Trust me.
- Izzy.
If your friend is finished stalling,
do we have a deal?
Deal.
Now give me that cube.
No, no, no, no.
A special prize
calls for a special competition.
Bring forth the Ultimate Challenge!
The ultimate what, now?
A dancing game. Seriously?
Both ponies agree -
best out of three.
Let's make this more interesting.
You only need to win one
out of three.
(MUSIC STARTS)
(DING!)
Yeah! That's how you do it!
Yay.
It's OK. You're just warming up.
ANNOUNCER: What can you do?
Round two.
I'll make this quick.
Focus.
(MUSIC STARTS)
(DING-DING-DING!)
Yeah!
Critters! Get my crystal polish
ready, would you?
Round three. Who will it be?
Oh...here goes nothing.
Hey! You hear that, Sunny?
Feel the rhythm take you over.
- You're feeling it?
- I'm feeling it!
- Yeah, you are, Sunny!
- Yeah, you do this, honey!
- (MUSIC PLAYS)
Yes! She's doing it, she's doing it!
(CRITTER SQUEAKS)
(DING-DING-DING!)
We won.
- We won! We actually won!
- Yes!
(ALL CHEER)
(ALL GASP)
An earth pony.
- And pegasi.
- And a unicorn!
Which you knew already.
I know it doesn't look like it,
but we're here to help.
Help? We don't need help,
especially from ponies like you.
Give me the crystal.
But I won!
You tricked me.
The crystal.
Now!
Uh...magic! Wing! Feather!
Mayonnaise!
- Bing!
- Bong.
- Bing-bong!
- Go, go, go!
(BING-BONGING IN BACKGROUND)
- You'll pay for this!
- Bing-bong!
Sorry about that!
- Uh...thanks for the tea!
- Bing-bong!
(ALL GASP)
Oh!
Mom?
Oh, my darlings.
Thank hoofness you escaped.
How did you find us?
(BUSHES RUSTLE)
Argh!
Oh, my badge, yes!
Oh, I'm so glad
I found my little fillies.
Now, I know that if you just
come back with me,
we can explain everything.
Spin the story,
and they'll love us again.
- Right?
- (HOOVES THUD)
- Let us explain.
- There she is!
Your Criminal Highness.
You're coming with us.
Argh! Unicorns!
Give me back my crystals
and leave Bridlewood.
Your crystals?
That crystal belongs to me.
Not any more, it doesn't.
I won it fair and square.
Huh! I certainly doubt it.
Unicorns are known to be cheaters.
You pegasi always thought
you were better than us.
Hey, that's our queen
you're talking to.
She's not a queen here.
- Who do you think you are?
- We're gonna zap you with our horns!
- This is our land!
- You're not welcome here!
Surrender the crystal
or I'll use my powers against you.
I'd like to see you try.
No pony has magic!
UNICORN: Bing-bong!
But we are here to bring it back.
Is it possible?
- Did she just say magic?
- This is a trick.
I know it sounds unbelievable,
but please, just let us try.
Please, Mom, trust us.
You two...
Fine.
You're wasting your time, kid.
Ready, Izzy?
Ready.
It... It...
Why didn't it work, Daddy?
Cos it was all just make-believe.
We can try it again!
Maybe...
Maybe we did it wrong somehow.
Wait, wait, don't go.
Oh, come on.
Work! Work. Please work.
- Come on.
- Sunny.
It's OK.
You did everything you could.
I... I thought it would work.
I was so, so sure of it.
What do we do now, Sunny?
I'm sorry for all the trouble
I caused you.
PIPP: Sunny! We can't give up.
I thought that I could make
a difference.
But everywhere I go,
I just make things worse.
That's not true.
We're all in this together, right?
- Yeah.
- Of course.
I'm so sorry I let you all down.
(SIGHS)
I guess this is goodbye...friends.
Better hurry...Sheriff.
I'm right here if you need to talk,
Sunny.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(DOOR OPENS)
- Sunny!
- Hitch! Hitch!
I figured it out! There's actually...
(BANG)
Huh?
What-What is going on here?
We can't tell you. We've signed
the Official Sprout Act.
Official Sprout what?
The Stallion-in-Chief.
(DRUMMING)
Sprout?
- Step!
- Oh, right.
Citizens of Maretime...
Can we try that again?
Sprout! What are you doing?
Aww, little Sheriff Hitchie
came trotting back - wah! -
just in time to see me do
what you couldn't.
Attack our enemies!
Wait, wait. No, Sprout, listen to me.
Listen to me.
The pegasi and unicorns
can be our friends.
There's no need to be afraid
of them.
Besides, they don't even
have any magic!
- What?
- No magic? Ha!
That's even better.
But we can bring magic back!
Bring friendship back.
So we don't have to fight?
Oh, that's a relief.
Wait, wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't listen!
They've been brainwashed!
You all be next
if we don't end this now!
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
(CLUNKING AND BEEPING)
Say hello to Sprouticus Maximus!
(CROWD GASPS)
Maybe this is a bit too much, dear!
Troops! On to Bridlewood!
(TOOT-TOOT!)
We have to warn them!
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
Sunny!
What are you guys doing here?
We don't care what anypony says.
- Yeah, we just want to stay friends.
- Pipp! Zipp!
I know you're upset, darlings,
my sweet little darlings,
but it's time to go home now.
Izzy Moonbow, you're going
to get us all jinxed.
- Come back to Bridlewood.
- Excuse me.
Do you see my mouth still moving?
That means I'm still talking.
You're all in danger!
I'm sorry. What?
(HORN BLARES)
Huh?
Would you look at this! Our enemies
delivered themselves to us.
No, no, no, we're not here
to fight, Mr Big Robot Pony.
I do not accept your surrender.
Load the Splat-a-pult!
(GASPS)
Oh! Why do I have to do
everything myself?
- We have to stop that thing!
- But how?
With magic.
Quick! I need your crystals.
There's a third crystal!
- Follow me.
- What?
Oh, no, you don't!
- I've got to rein that thing in.
- I've got your back, Hitch.
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
Argh!
Sprout! Stop!
Where are the other crystals?
This ends now!
What, and let them have magic?
Never!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Argh!
- Sunny!
- Got it!
We need the unicorn crystal.
I'm looking, I'm looking!
Hitch!
Found it!
No, no, no!
Oh!
(SCREAMS)
Oh. I'm OK!
(GASPS)
- (SCREAMS)
- Izzy!
Argh!
We need to shut these down!
(GRUNTS)
Alphabittle, look out!
(SCREAMING)
OK, that was a bad idea.
Sprout! Let's put the toy away!
Mommy, please!
I'm in the middle of something!
You come down from there right now!
I've almost got it!
But, Mommy, I'm in charge!
I said stop!
(GASPS)
No, no, no!
(BOTH SCREAM)
It... It didn't work.
(RUMBLING)
No, no, no!
Argh!
(GRUNTS)
(COUGHING)
Oh, Sunny.
I understand now.
It's not the crystals
that need to be brought together.
It's us.
We can bring back
everything that was lost,
but it's up to us.
We can stay separated
by fear and distrust
or we can choose friendship!
We can choose love.
That's the true magic.
What?
Argh!
(ALL GASP)
Whoa!
(LAUGHING)
We're actually flying!
Whoo!
Sunny! Check you out!
- What?
- I can't believe it!
Now, that's what I call a glow-up!
Look!
(ALL GASP)
Daddy! Daddy! The magic is real!
Whoa!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Yeah!
(CRITTER SQUEAKS)
(BARKING AND LAUGHTER)
(LAUGHS)
Oh, I see you've made a new friend.
Hi there, buddy.
Wow!
(CHEERING)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
Stunning!
Mommy? Was I a good sheriff?
Er... Look! A flying dog!
You did it, Sunny.
No. We did it - together.
Now we never have to be apart!
ALL: Hooves to hearts!
Phew.
Hey, guys, what did I miss?
Aargh!
# We got the light
We’re coming in stronger
# We’re in it together
# If you want it
It’s all inside your mind
# We got the light
Won’t wait any longer
# We’ll get it together
# If you want it
Then you can paint the sky
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# Dip and slide
Through the cut
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# We say high
You say what?
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# Dip and slide
Through the cut
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# We say high
You say what?
# Everywhere that I've been
# Yeah, they say I'm different
# But I'm good in my skin
Ooh-ooh
# If it doesn't feel right
# Break it in with tie-dye
# And don’t you stop till sunrise
# We don’t fly like we used to
# We take what we’ve been through
# And we can feel brand-new
Ooh-ooh-ooh
# I know I am a fighter
# I feel the fire
# I’m shining brighter
Ooh-ooh-ooh
# We got the light
# We’re coming in stronger
# We’re in it together
# If you want it
It’s all inside your mind
# We got the light
Won’t wait any longer
# We’ll get it together
# If you want it
Then you can paint the sky
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# Dip and slide
Through the cut
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# We say high
You say what?
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# Dip and slide
Through the cut
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# We say high
You say what?
# We got the kind of love
# Glowing up
Kind of love
# We got the light
# We got the kind of love
Ooh-ooh-ooh
# Glowing up
Kind of love
Kind of love... #
- Glowing up!
- Kind of looove.
We say high! You say what?
Race you to the bridge!
Oh, it's on.
No using your magic this time!
Last one there is a rotten sardine!
I'm gonna win!
Me first!
# Some days get the best of me
# Sometimes I feel I'm not enough
# Not enough
# That's not who I wanna be
# I know I'm not the only one
# No
# Everybody needs somebody
# I want somebody too
# Oh, yeah
# If you ever need somebody
# I'll be there for you
# You know the truth is
# We're not so different after all
# Can you feel it?
# I need a friend too
# I'll be here to catch you
when you fall
# Can you feel it?
# Cos we're better
# Together
# We're better
# Everybody needs somebody
# I want somebody too
# If you ever need somebody
# I'll be there for you
# You know the truth is
# We're not so different after all
# Can you feel it?
# I need a friend too
# I'll be here to catch you
when you fall
# Can you feel it?
# Cos we're better
# Better
# Together
# We're better
# Better
# Together
# Together. #
(MUSIC CONTINUES)