Blessed be the heavens and the earth,
The Chaos Pearl is born.
The Great God split it in two.
The heavenly energy within it
becomes the Spirit Pearl,
while evil energy forms a Devil Ball.
The curse of heavenly wrath
was cast upon the Devil Ball,
ready to be destroyed by lightning in 3 years.
Later, due to Shen Gongbao's intervention,
The Demon Ball reincarnated into Nezha,
the third son of Li Jing in Chentang Pass.
The Spirit Pearl became Ao Bing,
who was also the third son of the Dragon King.
Because of destiny,
the two became friends.
Nezha, influenced by his parents,
letting go of his demonic nature,
and save the Chentang Line.
Together with Ao Bing,
they face the Wrath of Heaven,
and finally
change their destiny.
broth3rmax translation
NE ZHA 2
Although saved from wrath,
your bodies are destroyed...
without that
The soul will disappear into nothingness.
The Sacred Lotus protects and guards the spirit.
Now I will use it
to recreate
your physical form.
Wow.
Amazing.
Start!
Something is wrong.
/ Is there?
This lotus root must be made into a dough
to make your body.
Have you been scratching your feet with your hands?
Oh, don't worry.
It's okay if my feet are sticky,
a little rinse will clean them.
It's not your feet I'm thinking about.
Do you blow your nose with your hand?
No, nothing.
Just lotus dough.
See?
Lotus dough.
Ready to pour.
Come on, come on.
One snot for each of you.
I mean, one serving.
Hurry! To save your souls.
I don't think so.
/ Annoying kid!
It worked!
Just a moment.
What is this?
/ Thanks,
I've been looking for this for a while.
It's time for formation.
The Flying Pig's memory is truly unmatched,
this is his carving skill.
Perfect renovation, right?
Thank you, Pig.
Don't move, it's not fixed yet.
Guru Dewa,
I have deployed the entire Chentang army
to protect against Shen Gongbao and
the East Sea dragons.
Take it easy.
The dragon is watching over the monsters of Hell,
none of them could escape.
Shen Gongbao himself was not a threat.
You have to see this.
Isn't this perfect?
Whoa!
I learned from the expert.
But, does it have to be exactly the same?
Can't you make me look prettier?
/ Huh?
Yes, that's right.
Parents always wish
the best for their children, huh?
Correct.
Make me tall and strong.
Also very handsome.
A man must be strong and fierce.
Also polite and attentive.
But also cute and adorable.
Can you stand up for yourself?
Tall and muscular.
With a touch of handsomeness.
/ Strong and fierce.
But very adorable.
What's this?
Then start showing your skills.
/ Come on!
I should have done it a long time ago.
Fixing it yourself is always best.
/ This must take a long time.
Let's do your work first.
You were born from the water element,
so you must be tempered with pure water.
The lotus is open!
Here he is.
Are you done?
Almost.
This version is definitely the most fascinating,
but it takes a long time to perfect it.
How about we
use the first one for now?
Yeah, the first version is okay too.
I agree.
Good.
You were born of the fire element,
then you must be polished in pure fire.
Sir!
Enemies were seen in the sea.
It seemed to be Shen Gongbao.
How many?
/ Just him.
How come?
Continue your spell.
We will overcome the intruder.
Guru Dewa,
let me ask my teacher.
Don't move!
Before the incense stick burns out,
your body is not getting better.
VISITORBET
►HIGHEST 1.3% SLOT REBATE IN INDONESIA◄
►find us on Google: VISITORBET◄
Shen Gongbao, what is required
for us to receive this honor?
Now that you know my plans with the dragon.
I can't deny that I'm... a little nervous.
The Chentang Line is tightly guarded,
and Master Taiyi in the city.
You're alone, you can't do much.
Who says... I'm alone?
[2 HOURS AGO,
DRAGON PALACE]
If they knew about the Spirit Pearl,
[WEST DRAGON QUEEN]
DRAGON KING OF
THE EAST SEA
not only will you fail
to avenge your son,
but the entire Eastern Dragon Clan
will bear the blame.
SOUTH SEA DRAGON KING
NORTH SEA DRAGON KING
When the truth is revealed,
you will be thrown into the abyss of purgatory,
surrounded by all your old "friends".
Just wait and see how we welcome you.
Trapped in the Dragon Palace...
how can you avenge your son?
I'm worried too.
You stupid dragons
don't deserve to be arrogant.
I'm just trying to help.
But it seems like you
I don't appreciate it.
/ Hmm?
You must have forgotten my abilities.
Ah!
I know this one.
Crack... Crack...
Sky Splitting Claw.
Thank You.
Master Shen can
bring this claw to the Chentang path,
and used it to
tear open a rift that led back to me.
Then the Hell Monster can
help destroy your enemies.
SKY-SPLITTING THUNDER WHIP
Hell Monster?
How could it be?
They were trapped by
the Restraining Seal for thousands of years.
How could they possibly escape?
Dragon... have they been released by the Dragon?
With the Sea-Stabilizing Chain that binds us,
impossible to escape.
This is a tactic that benefits everyone.
What do you think, my brother?
You won't be that good.
Straight to the point.
What is your request?
In this purgatory,
where fire burns our bodies,
A day feels like a year.
If you could turn down the heat of this lava a little,
ease our suffering,
We are ready to serve you
with all our strength.
What happened?
What is Shen Gongbao planning now?
Finally we're out! Hooray!
Wow!
Like that.
We're done.
How do I explain this to General Li now?
Luckily no one saw us.
Here.
/ What for?
I'll break your arm
and then you'll break my leg.
We'll say Yaksha did it.
/ Oh.
When the general saw
how badly injured we were,
He won't blame us anymore.
Try hard.
/ Hit it hard!
Hey!
Hey, you two!
Guru Dewa, you're here!
Hee hee hee!
Hahahaha!
He let Yaksha escape!
/ Huh?
It's your fault.
Who are you pointing at?
/ Who are you to pretend to be innocent?
Oh my,
the idiot and the moron!
Hey!
You guys are stupid!
Get out of here and protect me!
Yes sir, right away!
Don't forgive.
Shen Gongbao!
Ao Bing belum mati.
Chentang and the dragon paths
have no reason to fight.
Taiyi was reshaping Ao Bing's body.
Lie!
Hmm?
The dome shield...
Oh no!
Teacher!
Ao Bing!
Master Taiyi shaped a new body for me.
/ Shen GongBao
,
I saved your student.
Don't you thank me?
So,
Who is that in there?
Why? You're so ungrateful!
Teacher!
They must die!
Hahahaha!
Do you think you can break this protective shield?
Come on, hit me!
No!
That aura...
Ao Bing!
/ Father!
AO GUANG
Dad!
My mission failed to save our people.
No.
It doesn't matter.
Dad just wants you to be safe.
As long as you are here,
that is enough for father.
The lotus is open!
Your body, what is this...
/ Understand, it is indeed "newborn".
How can he take a beating like that?
Ao Bing!
Hey! It's not ready yet!
Don't move! Don't move!
Ao Bing, why?
Do not move before repair.
If the body exceeds its limits,
will be destroyed!
By the gods...
Fat!
Make another body...
make Ao Bing now!
Huh?
Create two bodies in sequence
clearly draining the energy of the Sacred Lotus.
/ Without a body, won't the soul scatter?
Teacher, do something!
/ Without the Sacred Lotus,
I can't do anything.
No problem.
I replaced you as the Spirit Pearl,
I deserve this.
If my sacrifice
can bring you back to life,
then it's worth it.
Who told you to do that?
I'm happy being the Devil Ball.
Don't try to die!
Dad,
Please save the Chentang Line.
We must stop making mistakes.
This is my last request.
There must be another way.
There must be!
You, try again!
Let Ao Bing share your body for now.
Share your body.
2 souls share 1 body,
rejection is inevitable.
Spirit Pearls and Devil Balls come from the same source.
Sharing one body
for 7 days would be no problem.
Yes, that's it!
Ao Bing, come in!
Fast!
Good.
This feels... weird...
Ao Bing, are you here?
/ Yes.
I can hear your voice in my head.
This is exciting!
But this is only a temporary fix.
What will happen after 7 days?
There is medicine in the safe of Yu Xu Palace.
Reparo Miracle Medicine.
It can restore the power of magical objects.
With that,
The Holy Lotus will bloom again.
But how do you get it?
I myself will go to the Great God
and beg.
Or are you planning
to report me and the dragons?
The Great God would not want to...
save a dragon child.
If my request is unsuccessful,
then we'll just take it.
The Yu Xu Palace is in the center of the Chan Sect,
protected by a great power.
/ For the sake of my son,
I am willing to break through the Heavenly Palace if necessary.
Your Majesty, please calm down.
Maybe I have a plan.
Chan's disciples were expelled from training
can take part in the Promotion Exam.
Passing the test not only receives immortality,
but also have the right to choose
one magical item from Yu Xu's Vault as a reward.
Do you suggest
Nezha take the exam?
to get the magic medicine?
/ No, no, no!
He's emitting demonic energy!
Once he uses his power, he'll be exposed!
Isn't Ao Bing one body with Nezha?
His divine aura could perfectly cover the Demon energy.
As long as he passes the test in 7 days,
we don't just get that magic... medicine...
But he can also...
/ Gain immortality!
So I'm not a Devil anymore?
This will save Ao Bing as well as Nezha.
Everyone... is satisfied.
This is not the right action.
So what is your suggestion?
Follow the rules.
Be honest with the Supreme God.
and trust his decision.
My wife and I will also ask for forgiveness,
so that the sins of the parents do not affect their children.
Ordinary people,
you only experience life for tens of years,
How dare you lecture me on morals?
Longer than I can remember,
I have lived for thousands of years.
Let me just tell you one fact.
If my son dies,
I will sink the Chentang Line with him.
Stop!
Ao Bing is my friend.
I will definitely save him.
But if you try to harm the Chentang Line,
I will destroy your Dragon Palace
to pieces!
Selain Nezha and Taiyi,
From now on, no one can
leave the Chentang Line.
If in 7 days I don't see the Reparo Miracle Medicine
or news about my clan spreads,
I will leave the Chentang Line
sink forever.
I don't trust all my relatives,
and I can't stay out of my body for long .
The Fate of the Chentang Line
is in your hands.
Yes,
that is true.
No message delivered
just by nodding.
Tuan Li,
We are all here to say goodbye
to Young Master Nezha.
We want to thank him
for saving the entire city.
You are very kind.
My son has caused a lot of trouble.
for years.
I knew from the beginning that Young Master
was destined for greatness.
Look at him, his forehead is wide,
His face is wide,
his nose is prominent,
chubby cheeks and thick lips.
All signs of a true hero!
I never judge a face wrongly.
Young Master, don't forget to brush your teeth after eating!
Bos,
Demon Hunters has now changed its name
to Nezha Gang.
All members will obey your orders.
Young Master, do you want to learn calligraphy?
I'm here for you!
/ Young Master, you're already 3 years old.
It's time to find a girlfriend.
/ Interested in musical instruments?
We are skilled in all tools.
I want to
play badminton.
What?
This is exciting.
Anyone want it?
Dad will play with you.
Haven't you always wanted to play badminton with dad?
Who...
the kick was a bit hard.
Hahahaha!
I am a war general!
Dad.
That's just my son!
How about...
we play another day?
Impossible!
Why stop when you're having fun?
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm coming too!
My wife, you don't have to do this.
/ Are you looking down on me?
I'm a war general too!
Nezha, catch this!
Son, why didn't you catch him?
If only I wasn't the Devil Ball...
What?
/ It's nothing.
Time to go.
Before you go,
would you mind
Hugging mom?
Don't worry, many people have seen it.
Wait.
This is a snack made by mom.
For you and your teacher on the go.
Yes, yes.
We'll go first.
Hey!
I haven't gotten on yet!
Your body is not fully repaired yet.
Don't push yourself too hard.
/ Okay, okay.
And watch your temper.
Stay calm out there.
Without mother and father near you,
Learn to take care of yourself.
You are a silly boy.
What's the problem with just hugging?
That's too much.
This isn't a goodbye anyway.
Let's go.
VISITORBET
►WE WILL PAY YOU NO MATTER WHATEVER YOU WIN◄
►search for us on Google: VISITORBET◄
Why are you sighing?
Does it feel bad?
Eat, eat, eat.
You know, just eat.
Look at me.
I'm worried about eating!
Do you think how can I pass the exam?
What's the test about?
It will test your forging progress.
In front of the judges,
You must defeat, with your bare hands,
3 earth-monster level demon kings.
Fight...
that's my specialty.
/ But once you release demonic energy,
your identity will be exposed.
/ Let Ao Bing control my body.
He is the energy of the gods,
which is equally powerful.
It looks easy.
Here, try it.
Nezha, relax your whole body.
Let Ao Bing control
and fight me.
Ao Bing, what are you doing?
Stay straight!
That's how it is when one soul
resides in another person's body.
Unless your determination is stronger than the body's owner,
you won't be able to have full control.
Nezha, defeated.
The harder you force,
the weaker Ao Bing's control becomes.
Use your feet!
He's so complete, he's so complete!
Do not panic!
I'm coming...
approaching you.
You're happy, huh?
We are almost at Yu Xu Palace,
and you're still playing around.
Look at you,
What kind of mentor are you?
Stand here and reflect on your mistakes.
Don't eat until you know your mistake!
You adults,
don't be like reckless teenagers.
I get it!
Sleeping pills.
What's that?
Eat this, and you'll fall asleep soon.
Once you sleep,
Ao Bing can take full control of your body.
Intelligent!
One is enough!
You should have said... earlier.
Good.
Guru Taiyi?
Now this feels right.
Why?
Stay cool.
I see you took over
Nezha's body completely.
Let's start again.
This time, I won't hold back.
You should also try your best.
I beg for your guidance.
/ Not bad.
Can barely match my abilities.
Master Taiyi, your nose is bleeding.
It's been hot lately.
Need some more drinking water.
No problem.
Kunlun Mountain! Here we come.
I heard that one day here
is equal to a year in the human world.
Don't worry,
we're not in the heavenly realm yet.
But these are many people.
/ They come to seek immortality.
The Chan sect is famous throughout the world,
and everyone wants to join it.
Look at this, jasper.
This is a sign of the eternal mandate of the Chan Sect.
With this,
you will be respected wherever you go.
Look,
being immortal is awesome.
Both of your brothers have been promoted.
You won't have any problems either.
I mean Nezha's brother.
His two brothers
among the best third generation disciples.
Do you know
How is Nezha always being naughty, huh?
So, I often tell stories about his brother.
to be a good example for him.
Let me tell you something.
Nezha idolizes his brother.
VISITORBET
►HIGHEST 1.3% SLOT REBATE IN INDONESIA◄
►find us on Google: VISITORBET◄
Oh wow, you're lucky
to meet the famous Demon Hunter.
Demon Hunters?
/ They roam the land, hunting
a ghost that brings disaster to humans,
maintain world peace.
Current Demon Hunter Leader
DEER
top disciple of Wuliang God.
Wasn't his predecessor Shen Gongbao?
ISTANA YU XU
Master Taiyi,
what is that smoke over there?
Oh,
it was Yu Xu Palace's most prized possession.
Tianyuan Crater.
DEWA WULIANG
Kak Taiyi, it's been a long time.
Brother Wuliang, I heard that during Master's exile
You take care of Yu Xu Palace.
I invite my students to take the Promotion Exam.
Nezha, beri salam Guru Wuliang.
Guru Wuliang.
So, you're Nezha?
The reincarnation of the Spirit Pearl?
Oh my!
How amazing!
The Great God has high hopes for you.
And you definitely won't be disappointed.
Look at him, his vitality is completely strong,
emitting good vibrations.
Lately, this boy has been practicing a lot.
His condition is not stable.
What do you want to do?
This is Yu Xu Palace.
I need to pee.
Crana.
/ Yeah.
CRANA
Take this child to the toilet (restroom).
Restroom?
I didn't say I wanted to rest.
You idiot!
Toilet, that's where you pee.
This kid is a bit naughty.
Please forgive him.
Wow!
Very white.
So white!
Wow!
Is this entire palace made of jade?
Where did they
get that much money to buy jade?
The word "Yu" in Xu Yu Palace means jade, right?
So what does "Xu" mean?
Simple?
Feel guilty?
Or emptiness?
Is the toilet made of jade?
Do gods also need to pee?
Did Teacher Wuliang also... poop?
This is a place of exile.
Keep your voice down.
How far is this toilet?
I can't take it anymore!
Hey, miss, wait!
You...
I didn't mean to.
/ I have to change my dress.
Go there by yourself.
/ But I don't know where the toilet is.
Go through this hallway, turn right, then left.
Oh.
Wow.
How luxurious!
Radical!
Emm...
Am I... lost?
Where are you going?
/ Oh.
I got lost.
Follow me.
Brother, it's great to raise the Spirit Pearl.
Another great achievement for the Sect.
Not really.
This is all thanks to the guidance of the Guru.
This Kunlun Dew is a rare miracle medicine.
Normally, it takes 6 months to fill one pool.
But today, when I asked someone to check it,
now it's full!
Your timing couldn't be better.
Bro, luck must be on your side, right?
What's wrong with you?
You can't even drink water properly.
This student of mine is a bit lacking in manners.
Please forgive him.
My pee is in the water.
My teacher is also a bit lacking in manners.
Please forgive him.
Brother, that time is important.
I think Nezha should take the exam soon.
Why the rush?
Let's have a drink first.
No more, please.
In that case, okay.
My student Deero will be the Judge.
The Demon Hunter's next target
can be handed over to Nezha.
Sis, we'll excuse ourselves first.
Taiyi, my brother,
is always impatient.
This year's Dew Taste
rich in a certain flavor.
Continue using this method in the future.
Yes, Teacher.
VISITORBET
►WE WILL PAY YOU NO MATTER WHATEVER YOU WIN◄
►search for us on Google: VISITORBET◄
Why stop?
It's been 6 hours, Teacher Shen.
Tired of continuing.
/ Useless!
Forging does not tolerate laziness.
Don't stop without my permission .
General Li Jing of Chentang Pass
comes to see you.
Guru Shen,
Yesterday's battle resulted in
many soldiers and civilians being injured.
We ran out of medicine.
I beg you to open a path
so that some healers could go to town
to buy supplies.
How bold!
No wonder you...
Whose doing is this?
You bastard...
I...
Stop... stop, stop, stop!
Bring me
who was caught earlier.
He left the city during the battle.
General Li, please,
Bring it again... this one.
This is a misunderstanding, Teacher Shen!
I'm a ghost too!
I caught this Yaksha
to clear my son's name.
Now that it's done,
and because he didn't do anything serious,
Just let him go.
/ Yes, that's right.
My role is small.
It's not important.
I don't think you understand me.
No one can leave here,
not even demons.
Especially humans.
Master Shen, please forgive me.
I am also a demon.
We're both the bad guys!
Pfft!
I... am not a criminal.
Everyone who knows the secret of the Spirit Pearl
must stay here.
/ Without medicine,
The wounded will not survive.
Teacher Shen, please,
I just ask you to save my life.
Sir!
We caught a spy.
This guy is from out of town
and he injured some of our soldiers.
/ Lock him up...lock him up too.
Bang.
Dude, is that you?
You...
Bro, it's me!
SHEN XIAOBAO
Xiaobao?
You haven't been home for ages.
I really miss you.
What are you doing here?
Father sent me to look for you.
Look,
The compass you gave me.
It tells me where you are.
Dad... how is he?
He is healthy.
Since you entered Yu Xu Palace,
father's energy is full,
as if he was taking a magic vitamin.
You are the only one from our village
who has succeeded in becoming a Chan Sect immortal.
Now, fellow ghosts from miles
away are riding the train with father.
By the way,
why are you here?
Didn't you promise me,
once I reach human form,
You will take me to Yu Xu Palace?
Look! I can transform into a human now!
All these years, I have been practicing diligently,
without a single day's rest.
You are my role model, bro.
Glory to Yu Xu, answering the heavenly call.
Traveling the world, bringing justice to all.
Tell me, bro,
what are you doing here?
/ I... I...
Are these your sea monsters subordinates?
Why are you besieging the Chentang Line?
Well, about that...
This...
Master Shen is defending the Chentang Line.
Huh?
Evil forces are attacking this city.
Master Shen and the sea clan came to our aid.
On behalf of my people,
I thank you for your noble actions.
No need for that.
Wow!
Dude, you are amazing!
Is this the demon that attacked Chentang Pass?
Ah!
You bring shame to the good name of the demons!
Shameless!
Hey, Xiaobao,
Can you
wait a few more years
before going to Yu Xu Palace?
Huh? Why?
I can transform into a human now!
Because...
I'm preparing for my promotion
to the 12 Golden Immortals.
so I can focus.
/ 12 Golden Immortals?
Once finished,
I'll take you there, how about that?
No problem, bro!
Your promotion is more important.
I can go to Yu Xu Palace anytime.
Besides that,
I'm not yet proficient enough in mastering the art of shapeshifting.
I'll go home and practice again.
Even more active.
Xiaobao,
This is what I've kept since I entered the palace.
/ What is this?
Yu Xu Palace gave all the disciples this immortality pill.
Try eating it, and you will...
gain 10 years of forging knowledge.
But...
This is too precious.
Bro, you are training for a promotion.
You should keep it.
/ I don't like the taste.
I prefer to forge myself.
You... have to take it back.
Share it with your family.
No, I can't.
Dad will blame me.
Xiaobao, you don't obey your brother?
Take the pill and leave now.
This is the front line.
If... you stay here,
I will be unfocused.
In that case...
I...
will go.
Bro, you have to
managed to reach 12 Golden Immortals.
I will continue to practice on my own.
I appreciate your help,
but the risks were too great
for me to let anyone through.
This Yaksha...
you also bring it back.
I didn't help you earlier.
But I helped the young master.
A good role model
can change his life.
Wait.
Give... give me a list of the medicines you need.
LEVEL 1: BANDIT HILL
I am Nezha, the valiant Third Prince.
I finish off the ghost,
I write in a poem that has not been told.
Today I come to remove the devil's breath.
Evil demons, prepare to die!
Still eating?
Woe to you.
Ahhh!
Who do you think you are?
Roaring on our Bandit Hill?
So you're the leader?
Go ahead.
and feel my power.
You're so arrogant, you brat.
Boss, teach him a lesson.
Show your skills.
You go first.
No, but, boss...
How dare I take your thunder?
Fighting that little kid is embarrassing.
If I say go ahead, go ahead!
Hey, kid.
Too young,
very naive.
So I'm willing to let this go.
You...
It's not too late to run home to your mother.
Why is this?
/ Why did you wake up again?
I don't know.
I'm an easy sleeper.
The shaking had woken me up.
Damn it.
He mostly took his pills
and now he is immune to sleeping pills.
Then increase the dose.
If you insist on staying here, you'll get hurt.
I was going to dodge to the right.
/ Sorry, I thought it was to the left.
Very weak.
Master Taiyi.
Maybe I should just stop.
He can practice for a few more years.
/ Not so fast.
He was just testing the demon.
The kid likes to...
pretend to be stupid.
Pil.
I need pills.
/ I'll give you a warning.
Now you know who you're messing with.
Oh no.
The pills are mixed in the soup!
Then I'll drink the soup.
And you tried to steal our soup?
That's asking to be beaten.
Let me do it.
Disgusting.
Super Powerful Mace Attack!
See?
I told you he was just pretending.
I wasn't paying attention earlier.
That doesn't count.
No way!
You suck!
Move!
Watch me beat him up.
/ Why did you throw up everything?
The taste is too strong.
I can't take it anymore.
Check this out!
Funny!
It doesn't work.
We can't win without it.
Deero is watching.
I can't give him the pills.
What should we do now?
I understand.
There is another way.
You don't suggest...
We can eat the vomit.
But, it's disgusting.
What is the problem?
Wait for me to drink Yaksha snot?
This should explain it.
"Suffer first, then see the results."
That's how Nezha defeated fate.
The lives of my parents and my friends are at stake,
and the people of Jalur Chentang.
It's EASY!
By ignoring prejudice
and overcome inner fears
I will change my destiny.
I remain humble
until today's show.
Guru Taiyi,
Save Nezha first.
We'll think about the Reparo Miracle Medicine later.
Impossible.
I can't believe this.
Son, let's compete again.
Pretend to be dead?
I'll hit you!
Luckily Nezha passed out.
You are so bad!
Let me avenge your defeat!
Unbeatable Whirlwind Punch!
Ahhh!
Should we arrest them all?
Even leaving one behind
could harm the people here.
Bring them all back to Yu Xu Palace.
The sect will guide them to the right path,
change evil into good.
Why is her face like that?
Nothing.
His appearance changes all the time.
Pearl of the Spirit, you know,
is not like ordinary people.
Next time be more careful,
you just scare me.
Who is this child?
Nezha maybe.
His younger siblings are Jinzha and Muzha.
She is the reincarnation of the Spirit Pearl
appointed by the Great God.
No way, huh?
Hunched over, staggering.
His eyebrows are drooping, his eyes are drooping.
His face is disgusting.
Not to mention the dark circles under her eyes.
More like a ghost.
Not now.
Brother,
what is the star sign tonight?
6 stars aligned,
once in 10 years.
Whenever 6 stars align,
This Jade Pulpit can transmit sound
and images thousands of kilometers away.
Our brothers and sisters are spread all over the world.
and finally reunited.
Tonight is the night.
The Golden Gods will meet.
I haven't gone up to the Twelve yet.
Maybe I'm not included.
It's just a matter of time.
/ No, it's not.
This is completely inappropriate.
I can't do it, really.
Then why are you sitting there?
/ Shut up!
What harm will it do you to see your teacher succeed?
Sauna!
Shh!
Brothers and sisters, I hereby welcome you
to your place.
Salam. Kak Wuliang!
Let me introduce a new member.
Kak Taiyi.
He has met the teacher's expectations.
and successfully maintain
reincarnation of the Spirit Pearl.
Have a little respect.
The war of the gods is just around the corner.
We are here to discuss preparations.
DEWA GHUANGCHENG
DEWA CHIJING
DEWA JU LIU SUN
DEWA HUANGLONG
The Chan sect was orthodox Taoist,
then we are destined to win.
But because the Jie Sect has risen rapidly
in recent years,
we must remain vigilant.
Sect Jie,
a place where furry animals and lust gather
as well as creatures born from mucus and eggs.
This war concerns the survival of our sect.
We must be careful.
Strengthen our strength.
That's the key.
/ Exactly.
That's why I started preparing early.
Immortality Pill,
the number is 9,000,
can be allocated based on levels.
DEWA DAORENG
This will definitely increase our strength.
How can there be that many?
/ For 100 years
Our teacher tirelessly refined the pills
with the Tianyuan Crater.
Working day and night,
sacrificing his own forging.
DEWA LENGBAO
Brother Wuliang has dedicated himself
to building our sect,
his contribution is commendable.
It is commendable.
THE GOD OF CIHANG
Long live the seventeenth century,
Are there other evil forces
plotting against us?
Teacher Cihang,
once the threat of the ghost was discovered,
The Demon Hunters will be dispatched soon.
So generally
roaming ghosts are not a threat.
But,
there is one exception.
/ Oh?
Who's that?
The dragons of the Eastern Sea.
Naga?
DEWA QINGXU
Didn't they give up
on the Sky Palace a long time ago?
No one can be trusted
except our own people.
To me, it seems like they just gave up,
hibernate temporarily.
Dragons have helped conquer
the monsters of hell for thousands of years.
What is their crime?
But they have their own strengths,
if they betray us in war,
the situation will turn around.
But we still can't do that.
DEWA WENSHU
Our reputation as being true and just
is known to all mankind.
If we selflessly
attack the surrendered,
How can everyone trust us?
Yes.
We must not act rashly.
Further consideration is required.
But...
/ Enough.
They are right too.
And you don't have to be so short-sighted.
Good.
The time of the 6 stars aligned is almost over.
Since there is no further discussion,
Let's end this meeting now.
Brother,
Jinzha and Muzha are
my own and Brother Puxian's students.
They have been forging here
for many years away from home,
never met Nezha,
DEWA PUXIAN
their younger brother.
/ Because there is still time left for the 6 stars to align,
Why don't you let them?
meet for a moment?
Great idea.
Oh my!
What should I do?
What?
Considering how I look like...
What is my first impression of...
ugly?
/ Of course not!
Really?
/ Despite being careless,
you have a strong will.
Although short,
you have a big heart.
Even though you are ugly,
your heart is kind.
Even though you have dark circles under your eyes,
pig life
and one tooth fell out
I still think
you're absolutely great.
And I'm sure your brothers agree with that.
Thank you for the compliment.
What are you doing?
Please meet my brothers.
/ Seriously?
How can I do this for you?
No, Nezha.
Nezha!
The boy was a bit shy.
Brother!
Ao Bing, are you crying?
This reminds me of my two brothers.
You have siblings too?
Mm.
Before.
Having two such nice brothers.
You are very lucky.
What were you guys talking about?
They said
they regret not visiting you
all these years.
They asked
news about the situation at home,
Are your parents healthy,
what are your hobbies,
and who your friends are.
They also said
whatever problems you will face in the future,
Look for them.
And remember, you have two older brothers.
who will always help and protect you.
Why are you...
/ Nothing.
Something in my eye.
Are you sure it's not the other way around?
Shut up!
I said it's nothing!
Okay.
You're the boss here.
I'm not talking to you.
Okay, I'll stop.
Are you still angry?
Nezha?
Nezha!
Ao Bing,
Since childhood I was rude and didn't know the rules,
making my parents worry all day.
Your father,
thinking he was the one who attacked the Chentang Line,
I know he just sacrificed everything
for your sake.
And today,
My brothers are so kind to me.
Our family sacrifices a lot for us.
You are a monster,
and I am the devil.
We are both a burden to the family.
So what if we were both born as demons?
God or devil, I decide.
Once you are safe,
we must have a place among the gods.
so that our family doesn't have to worry anymore.
/ Yes!
Only by becoming gods
can we be respected by all humans.
Agreed!
I will become a god!
LEVEL 2:
WATERFALL ASCENSION
Only with courage and perseverance
can rapid progress be achieved.
At this rate,
hundreds of years will be wasted.
Regarding forging,
the priorities are fitness, energy and enthusiasm.
If you find it difficult, or feel tired,
that's because you were born a devil.
Just by exerting your abilities
you have the opportunity to change your destiny
and attain immortality.
It's not life and death that I fear,
opposing the authorities
is something I respect.
Fate is in my hands, not heaven's plan.
This naughty boy will become a pious man!
Good!
Just a few sentences, but so powerful,
so inspiring.
It's a great poem indeed.
This is something you all need to learn.
Really?
Is it that good?
I just made it up.
/ It's good.
Word for word, and encouraging.
One poem like this
show your ambition, young man.
A true young hero
with a bright future!
Oh, seriously. Never mind.
Actually, there are still a few shortcomings.
More like
it has a lot of shortcomings.
I asked, what are the dark circles under the eyes for?
It's clear that you often stay up late.
Your life is not disciplined,
your diet is unhealthy,
you can't even manage
basic self-control.
How dare you dream of becoming a god?
I was born with dark circles under my eyes.
Appearance is a reflection of the heart, you know?
Try looking in the mirror.
It's ridiculous, reckless and careless.
If you become my disciple,
I want you to reform your human form.
Can be reshaped?
Then there is hope for my appearance, right?
Please teach me.
/ I've guessed your intention to find a teacher.
Listen, son,
I see you have great ambitions,
then I take you as my student.
/ Cool!
Teacher!
Come on, practice with your friends.
Practice what?
/ Of course immortality.
I don't need to be taught that.
Show me how to be more handsome.
You're ridiculous!
More concerned with looks
than forging? Set your priorities straight.
Will you teach me or not?
/ We are no longer teacher and student.
You deserve to have dark circles under your eyes for the rest of your life.
That's too much.
I won't go easy on you!
What is this?
Want to challenge me?
3 pills are definitely enough.
/ Son,
go back to where you came from.
If you continue to disturb our lessons,
will have a bad impact on you.
Sorry.
You are no match for me.
Impressive, son.
Apparently I underestimated you.
Feel this!
Yeah, teach this rancid kid a lesson.
Teachers will definitely win!
So fast!
Did you see it?
There is no grudge between us.
You better go.
I can't lose.
You won't be able to touch me.
Let alone fight me.
Smart move!
Choke him tight.
Fast movement sucks.
Give up?
Wait, you...
Finally you know.
I'm not fast.
I just turned into an electric current,
move quickly to any location.
In the water,
I am invincible!
Impressive freezing science.
Keep calm,
push yourself and your body will be destroyed!
Ice doesn't conduct electricity.
Let's see what else you're capable of.
Lakes and seas...
Clouds and skies...
With the divine spell in my hand.
Rise and Go!
Dad!
Seriously.
Rain Summoning Spell.
End this now!
Late.
You're done.
Teacher!
Teacher, are you okay?
I have no intention of taking your life.
You don't have to sacrifice your hand.
Students, listen,
bring the demon back to the palace.
Ready!
Stop!
Put down your weapons.
All of you, put down your weapons!
May I ask if you are a member of the Chan Sect?
That's right.
/ Ah.
They are the gods of Yu Xu Palace.
You have to be respectful.
Entering Yu Xu Palace and receiving
teachings of the true path
maybe there's nothing wrong with it.
Everyone, put down your weapons!
Dad!
Xiaobao?
Why are you back?
Xiaobao, calm down!
Little one!
Demon! You're so rude!
No!
Dad!
Nezha, freeze this river now!
You won't be able to escape!
Dad!
/ Go away!
Go now!
Run!
Dad...
There is nowhere to run.
Move aside.
He just wanted to save his father.
You don't have to be that cruel.
Hmph.
Ginseng bergamot,
cat's tail plant pollen,
munjeet, borneol,
dragon blood.
Another basket of
hibiscus flowers,
angelica,
pseudo ginseng powder,
sappanwood,
poisonous beans.
My lord,
Everything is complete according to the list,
along with 100 baskets of seafood.
It just so happens that our food supply is running low.
Teacher Shen, wait a minute.
We have prepared the food.
Would you kindly attend?
You...
Thanks to the kindness of Lord Li,
I was promoted to servant.
He may be a ghost,
but he has a good heart.
As long as you behave well,
there is no reason he should not have a future.
I wonder if
this dish suits your taste or not.
Front...
reasonable.
Then add more.
Try this liquor too.
/ I stopped drinking liquor a long time ago.
In forging one must... suppress one's desires.
As the saying goes,
people must stop the urge
to perfect the soul.
Another expression says,
one must practice well to polish virtue.
Talk won't help.
I've reached... the point of no return.
You can't hide forever.
Soon the truth will be revealed.
If you continue to harm lives
make more mistakes,
even though you can fool everyone,
you can't fool yourself.
And your further forging will not be better,
the point is that
Do good
and walk on the right path.
Enough!
What nonsense!
You don't know anything about forging.
Sir!
Some came here to meet Master Shen.
Brother.
Who did this to you?
/ Taoist.
They attacked.
Dad...
one hand
disconnected.
Who did this?
Her name is...
No...
Zha.
Congratulations on passing Level 2.
Please tell Kak Wuliang.
/ The teacher in isolation is purifying the pill
and has not appeared yet.
/ Before Level 3,
why don't you just rest for a few days?
We only have 2 days left.
No need. I'm still fit.
Let's continue with the exam.
/ Well, if that's what you want.
Final test
is the Demon Queen of Skull Mountain,
Shi Ji.
There are those who insist on seeing Master Taiyi.
Huh?
/ Help us!
Chentang Line...
Something happens!
Dad.
Mother.
Dad?
Mother?
Dad!
Mother!
Calm down.
Let's keep looking.
Keep looking.
I received an important report as soon as
I finished my exile.
Who could commit such a terrible crime?
Teachers, according to Shieldos,
they were hit by a tremendous force
and lost consciousness.
When they woke up,
The people of Jalur Chentang have been massacred.
We haven't got that magic pill yet.
Why did they do that?
Brother, do you know something?
No, no.
I just wondered,
where does all this lava come from?
Correct.
There are no volcanoes for hundreds of kilometers.
This is very strange.
Everyone, come here quickly!
What kind of ghost is this?
This...
dragon claw marks.
Impossible!
All the dragons are in the East Sea,
protected by a Retaining Seal.
No one can leave.
Teacher, if I remember correctly,
Queen Ao Run of the West Sea
have special abilities
called Heaven...
Sky Splitting Claw.
You think he's using the Sky Splitting Claw
to cross to Chentang Pass?
That explains the origin of this lava.
It must have been transported from a sacred fire from a distance.
But he was watched by the Dragon King of the East Sea.
It was impossible for him to cross.
So there is only one more possibility left.
Something that worries me the most
happen.
The King of the Eastern Sea betrayed us?
This is a very serious accusation.
Maybe we are wrong?
No.
They are the ones who did it!
What are you doing
Don't be reckless.
Are you going to the Dragon Palace?
That's the way to Skull Mountain.
Dragons slaughter innocent people,
commit this unforgivable abomination.
There is no need to consult with fellow Golden Gods.
I'll attack first, explain later.
Crana, come back to the palace with me.
Call all Demon Hunters.
Okay.
/ Sis,
her parents Nezha were killed by the stealth.
Don't let anything happen to that child.
Go with Deero to find him now.
Yes.
I know you are sad now,
but please can you
calm down for a moment?
Can you take me to the Dragon Palace first?
I will face my father and teacher
to get an explanation for all this.
Can it bring my parents back?
LEVEL 3:
SKULL MOUNTAIN
Mirror mirror on the wall,
Who is the most beautiful within 10 kilometers?
You, Your Highness.
RATU SHI JI
And who is the most beautiful for 100 kilometers?
You, Your Highness.
How about 1000 kilometers?
/ You, Mr. Queen.
And 10 thousand kilometers?
And all over the world?
/ Still you, Lord Queen.
Do you think I'm stupid?
At the very least, lie smarter.
No, no.
I'm just trying to keep you from getting upset.
Do you know?
Telling the truth won't make me angry.
Seriously?
I, Queen Shi Ji, my beauty is indeed charming,
but I know there is always someone more beautiful.
Please ask then.
Am I the most beautiful of them all?
/ No.
Fair enough.
Am I the most beautiful for 10 thousand kilometers?
/ No.
How about 1000 kilometers?
How about 100 kilometers?
/ No.
10 kilometers?
Am I the most beautiful on this mountain?
No.
You bastard!
There are no other women on this mountain.
I am a woman too.
You promised you wouldn't be angry.
You are prettier than me?
Please!
/ It's so annoying!
Demon, show yourself!
Who are you calling a demon?
The real one is Queen Shi Ji.
Damn brat.
Have we met?
What do you want?
Your demonic energy could be discovered.
Leave it to me.
Don't interfere.
You think you can beat me?
This whole mountain is my body.
Just see how you destroy me.
If you force your strength any more,
your body will be destroyed!
I said,
don't interfere!
It's started!
Wow!
I'm finished.
Luckily there was still some left.
I will live to fight again.
Damn brat.
Just you wait.
Nine-Dragon Fire Trap!
Can't escape!
Oh my!
Reckless boy.
Your body is almost gone.
Do you want to commit suicide?
What was that fire?
Isn't Nezha
an ice wizard?
Who... said that?
Ice, fire, I taught him everything.
Its power is
combination of ice and fire.
/ Is that possible?
Mutiara Roh is blessed with unparalleled talent.
Don't judge her by normal standards.
Who among us is a teacher?
Do you think you know better than me?
/ I wouldn't dare.
However,
I do feel the presence
that powerful demonic energy earlier.
About that...
Shi Ji must be the one who released the demonic energy.
/ What did you say, fatty?
I don't...
Are you the one who released that energy?
Tell me, is that true?
Say it!
/ Yes, it is me.
Don't shake me.
I'm going to throw up!
See? I told you.
Nezha, you have passed three levels.
Today, I personally recite
Ascension Mantra to you.
I've experienced all of this before.
Maybe I was too nervous.
The Ascension Mantra took longer than I remembered.
From now on,
you are the god of the Chan Sect.
This is Yu Xu's Treasure Vault
home to all kinds of rare magical items.
Reparo miracle drug.
You can only choose one.
Don't you need to think about it first?
/ Reparo miracle drug.
VISITORBET
►HIGHEST 1.3% SLOT REBATE IN INDONESIA◄
►find us on Google: VISITORBET◄
Yu Xu Palace has sent an envoy
to tell the 12 Gods
about what the dragon did.
However, due to the great distance,
My brothers and sisters couldn't get here any faster.
This time, I'm leading the hunt myself.
against the dragons.
Nezha,
Are you willing to fight with me?
Let me go back to Jalur Chentang first.
Then we will avenge the actions of the Dragon King.
Okay.
With your extraordinary combat abilities,
you will be of great help
in destroying the Dragon Palace.
I have paid off
all my debts to you.
Wait.
When I get my body back,
I'll go to the Dragon Palace with you, how about that?
You know exactly what I'm going to do.
Your presence there will only make things difficult.
Next time we meet,
we are enemies not friends.
Ugh...
This is Karma.
No, you don't go!
Your soul will be shattered
before you reach the Dragon Palace.
Nine-Dragon Fire Trap!
Can you calm down?
Leaving now
won't change anything.
Don't bother me.
Let me out!
No.
I promised Nezha.
I will save you no matter what.
Dad! Dad!
Suffocating!
GIVE SUPPORT AT
trakteer.id/broth3rmaxSUB
DRAGON PALACE REMAINS
Who's that?
I'm so tired.
Ao Guang, do you admit guilt?
So,
did you know?
Is Ao Bing still alive?
I will accept whatever punishment you give,
but please forgive my son.
Nonsense!
The Heavenly Palace ordered
your clan to hold back the monsters.
Not even colluding with them
and massacred the Chentang Line.
What?
The dragons have committed unforgivable crimes.
Today,
justice will be upheld.
Covering the earth and the sky.
Release the boundless power.
Let Tianyuan rise and stand tall.
Have full power over them all.
Open the Crater!
Show yourselves!
What have you done
to the Chentang Line?
Didn't you tell us?
to obey Master Shen's orders?
Shen Gongbao?!
Speaking of emergencies,
you have to focus on the present.
My king, we can't just sit here
waiting to die!
If I join the fight,
the Restraining Seal will...
Just leave it to us.
Combine all our strengths,
we can hold it long enough.
Good.
I'm fed up!
You pathetic ghost!
This is a once-in-a-thousand-years chance
for revenge.
Get out of this purgatory!
Destroy the Dragon Palace!
Soul Sword!
Old fool!
Taste my sword!
Releasing demonic energy like this...
Aren't you afraid of exposing your own identity?
I told you,
if you dare to harm the Chentang Pass,
I will destroy your palace to pieces!
Say it!
Is Ao Bing dead?
Hurry! Move!
Rise!
Any last message before you die?
Just see how long your body can take it.
I don't care whether I live or die.
As long as you die!
Now is the time!
Look at the consequences of your actions!
What mass extermination do you want?
The chain.
Even the Dragon King of the East Sea
is no match for your strength.
I was right all this time.
You are exactly what the Chan Sect needs.
Your parents spent their entire lives fighting crime.
From now on,
you must carry on their legacy.
and destroy all demons.
Let me avenge your loss
by turning all these bastards into pills.
Control me!
/ Yes, teacher!
Nezha!
/ Nezha!
Dad!
Nezha!
/ Ibu!
Son, are you okay?
Your body...
I I...
They already know
about you and Ao Bing.
I I...
I think...
will never meet you again.
The teacher was still chanting the mantra.
We have to buy as much time as possible.
Nezha, it wasn't my father who slaughtered the Chentyang Pass.
The real culprit
it is him, God Wuliang!
Shieldos!
For naga.
Brother,
Long time no see.
Why are you here?
Shen Gongbao,
You are in cahoots with the dragons.
What are you planning?
I should be the one asking... you.
You're the one who caught my father.
What are you planning?
Who said I caught your father?
Only you know the condition of my family.
If you don't give that order,
why are Nezha and the Demon Hunters
hunting my father?
And my brother was injured by an arrow...
That's clear
caused by your disciple, Deero!
There are candidates that I recruited myself.
Nothing can escape you.
After all, I've been doing all
your dirty work for years.
I can also guess your purpose here
acting up on Chentang Trail.
You want to trap... trap the dragons,
don't you?
Is this how you repay me,
your brother and mentor?
You always use me...
for your own gain.
Between you and me,
there is only hatred, not gratitude.
Can I make a deal with you?
God Teacher.
As the overseer of Yu Xu Palace,
You must know the spell to
release the Sea-Stabilizer Chain.
I do know,
then why?
You... you want to rebel?
A thousand years ago, the four of us
fought against the heavenly realm together.
So who betrayed us and
throw us into purgatory?
Now Wuliang is targeting Ao Guang,
that's clearly what we want.
I have long heard that God Wuliang
recruits candidates without favoritism.
I believe you know very well what we can do.
If you can free us from purgatory
and help us achieve eternity,
We are ready to provide service.
Plus the secret of the Spirit Pearl and the Demon Orb.
Spirit Pearls and Devil Balls?
/ How sad!
Where... where is your enthusiasm to reply?
We were young and knew nothing!
A thousand years of imprisonment
has taught us about the rules
and its rulers.
Very clever.
But you guys are so unpredictable.
How can I trust you guys?
Unless you let me give you...
We are ready.
The three dragons were willing to agree
to let Wuliang curse them.
If they try to disobey in the future,
Wuliang could take their lives at any time.
Wuliang then fulfilled his promise,
freeing them from the Ocean Stabilizer Chains.
Whenever a power is found,
he orchestrated the massacre,
framed others,
and sent troops to capture them.
Menu Shen Gongbao,
He often did such tasks for Wuliang.
The reward was the opportunity
to join the Chan Sect.
This time, Wuliang came to destroy the Chentang Pass.
and trap the East Sea dragon.
One thing leads to another,
he eventually recruited tifa the dragon king.
and from them,
he knows the secret of the Demon Orb and the Spirit Pearl.
After that,
they intentionally left
2 survivors clueless
to tell the story of the events
that befell Yu Xu Palace.
Seeing no hope of breaking through,
Shen Gongbao had one plan.
He told the Yaksha to scare us,
then hid us in the drain.
Then, he waited for
the right moment to pick us up.
And you?
My family is gone.
There's nothing left for me to hold on to.
There!
The demons captured by the Demon Hunters
not what outsiders think,
changed his nature in Yu Xu Palace.
Instead, they were thrown
into the Tianyuan Crater by Wuliang.
refined into an immortality pill
to strengthen the power of the Chan Sect.
Brother,
How could you do such a cruel thing?
How...
how can you explain to our teacher?
and the teachings we have received?
Now that you know what Wuliang did,
You have to stop before it's too late.
Take him back to the palace
to receive the Great God's punishment.
The Demon Hunters were personally
trained by Master Wuliang.
You think a few words can turn us
against him?
It turns out,
My suspicions about the dragons were wrong all this time.
Release them!
Let me help you.
You betrayed us?
We learned that from you, sis.
In the past, in order to protect our people,
I have no other choice!
Well, in order to protect myself now,
I have no choice.
My king, wait for us!
Don't leave us!
/ My king, take us!
King! King!
You have all been betrayed!
Dragon King of the South Sea.
Dragon King of the North Sea.
Dragon Queen of the West Sea.
[AO QIN - AO RUN - AO SHUN]
Nephew,
now it's time to play with your uncle.
Feel my spear!
Feel my axe!
Feel my wheels!
Feel my wheel 100 times!
200 times!
300 times!
That's enough, huh?
Nonsense!
Not that much.
Your body is still unstable.
Don't push yourself.
Because of my mistake,
I am willing to give up my life to free the dragon.
Young and brave.
Let me play with you, kid.
Harassing a small child,
despicable and shameless!
Hey!
How dare you attack your teacher's brother!
Bullying an uncle,
eat pig's feet!
This isn't going to work.
This is messed up.
So let's make it even more chaotic.
How about steam?
Of course.
Finish them off!
Beware of sneak attacks!
There you are.
Be careful, it's me!
/ Sis?
Sorry.
Nezha!
Ah!
Surprise!
Hahaha!
Shapeshifting Spell?
Are you crazy?
/ You can't fool me.
Hmm.
What are you...
/ Code.
My older siblings' toenails are like my grandfather's toenails.
What?
/ You don't know the code.
Imposter! (Impostor).
So you're an Imposter!
Hard to believe!
You deserve that.
Hmm.
Code.
Eh... Grated coconut, scratched head?
Wrong!
The correct one is "My older siblings' toenails
are like my grandfather's toenails"
and my grandfather's nails are stiff".
I'm the real one!
How come I don't know this code?
We just made it up!
Can't you make it easier?
It's so hard!
You idiot!
Don't come near me!
Imposter!
I'm the real Ao Shun!
/ Lie! You don't know the code!
You don't know either!
That's right.
Does that mean I'm an Imposter too?
Oh my god.
Tai Chi flows in divine harmony.
The five elements are perfectly aligned.
The true fire of Samadhi ignites gold.
One perfect pill, its power revealed.
Go and Rise!
What are you afraid of?
We're used to soaking in lava
as if we don't feel anything.
Hot! Hot!
Oh no!
This is the true fire of Samadhi.
What do you see?
If anyone has to eat this,
it's me!
It's also delicious.
Let go of my father!
Hey!
/ Freeze!
What a great Spirit Pearl!
A perfect match for the Devil's Ball.
Ao Bing!
Hyah!
Frozen!
Ah!
The Heart-Piercing Curse.
Since I already know your identities,
How could I not have a backup plan?
This is impossible!
The curse is quite complicated.
When can you cast it?
Oh...
That's why the Ascension Mantra is so long.
You inserted something.
You old fart!
Even the Devil's Ball
won't be able to escape
the Heart-Piercing Curse that quickly.
A thousand thorns have pierced your veins.
Struggling at any time
will only result in your body
torn.
No wonder I can't feel the aura of life.
You guys are petrified.
But still alive.
Just hurt Nezha.
Pearl of the Spirit
and the Devil's Ball
is a valuable asset.
I can treat you well
but now it is only made into pills.
Ao Bing!
Dad!
/ You...
you are still alive!
Uh!
The Heart-Piercing Curse was cast by Wuliang.
And it was he who massacred the Chentang Pass
, trapping it as if it was the work of the dragons.
Father, Nezha has been deceived.
Don't blame him.
/ Whatever you want to do, do it to me.
Don't bother my parents.
Killing you won't change anything.
We are all condemned to die here.
If anyone still holds a grudge,
please go ahead.
Brother, the Chan Sect has a noble reputation,
How could you do something so cruel?
Don't make the same mistake again!
Why don't you just go back
and confess to Master?
I will ask for forgiveness on your behalf.
You...
you idiot who's talking nonsense!
Should the place of the gods in this world be secured?
or you lazy ungrateful people
who are half-hearted like the demons,
I will not waste
my time and effort all this time!
Even though this will result
in my destruction
and my own humiliation,
I do this
for the eternal power of the Chan Sect.
Conscience...
My conscience is clear.
Another one is ripe.
I can't eat it anymore.
You should try it.
Thank You.
When my fins are cooked,
you should try them too.
The chicken feet are also cooked.
We can exchange and share.
What is this?
My body...
He became a pill!
I'm still very young.
I don't want to die.
No, let me out.
Please!
Stay calm!
Focus on your energy!
Hang on as long as you can.
Son!
Your power is greater than father's.
You can get through this.
If you can hold out
until this heart-piercing curse disappears,
you may have a chance to escape.
The heart-piercing curse
takes at least 6 hours to cast.
I'm scared,
I won't be able to last that long.
My wife.
/ Mother!
Wake up, mom.
Nezha, Nezha?
Nezha.
/ I'm here, ma'am.
You guys don't give up.
Don't worry about us.
Try to
Stay focused.
/ I'm fine, ma'am.
I don't feel the fire.
Nobody can kill you, son.
If I'm right,
the fire of the Devil's Ball and the true fire of Samadhi
originally the same.
Then this Tianyuan Cauldron cannot harm you.
That's right.
I am wrong.
Don't bother.
This is just my avatar.
As I suspected, the Devil's Ball
indestructible.
No wonder the Great God had to
destroy you with the Wrath of Heaven.
Nezha,
I see you are a good boy.
How about I give you a chance
to prove it?
Forgetful Pill.
Eat this.
and I will release your parents.
What do you think?
Maybe I'm cruel,
but I always keep my promises.
Otherwise, those ghostly bigwigs
will not swear allegiance to me.
As long as you eat this,
I swear to the Heavens,
I will not harm your parents.
What are you doing?
Using the lives of parents
to threaten a child?
And you call yourself a god?
You don't even deserve to be human.
Nezha, just leave us alone.
You have to stay alive.
Hang in there until the heart-piercing curse is gone
or your two brothers are looking for you.
You think I can't kill the Demon Ball?
It's just a matter of time.
Once you die,
I have hundreds of ways to destroy him.
I just don't want to die in vain.
Why don't you just let me eat it?
Why did mom forbid it?
If you sacrifice your life for our lives,
Do you think we will be able to live in peace?
Nezha.
No, ma'am.
It will hurt you.
/ It's okay.
This is the end.
Mom just wants to hug you one last time.
This.
I don't think I'll be able to see you grow up.
From now on,
You have to determine your own path.
I... I'm useless.
Useless.
I was born as a devil,
and always make you suffer.
I really want to,
make you proud.
This is all my fault.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Forgive me.
Every day I'm with you,
I am so happy.
I never cared
are you a god
or the devil.
What I know
you are my son.
Mother
will always
loving...
Nezha, stay calm!
Stop!
Your body could be torn apart!
What True Samadhi has given in return
the need for fire to re-form the body.
Nezha's physical form
it's whole now!
Dad,
Take care of your mother.
Help me get through this crater!
Oh no!
They absorbed the energy of Tianyuan Crater!
Maximum Roots!
Demon Hunter, by my command,
proceed!
Dad, you have to save your energy
for self-protection.
We've been backwards for too long.
We thought if we gave up everything,
Wuliang would let us live.
But in the end, they still want us dead.
If that's what they want,
then we will fight them to the death!
Yes, let's fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Don't let them out!
Don't give up!
Hang in there!
han...curious...
right!
The crater!
My pit!
That is the foundation of the Chan Sect!
Kill all these bastards!
Attack!
You ungrateful traitor.
Can't tell right from wrong!
Dragon Wave Roars!
So his two henchmen are monsters too.
Demon, god...
it's all part of your trick!
You lowly, despicable person.
How dare you defy me!
Witness my true power!
I will give you both
one last chance because
I am a valuable candidate.
Surrender now
and I will grant you immortality.
To hell with eternity!
I am all demons.
So why?
You claim to be a guiding light,
but all you do is bully the weak,
and bring chaos to the world.
You are the real evil!
You idiot, you don't know anything,
the god who rules the world.
Sideing with those in power
is the only way out.
Whether you accept it or not,
there is nowhere for you to run.
If there is no purpose to go,
I will pave my own way!
If not accepted,
I will return it!
Teacher!
My face...
You guys...
stupid brats have
broken my Eternal Youth Spell!
Old fart.
Camp... back to the palace.
Wait for me!
My father plans to lead the dragons
deep into the ocean to hide.
Now that your identity has been revealed,
why don't you come with us?
No.
All my life I have been hiding,
hide oneself
until there is nowhere to run.
Now I finally know
how to face this world.
Wuliang is one of the most powerful gods
and trusted by the Great God.
Maybe he didn't fall that easily.
Besides, gods and demons
walk on different paths.
like fire and water.
God, ghost...
All just an excuse to control
those who are different.
So what?
Do you think you can change that?
I want to try.
Maybe I'm too old
to fight against the world.
Ao Bing.
Dad knows
after you decide,
you will always continue.
My son, in the past,
father put a heavy burden on you,
never care what you think.
Dad apologizes.
Dad just wants to use my experience
to give you a good life.
But now dad knows,
The experiences of the older generation
are just the past,
and may not be right for you.
You have to walk your own path.
From now on,
follow your heart.
I knew you would come back.
/ Why?
Because we are both too young.
Too young to be afraid.
broth3rmax, 23 Maret 2024
THERE'S A BONUS SCENE?
WE JUST WAIT
broth3rmax, 23 Maret 2024
NO RESYNC/EDIT/RE-UPLOAD
INSTAGRAM @broth3rmax
TELEGRAM: t.me/broth3rmax_chat
FOR ADVERTISING ONLY, WA 087814427939 (NEW)
IF YOU WISH TO SUPPORT AT
trakteer.id/broth3rmaxSUB
VISITORBET
►HIGHEST 1.3% SLOT REBATE IN INDONESIA◄
►WE WILL PAY NO MATTER WHATEVER YOU WIN◄
►search us on Google: VISITORBET◄