Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
We knew that they would come for us.
Like they always had before.
We tried to warn the others
that they would come for them too.
Because we knew how far they would go.
Four years ago, I was fasting in the bush.
I saw that a swarm of giant mosquitos
would be coming for us.
I also saw that a person, a guardian,
would come from the north to help us.
We heard stories about
this place called Bigstone.
We thought this person
could lead us there.
This is Cree land.
You're Cree?
Do you speak Cree?
Were you tracking her?
I think she might be okanaweyihcikew.
Find out everything you can on her. Hurry.
I need to talk to the
Elders and the leaders.
Wait.
No.
Our search may be over.
You were so busy playing around while
there was a battle going on,
you didn't notice her coming.
Just like your farts.
Welcome Niska.
Get her some food.
I was woken up
to come and meet this woman.
Where is she?
There she is.
From Kiskachewanohk.
Niska come.
I am glad to meet you.
Long ago, we were told that someone
would be arriving from the north.
We have been waiting
for you for a long time.
You are the guardian.
And now we will dance.
Two more children have been brought back
along with one of our own. Welcome.
You are welcome here
in Kitsaki, Niska.
Come. Get some rest.
Welcome Niska.
Waseese is in an evil place.
The kids are trained to become
Jingo puppets.
They are subjected to unspeakable things.
Wouldn't you rather talk to Waseese?
We can get her from the Academy.
But there is one thing
we ask of you in return.
We need you to take the children
to a safe zone up north.
No, it's real.
And we need someone
to take the children there.
We look at these rocks as
life forms, similar to the trees.
This reflects how we see and think.
This is a balsam tree.
We use them in many different ways.
What are you doing here?
You better go convince her then.
Come in.
All of our relations are meeting here.
We need to do this in a good way
and think in a good way.
Thank you grandmother.
We must evacuate the camp
children by tonight.
The Jingoes have built a new mining road
overnight that is heading
straight for our camp.
We're concerned that we've run
out of time for the raid.
We want to help but they've advanced much
faster than what we thought.
Long ago, our grandfathers were here.
They all lived here.
But then this government
forced us to leave.
They even tried to kill us.
But they could not do it.
We are still here.
The goose is never alone on a journey.
In order to succeed,
she always travels with a partner.
This is what we also have to do as people.
Thank you grandmother.
Niska, do we agree or not?
Somonis, prepare the
camp. Leo and Charlie,
you'll raid tonight for the last time.
Run!
Any sign of them?
How many?
Twenty...
I'll get the kids out.
You lead the line.
No.
The kids need protection.
You can do this.
Nothing makes me more proud
than to stand with you all.
If we take our last breaths fighting
against our colonizers,
then it will be a good way to die.
Somonis will lead the line.
Give me enough time to get them out.
It was her mother that brought her to us.
All the way down from the north.
She came back to her people
to protect us on that day.
We call her the guardian.