Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[intense music playing]
[female voice] We're all around you.
Living right under your noses…
and you have no idea.
Things were a lot simpler in the old days.
We hunted you,
and you hunted us.
In Los Angeles,
no one fought harder
than a place called Boyle Heights.
So, we struck up a truce
to maintain the peace
between our kind and yours.
We lived in secret,
and you convinced yourselves
you had never really believed.
You forgot to be afraid.
You made books and movies about us
and got most of the details wrong,
while we became richer
and more powerful
than you could ever imagine.
To this day, there are some
who still uphold the truce,
who keep our secret.
As long as we stick to the three rules.
Don't let humans know we exist,
don't feed on the unwilling,
and never ever enter Boyle Heights
without permission.
[car revving]
[footsteps approaching]
-[whirring]
-[woman humming]
[timer buzzing]
[breathes deeply]
[humming]
-[gasps] Jay!
-Sorry.
-[sighs] You scared me.
-[Jay] I got distracted.
[woman] How sorry?
I'll-make-it-up-to-you sorry.
Oh, you'll-make-it-up-to-me kind of sorry.
How are you gonna do that?
[gentle music playing]
[woman chuckling] What?
Nah, you look nice.
I look nice?
[chuckling] You're so stupid.
[car revving]
What the--
-What is it?
-[Jay] They shouldn't be over here.
[revving]
[tires screeching]
-Oh my God. Jay, who is that?
-[car revving]
[Jay] A dead man.
[woman] Put the gun back.
We cannot do this.
Holy shit, please keep driving. Jay.
Jay, it's green, just go!
-[revving]
-[tires squealing]
[squealing]
[tires screeching]
-[woman] Jay, what's going on?
-[Jay] I gotta warn my guys.
I need you to take the car
and go to your brother's. Okay?
[shuddering]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[knocks on window]
-[gasps]
-[glass shatters]
-[screams]
[tense music playing]
Maria!
[music continues]
[panting]
[man speaking indistinctly on film]
[snoring]
-[claps]
-[gasps]
Good morning, Mr. Perez.
What were you dreaming about?
Sorry. I… [inhales sharply]
[woman giggling]
[kisses]
[upbeat music playing]
[skateboard wheels squealing]
[music continues]
[birds chirping]
Hey, uh, B-plus, 60 bucks.
Thank you, sir.
You're a lifesaver, you know that?
You're saving my ass with this paper, bro.
We're gonna check out
this club downtown, Three Kings?
Table, bottle service.
-Right.
-It's 300 a head. You wanna roll with?
Shit, 300 a head? Uh…
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nah, I already got some stuff
I gotta get into.
-I bet you do.
-Next time, my bad.
[man] All right. Stay easy.
[upbeat music playing]
[Benny] Yo!
Yo, what's good, Benny?
Hey, what's up, slick?
You got that kit for me?
Let's call it an even 40, bro.
40, like 40 bucks?
-That's what I said.
-[sighs]
[Benny] I'mma put The Heights
on the map. I'm telling you, bro.
Step one, finish this track.
Two, set up the label.
Three, world domination. It's simple.
Building an empire,
but you can't even play me one track, bro?
[laughs]
[Benny] Hey.
When it's ready, it's ready, all right?
[upbeat music continues]
-[chattering on TV]
-[sizzling]
[woman in Spanish] Hello, Benny.
Hey, Grandma.
[Grandma] You came at a good time.
[Benny in English] Yeah? Why's that?
[Grandma in Spanish] I just took out
some flautitas and some empanadas.
[Benny in English] Nice!
[Grandma in Spanish] Are you hungry?
[Benny in English] You know it.
[in Spanish] But why do I bother shopping
if you're never
going to cook me a sancoche?
You know I don't cook that.
You know that one of these days
I'm going to buy you a house.
[groans] I don't need
my own home, my love.
What I do need is for you
to finish your studies
so you can take care of yourself.
[in English] Because someday
I'm gonna die, and so will you.
Ay, Ma, why you gotta talk like that?
So negative. I don't like it.
[in Spanish] Well, that's life, son.
We all come tumbling down.
[hip-hop music playing on headphones]
[birds chirping]
[music continues over speakers]
[Jay, muffled] Bro, you told me
you could handle it.
No, I told you. This is--
Come on, Jessie,
you're really gonna do me like that?
I need someone to cover the car tonight.
It's about Maria.
Yeah, well, I thought I could rely on you!
Yeah, fine, whatever.
Why are you creeping?
If I'd know you was coming through,
I would've rolled out the red carpet.
I have to pick up some things,
check in on Grandma.
-Check in on your punk ass.
-Ha.
Oh, wait a minute. What's this?
Bro, that some gray hairs on your head?
Hey, I'm serious.
You're getting old, papi.
-Just wait. It's gonna happen to you too.
-[laughs]
I don't know if you're working tonight,
but maybe we could go to Mario's,
grab a pizza, watch the game.
[Jay] I got something else tonight.
All right,
then who's covering the car, then?
[Jay] I had to cancel.
Everyone's booked up.
All right, but you see,
I was thinking, like, what if,
you see, what if I take the car? Right?
-'Cause I could use the money.
-No way.
-Why not?
-[Jay] One, you're a bad driver.
Bad… That's bullshit.
When was the last time
you were west of K-Town?
Hey, Jay, my man, look,
I am way more responsible
than all them dudes
you got out there at the depot.
Yeah, except them dudes at the depot,
they got chauffeur's license,
they're insured by the company,
and they actually own a suit.
I… You see, the thing is, though,
Jay, I got a suit. I got a suit, Jay.
[scoffs]
What, you and Maria been fighting?
That's what it is?
You having some relationship issues?
If you want to talk to me,
you can talk to me.
I give great advice.
That's what people be saying.
-[Jay] Yeah, right.
-[chuckles]
Man, whatever.
[objects clattering]
Where'd you get that?
Don't worry about it.
[lock clicks]
-What's this thing you gotta do tonight?
-I said don't worry about it.
All right. Fine, man.
I didn't even… [mumbles]
-[sighs]
-[Benny] So secretive, man.
-[Jay] Hey, Benny.
-[keys jingle]
Scratch it, I'll kill you.
Yo. You serious?
Man! I'm gonna need me one of these.
You can't afford it.
Well, I'mma flip my beats,
and I'mma get me a better one.
-What do you think about that?
-Listen to me.
Take them where they need to go,
come straight back.
-[in Spanish] Understand?
-Yeah, I understand.
-[in English] Check it out.
-[engine starts]
Oh shit.
-That's pretty cool.
-[chuckles]
Insurance and registration
are in the glove compartment.
Chauffeur's license on the visor.
Everything's under my name,
so if anyone asks, you're me.
-I'm going to Beverly Hills?
-[Jay] Hey, pay attention.
If anyone asks, you're me, got it?
-Yeah.
-Dispatch says it's an all-nighter.
Probably a twentysomething
director wannabe high out of his mind.
Act professional, and he'll give you
a fat tip at the end of the night.
[hip-hop music playing]
Hey. Don't blow the sub, Dr. Dre.
Look, if the subs want to bark,
you gotta let 'em bark.
No, the subs don't wanna bark. Okay?
I'm serious. I'll yank you out of here.
-I'll take the no-show penalty.
-Okay. No barking, you got it.
Thanks for doing this.
Hey, just, um, be careful, all right?
I'm always careful.
["Got the Love" by Terrell Morris playing]
♪ Baby wanna walk, talk
And drink a little ♪
♪ Stop the talk… ♪
[laughing] I got… I got the car!
♪ You'll change the party ♪
♪ You'll wake up on me
I'll make you coffee ♪
♪ You'll come from… ♪
Huh? What?
♪ From visiting your people
On your spare time ♪
♪ Spend time showing you my best side ♪
-[horn honks]
-Oh!
That was a cop. That was a cop.
♪ You'll look even better
On my bedside, whoa ♪
♪ I could be the number
That you memorize ♪
What? I went in front of the guy!
♪ Maybe I got the love that'll lead to ♪
♪ A little more than actin' up in secret ♪
♪ I don't mind actin' up
In the street too ♪
♪ Baby, just take the plunge
And let T do it ♪
♪ Only I got the love
Got the love, got the love ♪
♪ To take you to your paradise ♪
♪ Only I got the love, got the love ♪
♪ That made you dance
Through Paris nights ♪
[sighs]
Wow. [exhales sharply]
Wow, wow.
[shoes squeak]
Okay. [sighs]
[chuckles softly]
Um, good… good evening, Miss Moreau.
You're the driver?
Uh, yeah. Yes. Yes, I am.
Miss Moreau is running a little bit late.
I'm her friend Blaire.
Okay, cool. I'm… I'm… I'm Jay.
Hi, Jay.
-[chuckles]
-Something wrong?
No.
Mm-mm.
What?
Your zipper is down.
Oh shit. [chuckles]
-[zipping]
-Wow.
[chuckles] Sorry, I… I… I don't…
I don't mean to be unprofessional.
I just… I should…
I had no idea that it was down.
-[Blaire] Okay. [chuckles]
-Yeah.
I'm just gonna stop talking 'cause I feel
like I'm making it worse now. [chuckles]
Well, how about you open the door for me,
and then maybe we can call it even?
Thanks.
[unlocks door]
[chuckles nervously]
Thanks. [chuckles]
You know, if you need me
to adjust anything, like the…
-like the AC, I… I can do that.
-Hmm?
Or… or more warm, if you're like…
if it feels chilly for you 'cause I know--
-Okay.
-You know, women's bodies--
Women's bodies?
I'm good. Thank you.
Like, I know
people get cold, so whatever--
Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah. I got you.
She's gonna be pissed
if you don't open the door for her.
Oh. [splutters]
You're right. My bad. Thanks.
[gentle music playing]
Hello, Miss Moreau.
I… I'm Jay. I'll be your driver tonight.
You're adorable.
Do you need help with your bags?
You don't look like a driver.
-[sighs]
-[door closes]
-Okay?
-[Moreau] Mm-hmm.
[door closes]
[chimes]
-[Benny] Uh…
-[chimes]
Are you sure you know
what you're doing there, Jay?
Um, no, I was just trying
to put the address in.
Except I haven't given you
the address yet, have I?
[chuckles]
Right. Yeah. I know.
[Moreau] We're hitting every one
of these parties tonight,
and we need to get
to the last stop by morning.
That's nonnegotiable.
Are we clear?
Yeah.
Oh, and Jay, can you turn the air on?
Yeah. Make it icy.
[mellow electronic music playing]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[sirens approaching]
Hey, driver. You wanna put on something
that doesn't suck?
[Benny] Yes, ma'am.
["Boom Boom Boom" by Cokah playing]
Actually, Jay…
let's play a game.
What would you do if you knew
tonight was your last night on Earth?
[Benny] Wow, uh… I never really thought
about it, to be honest.
-Okay. Well, think about it.
-[Moreau chuckles]
I mean, you must have some fantasies.
I don't… I don't really like
to think that way, you know.
Like, to fantasize?
Yeah, you know, it's like,
I'm doing things today.
I'm building things for the future.
You know what I mean?
-I'm not sure you understand how to play.
-[Benny] I do. What I'm trying to say is--
Last night on Earth, Jay.
Drugs, women, men,
old enemies you're just waiting to pop.
[chuckles] Nah, sorry,
I'm a pretty chill guy.
You know,
I go to school, live with my abuela--
[Blaire] You live with your abuela?
-Yeah. [chuckles]
-[Blaire] That's cute.
New game. Fuck, marry, kill.
Me, Blaire, your abuela.
S… sorry, what?
-I know you know this game.
-No, I do. I… I know this game.
It's just, you know,
I'm trying to be professional.
-Look, Blaire. Me, the Pope, the driver.
-[scoffs] You're not even trying.
-[Moreau] Personally, I would bang me.
-Fine. Okay, you could get it.
Kill the Pope, which I guess
puts me marrying Jay, the driver.
-He seems like husband material.
-[Moreau] You hear that, driver?
Come on, fess up.
Me, Blaire, your grandma.
I'd definitely kill you.
Finally, he bites back.
Maybe he's not a total dud.
I don't know. Maybe not.
Hey, driver. Keep your eyes on the road.
["Boom Boom Boom" continues]
♪ That DJ wrong for playin' that song ♪
♪ He dun turned her on like
Boom boom boom ♪
♪ Yo… dead wrong
She dropped that thong ♪
♪ In the club for a random… ♪
♪ Who she a chat to
What she a chat 'bout ♪
♪ About to get hit like
Boom boom boom ♪
♪ Huh sis, what sis, you so childish ♪
♪ Boom boom boom ♪
[dance music playing in distance]
[indistinct chatter]
Thanks.
[Benny] Some party.
You wouldn't know a party
if it fucked you in the face.
[trilling]
[car pulling up]
[car door opens, closes]
What's up, G?
What's the word?
Three generations deep,
and I'm the one to break the peace.
That's on him. Not us.
Victor knows we're off-limits.
He's starting a war with Boyle Heights.
He took Maria… to get to me.
-There's no turning back.
-[sighs]
[Jay] We have until tomorrow morning.
After that,
either Victor's dead, or we are.
[gun cocking]
Let's go put this work in.
[cars approaching]
[woman screaming]
[gasps]
[breathes deeply]
[metal clinks on ground]
[mysterious music playing]
-["Fast (Motion)" by Saweetie playing]
-[Moreau] Back in the car, driver!
-♪ Fast, I'm coming in fast ♪
-♪ Uh-huh ♪
-♪ First place, you coming in last ♪
-♪ That's right ♪
♪ I'm hitting that, hitting that gas ♪
-♪ I'm hitting that, hitting that ass ♪
-♪ My body ♪
-♪ I'm coming in fast ♪
-♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ First place, you coming in last ♪
♪ I'm hitting that, hitting that gas… ♪
[both laughing, speaking indistinctly]
Yo, Jay.
You want some?
Uh, I… I can't really do that.
-Sorry.
-[Moreau] You can't?
-[Benny] I can't.
-That's boring.
-[drink splashes]
-[both laughing]
Zoé!
-That's gonna be a fine.
-[Zoé] Oh, there's a fine?
-[Benny] Yeah.
-Don't worry, driver. We can afford it.
♪ I put it in motion ♪
♪ I put it in, I put it in ♪
♪ I put it in motion ♪
♪ Iciest bitch in the whole damn land ♪
♪ I hit the road in an all-white Lam' ♪
♪ I keep a fresh set up on my hands ♪
♪ You don't like me, but you on my 'Gram ♪
♪ How you look, how you look
How you sound, ho? ♪
♪ I'm a boss, I'm a brat, hard to handle ♪
♪ I'm a real life mood, a real life muse ♪
♪ Got some pretty-ass toes in my sandals ♪
♪ I can't help, I was born like this ♪
♪ Ain't my fault that you want my drip ♪
♪ Little bitter bitch
Could have been my friend ♪
♪ Now you gotta listen
While I pop my shit ♪
-♪ Fast, I'm coming in fast ♪
-♪ Uh-huh ♪
-♪ First place, you coming in last ♪
-♪ That's right ♪
♪ I'm hitting that, hitting that gas ♪
-♪ I'm hitting that, hitting that ass ♪
-♪ My body… ♪
Stay.
See you soon.
♪ I'm hitting that, hitting that gas ♪
♪ I'm hitting that, hitting that ♪
♪ Locomotion ♪
[door closes]
[pen scratching on paper]
[phone vibrating]
[breathes deeply]
[suspenseful music playing]
[vibrates]
[phone clatters]
[phone keys clacking]
[line ringing]
[Jay on recording] Hey, it's Jay.
Leave a message.
-[beeps]
-[sighs]
Yo, it's Benny. Um, look,
I don't know what you're up to,
but, um, I… I think there's
something… something weird going on,
and just whenever you get a chance,
just hit me back, aight?
Serious.
[breathes deeply]
[sighs]
Whoa.
[panting]
[whispering] What the… Oh my…
Oh, no, no, no. [chuckles]
[suspenseful music playing]
No, no, no.
[siren chirps]
[music continues]
[bag thuds]
[indistinct chattering on police radio]
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
[indistinct chattering on police radio]
[panting]
[officer] Hey!
[indistinct chatter in distance]
[Muzak playing]
[elevator dings]
[indistinct chatter]
[concierge] How may I help you, sir?
Hi. Uh…
-Sir, you are sweating.
-[Benny] Oh.
-Is everything all right?
-Yeah, yeah.
-I, um… I was just…
-Mm-hmm.
-I… I was outside and--
-What's that on your shirt?
-Huh?
-Your shirt.
I…
I… I got, um…
This is a members-only establishment,
so perhaps I should call somebody.
-No, no, no, I'm fine. It's just--
-It's okay. It'll just be one second.
No, no, no, no, hey, hey.
It's… it's okay. I just… I, um…
[inhales deeply] Please accept
my most sincere apology, sir.
[chuckles]
May I?
Yeah.
Mmm. Will you be meeting anyone upstairs?
[Benny] Mm-hmm, yeah. I, um…
I'm… I'm meeting the… the two girls,
uh, Blaire and… and… and… and Zoé.
Of course, sir.
They're with Daniel and Max as we speak.
The owners, sir.
-Great.
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
-Allow me to escort you to the elevator.
-Mm-hmm, yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
Please, I don't…
I don't… I don't have all day.
[Muzak playing]
[cranks, clicks]
[cranks, clangs]
[whirring]
[Muzak continues]
Should you need anything at all,
there's a phone located in your room
that links directly to my desk.
Myself or a member of my staff
will be happy to assist you.
[elevator dings]
[eerie music plays]
And, please, drink responsibly.
[ominous music playing]
[slurping]
Hey.
H… hey.
-This isn't what it looks like.
-Okay. I'm just…
-[grunts]
-[roars]
[panting, shuddering]
[Zoé] Oh my God.
He's shaking.
[laughing] I love it when they shake.
It's so cute.
-[grunting]
-Max over there tasted like motor oil.
[chuckles]
I bet Jay gives good blood.
-Don't you, Jay?
-[gasping]
[splutters] I'm not Jay.
-What?
-[splutters] I'm not Jay. My name's Benny.
I'm just… I'm his brother.
I'm just covering for him. [splutters]
[grunts]
I knew it.
What did I tell you?
I knew this little shit
couldn't be Jay Perez.
[sighs]
All right. [inhales deeply]
Let's drink the driver.
What? No, no, no, no.
-I don't know. He could come in handy.
-Handy for what?
I don't need someone
to hold the door for me tonight.
-[Benny] No.
-[Blaire] Wait, wait.
I bet he could take us to Jay.
Benny, do you think you could do that?
You think you could show us
where your brother is?
[chuckling] That was great.
[laughs]
Oh, is he okay?
Hey, Max, buddy!
-Did they go a little too hard on you?
-You had one thing to do.
-Just one.
-I know. I'm sorry.
I got a little distracted
because someone walked in on us.
[Daniel] Max!
Hey, what's wrong with him?
Max.
-What… what did you do?
-Max?
Hey, Max. You okay?
[in deep voice] Yeah, man, I'm fine.
I'm living my best life.
Are you crazy? Is he…
-Is he--
-He's dead. Yes, Daniel.
Yes, he's dead.
I killed him.
-No, you can't do this.
-[Zoé] No?
We're protected. This place is protected!
You're protected?
How protected do you feel right now?
Hmm? [laughs]
Blaire, finish your drink.
We're running behind schedule.
-Hey. You stupid bitches.
-[Zoé] Mmm.
They're gonna come after you for this.
The bosses will burn you alive.
-Oh.
-[Daniel] Yeah.
-You can't kill in here. It's off-limits.
-[laughs]
Oh, are those the rules?
You can't. You're gonna ruin this place.
Well, that's the point.
No more happy endings.
-[clangs]
-No, wait, hey!
Wait, no, no, no. Don't, please, wait.
You can't kill me.
You can't. What about the truce?
-The truce is dead, handsome.
-Wait. Wait. [groans]
[Blaire slurping]
[panting]
Hey, uh, officer, listen. Um, I…
I need… I need your help. I… I got this…
It's an emergency.
There's these two women, right?
-And they're after me and--
-Two women?
-Mm-hmm.
-After you?
Yeah, I've been… I've been driving them
around all night, but I think that's--
Is there anything
you want to tell me about, son?
-No, listen, I'm trying--
-How much have you had to drink tonight?
-I haven't drank anything.
-Any drugs?
-No drugs.
-Weapons on you?
Listen, there's
this secret floor in there, okay?
There's this crazy shit
that's going on in there.
I need you to call backup.
I need you to call everyone, call--
Exactly what'd you see up there?
[panting]
They killed these two guys, all right?
They were drinking their blood, man.
Okay, that's enough.
Put your hands behind your back.
Put your hands behind your back!
Hey!
Come on. Take… take me to jail right now.
Get me… get me out of here. [grunts]
Mm-hmm. Let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa. No, no.
-What happens upstairs stays upstairs.
-No. Okay.
-You should know better.
-Yeah, I'm not gonna say--
-Get in the trunk. In the trunk!
-I won't say nothing!
-I'm not gonna say anything!
-Excuse me, Officer Anderson.
You girls.
Yes, us girls.
This kid is saying
you killed two men upstairs.
-That can't be right, right?
-[Blaire] Of course not.
Benny here has no idea what he saw.
Do you, Benny?
We just gave those boys
the best suck they're ever gonna get.
Let him go. He's ours.
[chuckles]
Yeah. Victor know about this?
What do you think, dipshit?
We're just making our collections.
Business as usual.
-Well, I didn't get a call.
-Oh, you didn't get a call?
Maybe you're not important enough
to get a call.
Yeah, maybe I should just call Victor now.
[Zoé] Why don't you do that?
I'm sure Victor would love to hear
from his favorite little piggy.
[Blaire] Hand him over.
[exhales]
Okay, all right. Fine.
[keys jingle]
[handcuffs click]
[Zoé] Go turn the car around.
Huh? Hey!
No more funny games.
[ominous music playing]
-[clicks]
-[liquid pouring]
[mechanical whirring]
[phone camera clicks]
[muffled] Wait! No.
Don't go! Wait! Don't leave!
[engine revving]
[sinister music playing]
[Zoé and Blaire laughing]
Yeah.
-Yeah, you count this out?
-[both laugh]
[speaking indistinctly]
[gulps]
[panting]
[heart beating]
[clicks]
[heart beating rapidly]
[grunts]
Back in the car, driver.
[Benny] Hmm.
[intense music playing]
[engine revving]
[music continues]
[somber melody playing]
Don't get up. I know where the bar is.
-What the hell are you doing here?
-I'm having a drink with my bosses, Eva.
Better make it a good one.
-It's gonna be your last.
-[Victor] I'll keep that in mind.
We told you what would happen
if you stepped foot in Boyle Heights,
and yet, here you are,
being reckless as ever.
Drinking blood cocktails
on white upholstery,
and I'm the reckless one?
[Eva] You need to remember your place,
Victor. You're middle management.
Give me one reason
why I shouldn't call Martin right now.
-Because I've had a change of heart.
-What heart?
I deserve that.
This view never gets old.
Yeah. But now we're gonna have to ruin it
with your dead body.
I should have let her do
what she wanted with you.
I wanted to barbecue you
the moment you fed outside the lines.
But Grace said that would be impulsive.
I think the word I used was tacky.
Well, I'm glad you didn't.
I know you've never trusted me,
never given me any real power.
But if you hadn't tried
to run me out of my own city,
I wouldn't be seeing so clearly now.
-Are you on something?
-You violated the truce.
It's the one thing that's kept
our kind safe all these years,
and you just pissed on it.
For years we've been told
who to feed on and where
and treating humans
like they're our equals.
It started to feel like a prison.
So I got frustrated
and did something impulsive.
Should we say
tacky?
[Eva] Tacky?
You fed where you weren't supposed to
and started a war with Jay Perez.
If he comes for us,
Boyle Heights will follow.
Do you like your fancy clothes
and your concrete mansion?
Because if we get exposed,
that all goes away. For all of us.
I know.
I put you two in a terrible position.
Do you think that I don't get frustrated?
Do you think that when my pool boy
leaves a leaf in the pool,
that I don't wanna string him upside down
and suck him dry?
But if I pitch a fit every time
somebody pisses me off,
what does that make me?
A man.
Stupid as shit.
Like I said.
I'm sorry.
No, a ban is a ban.
You're gonna have to do a lot better
than that if you want me to reverse it.
You know, forever is a very long time.
Give it 40, 50 years.
Who knows? Maybe this will blow over,
and you'll be able to come back.
[sighs] Oh, I think you've misunderstood.
I'm not going anywhere.
In fact, my girls
are down there right now,
ripping your entire network apart
one neck at a time.
So, everything you see belongs to me.
After I kill both of you, of course.
-Martin!
-[feedback squeals]
I, uh, think you might
have to speak up a little.
[laughs]
[Benny mumbling]
This is not real. This is…
Come on. She's here, then she's there.
[muttering]
-You need to calm down.
-Calm? Be calm?
-You want me to calm down?
-Yeah.
-I'm calm.
-Oh, you're calm?
-Yeah. This is me calm.
-This is you calm?
-You seem kind of worked up.
-What do you want me to do, huh?
I'm here… I'm here in this car with…
with you and whatever the hell you are.
-[scoffs]
-Oh. [scoffs]
-This is… this is stupid.
-Oh, wow.
-I… I honestly--
-So dumb.
I don't expect people to understand.
-It's a lot. It's a lot.
-Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, especially for you.
What is that supposed to mean, huh?
It means you're a kid.
Like, you…
You… you think majoring in economics
is gonna solve all your problems?
Do you think
that this is how the world works?
Okay. All right.
Well…
[sighs] Don't worry.
It'll all be over soon.
All over? All over? How?
Is… is my brother… is he like a, um…
No, it's not like that.
Then what's it like, then? What's it like?
Let's just say your people
and my people don't really get along.
Who do you think runs the city?
Cops?
Politicians?
We do.
We?
Right.
And… and our kind, like your kind,
answer to leaders.
All right.
There are five bosses that control
most of the major territories of LA.
-[chuckles] It sounds like the mob.
-Please. We're not amateurs.
Victor's, what, like, your boss?
Your boyfriend?
Oh, twist. Benny's the jealous type.
No, no, no. I just…
I don't… I don't know what's going on.
So, Zoé and Victor are together.
And then, Zoé's my girl.
So, she and I manage money
at the different businesses
and blood clubs.
-We manage the-- [chuckles]
-Blood clubs?
Yeah, but Victor's sick
of not having any real power,
so tonight, we're making our move.
The problem is you can't make a move
against one of the bosses
without the rest of them
coming for your head unless you--
Unless you take them all out
at the same time. Same night.
Exactly.
And… and my brother?
Jay's crew runs Boyle Heights.
They know what we are and how to kill us.
Victor thought he could use him.
Just turn Jay's crew loose on the bosses.
Jay kindly instructed him to go to hell,
which Victor didn't like very much,
so the plan was for us
to bring Jay to Victor
after all of this was done.
That was the plan
until you showed up.
So, Benny, you know
where your brother is tonight?
["To the Top (Remix)" by SUNDUR playing]
[unzipping bag]
Hey, no, you can't smoke that in here.
It's gonna…
It's gonna get in the leather.
[laughs]
That's funny.
Mmm.
You wanna hit this?
-Honestly, it might make you feel better.
-No, I'm… I'm okay.
Here. Let me.
♪ I'm heading to the top ♪
[exhales]
♪ All at once, it made my heart soar ♪
[Zoé] So, how did it go?
[Victor on phone]
Well, my shirt is ruined.
I think we might actually pull this off.
Yeah.
[Victor] Three bosses down.
[Zoé on phone] And two to go.
Ah, you should've seen
the looks on their faces.
[Zoé] I wish
I could've been there with you.
[Victor laughs]
So, how's Jay?
Yeah. [sighs]
About that.
I… I need to tell you something.
[Victor on phone] What is it?
We, um, got his little brother instead.
[groans]
[Zoé] I'm sorry. We didn't know.
It's okay, baby.
It's okay. We can use the brother.
Really?
[Victor] Really. It makes it more fun.
Think of him like insurance.
[Zoé] Okay, babe.
-Do you think he gives good blood?
-[Zoé chuckles] Yeah.
I think he gives real good blood.
I'll take care of Jay.
I don't want you to get distracted.
Clear downtown and Venice.
Then the city is ours.
We can't let them regroup after tonight.
[dramatic music playing]
You sure about this? I don't like him.
I don't even like breathing
the same air as this vato.
This is the only chance we got.
-[gun cocks]
-What if we don't know where Victor's at?
[Jay] Gio made Victor.
He'll know.
-I want him alive.
-All right.
[suspenseful music playing]
[car door closes]
[man] Shit.
What the hell happened in here?
["You Turn Me On" by Opus playing]
♪ We always get it on
And kept it goin' on so strong… ♪
Sweep the house.
Split up. Three and three.
[in Spanish] Watch out.
♪ 'Cause when you kiss my lips
So tenderly ♪
♪ You turn me on, girl ♪
♪ We always get it on
And kept it goin' on so strong, girl ♪
[suspenseful music playing]
Don't move. Move, I gotta put
this knife through your heart.
I don't think you want that, do you, Gio?
Right, baby. I don't want that.
Yo, what the hell happened to you?
[Gio] Oh, don't look at me.
I look hideous.
-You know what I need?
-[Jay] Hmm?
I need some blood.
Can you get me some blood, Jay?
First, you gotta tell me
where Victor's at tonight.
[Gio] That snake. [gasps]
He's coming for all of us.
[inhales] All the bosses.
All the territories.
He's clearing the board.
Victor did this?
[Gio] His girls did this.
-You know the ones.
-Haven't had the pleasure.
His little monsters
left me like this to suffer.
Hey. Hey, wake up.
Rise and shine, come on.
-[Gio] I'm awake.
-Where were they going?
I'll tell you if you give me some blood.
You gotta tell me what they said first.
Three Kings. [exhales]
Get the boys. We're going downtown.
But first, give me some blood!
-[screeching]
-[gun firing]
[whooshing]
[mysterious music playing]
[high-pitched whirring]
Can you hear that?
What did I just smoke? I…
I feel weird.
[Zoé] Angel dust.
-What?
-[Zoé] Relax.
-I'm joking.
-Are you?
Uh, maybe. Maybe not.
Ask Blaire. She rolled it.
That girl really needs to get laid.
Well, that's a different kind of service
than the one this car company offers, but…
[laughs] That's good, Benny.
Can I call you Benny Boy?
No.
You know, it's not your fault
that she likes you.
She likes everyone,
so don't feel special or anything.
[chuckles] Yeah, I know,
it's not… it's not like that.
I… I mean, I'm not…
I'm not saying she isn't attractive.
I'm just not really looking
for a relationship right now.
Is he looking at me?
Who?
[Zoé] The clerk.
I… I don't think so.
[Zoé] You sure?
Yeah, you know.
Nobody's looking at you, Zoé.
He's calling someone.
Zoé.
Zoé, chill, yo. Hey. Chill.
…three bodies appeared
to have been drained of all blood.
Wait.
[clerk] Just a slushy?
-Yeah, just the slushy.
-[clerk] Okay.
-Is that…
-Okay, that's gonna be two--
-[spits]
-[groans]
-[grunts]
-Who was on the phone?
-Do we really have to do this?
-Take the money!
Get out of here, okay?
I don't want any trouble!
You a tattletale?
-What? You're insane!
-[duct tape ripping]
-Get her off of me! Do something!
-Just do what she says, man.
-Who was on the phone?
-It was my mom!
Okay? She just wanted me to pick up
more cat food on the way home from work.
I swear to God. I just…
Jesus Christ, are those…
Shut him up!
Shut him up?
What do you mean, shut him up? No!
[muffled yelling]
-That's my girl. [laughs]
-[duct tape thuds]
-[register dings]
-[Blaire] Let's go.
[muffled whimpering]
[grunts]
What?
What is wrong with you?
You can't be alive for 200 years
and not go a little crazy.
[hip-hop music playing]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[dance music playing]
What should we do with Benny?
I mean,
we can't just leave him in the car.
Hey, so, um, listen,
I… I got this idea, right?
And I… I was thinking,
maybe why don't I just go?
You guys can just take the car,
and… and… and… and I'll find my way home.
I'll find a bus.
-It sounds like you're trying to ditch us.
-No, I'm not--
Hey, you know what? I actually think
that's a really smart idea.
Yeah?
[Zoé] Yeah.
Yeah. You know,
'cause, you know, all… all this shit,
I'm not gonna say nothing about all this.
I just think this is a time where I feel
like we should go our separate ways,
and… and believe me, it was…
it was great meeting you guys, you know.
-It was great meeting you too.
-And the secrets, they're safe with me.
-It's me, you know.
-Okay.
Well, if he says
he's not gonna say anything,
then we can trust him.
Right?
-Sweet. Uh, okay, great. I mean--
-[grunts]
You're gonna stick around
a little while longer, Benny Boy.
-[Benny coughs]
-[Zoé] We're not quite through.
You remember what I did
to that guy at the hotel?
[grunts softly]
I tore his neck open like a bag of candy.
If you do anything stupid inside,
I'll start stacking bodies.
I think what she's trying to say,
Benny, is we would love
if you came with us.
-Good?
-[whimpers]
-Fun! Fun!
-[sighs]
[club patrons shouting indistinctly]
Hey, uh, your friend over there?
Yeah, she's insane.
I'm talking next-level crazy.
Yeah. You wanna stay out of her way. Okay?
I gotta get out of here.
I can't do this shit.
I need you to be smart. All right?
If you do anything stupid,
like try and run or tell anyone about us,
I'm gonna have to kill you. Okay?
And I don't want to have to do that.
-Bruce!
-Hey.
You don't want to have to kill me.
Great, I mean, that's fantastic.
I'm looking out for you.
-You call this looking out for somebody?
-[woman] Benny! Come on.
-[Blaire] Hey.
-Excuse me. [grunts]
[indistinct conversation]
-Benny?
-Go on, man.
[man] Oh, no way.
Hey, um, do you think
you could help us out?
You know, tell them
that we're your friends.
Like, we're with you or something?
Please?
Sorry, I don't know. I… I just, uh…
He can't help you because he is the help.
I mean, look at him.
Looks like a butler or something.
[smacks lips] Uh…
[man] Oh shit.
-I was right? [laughs]
-[chuckles]
[all laughing]
["High Beams" by Tkay Maidza playing]
♪ Ooh-wee, yes, Lord ♪
♪ High beams, we goin' ♪
♪ Yes, we stay low ♪
♪ I feel way gone ♪
♪ Ooh-wee, yes, Lord ♪
♪ I've been slept on ♪
♪ LA, can't go ♪
Benny has his hands full tonight.
[giggles]
Maybe find someone else to leech onto.
Do us a favor.
Send the Gen Z
off to the back of the line.
[Bruce] Back of the line. Let's go.
-You kidding?
-Wait. No.
-You heard me. Not tonight.
-Look, no--
["Big Titties" playing]
♪ Catch me at the show
Signing on some big titties ♪
♪ Pull up on who… ♪
What are you looking at?
I don't think
I've ever met anybody like you.
[Blaire] Well, don't get weird.
I was just trying to make you look cool.
Yeah, well, it worked.
I don't know why you care what they think.
I don't.
You're never gonna remember their faces.
They're insignificant.
What does that make me?
I guess we're gonna have to find out.
♪ Ain't forcing shit
If ain't no chemistry ♪
♪ Then I go whiff out, yeah ♪
♪ I'm a five-star guy, by far
You a sidebar ♪
♪ You a bounced check, I'm a swipe card ♪
♪ Dive in the pussy headfirst
I'm a lifeguard ♪
Whoa.
[Zoé] Busy night.
[Blaire] Yeah.
And not a lot of friendly faces.
Let's keep this cool and quiet.
-I hate going in quiet.
-Zoé.
You wanna get the bag, I'll get Big Lou?
[Blaire] Mm-hmm.
It might get a little messy in there.
-Drink up. You won't feel a thing.
-[glass clinks]
[Jay] There'll be
a lot of sharp teeth in there.
Nobody makes a move
until we see Victor's girls, all right?
Y'all hear that?
[suspenseful music playing]
["Daemon" by Sunda Arc playing]
[man] Good evening, ladies.
Who are you? Where's Big Lou?
[man] Big Lou is no longer with us.
Don't you recognize me?
I don't think we've had the pleasure.
["Daemon" continues playing]
I don't like this. We should move.
[Zoé] We're not going anywhere yet.
[man] Lost a lot of friends
to things like you.
You don't remember me?
Remember what?
I gave you that,
but I didn't get to finish the job.
LA was always off-limits.
Yeah, I think it's brave
what you're doing,
stepping out on your own like this.
But, if you break the rules,
you lose certain protections.
I mean, with the truce falling apart,
it's open season on you freaks.
See my friend here?
She can drain your whole body
before you even pull the trigger.
[chuckles] You think I'm here alone?
Oh…
What were you saying?
♪ One, two, fleeka ♪
♪ You wanna pop my speakers ♪
♪ Three, two, three
Better blow ya mama's teeth out ♪
♪ I chew like I'm pika
Then I spit like I'm Nina ♪
♪ Wish you merry Kwanzaa
Set fire to my sneakers ♪
♪ One, two, fleeka ♪
♪ Might need some anesthesia… ♪
[tense music playing]
["Daemon" continues playing]
[laughs]
Ah. Look at them.
For once,
they're helpless.
Kill them.
[music intensifies]
[grunting]
[all grunting]
-[yelling]
-[groans]
[grunting continues]
Who still uses crossbows?
Night Legion.
-What?
-You asked who still uses crossbows.
Night Legion does.
They like to hunt things like us.
They've been at it for centuries.
And Benny, like, totally bottles them
in the face, apparently.
Yes, he does.
Come on.
These scumbags are like cockroaches.
When there's one, there's many.
[groans]
["Girl Crush"
by Boys Noize &amp; Rico Nasty playing]
♪ I think I got a girl crush ♪
♪ I think I got a girl crush… ♪
[intense music playing]
Benny!
Is there a problem?
-You know you're not allowed to be here.
-Move.
No.
[grunts]
-[stabbing]
-[grunts]
[gasping]
[groaning]
[people screaming]
Oh shit!
[all screaming]
-[Blaire] We gotta get off the streets.
-Yeah, we need to lay low.
Is there someplace safe you could take us?
No. We're not going anywhere
until I find out
where this Victor is
and what he wants from my brother.
Well, look at you.
Benny Boy. Making demands
like he's running the show tonight.
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
I like you, Benny.
I think you're kind of sweet,
so I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret.
Victor's gonna find Jay tonight,
and when he does, well…
Well? Well, what?
Well, if you stick with us,
then maybe we could get to Jay first,
and we could convince Victor
to go easy on him.
So, Benny, what's it gonna be?
You wanna see your brother,
or you wanna piss off?
-[crossbow fires]
-Shit!
[people screaming]
[Zoé] Run!
♪ I just need a manicure
Red tips, bad bitch ♪
♪ …if you insecure… ♪
-[door closes]
-[engine starts]
-[tires screeching]
-[horn honking]
-[crossbows firing]
-[people screaming]
[mumbling]
Come on! Try and get me, dickheads!
♪ Chewing on frozen waffles ♪
♪ Thinking 'bout my sex life ♪
-♪ Haram in my cell phone ♪
-[roaring]
♪ I don't need a bitch
Come and tell me shit ♪
♪ I'mma screen your bitch
You the type to snitch ♪
♪ 'Cause everybody wanna be a legend ♪
♪ Everybody wanna be a legend ♪
♪ Everybody wanna be a legend, ha ♪
♪ Everybody wanna be a legend
Wanna be a… ♪
[song continues in background]
Crazy night, huh?
Tell him to put his gear down.
[woman] It's all right.
You see the light now, don't you?
I heard what they did to your girl.
I know what that's like.
We all do. That's why we're out here.
We got resources. We got a network.
Wake up, Jay.
You can't beat them on your own.
Yeah, I don't wanna beat them.
I want Victor.
[chuckles]
Okay.
If you survive the night,
come find me.
Hey, uh, Benny?
Are you sure that we're safe here?
Yeah, of course. Nowhere safer.
I've lived here my whole life.
-I know, I just meant maybe--
-Listen, um…
So, my grandma works nights,
but sometimes she comes home early.
So, all I'm asking
is that you guys be quiet, please.
-I got it. Yes.
-You got it?
We will be on our best behavior.
Right, Zoé?
-Well, this is quaint.
-Shh.
-[Grandma screams]
-[Benny] Hey! It's me!
[in Spanish] Oh my God!
I almost killed you!
All day by myself!
If you're gonna be studying--
[in English] Hello.
Can you please put the bat down? Please?
-Where have you been?
-[Benny] I--
[in Spanish] These two
don't look like college students.
[in English] Look, I…
I lost my phone and, uh…
Blaire, Zoé, this is my grandma, Rosa.
Grandma, this is Blaire and… and Zoé.
-'Sup?
-Hey.
Okay. Good night now. Have a nice evening.
Listen, they're waiting for a ride,
so I was thinking maybe they could,
you know, wait here a bit.
[in Spanish] What happened to your hand?
[in English] No, it's fine.
I'll get a Band-Aid--
[in Spanish] What Band-Aid? No Band-Aid!
-[in English] You're gonna need stitches!
-Ma, it's okay. It's okay.
-[sighs]
-[in Spanish] Who did this to you?
[Benny hesitates, in English]
Nothing. It was an accident.
[tires screeching]
[man] Yo, that was a bloodbath, G.
We keep going like this,
it's suicide for sure.
[tires screeching]
[siren wailing]
Damn.
[key clicks out of ignition]
[sighs]
[Anderson] Hands on the dash.
Eyes forward.
You. You got any weapons
or drugs in the vehicle?
No, sir.
[Anderson] Hey. Hands.
-My ID.
-[Anderson] I don't need to see that.
I know who the two of you are.
Victor would like to meet for a drink.
Rosso Puro.
Thirty minutes.
We're free to go?
[Anderson] Oh yeah. I almost forgot.
Benny says hi.
[in Spanish] How did this happen to you?
[Benny] Grandma, that is a long story.
But I swear I'll tell you later.
Okay?
Do they speak Spanish?
[in English] I don't know.
Is this little Benny?
[Benny] Yo, put that back.
No. It's so good.
[Grandma] You know,
Benny's never brought a girl home before.
-Let alone two.
-Abuela, seriously?
[in Spanish] What?
[chuckles]
[in English] Can I help you out with that?
I… That's okay.
I… I think we're fine here.
Thank you, dear.
["Utrus Horas"
by Orchestra Baobab playing]
[spluttering] Yeah, all right,
you know what? I think we're good here.
You know, I feel good.
Hand feels good. Uh…
You… uh, you… you… you feel good?
Do I feel good? You woke me up
in the middle of the night, Benny.
I'm… I'm sorry, but maybe
you should get back to sleep?
[in Spanish] I like this one better
than the other one.
But be careful.
I don't need great-grandchildren.
[chuckles]
[in Spanish] Good evening, Rosa.
It was a pleasure.
[Grandma chuckling]
-[Victor on phone] What's wrong, baby?
-We got jumped downtown.
Night Legion was all over us.
At least they took care of Big Lou.
How many did you kill?
[Zoé] Three.
Maybe four. Boyle Heights was there too.
[man grunting]
[Zoé] I thought you said
you were gonna take care of Jay.
[Victor] Don't worry.
I'm on my way to meet Jay.
Just stopped for a drink.
Okay.
I don't know. I'm getting worried.
This night's going sideways.
We can't stop now. We're nearly done.
I'm gonna drain the kid.
I'm gonna smother the grandma,
and we can hit Venice tomorrow.
[Victor] We need to clear Venice tonight.
Rocko is too unpredictable.
If we mess this up,
there will be no tomorrow.
-[man grunting]
-Venice is the last kill.
-[man whimpering]
-I know you can do it.
Just keep a hold of the kid,
and we'll party at dawn.
The world will be ours, babe,
just me and you.
[breathes deeply]
Yeah.
Let's get it done.
Now,
where were we?
[whispering] It's kind of cool.
[knife clatters]
Huh.
All right.
[hip-hop music playing on speakers]
This is super cool.
[chuckles] Yeah, all right.
You… you can put that down.
[sighs] Sorry.
This is all just leftover
from when I was a kid.
I was gonna get rid of all of this stuff.
I haven't really had the time to upgrade--
Yes. Did you build all of this?
Yeah, but you know,
can we just maybe turn this down--
Mm-mm. No.
Why not?
'Cause I like it.
I think it's really good.
I mean, I'm assuming
B's Session Number Three, that's you?
Oh yeah. You know,
this is actually… it's a… it's a classic.
Oh, this is a classic?
Oh yeah, yeah. Everyone says so.
-[Blaire] Oh, everyone says so?
-Mm-hmm.
People, like who?
You know, people like… my grandma?
-Yeah. [laughs]
-[Benny laughs]
So, when are you gonna play this
for other people?
Well, I'm planning on it. I… I want
to do something… something with this.
It's more than fun.
I wanna turn it into something real.
And when I do, you know,
then you could tell people
that you're my first fan.
-So, in a way, you're welcome.
-Oh, I can?
Yeah, you know, if you want.
Well, I mean, for what it's worth,
I believe you. It's really good.
You're really talented.
[inhales] And you're a very good driver.
-[laughs] Thanks.
-[Blaire] Mmm.
[chuckles]
Well, what… what about you?
What about me? [chuckles]
You know, is there anything that you like?
Anything you're passionate about?
I mean, like, in a past life.
[inhales deeply]
Zoé and I are always talking
about, like, the shit we're gonna do.
-You know?
-When did you two meet?
Um… [laughs]
She had this place
in Laurel Canyon in the '70s,
and she would throw these parties.
So, they would go
for like three or four days.
Everyone was there. And she loved Bowie,
so she had this, like…
the Bowie haircut, you know.
She was cool, man.
The queen bitch, that was her.
-[chuckles]
-Yeah, that checks out.
And I was, like, just like a stray
when I first moved here,
and I didn't feel like I fit anywhere.
And it was like she saw me.
She told me everything could be beautiful.
[chuckles softly]
She said a bunch of stuff.
And then she turned me,
and she gave me this life.
[inhales deeply]
Honestly, you should take this
to a producer.
-[Benny] Yeah.
-[Blaire] You could make real money.
[Benny] I know, I know, it's just
I don't think it's where it has to be yet.
Where does it have to be?
What's it missing?
It's missing a little something
before it becomes like a--
-Like, what? A classic?
-Yeah.
-Mmm.
-Yeah, a classic.
[Zoé clears throat] We need to leave.
Yeah. Cool.
Hi.
We're done with Benny, right?
He can stay here.
I don't think so.
-Well, this has nothing to do with him.
-He's coming. That's how it's gotta be.
Why are you being like this?
Do you want to be the one to tell Victor?
Hey.
I'm coming with you.
Good.
[Benny] Let's go.
[Jay] Anything happens to me,
you take care of Benny.
You protect him.
[man] Consider it done.
[intense music playing]
[Jay] Where's Benny?
-[cutlery clinks]
-Jay. So glad you could make it.
You put a hand on him or Maria,
I swear to God--
Is that her name? We'll get to her.
But first, sit.
-Where are they?
-Sit.
It's funny to think, though.
Almost a hundred years ago,
my kind sat across from your kind,
much like you and I right now.
And then they came up with that truce.
[Jay] Well, you broke that truce.
You took people from my neighborhood.
Innocent people.
Did you think we were gonna let
you get away with that?
We? Who's this "we" you're talking about?
Everyone's gone. I had them all killed.
You should have taken my offer.
Now it's all going to be mine.
You see, you're the last piece.
Once you're gone,
this city's just one fat neck
waiting to get sucked.
You want me?
Fine. Fair game.
Maria and Benny
have nothing to do with this.
Let them go.
That's not how this is going to go.
Nobody walks.
You know that.
[grunts]
[grunts, pants]
-[grunts]
-How do I look? Do I look okay?
[Jay panting]
-Do you want some?
-[grunts]
I saved her for you.
Your sweet Maria.
What?
I saved her for you, Jay.
-[laughs]
-No. No.
Don't go soft on me now.
We haven't even gotten started yet.
[Jay panting]
[Zoé] Last kill.
Let's do this.
[dramatic music playing]
Maybe lean close. This guy's a freak.
Look what the night dragged in.
Couple of strays.
Good morning, Rocko.
No such thing as a good morning.
[Zoé] Mmm, maybe not for you.
I don't know you, do I?
No, but I'm… I'm with them.
[chuckles] That doesn't really change
your problem, amigo.
-I don't know you.
-Don't worry about him. He's cool.
Yeah, chill, he's with us.
You cool?
Cool, dude.
Rough night?
You look a little, uh, banged up, bro.
Yeah, I'm… I'm a little banged up, bro.
[tense music playing]
[laughs]
Oh, I'm just messing with you, man!
I'm goofing!
Mi casa es su casa!
Enter at your leisure.
-Madam.
-[Blaire] Mmm.
[door stopper clatters]
["Senden Baska" by Kit Sebastian
Elliot Martin and Emine Merve Erdem plays]
[sniffing]
Oh, you smell nice.
You give good blood, don't you?
I can tell.
I have a nose for these things.
I see things, man.
Visions.
Some people say
I'm like a… like a psychic or something.
-Yeah, I… I bet they do say that.
-They do.
Rocko.
Yes?
Not this one.
[laughs]
Oh, whatever, man.
I'm not into virgins. You know that.
[inhales deeply]
-I'm… I'm not even a--
-Hey. Don't lie, man.
Third eye sees all.
This is weird.
You guys didn't call.
You showed up unannounced.
Is this like a booty call or something?
I'm not that kind of girl.
[Zoé] We just wanted
to surprise you, Rocko.
What, you don't like surprises anymore?
You know I love surprises.
Surprises are tight.
[chuckles]
Do you want to leave us for a minute?
-[Rocko] Yeah.
-[Zoé chuckles]
Yeah, why don't you guys, uh,
leave us to it for the minute
and go out to the pool?
Let the grown-ups, uh, conversate.
[lighter clicks]
We'll be out there soon.
-Bye, virgin.
-[chuckles]
[dogs barking in distance]
[Blaire] Drink?
[glasses clink]
What?
I don't know how you could be
so chill about all this.
You know? It's like,
you're out here every night
doing this Kill Bill-type shit. [laughs]
-It's crazy.
-[laughs]
-It's kind of… it's kind of crazy.
-It's not every night.
-It's not?
-No.
[laughs]
[Blaire] If I'm still alive tomorrow,
I am sleeping all day.
[both laugh]
-[Blaire] Mmm.
-Sounds nice.
[Blaire] Mmm.
It is.
What's it like?
Hmm?
You know.
Honestly…
sometimes it feels awesome.
You can do whatever you want.
You don't have to hold back.
You're completely free.
Sometimes.
I just killed this dude an hour ago.
Mm-hmm.
Fresh type O.
Clean blood.
[Zoé chuckles]
Can't beat it.
[laughs]
Cheers.
["Yanimda Kal" by Kit Sebastian
Elliot Martin and Emine Merve Erdem plays]
[gulps]
[exhales]
So,
what's with the late-night hang?
You girls never cross the 405.
We were in the neighborhood.
Figured we'd stop by.
Knew you'd be up late.
-[clinks]
-[suspenseful music playing]
So, you got any family?
I got Zoé.
She's got me.
No, but like…
like real family.
You know, my, uh…
my grandma scooped me up
after my mom passed,
and it was me, and it was her,
and it was Jay.
And Jay, he… he…
he took care of me.
He… he didn't have to.
You know, he's… he's just my half brother,
but he's… he's like
the only father I've ever had.
I'm sorry.
You're not like her, you know? Like Zoé.
I mean, I… I see you, you're…
you're alive.
Can I ask you something?
Are you gonna kill me?
No.
I don't want you like that.
[passionate music playing]
[Rocko] So how come
you never come to visit anymore?
-[liquid pouring]
-We had a good thing going back then.
[chuckles]
Reagan was president.
Shit, it was that long ago?
-Mm-hmm.
-[Rocko] Wow.
Time flies.
What?
Is something wrong?
No. No. Nothing wrong.
Oh, it just hit me. [chuckles]
Maybe just this one thing.
The part where you and Victor
decide to kill and steal
from your own blood.
-[roars]
-[laughs] You wicked bitch.
Oh, you bloodsucker.
[both laugh]
What?
-I have to tell you something.
-What happened?
Your brother. Victor has him.
[glass shattering]
[intense music playing]
Benny, get the car.
[all yelling, grunting]
[thuds]
[yelling]
[screaming]
-[objects clattering]
-[groaning]
[grunting]
-[door lock chirps]
-[engine starts]
-[crossbows firing]
-[yelps]
[man] Tango down!
[pants]
[tires squealing]
[grunting]
-[man yelling indistinctly]
-[pants]
[grunts]
[Blaire grunting]
[groans]
[man yelling indistinctly]
-[yelling]
-[crossbows firing]
[all yelling]
[grunting]
[groans]
Drive! Drive!
[tires squealing]
[Blaire] Babe, you're okay. We did it.
-[sobbing] I'm sorry.
-[Zoé gasping]
The night's over.
We'll go home, and you'll be okay.
Benny, she needs blood.
Oh God.
We have to get to the last stop.
Okay. Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
[birds chirping]
[tires squealing]
-[Benny] Okay, let's get her inside.
-No. Hey, you take the car and run.
-Okay?
-What are you talking about?
This is Victor's house.
Okay, and he has Jay,
so I'm not going anywhere.
I'm sorry. Okay?
I'm sorry, I am. But it's too late.
No, it's not too late. If there's a chance
that he's in there, then I'm going in!
You're dead the second you go in there.
Don't you understand?
Not if you help me.
It's over.
Promise me.
-Okay. Come on. Come on, come on, come on.
-[gasping]
[Blaire] You're good.
All right. Ready? Ready?
Okay. Come on.
[gasping]
[engine idling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[solemn music playing]
[mechanical whirring]
Jay.
Hey, Jay.
Hey. Hey, yo, Jay.
Hey, it's me. It's Benny, hey.
[muffled speaking]
You see me? Hey.
[whispering] I'mma get you out.
[inhales deeply] I'mma… I'mma…
[panting]
I'mma get you out of here.
I'mma get you out.
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
[footsteps approaching]
[Victor] Look who's decided to join us.
[Zoé] Benny.
Did you miss us? You missed us.
I'm sensing some tension here.
Yeah, Benny's had a busy night.
I've heard so much about you.
Why don't you join us? Take a seat.
-I'd rather stand.
-Oh.
So, tell us, Benny.
What are you doing here?
[Benny] I'd like to make a deal.
Let Jay go. Take me instead.
It's an interesting proposal.
[clicks tongue] Benny.
Hey, Blaire.
What's wrong?
I didn't say anything.
Benny, have you ever tried fresh blood?
[smacks lips] There's nothing like it.
I remember when I first came here.
The blood tastes different.
I had to get used to it.
I had to develop my palate.
Now I can't get enough.
-[Benny groans]
-[Victor laughs]
[groans]
After considering your proposal,
unfortunately,
I'm going to have to decline.
-[laughs]
-But here's my counteroffer.
Because I run things now,
you will be our appetizer.
["One Way or Another" by Blondie playing]
Jay will be our main course.
And I think I'll save abuela for dessert.
-[yells]
-[grunts]
Hey! Don't you fucking touch him!
What are you doing? He saved us tonight.
Well, then I guess
we'll make it quick, then.
Hold him down. It's time to drink.
♪ One way or another… ♪
-[Blaire] Don't.
-Oh. This is interesting.
She's just confused.
-You're not confused, are you?
-Not at all, actually.
[Zoé] Hey.
Everything's okay. What's going on?
-We won! We won!
-We won?
Blaire, stop. You don't gotta do this.
-I'll tell you when you can talk!
-I don't work for you anymore.
So I'm not gonna listen
to any more of your crazy bullshit.
You're gonna let him
talk to us like that, Blaire?
I can't do this.
No, no, no, no!
Everything is finally good.
-We're finally good.
-I'm telling you, I'm done.
Hey! I need you.
I can't do this without you.
I don't want to do this without you.
-I want out. Oh!
-No, Blaire, no!
You were nothing!
I made you! I made you!
You can't leave me.
-You need me.
-Not anymore.
-No!
-[Benny] No!
[grunts]
[gasps]
-Look at what you did, Benny.
-No!
Look at what you did.
[grunts]
-[chuckles]
-[Benny grunts]
[Victor] She's had a weak heart.
Put her out of her misery.
This was supposed to be our night.
[Benny] No.
Night's over.
-[door lock chirps]
-[engine revving]
[sizzling]
[dramatic music playing]
[Zoé screaming]
[continues screaming in pain]
[screaming stops]
[gasping]
[suspenseful music playing]
[chain clinking]
[Jay panting]
Benny.
Jay?
-Hey. Jay.
-[Jay] Run.
-Jay. Where is he? Where is he?
-Run. Run. Now.
It's a trap. Benny-- [grunts]
[panting]
[grunts]
-[bites]
-[groans]
[groans, whimpers]
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[intense music playing]
[yelling in slow motion]
[sizzling]
[grunting softly]
[grunting]
Benny, you're okay. No, Benny. Benny.
Hey. No. You're okay. You're okay.
It's okay.
[crying softly]
[biting]
[exhales]
Here.
[sucking]
[ethereal music playing]
[birds chirping]
[wind whooshing]
[gentle music playing]
[plane engine roaring]
[music continues]
[gasps, pants]
[breathing heavily]
[music continues]
[grunts softly]
[sighs in relief]
["I Knew" by Sister Mantos playing]
-[Jay] I, uh, spoke to the depot.
-[Benny] Right.
"Jay, you can never ever drive
for the company again."
-I told you not to scratch it, fool.
-I did a little more than a scratch it.
-Yeah, you did, man. Yeah, you did.
-[chuckles]
But, um, I wouldn't be here
eating this fine slice of pizza
if it weren't for you.
Well, you'd do the same for me so…
[smacks lips]
Things are gonna be different, you know.
The whole world's changed.
And everyone's gonna have to take a side.
Just don't forget where you came from.
I know where home is.
Oh, I, uh, left you a little something.
[chuckles]
[intense music playing]
[woman whispering]
[giggling]
[indistinct whispering]
[woman laughing]
-[man whispering]
-[laughing]
[heart beating]
[woman giggling]
Come on. Ask him what happened.
[man] Yo.
Benny, man. Hold up.
What's up?
Where you been, man?
We see you at the club,
and then you went MIA.
[woman] Yeah. Um, Benny.
[tires screeching]
Are you okay?
Never been better.
Hey.
Get in. We're running late.
["Come Alive" by Jorge Lendeborg Jr.,
Deputy, The Kid Daytona and Mez playing]
Yeah, I gotta go,
but I'll see y'all later, yeah?
-Yeah.
-[mouthing]
-[car door closes]
Y'all want a ride?
♪ I love it here, I'm never leaving
Long as I'm breathing ♪
♪ Nobody had the faith in me
My… believed it ♪
♪ Nothing like my barrio
There ain't no comparing ♪
♪ Mariachis playing from a block away
You hear it ♪
♪ From South Central to the Hills
Valid any district ♪
♪ Skateboard to class
Kick, push, kickflipping ♪
♪ Navigating through the waters
With the big fishes ♪
♪ Can't let 'em reel me in
Like I'm a meal ticket ♪
♪ Boyle Heights raised me
I'm losing my mind lately ♪
♪ Speeding through the road of life
Got my mind racing ♪
♪ Bright lights blazing
I got on some good shades and ♪
♪ Hollywood shady
Can't forget the hood made me ♪
♪ Made me, yeah! ♪
♪ No lie come alive in the nighttime ♪
♪ On the Westside
With a dime on my right side ♪
♪ Never mind all the trouble
That I might find ♪
♪ Don't gotta ask if I'm rollin'
Know I'm gonna ride ♪
♪ No way I'd ever leave
There's no place I'd rather be ♪
♪ Post up on Soto Street
Eastside, that's what made me ♪
♪ Late night, no getting sleep
Still goin' in, this life chose me ♪
♪ West coast L.I.F.E.
Live like K.I.N.G.'s ♪
♪ I just hustle, I don't brag
I do papers, they give me cash ♪
♪ Keep it 100, keep it a stack
I ain't no dummy, and that's a fact ♪
♪ I'm way quicker, I'm way smarter
Never slip, never lack ♪
♪ Feeling like I won the chip
Feeling like Kobe, feeling like Shaq ♪
♪ Like LeBron in the 6
Feeling BIG like I'm Chris ♪
♪ Got my shades loc'd out
So surreal, what a trip ♪
♪ Your side and my side
Our kind and your kind ♪
♪ When you meet me, think I'm shy
But I ride in the night, whoa ♪
♪ Eastside evil
Let 'em know I got a hero flow ♪
♪ Lakerland deadly
That's a hustle me oh no! ♪
♪ Me oh my, too legit, superfly ♪
♪ Grilling at my migos like they UFOs
So who am I? ♪
♪ What I had to give to get
To where I'm going, where I been ♪
♪ I leave it clean like Fabuloso pouring
I'm a missile manic Jordan ♪
♪ Automatic and a poet
Take a lick and sip a Moët ♪
♪ Never know that I was chosen ♪
♪ No lie come alive in the nighttime ♪
♪ On the Westside
With a dime on my right side ♪
♪ Never mind all the trouble
That I might find ♪
♪ Don't gotta ask if I'm rollin'
Know I'm gonna ride ♪
♪ No way I'd ever leave
There's no place I'd rather be ♪
♪ Post up on Soto Street
Eastside, that's what made me ♪
♪ Late night, getting no sleep
Still goin' in, this life chose me ♪
♪ West coast L.I.F.E.
Live like K.I.N.G's ♪
♪ In the nighttime, I feel like I ♪
♪ Could do anything ♪
♪ I feel like a god ♪
♪ When the sun sets, that's when I rise ♪
♪ That's when I shine
In the night's sky ♪
♪ In the nighttime, I feel like I ♪
♪ Could do anything ♪
♪ I feel like a god ♪
♪ When the sun sets, that's when I rise ♪
♪ That's when I arrive, in the nighttime ♪
[techno music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[ethereal music playing]