Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[ominous music playing]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[film projector rattling]
[indistinct dialogue]
[birds calling]
[insects chirping]
[insects buzzing]
[ominous music playing]
[man shouts indistinctly]
[music intensifies]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[rain pattering]
[reporter] We've got heavy rain
being reported around the region.
But we've got wind gusts
of 30 or 40 miles an hour.
Visibility is poor, so you motorists
be careful out there.
[man in Portuguese over phone]
How's it going?
[woman] Yeah, you know.
[thunder rumbles]
Is Dad there?
[man sighs]
He's not going to talk to you.
-[rain pattering]
-[TV continues indistinctly]
Do you think
it would make a difference if I…
-[man] Came home?
-No.
No.
If I write to him.
[thunder rumbles]
[distant rumbling]
[rumbling approaching]
[door handle creaking]
[woman] I've been having bad dreams.
I just want to leave.
I was wrong, okay? I never…
[TV continues indistinctly]
I just want things to go back
to how they were.
Fuck…
[man] Listen, I have to go to work now.
[reporter in English]
That arrest led investigators…
[TV warping]
[man in Portuguese] You there?
[dripping]
Simona?
-[man sighs] Simo--
-[call disconnects]
[TV turns off]
[rain pattering]
Hello?
[distant thud]
[loud rumbling in the distance]
[thunder rumbles]
[eerie music plays]
[in English] Hello?
-[creaking]
-[gasps]
[fluttering]
[stone box rumbles, thuds]
[heavy breathing]
[thumps]
[screams]
[screaming stops]
[pin clinks on floor]
[lights flickering]
[ominous music playing]
[door clangs open]
[door squeaking]
[indistinct whispering, shushing]
[man in English] Everybody out.
[in Spanish] Let's go.
[in English] Come on, huh?
Come on.
[in Spanish] Let's go.
Keep moving.
[in English] Let's go.
-[woman in Spanish] Take care.
-You too.
[in English] If you want to stay
any longer, I need your ID.
It's been two weeks now.
Yeah. Okay, you'll get it. [light chuckle]
[bus engine revving]
[bell rings]
[woman] Ambar, are you coming?
-We don't want to be late.
-I'll be right there.
[doorbell rings]
[man] Don't mind the mess.
We just took over the place.
We're still fixing it up.
Your, uh, room's just over here.
You have a good view from this floor.
Not that Cleveland's much to look at.
How you finding it?
-Uh, yeah, it's nice.
-[keys jingling]
[scoffs] Not been here long, then.
[door opens, shuts]
How many others live here?
Uh, you're the second.
Freja's the first.
Her English ain't so good.
Where's she from?
Somewhere they don't speak English.
[door creaking]
Uh, ladies only.
No guests after 9:00.
No smoking, no pets.
Okay.
Oh…
[train horn blaring in the distance]
Radiator's off.
Once it's on, one side is warm--
-[Ambar] Oh, sorry.
-[man] Shoot. I got it, I got it.
[Ambar] Are you sure? I can just--
[man] I'll prop that up. Okay. [grunts]
[sniffles] Don't worry. I'll replace that.
[pants]
-So, where are you from?
-Uh…
South of here.
How far south?
Not very far.
[scoffs]
You got a job?
Yes.
They pay cash?
Yeah.
-One month's rent upfront.
-[chuckling] A month?
You want the room or not?
[train horn blaring in the distance]
Key is in the drawer.
Anything else, I'm upstairs, top floor.
Just holler.
[Ambar] Thanks.
[door creaks shut]
[rain pattering]
-[rain pattering]
-[building creaking]
[phone beeps]
[female voice in Spanish] Saved messages.
[woman in Spanish over phone]
Hi, sweetheart. It's Mama.
Sorry for calling so late. [inhales]
You know I can't sleep in these beds.
Thank you for today.
I know you have plans,
but I need you to come in tomorrow.
-[distant crying]
-Please come.
-Your visits are the only thing--
-[phone beeps]
[crying continues]
[woman sobbing]
[wind howling]
[sobbing continues]
[sniffles, sighs]
[thunder rumbling]
[somber music playing]
[indistinct announcement over PA]
[in Spanish] Can you stay a little longer?
Of course.
[thunder rumbles]
[train horn blaring in the distance]
[light switch clicks]
-Oh, sorry!
-[Freja gasps] Sorry.
Uh, Freja?
Sorry, I'm… I'm Ambar.
Red said it's just the two of us.
Red is full of shit.
[door creaks open, shut]
[eerie music playing]
[bell rings]
-This needs to be double stitched.
-Okay. I'm sorry, sir.
-This hem's no good either.
-Yeah, I'm sorry.
-It won't happen again.
-I need you to hurry up.
-You should be doing twice as many.
-Yes.
-Pick up the pace.
-Yes, sir, I'm sorry. Thank you.
[male reporter]
He adds the raids go after employees,
but not the business owners
also committing crimes by hiring…
[woman speaks quietly] Come on, we agreed!
[sighs] But why? Can I know why?
Yes! Fine.
Bye.
Well, how much is the ID?
-The price went up to 3,000.
-Three?
-Come on, you said it was one!
-[woman] I know, but…
-This guy's an asshole. I'm sorry.
-Why?
Birthplace. If it's Ohio,
it's still a thousand.
-No, it has to be Texas.
-[woman] Why can't you come from Ohio?
-I can't.
-Then it's gonna have to cost you more.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
You'll think of something.
Texans are resourceful people.
[both chuckle]
[soft rock ballad playing on radio]
[man] Be nice when we go out there.
[woman] I'm trying to be nice,
but I don't know who she is.
You hardly knew her mother!
[man] It's gonna be a nice evening
as long as you are able to,
you know, be nice.
[woman] I'll do my best.
[footsteps approaching]
[woman] Carlos? Dinner.
-[in Spanish] Can I help?
-No, it's okay.
I hope you like meatloaf.
Yes. [chuckles]
It smells delicious.
Thank you for inviting me.
[man] Of course.
It's our pleasure to meet you.
Thank you.
You must be Carlos.
-[in English] What?
-Oh, we don't--
Carlos isn't used to speaking Spanish.
Oh.
I'm… I'm sorry.
Carlos, Ambar's mama was my cousin.
That makes Ambar your second cousin.
Are you all set for Friday?
Yes.
Yes, thank you very much.
No promises,
but I did put in a good word for you.
Don't forget to bring your ID.
They were pretty big on that.
So, how do you like the city, Ambar?
I mean, it's nice.
-Just a little cold. [chuckles]
-[man] It's freezing.
-I have to wear two pairs of socks here.
-[chuckles]
[man] You know,
you should get a proper coat.
Sylvia, don't we have something
we can give her?
Oh, no, no. That's okay. I can buy one.
No, it's fine. I--
I have an old coat in my closet.
Well,
thank you.
So, Beto says you didn't go to college.
Well, I was going to,
but then Mami got sick.
Um…
I'm gonna go to night school
to study business management.
It's a great thing you did,
staying by her side through her illness.
Well, she needed me.
Putting your life on hold all those years,
not a lot of people would've done that.
-Are you listening, Carlos?
-[all chuckle]
[sighs]
[loud rumbling]
[rumbling continues]
[thumps, rumbles]
[rumbling]
[flickering]
-[Red] Lose something?
-[gasps]
[Ambar] Hey.
No. Uh, there was a sound.
[Red] Basement's private.
Sorry. Um, I-- I actually need
to talk to you about something.
Look, it's late. I need to finish up,
so let's talk tomorrow.
-[door slams shut]
-Study's private too.
[Ambar] Oh, um…
Well, I need to talk to you
about my deposit.
Why?
Well, I'm very sorry,
but I need my deposit back.
Something has come up. You can have
the money for last night and tonight.
You just moved in.
I know, Red. Please, I… I need that money.
I already spent it.
-What?
-[Red] Refurbishments, tools, materials.
It's done. Sorry.
[Freja crying]
[crying continues]
-[Ambar inhales]
-[knocks on door]
[Ambar] Hey, are you okay?
[hinges creak]
Freja?
[ominous music playing]
[water boiling]
[reporter] Coming up next, we find out
what really happened to the four hikers
that went missing
in the Swedish wilderness.
[kettle whistling]
[Mama in Spanish]
You've always had such beautiful hair.
[Ambar] You'd brush it a hundred times
before letting me leave the house.
And aren't you glad I did?
[chuckles]
Yes.
[Mama] Are you sure you're happy to stay?
Of course.
Hmm.
You're too kind, Ambar.
What's that in the corner?
[ominous music playing]
-[door screeching]
-[gasps]
[sighs]
[man] You want what?
Can I get paid for next week?
You know how many girls would kill
for this job?
-And you ask me for an advance?
-But what if I do double shifts?
Every day you're getting slower!
-You're lucky you still have a job.
-[bell rings]
I'm sorry. I'll move faster.
[man] You just got here,
and you keep saying that!
I know, but I promise. I'm sorry.
Why don't I put you on packing?
I'm not supposed to, but just for today.
And you come back tomorrow
and prove to me you're good for this job.
-Okay.
-Okay?
How about a thank you?
[loud indistinct chatter]
[fluttering]
[female voice] Ambar.
[gasps]
[bell rings]
[rock music playing over speakers]
[woman] Why do you need the ID so soon?
What's so important about Friday?
I have a job interview.
So take the damned ID
which says you were born in Ohio.
You can just say Texas was a mistake
on your application or something.
-I can't.
-Why not?
-Well, it's complicated.
-So explain!
[Ambar] My uncle.
I called him up
and asked… asked for a job, and…
he said he couldn't help me
because I wasn't a US citizen, and…
I lied and said that I was born--
In Texas!
Mami used to live in Texas, and…
now I'm stuck.
I didn't want to come here like this.
But Mami got sick,
and then she'd get better,
and I could make plans.
[inhales]
But then things would get bad again,
and I'd have to stay.
I was relieved when it was all over.
I could finally leave for a new start.
You know, people always told me
I had an eye for fashion.
A gift for seeing
who people would like to be.
We came here, and I thought I would
open up a shop or maybe start a website.
Five years later,
and I'm still working
the same shitty job. [laughs]
We are too kind.
Why else am I still living
with several members of my family?
I should make them work for me.
I love them, but life would be
so much easier without them.
[laughs]
Listen, this is clearly the drink talking,
but why don't I lend you the rest?
-What?
-You're going to have a real job soon.
You can pay me back.
And then maybe lend me
some money to do my own thing.
Oh my God.
Kinsi, are you… are you serious?
Yes! I'm serious.
When can you get this done?
[Kinsi] As soon as you get me the money.
[unzipping]
What are you doing?
Get this to your guy
and… and get me my papers.
You are sure?
Yes!
[chuckles]
[dog barking]
[sighs]
[loud thump]
[creaking]
[light flickering]
[ominous music playing]
-[door closes]
-[keys jingling]
-[banging]
-[man muttering in foreign language]
-[indistinct, shaky muttering continues]
-[banging]
-[muttering continues]
-[banging head on door]
-[banging continues]
-[muttering continues]
[banging, muttering stops]
[footsteps approaching]
[light turns on]
[footsteps stop]
[man chanting]
[light turns off]
[loud bang on door]
[laughs]
[woman speaking Romanian in the distance]
-[women laugh]
-[door unlocks]
[door bangs open]
[indistinct dialogue continues]
-[Ambar] Hello?
-[woman gasps]
-[in Romanian] What are you doing?
-[in English] Sorry.
-[in Romanian] Who's this?
-[woman] I don't know. She scared me.
[In English] Hi. I'm… I'm Ambar.
-Maria.
-Petra.
-[Ambar] Are you guys staying here?
-For now. Drink?
Um… No, no, thank you.
I've had plenty tonight.
If I have another one,
I don't think I'll make it
into work tomorrow. [chuckles]
-[Petra] Huh.
-[Ambar] What do you do for work?
-[chuckles softly]
-[slurping]
[Petra chuckles]
[chuckles]
Yeah, it's… it's tough out there.
Yeah. It's so much better in here.
Right. Right.
At least the rent is cheap. [chuckles]
It's cheap because it's shit.
Sure. [chuckles]
[Petra] Cigarette?
Uh… Yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
[Red] Evening, ladies.
-You ready to go up?
-[Petra] Mm-hmm.
[in Romanian] Let's go.
I thought you said
this place was women only.
There was this other guy downstairs.
Oh, that's just Becker. He's my brother.
It's just me and him, don't worry.
[water pouring]
[spoon clinking]
[loud, thumping music
playing in the distance]
[women speaking in Romanian]
[laughing]
[building creaking]
-[thumping music continues]
-[loud laughter and chatter]
[suspenseful music playing]
[wind chimes tinkling]
[mysterious music playing]
[creaking]
[indistinct chatter
over vintage tape recorder]
[man chanting]
[in English] ...as performed
within the ritual sacrifice.
You will then give her the elderly,
women, children.
In return, you'll receive the blessings…
We don't know
how it began or how it ended.
[ominous music playing]
-[tape shrieks]
-[gasps]
[door shuts]
[indistinct chatter]
-[man 1] Good luck.
-[man 2] Let's go.
[man 3] All right, let's move it.
-Come on.
-[car horn honks]
Come on, come on.
[line ringing]
[man 3] Come on, come on.
[Kinsi on voicemail] Hey, it's Kinsi.
It sucks that you missed me,
but leave a message
and I'll call you back soon. Bye!
-[Ambar] Have you seen Kinsi?
-She quit this morning.
All I get is a text.
Didn't even bother to call.
-Do you have her address?
-I can't give you that.
-Come on. I need it.
-Why?
-I… I just really need it.
-It's against company policy.
Company policy?
What company policy? It's just you!
You ain't worth the hassle.
-You're fired.
-No, no. Hey, wait, wait--
Hey, Kinsi, it's Ambar.
Call me back.
[tense music playing]
[Kinsi on voicemail] Hey, it's Kinsi.
It sucks that you missed me,
but leave a message and I'll call--
[sighs]
[creaking]
[panting]
[muffled high-pitched cry]
[shower turns off]
[woman, muffled] Help!
Help!
[woman sobs]
[Ambar panting]
[woman sobbing] Help!
[woman continues crying]
[Ambar shuddering] Freja?
[crying continues]
-[Ambar gasps]
-Oh, shit!
-I'm so sorry.
-[Red] What the fuck!
What's wrong?
Have you seen Freja?
Uh, she… she moved out.
What? When?
A couple days back.
People come and go from here all the time.
I'm sorry. I need to--
[Red] I wanted to talk about your deposit.
With the new girls here,
it's a little easier, so…
-I can get it back to you.
-Okay, now?
No, I don't have cash
on me right now. [chuckling]
Um…
Tomorrow.
[panting] Okay. Thanks. I'm sorry.
-[locks door]
-[keys jingling]
[sighs]
[Becker coughing]
[Red] Hey, Beck, you okay?
[creaking]
[lights flickering]
[fluttering]
[distant rumbling]
[eerie music playing]
[phone beeps]
[female voice in Spanish] Saved messages.
[Mama in Spanish]
Hi, sweetheart. It's Mama.
Sorry for calling so late. [inhales]
-You know I can't sleep in these beds.
-[fluttering]
Thank you for today.
I know you have plans,
but I need you to come in tomorrow.
Please--
[Mama in Spanish]
Hi, sweetheart. It's Mama.
Sorry for calling so late. [inhales]
-You know I can't sleep in these beds.
-[fluttering]
Thank you for today.
I know you have plans--
-[phone beeps]
-[continues fluttering]
-Ambar.
-[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
[creaking]
[lights flickering]
[woman crying in the distance]
[crying continues]
[sobbing]
-[footsteps approaching]
-[frantic panting]
-[panting gets louder]
-[Ambar gasps]
[woman sobbing] No.
[softly] Please don't…
[raspy breathing in the distance]
[raspy breathing approaching]
[woman sobbing]
Please, Mary, no.
[Mary] I must prepare you,
or Arthur will hurt us both.
[heavy breathing]
-Come here!
-[Ambar and woman gasp]
[Ambar panting]
-[woman groans]
-[glass shatters]
[both groan]
[Ambar gasps]
[Mary] Stop!
-Come here.
-[woman groans]
[Mary] Hurry up! Stop!
Hey!
You'll do what I say.
[panting]
[woman crying in the distance]
[crying continues]
[sobbing] No, Mary. No.
Please, Mary.
[cries]
[crying continues]
Please, Mary.
[sobbing]
Mary, please.
[crying]
Don't listen to Arthur.
-Please, let me-- [screams]
-[gasps]
-[Ambar in Spanish] Come on.
-[line ringing]
Pick up the phone!
[line continues ringing]
-[Beto on phone] Ambar?
-Beto?
[Beto] It's the middle of the night.
Are you all right?
Beto, can you pick me up?
I'm at 1521 Recolte Avenue. Please.
[Beto sighs]
Please, Beto. I can't stay here. Please--
We're out of town.
We're looking at a college
for Carlos, remember?
Listen, if you're in trouble,
call the cops.
No, I can't call the police.
-[Beto] Why not?
-Because…
Because I wasn't born in Texas.
[Beto] What do you mean?
[inhales deeply]
I came here after Mama died.
[Beto] Ambar…
I'm so sorry. I'll make it up to you,
but I really need your help.
Can you wire me some money?
Please, I promise I'll pay you back.
[Beto] I'm sorry.
It's just… we'd never even met before.
Look, I'll come see you as soon as I can.
Just try and stay
out of trouble until then.
Red?
[door unlocking]
Red, I need my--
[sighs] Where's Red?
He said he'd give me my deposit back.
-I'll send him down when he gets back.
-No--
[door locks]
[door opens, shuts]
[ominous music playing]
[panting]
[man] No. There's no vacancy. Not here.
-I'll pay the rest tomorrow--
-Just get out of here, okay?
[softly] Come on.
[siren wailing]
[man] Hold up.
Hey, where you going, darling?
[rap music playing over speakers]
[coins clinking]
[Mama in Spanish]
Hi, sweetheart. It's Mama.
Sorry for calling so late. [inhales]
You know I can't sleep in these beds.
Thank you for today…
[continues indistinctly]
[train rumbling]
[man over PA]
This is the red line to Tower City.
Next stop, West Park.
[exhales]
[lights flickering]
[ominous music playing]
[wheezing hiss]
[shrieks]
[gasps]
Fuck!
[exhales]
[female reporter]
The 444 team has been tracking
this major weather storm all day.
We are here tonight to let you know
just how long the snow…
Thank you. Can I--
Sorry, can I actually have another one?
[police radio chattering]
[indistinct chatter]
[laughing, speaking indistinctly]
[line ringing]
[engine idling]
[turns off engine]
[door opens, shuts]
[footsteps approaching]
[sighs]
Did you bring my deposit?
Hello to you too.
Sorry, hi.
[Red] No, I was out.
It's back at the house.
You sounded like you were upset,
so I came straight here.
Okay. Can you bring it?
You want me to drive
all the way back across town,
pick up your money, and bring it here?
-I can't go back to the house.
-Why?
I don't want
to take you back there either.
Becker and I
didn't see eye-to-eye on your refund.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
[inhales deeply] Becker's a bit off,
but he took care of me growing up.
Our dad, I had a hard time with him.
Becker stuck up for me.
But he's sick now.
And the way I see it,
he looked after me…
Now it's my turn.
You know what I mean?
Come on. Let's get your money.
[ominous music playing]
[music intensifies]
-[door opens]
-[indistinct chatter]
The money's in your room.
[pop music playing over speakers]
What did I tell you girls
about smoking in the lounge?
[Maria] We weren't.
Ambar, come have a drink.
No, I'm not staying. Thank you.
[in Romanian] Come help me!
[in English] Red, where's the wine going?
[Red] Wherever. I'll be there in a minute.
[indistinct chatter]
[chatter and laughter continue]
[footsteps approaching]
[switch clicks]
[drawers clattering]
[Red] You sure you don't want a drink?
Where's my money?
You sure?
Where's my money, Red?
Suit yourself.
I know this house is kind of weird.
My dad used to dig up
and collect all this strange stuff.
He was a real nutjob. Killed our mom.
-I want to leave now.
-Come here, come on.
It'll warm you up.
Get out of my way.
[Red] I wish you hadn't called me.
-I was gonna help you.
-Get out--
I hope you know that part was true.
If you hadn't left,
I would've given you your money.
-You'd be out of here.
-Red.
But Becker…
He needs you.
Fuck you.
[sighs]
Let me make this as easy
as I can for you. You gotta drink--
[bangs on door]
[Ambar breathing heavily]
-Beck, I got this.
-Quiet.
-[Red] Beck, I got--
-Shut the fuck up.
[Becker chanting]
-[in English] Let me teach you something.
-[panting]
[Becker coughing]
Open your mouth.
[intense breathing]
Open
your mouth.
No.
[Ambar gagging]
[groans]
[Ambar gags, coughs]
[grunts, pants]
Please don't try to leave.
He'll make it way worse.
-[intense breathing]
-[door locks]
[sighs]
[footsteps approaching]
[Petra] Please?
[knocking on door]
[Petra] We come in, please?
[knocking continues]
-You're alone?
-[Petra] Yes.
[softly] Come on.
[locks door]
-Becker?
-Yes.
We should stay together.
-You want to fight him?
-No. He'll kill us.
-He's different. We must leave.
-Now?
No, he's downstairs,
always by the basement door.
We should wait.
But in day he sleeps.
You think they're keeping
other women in the basement?
I don't know. I don't want to find out.
There's something wrong with this place.
What have you seen?
I keep dreaming about home.
My son is there.
But he's changed, something's different.
I like him like this.
I can't leave him.
So I hold him.
I hold him tight, do not let go.
And… And I see this box.
A stone box?
[sniffles]
[Petra] Even when I'm awake, I see it.
-I've seen it too.
-[Maria] No.
[sobbing]
[Petra] I think the box is here.
Where?
Basement.
I want to go home.
[ominous music playing]
[metal scraping]
[Becker grunts]
[Becker coughs]
[thumps]
[woman crying]
[woman speaking indistinctly]
[Petra] You hear it too?
Yeah.
All night, the same.
Women crying.
[in Romanian] They're dead.
[Petra sings in Romanian]
[Petra continues singing]
[singing continues]
Ambar.
[in Spanish] Stay a little longer.
[Petra whispers] Ambar.
[Ambar gasps]
-[Petra] Ambar. Wake up!
-[Red] Come here.
[Petra speaks Romanian]
-[Maria in English] No, Petra!
-[Red] Get up!
-[Ambar grunts]
-[Red groans]
-[Red] Beck!
-No!
[Red groans]
[Ambar groans, coughs]
-[panting]
-[Ambar coughing]
[doorbell ringing]
[sinister music playing]
-[Becker grunts]
-[Ambar groans]
-[door closes]
-[Becker] Go.
-[Red] Why do I have to--
-[Becker] Now!
[doorbell continues ringing]
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-[banging on door]
[exhales] Hey, man.
It's a little early to be coming around.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but I'm looking for somebody.
Her name is Ambar Cruz.
-Sorry, don't know her.
-She's 5'7", brown hair, this long.
-She said that she was living here.
-[Red] Still no.
-[Beto] I'm sorry. I know it's early, but…
-[Ambar panting]
-Beto!
-[Red] Like I said, I ain't seen her.
She's in trouble.
Maybe she isn't using her real name.
If she's lying to you about that,
maybe she's lying to you
about where she's staying.
[Beto] Yeah, I just want to be sure,
you know?
-[Ambar] Beto!
-[Red] Hombre.
She ain't here.
That's her coat.
-What the hell are you talking about?
-[Ambar] Beto!
-That's her coat. My wife gave--
-Hombre, settle down!
-Don't hombre me--
-[glass shatters]
[in Spanish] Beto, help!
[grunts] Ambar!
-Ambar!
-Beto, up here! Third floor!
Beto!
[grunts]
[Red] Becker!
[Ambar] Beto!
-[banging on door]
-[doorknob rattling]
[Beto] Ambar!
[Red] Becker!
-[Beto in Spanish] Where are you?
-[Ambar] Beto!
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
Step back!
Beto, watch out, there's another guy!
-[Beto groans]
-[Ambar in English] Stop! Stop!
-[punches landing]
-[Beto groaning]
Leave him alone!
[screams] Leave him alone!
[punch landing]
[in Spanish] Son of a bitch!
-[Becker grunts]
-[punches landing]
[beating continues]
[Becker panting]
[sobbing]
[heavy panting]
Jesus, Beck. Look what you--
Prepare her.
Upstairs.
Now.
[wind whooshing]
[Maria sobbing]
[footsteps approaching]
-[crying] No! No!
-[Red] She's ready. Just calm down, man.
Her next.
[Maria speaking Romanian]
That's too many in one go, Beck.
You don't--
[Maria screaming, crying]
What are you going to do to us?
Are you going to kill us?
-Of course you're going to kill us.
-Quiet.
Why are you doing this?
I'm trying to help my brother.
[Ambar] By doing this?
He's sick.
You haven't seen him after,
there's benefits. Believe me.
We moved back home because we couldn't
afford Beck's medical bills.
He wasn't doing so good.
I wanted to convince the old man
to let us stay for a while.
Then we saw what he'd done…
to those girls.
He made Mom help him,
and then he killed her too.
Mary?
Yeah.
We did the world a favor,
getting rid of our dad.
I wanted to leave right after,
but Beck said we could fix the place up.
But just like Dad,
he started spending more time
with that damn box.
He thinks it chose him.
And then he started getting better.
Beck says he only needs
a few more hits,
and then we can stop all this.
Hits of what?
How many, Red?
-How many women?
-He's my fucking brother.
Okay.
You need to get out of here.
[Red] We're done.
[whispers] Red.
Hey.
Hey, look at me.
Come on, look at me.
Let's get out of here.
[exhales]
[keys jingling]
[clicks]
[chain clinking]
I'm sorry, chica.
[footsteps approaching]
Red.
-She's almost done. Just gotta--
-Her next.
[panting]
Don't fight.
The last one fought.
[knuckles cracking]
[gasps]
Stop!
[groans]
[gasps] No! No, no!
[crying] Red!
[screams] Red! Red!
No!
Help!
Get help.
Please!
Oh my God.
[crying] Stop. Stop!
[sobbing]
What the fuck.
Stop! Help!
Stop!
[screams] Help!
[grunting]
-[Becker panting]
-[Ambar grunts]
Please, please. Please wait--
[groans, coughs]
-[Becker] Quiet.
-[coughs]
[gasps, pants]
[crying] Oh my God.
No!
[sobbing]
[grunting]
[screams] No, no, no, no, no!
No! No! Stop!
[panting]
Becker-- Becker, Becker. Becker, stop.
Oh my God.
Becker. Becker, hey.
Please. Please stop. Please stop.
Come on. Come on, come on, come on.
Becker. Hey.
Becker.
Please let me go.
Come on.
[yells]
-[Becker chanting]
-No!
Please, let me go.
[ominous music playing]
[crying] Becker, Becker, please.
Please stop!
You should feel honored.
[door bangs shut]
[crying]
[panting]
Let me go. [panting]
[stone box droning]
[Ambar panting]
-[thudding]
-[whimpers]
No. No, no, no. No…
[rumbling]
[thudding gets louder]
Come on, come on.
[wheezing hiss approaching]
[wings fluttering]
[Ambar grunting]
[thudding, rumbling]
[panting]
[grunts]
[thudding, rumbling gets louder]
[grunting]
-Ambar?
-[Ambar] Beto?
-[in Spanish] Ambar, hold on.
-Beto.
[in English] Come on.
-[Ambar in Spanish] Are you okay?
-Yes, I am.
[wheezing hiss approaching]
[rumbling]
Let's go. Hurry.
[Ambar gasps]
[Beto] Help me!
Help me!
[eerie whispering]
[Beto] Together!
[lights flickering]
One more!
[Ambar yelling]
[Ambar] Beto?
Beto. [panting]
[inhales deeply]
[panting]
[Mama hums tranquil tune]
[humming continues]
[Mama]
You've always had such beautiful hair.
You'd brush it a hundred times
before letting me leave the house.
[Mama] And aren't you glad I did?
Yes.
[raspy breathing approaching]
[wings fluttering]
[rumbling]
[Mama] Can you stay a little longer?
Please stay.
[rumbling noise approaching]
[thudding]
[Mama] Stay with me.
I don't want you to go.
[breathing heavily]
[raspy breathing continues]
[lights flickering]
[rumbling noise approaching]
[squeaky call]
[wheezing hiss]
[Mama] I need you to stay with me.
[Mama] Can you stay a little longer?
[wheezing howl]
Stay a little longer?
No.
I can't stay here.
[Mama crying] I need you.
-Please, Mom, I have to go.
-You're too kind.
-No.
-[Mama] You need to stay, sweetheart.
-Stay a little longer.
-No.
-I can't do this again.
-Stay still.
No.
[Mama] Stay still.
[Ambar] No.
[both grunting]
[yells]
[Mama groans]
[lights flickering]
[Ambar whimpering]
[gasps, cries]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
[rumbling]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Petra screaming] No!
-[Becker roaring in the distance]
-[Petra grunting] No!
[panting]
[Petra continues screaming]
[Petra crying, speaking Romanian]
[Becker in English] Quiet.
[Petra crying] No…
What is it?
[suspenseful music continues]
-Go check.
-Why?
[Becker] Something's different.
Open it.
-Why? What is it?
-Just open it.
[music intensifies]
There's nothing.
[Ambar grunts]
[Red groans]
Fuck!
[Ambar grunts]
[Becker grunts]
[Becker groans]
[both grunting and groaning]
[screams]
[groans]
[Ambar] No, wait!
-[Petra grunts]
-[Becker groans]
[Petra screaming]
-[Becker grunts]
-[Petra screams]
[Becker panting]
[Ambar groaning]
-[Becker] Come on.
-[screams]
[Ambar] Stop! Stop!
-[Becker grunting]
-[Ambar groaning, choking]
[groans]
-[Ambar grunts]
-[gags]
[Becker choking]
[Ambar grunting]
-You won't--
-[Ambar grunts]
[Ambar screaming]
[drops weapon]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
[in Spanish] Motherfucker.
[groans]
[sniffles, groans]
[panting]
[Red groaning]
[groaning continues]
Please. I didn't mean to.
Please don't do this.
Ambar.
Beck.
[wheezing howl]
[raspy breathing]
[somber music playing]
[latches door]
[Ambar breathing heavily]
[raspy breathing]
[panting]
[exhales]
Aah!
[breathing heavily]
[fluttering]
[ominous music playing]
[rumbling]
[thumping]
[raspy breathing]
[calm music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[eerie music playing]
[sinister music playing]