Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
This city.
What can I tell you about the city?
New York.
A place where the men work hard
and the dames well,
they do what it is they do.
The lively city hides
the underbelly that runs
through the gutters
and the smoke filled streets.
That's where I come into play.
My name is Detective Sal Pelletier,
when I tell you I seen it all.
I mean, I seen it all, from
the mobsters to the whores,
the crooked bankers to the killers
that hide in the shadows,
waiting to strike
when an opportunity appears.
Sometimes I look out of
my window at this city
and then I look up at the sky
and I see dark clouds,
and all I can think is that God himself
is trying to hide this city
from his own eyes.
Oh, yeah,
I seen it all, alright.
But tonight's story doesn't take place
in some mobster's warehouse
or some rundown bar
full of the unfortunates
of this great city.
Our story takes place
in the suburbs of New York,
a nice street, a middle-class
household with a perfect lawn
and perfectly respectable residents.
But as we know all too well,
darkness can hide
in the lightest of places.
So let me tell you about Veronica.
Veronica, Smart.
Beautiful, intelligent,
but with a life that will be anything
but respectable.
Veronica was married to Cliff see.
They met when they were
just college sweethearts.
He'd done all right for himself
up in the high rises of work
with a love of a good woman at home.
But temptation can hide around
any corner of this great city.
And Cliff.
Well, Cliff had succumbed
to the ways of a woman
who wasn't his wife.
So that's where we meet them.
That's where we meet her.
Veronica Smart.
Welcome to the world of NOIR.
I wish we could stay here all day,
locked away in our own private heaven.
Well, it certainly beats a cheap motel.
I'll give you that.
There is nothing wrong with a cheap motel
for a quick getaway.
It's got clean sheets
and a firm mattress.
As long as the water is hot
and the shower works, then
we don't need anything else.
Oh, Cliff, you know, the sorts
who check into an
establishment like that,
as my mother would say,
they're not the respectable type.
Well, we are here in the house
perfectly respectable.
Well, sadly,
I've got to get back to work.
My boss can be a real tyrant.
Maybe if you ask him nicely
he'll give you the day off.
OK, Mr.
Smart, please, may
I take a leave of absence today?
Of course Miss Layton,
I'm sure you have
important business to attend to.
Very important and
very respectable business.
See, that's the problem.
Nothing about this is respectable.
The surroundings may be tasteful,
but we both know.
What we have is a good thing.
A quick getaway to a motel,
a few stolen moments in the office
with the blinds closed.
We can't do it anymore Cliff.
Do what?
Stop acting like a fool, Cliff.
We both know that you're not.
I'm a fool for you.
It's not funny Cliff,
nothing about this is funny.
You mean so much to me.
You know that, but
I can't break a vow I made to my wife.
I think you did already.
I think we should end it now.
You go back to being my boss.
I go back to my life, auditions,
and I can find somebody
who loves me and only me.
We can say hello,
go for the occasional
dinner with friends,
but that's all it could be Cliff.
I understand.
I do.
I know you deserve more, but Lana,
I don't want to be without you.
Cliff, did you hear that?
What?
Cliff thats the door.
Someone's trying to come in.
Get behind the door.
What? The door.
I'm not hiding from your wife
like I'm some sort of shameful secret.
Sweetheart, you are a shameful secret.
Lana, please.
Working hard.
I see.
My dear husband.
Sweetheart, baby.
What are you doing at home?
Well, I could ask you the same question,
but I think you have to you, Mrs.
Smart.
I just came to drop something
off to your.....
Oh, so you are aware he's married.
I did wonder whether you were clueless
or just a whore.
Mrs Smart,
this has never happened before.
I'm sorry.
What's your name?
It's Lana.
Please don't look at me like that.
We've all made mistakes,
and I'm sure that you've made a few
in your many years on the planet.
Let me give you a word of advice,
sweetheart, from me to you.
Looks fade.
I can see that, Mrs.
Smart.
Lana, maybe you should leave.
Say something, anything.
It's just...
It's just what, what
excuse are you going to throw at me?
We were just talking, I miss talking.
Feel like we don't do that anymore.
You don't want to hear about me?
Talk about us.
It's all auditions
or standing in line at some cattle call.
So this is my fault
because I have ambition?
I messed up.
That's on me.
It's just sometimes you
you feel so distant,
like something I can see,
but I just can't quite touch.
That, is for the cheap roll in the hay.
And that is for trying to put it on me.
I've told you Cliff,
I've told you for 16 years
that this dame has ambition,
that is what you married.
Sweetheart, listen to me.
I have been there for you.
I've loved you.
I've sdvoted my whole life to you.
I know,
I know, look, I'm crazy.
I should be locked in a loony bin
for what I just did.
Well, what can I do to make this better?
Well, I'm on my knees.
A broken and sorry, man.
Begging for your forgiveness.
Get up.
I can't stand weak.
A cheap night is one thing, but weakness.
That is something I won't accept.
I can't bear to see
the disappointment in your eyes.
Men disappoint Cliff.
It's who you are by nature.
I shouldn't be surprised.
What about the promises
you made me, huh?
You're 40, Veronica and still no baby?
You son of a bitch!
Maybe it's time to settle down
and become a housewife.
A mother, you know, a respectable job.
A respectable job.
It's not a job Cliff.
What's so wrong about
being a housewife or a mother.
It's sure as hell a lot more respectable
than this silly, childish dream.
What did you just say?
You heard
and I ain't apologising for saying it.
Goddamn Veronica.
I thought this job at the school
teaching art would make you happy,
you seemed so excited.
Firstly, I don't start
until tomorrow, and secondly,
the only reason I took
this job was to get
me out of this goddamn house.
Oh.
As well as giving you more time
to bring your lady friends home.
Do you think I ever wanted
to be the kind of guy
who stepped out on his lady?
No.
But Lana listens to me,
she cares about what I have to say.
Well that must have been
wonderful for you.
Look, I have things that I need.
The guys are always asking,
when are we going to welcome our own
little bundle of joy in the world?
What am I supposed to tell them?
Where the hell are you going?
I have come home to find you
in bed with another woman,
and yet somehow you've
managed to make that my fault.
I ain't blaming you, baby.
Make friends with the
spare bed tonight Cliff.
I have a feeling
you two are going to become very close.
Take your filthy
cheating hands off of me.
Veronica, ain't the forgiving type.
They say hell hath
no fury like a woman scorned.
Well, that saying
could have been created
for Veronica herself.
So
the next day, Veronica
would start a new job
teaching the kids in the ways of art.
When she walkd in the door
she sure as hell didn't look like
no teacher I'd ever seen.
Is that for me?
Yeah.
Good morning, class.
My name is Veronica or Mrs.
Smart.
Good morning, Mrs.
Now I'm here to teach you
the beauty of the arts.
She was a piece of work, all right.
Jimmy was mesmerized.
He was only one of a few.
She could have been
talking about anything,
but he wouldn't hear a word.
Who is this woman?
She's like a real life
movie star in front of me.
I can't concentrate.
I think she knows
that I'm staring at her,
but I can't look away.
It's like somebody pinned my eyes open
in only her direction.
Her legs, her breasts.
The lashings of red lipstick
illuminating this gray
and drab classroom.
I'm aroused.
I can't let her see.
Of course, she saw that.
S he's smiling.
Shit, she saw me.
Who is this woman?
And James, isn't it?
What? Oh, yeah, James.
Well, Jimmy, OK, Jimmy,
what kind of art excites you?
Well, I think that art is all around us.
An old lady selling roses on the street.
Rain on a humid day.
A beautiful woman.
Of course,
that might be the most exquisite
work of art ever.
Who is this woman?
She's beautiful.
She's confident.
She's everything that a girl like me
dreams of becoming.
I want to stare at her.
Like a gentleman would stare
at an exquisite painting.
Oh, look at her hair.
Her long hair that cascades down her back
blonde, no golden.
I want to know her.
I want her to know me.
Who is this woman?
And Vivian, isn't it?
Yeah, I'm Vivian.
OK, Vivian.
So what kind of art do you like?
Vivian's art is about
as interesting as her.
You think it's OK to berate
a woman in front of her class?
Now, let me tell you something.
There's only one thing
this world hates more than a crook.
And that is a bully.
Why don't you apologize
to Miss Pierce here and pray
she's understanding
enough to forgive you.
Sorry, Vivian.
It's OK.
Now, Vivien,
what kind of art do you like?
Oh, Vivian's just kooky
for the movie pictures.
Oh, hi, I'm Betty.
I'm Vivian's best friend.
Well, it's lovely to meet you, Betty.
So, Vivian, the movie pictures?
Yeah,
but it's a world
so far away from us, ordinary people,
that I'll never get to experience that.
And why do you think that?
Because we're nobody.
Well, I don't believe that's true at all.
Now, it's my understanding
that your previous teacher
gave you all the picture of a famous
painting to discuss.
So why don't we start there?
OK.
Well, I guess I just don't see it.
Don't see what?
Well it's nice I guess.
but it's kind of simple.
Why is it so famous
when many people can draw this way?
You think you could do an oil
painting like Thomas Hart Benton?
I'm not saying that I could,
but I know others who could.
Now, does anybody else have an opinion
on the painting?
It feels cold.
The towering skyscrapers
below a darkened sky.
The American flag
blowing in the wind, but
the colors are muted.
I like the way it feels stationary
like the moment froze
and he painted that way.
It seems bleak, though,
but at the same time
saying that the artist
was seeing things that way.
Yeah.
Like he at that moment, maybe
wanted to change or was battling
something within himself.
It shows that behind
the beauty of the city is a danger.
Maybe not everything
is as it appears to be.
Jimmy, Vivian, that was beautifully put.
Jimmy, Jimmy, you got to light?
Yeah, sure.
You know, I really enjoyed
your class today.
It's nice to have a teacher
that knows about the subject
that they're teaching.
Well, thank you very much.
You know, you seem to understand
it quite well yourself.
Well, when you spend a lot of time alone,
gives you time to read.
Jimmy, can I say something?
Sure.
Your eye for the arts
is really rather extraordinary.
You seem to see things like somebody...
Older?
Older, yes.
Comforts me, honestly.
Sometimes I think
the real world can seem so.
grey, so...
Noisy? Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
But well, if you look at a painting
like Van Gogh's Cafe
Terrace at Night, well,
colours the soothing yet
vibrant feelings that it gives you.
Well, that's my escapism.
What got you into art Jimmy?
My mother.
I was just a kid.
I remember her
sat in the kitchen painting,
she used to always say that
the light in the kitchen was perfect,
and you must have good natural light.
I'd sit and watch her for hours.
I'd look at the bliss
on her face like she just
vanished.
Into her own magical world.
Well, you know, maybe that's something
you should take up for yourself.
Live your passion.
I said, I loved art,
I didn't say I could paint,
and trust me, I can't.
Plus guys like me from this place.
Well art exactly ain't In my future.
Where is your mother?
She skipped out on us when I was little,
so I got stuck with him.
God, I'm sorry, it's your first day
here, and I'm troubling you with my woes.
I found my husband in bed
with another woman last night.
I'm sorry. I.
I don't know why I told you that.
You know,
you're not like the women around here.
Jimmy, Jimmy.
Hey, Jimmy, you ready to go?
Yeah, sure. I'm just talking to Mrs.....
Have you seen Vivian?
Not since class,
oh wait here she comes, control yourself.
Vivian you look as beautiful
as a bright summers day.
Shut up Riff.
Mrs Smart .
I really enjoyed your class today.
It was very uplifting.
Uplifting?
Well, thank you very much, Betty.
Umm Mrs. Smart.
Can I just say that?
Wow.
You look like a movie star.
Well, so I've been told.
Actually I am an actress.
What, like in the movies?
Sure.
Well, only a few small roles,
but I have done many plays.
One critic once called me dazzling.
Dazzling. Wow.
That's my dream, to be somebody
that people talk about
my face on the big screen.
You would look magnificent Vivian,
a real bombshell.
Oh, you really think so, Riff?
Sure thing.
Well, you know,
I was actually thinking about
perhaps teaching,
acting to people like you, young people
who you want to make it in the movies.
Oh, this is smart.
I mean, I would love that.
Well, money.
My mother. Oh, baby.
And I wouldn't dream of charging.
Everybody deserves a shot.
Oh, Mrs.
Smart, then I would love to.
Oh, you have no idea
how happy this makes me.
How about you, Jimmy?
You have a face the camera would love.
Really?
Well, I don't know
about all that acting stuff, but
I'd sure love to sit and listen to
you talk about it.
Can I come, too?
I'm a real movie picture fan, you know.
Oh, well, sure.
Well, this sounds like a plan.
So why don't we say my place
tomorrow night, say 7:00?
What will your husband say?
Well, he's working
very late tomorrow night,
so we'll have the place to ourselves.
Well, I will be there with bells on.
Oh, maybe you could show me
how to make my hair like yours.
I think I would trade
in my best friend to look like you.
Wait, What? Vivian Pierce, where are you?
Great! Mother.
I was just talking to Mrs.
Smart.
She's my new teacher
and she's an actress.
It's lovely to meet you.
Charmed, I'm sure.
Now, Vivian, Betty
let's go
we're having an early supper tonight
before your father heads
off to work late, again.
Mrs Smart .
I can't wait for us to begin our lessons.
Mrs. Smart.
Boys.
I don't think she liked me very much.
She doesn't like anybody,
including her own husband.
Poor schlep.
I'd always had problems
in the neighborhood where kids
like Jimmy and Riff lived.
It wasn't the safest
of places in the town.
Poverty was the word of the day,
the kind of place the rest of the town
looked down on like a blemish
that wouldn't go away.
I think she looked at me today.
Who? Vivian.
I swear she did, Jimmy.
She looked round
and for a moment, our eyes connected.
I think you see what you want to see.
Trust me, I've known her for years.
You've known for years.
When has she ever shown
any interest in a guy like you?
What do you mean a guy like me?
What kind of crack is that?
No crack. It's cool.
It's just... It's just what?
Come on Riff,
you've been loopy for Vivian
since we were 10 years
old, it's time to move on.
Go swivel Jimmy.
Pair of aces.
Damn it, man.
I can't concentrate.
My mind feels like cotton candy.
I mean, it wasn't just me, right?
Mrs Smart is...
A babe?
A doll?
Yeah, but it's more than that,
before you turned up
we were really talking.
Man.
She's like a hundred?
No, Jesus.
She's like 40 I bet.
That's a woman who's
seen a lot of things.
Yeah.
Like the backseat in many a Chevrolet.
Hey don't talk that way.
You shouldn't talk that way about a lady.
She's taken Jimmy,
did you not see the rock on her finger,
He's a deadbeat, he cheats on her?
Wait she told you this?
Yeah, I told you we talked.
Damn it.
I can't wait to see her tomorrow.
Oh you are lost to the darkside
my friend. Darkside?
Women.
And Vivien?
It's Destiny.
Seeing her today just made me realise
girls, they don't know anything
about life, love,
sex... Sex.
You think you're going to be
playing backseat bingo with her?
No, you clown.
I'm just saying that
today opened my eyes.
I mean, come on.
She's like something from a movie.
Well, Jimmy, as much fun
as it is, I really got to go.
I'm going to miss the best time.
Riff,
I can speak to my old man.
See if you can stay with us.
You don't deserve to
be out on the street.
You got to be able to...
I know, Jimmy, you've
given me the same speech
since the funeral.
But I'm fine. Really?
I got everything under control.
Yeah, but I got this, Jimmy.
Sleeping down the docks again tonight?
Yeah, I found this great old building.
I share it with like 300 bats.
Shut up.
You hear that?
Oh, shit.
My dad's home. Jimmy!
So this is what happens
when I'm not here?
No.
You just thought you would
steal my cigarettes
and act like a big man
when I ain't around.
I should go.
It's lovely to see you, Mr. Flynn.
May I say you are looking
particularly rugged today.
Get out!
I'm going to go to my room.
Why?
You scared of your old man?
No, sir.
I just.
So you think you're a man now
because you started smoking cigarettes?
Go on.
Show me how much of a man you really are.
Leave me alone.
You know, we should put a dress on you
so anyone can see
how much of a girl you are.
Look at you,
you dress like some rebel
but you,
you're as soft as a newborn
babies backside.
Oh, wait.
I need you down at the garage
tomorrow night,
we've got two cars coming in
that need to be finished.
Sure.
Oh, no, I can't.
I've already made plans.
Plans?
You don't have plans
you're just a kid.
I'm sixteen.
I'm sorry, Dad,
but I can't make it tomorrow.
Oh, you will be there,
or you can pack up your stuff
and see how you do out there on the street
Dad please.
You are sixteen Jimmy,
it's time to be a man
and make an honest wage.
You can't expect me
to have you here living forever.
Now, go to your room and stay there,
I got a friend
coming over tonight
and I do not want to be disturbed.
A woman?
None of your goddamn business,
you don't even know what a woman is.
Now get out of my sight.
Yes sir.
At Vivian's house.
Well, Vivian was brought up
under the eyes of God,
a devout kind of family,
a cross on the wall
and a Bible on the nightstand.
But Vivian is a teenage girl
starting to question things.
I'm glad your mother
let me stay over Vivian.
Oh, me too.
Plus, I know it's
your father's cards night?
His friends give me the heebie jeebies.
Betty, do you think I could ever look
like Veronica Smart?
Vivian, you've not stopped
talking about her since we left school.
Sorry Betty, it's just
I've only ever seen women
like her in the pages
of our celebrity magazine.
Imagine a woman like that.
Living right here in our town.
You sound screwy Vivian Pierce.
It's not like she's Lana Turner.
Oh she was so perfect.
OK, I'm officially ignoring you.
Sorry, Betty.
You are going to come to hers
tomorrow, though, of course.
No way.
My mother would flip her wig.
She thinks that actors
are lower than whores.
Her words, not mine.
Well, I think your mother and my mother
are the same person.
I'm going to brush my teeth.
It's spearmint!
Oooh, I'm sorry Mrs Pierce.
Now, Vivien, I need to talk to you.
Am I in trouble?
No, I'm worried about you.
And so is your father.
You come home from school and disappear
so fast to your room
that we barely get a hello.
I'm fine, mother, honestly.
It's just.
Oh Vivian, it's just what?
Well, when did you first start
to get feelings for boys?
You know, in the non friend way?
Vivian, you are too young
to be thinking about that.
I'm fifteen mother, please.
There is a time and place for a man
and that time is not now.
Do you want to end up like the neighbours
daughter out all hours, drinking,
cavorting around
with every boy that looks at her?
Sure sounds more fun than this.
Look.
I know I sound harsh,
and I'm not saying
that when you're older,
you can't make your own choices,
but I have to guide you now
so those choices
you make in the future are good ones.
Worrying about boys and playing this
kind of music is most
certainly not a good one.
It's just music, mother.
I don't think Satan plans
on coming through my record player
to corrupt me.
Vivian!
You are not too old to be put over
your father's knee.
Sorry, mother.
You just need to say
your prayers before bed.
Go to church.
Study hard.
And then you can think about a husband.
But mother, if I'm too young to date,
surely I'm too young to think
about a husband.
Vivian.
Nobody likes a smart mouth.
Now turn those records off
It's time for bed for you two.
Oh no, five more minutes mother, please.
Fine.
Five more minutes then bed.
OK.
Oh, sorry Mrs Pierce.
Oh Vivian,
I forgot to mention,
I think I know who was going
to ask you to the dance.
Do you think she would let me
try on one of her dresses?
Oh, I bet she gets them from Europe.
OK, good night, Vivian.
Sorry, Betty.
After catching Cliff
and Lana in the sinful act,
something in Veronica changed
or maybe just brought
the real her to the surface.
Either way, the kids were so blinded
by her, they wouldn't see anything
the dame wouldn't allow them to see.
It's the evening after
and Cliff is away with work.
Veronica, well Veronica
is dressed like a goddamn lounge
singer, wearing a bright red dress,
showing off all her killer curves.
Anybody order a group of street rats?
Speak for yourself Riff Randall.
I am so pleased you could all make it,
come in.
Woah!
You've got a real nice
pile of bricks here Mrs Smart.
Oh, please call me Veronica.
OK, Veronica.
Now, who would like a drink,
something to get this party started?
Alcoholic?
I won't tell anyone if you won't.
Then I'll have a beer.
How about you two?
Oh, no, just a lemonade for me, please.
Sure. You got whiskey?
I do indeed.
So I heard your old man
is stepping out on you.
Riff, Jesus.
No, it's fine, honestly.
Men are pigs.
(Pig noises)
Mrs. Smart?
Um, I mean, Veronica,
your dress is so magnificent.
Oh, what? This old thing.
Oh, I would love a dress like that.
And your hair.
How do you get it to look so glamorous?
Vivian.
Well, I think you have a beautiful face,
stunning bone structure, and those eyes.
They could melt the heart of a sailor.
Oh, oh, oh.
Ok Vivian, relax.
I could relax you, Vivian.
Ewww.
Do I see a little love connection here?
Flirtation?
No, you do not.
Riff has been trying to get me to go
steady with him since
we're six years old.
He's not my type.
Maybe you don't know what your type is.
So how about you, Jimmy?
You got a lady in your life?
Girls my age aren't appealing to me.
I'm going to wait
till after high school to find my girl.
I see.
Can I get another drink?
Oh, sure, help yourself.
But just don't let your parents know
I'm letting you drink liquor.
Can I smoke?
Sure.
As long as I can bum one from you.
Can I bum one also?
Here, Vivian, let me light it for you.
I think I'll save this for later.
So, Jimmy, when you're alone,
what is it you like to do?
Listen to music, read books,
play my guitar.
Oh the guitar.
I play the violin.
Oh really, well the violin,
the guitar, hell even the goddamn drums.
I think it's all wonderful.
Hey, Riff, turn up the music.
Let's dance.
What? Here, now?
Here and now is all we have Jimmy Flynn.
Veronica, Riff and Jimmy
danced around the room.
Veronica looked happy and the kids ate up
that happiness with a silver spoon.
Jimmy played it cool,
leaning on the cabinet of trophys
from her husband's college days.
It's rude to stare, Jimmy.
I'm sorry.
The last man who stared at me
that way, ended up laying
beside me for the next 16 years.
She got him!
Oh, I'm so, so sorry.
I'll clean all that up.
It's fine, honestly.
My husband, he breaks a lot of glasses.
What's he doing?
Throwing them around the house.
In that moment, Veronica started to lie.
Yeah. Sometimes he...
He what?
Never mind.
Marriage is tough kids.
You try so hard to
to be the perfect housewife,
and yet still it's
it's never quite enough.
He cheated, many times I suspect,
he didn't even apologize.
He just said that
the man's got to do
what a man's got to do.
That's what he said.
Listen to me bringing the party down.
I'm so sorry whilst
we are here in this house.
Let's forget all the bad in our lives
and just focus on the good.
Oh, Veronica, I just wanted to ask,
what movies have you starred in?
Did you see Hunt for Love
with Cary Grant?
Oh, I love that movie.
Well, I was the nurse
who got him back to health.
So you met him?
Darling, met him? We're friends,
we bonded over our love
for the silent movies.
Oh, Vivian.
The stories I could tell you.
Oh, I would love to hear them.
So, Jimmy, you got a talent?
Boosting cars?
Mmm, a bad boy?
I prefer rebel.
You have ice?
Sure it's in the kitchen.
Help yourself.
Vivian why don't you help
Riff with the ice
and maybe bring in some snacks?
Sure thing.
Veronica, why us?
What do you mean Riff?
Why would you want to be friends with us?
I mean,
you're a beautiful, wealthy woman.
We're hardly your usual crowd.
Honestly,
I never really fit in around here.
Housewives, they look
at me like I'm trash and the men
look at me with lustful eyes.
I guess
I just needed a change
of energy around me.
You know,
you have a really neat set of records.
Oh, thanks.
My husband hates them of course.
He's not really that big
into the music or movies or art.
He's a bit square when it comes
to those things.
You like this one?
Sure.
Tell me more about you, Jimmy.
What do you want to know?
Everything.
Well, I'm 16,
but I think I'm more mature my age.
I ride a motorcycle.
So, are you going to come over here
and dance with me
or you just going to leave
this girl dancing all by herself.
I love to dance.
I love to dance with a man
who loves to dance.
It's been a long time.
Forgive me for saying
but why not just ditch the loser
if he ain't keeping your engine running?
Oh, Jimmy, it's not as simple as that.
Let's just forget about him.
Let's just pretend that
nobody in the whole world is around.
We just keep on dancing.
Your smell it's.
It's
quite intoxicating.
You smell of cigarette
smoke, liquor and
engine fumes.
I'm sorry.
Don't be, I love that smell.
Jimmy, when you go out on your bike
where is it you go to?
I know a spot
out by the woods near the cemetery.
It's quiet.
Gives me time to think
Maybe I need a spot like that.
I can take you to mine.
On your bike?
Sure.
You could hop on and hold on.
We could go now.
Oh, Jimmy I'd love to.
We could come with you.
I have my car, I could drive us over.
Well, sure. I mean, why not?
The more the merrier.
Looks like tonight's
going to be quite an adventure.
Jimmy Flynn.
After a night of fun
with her new friends, the next day,
a Saturday, Veronica
travelled into the city to pay
a visit to Cliff
with a surprise for her sweetheart.
She had the perfect guise to see
if Cliff was a man of his word.
Good morning Mrs Smart.
Good to see you Mrs Smart.
He's in his office Mrs Smart.
Maybe I didn't make myself clear Cliff.
Sweetheart.
Baby, what are you doing here?
Oh, I had something to
attend to in the city,
so I thought I'd bring you a gift.
This is just work Veronica,
you think I'd fool around in my office?
I don't know, Cliff.
I didn't expect you
to fool around in our bedroom,
but you proved me wrong on that one.
Mrs Smart.
I understand what I did was wrong,
but I assure you
I don't want your husband.
You are acting crazy.
Oh, is that so?
And you are acting like a desperate fool.
Did I not tell you to get rid of her?
Excuse me.
She's leaving at the end of the week.
This is just work, Veronica.
You really expect me
to believe that this thing
will be gone by the end of the week?
That's right, Mrs.
Smart.
This "thing" handed in her notice today.
It's
true baby, Lana's an actress.
She's been auditioning
for new plays on Broadway.
And I found out today
that I got a part in the new
Eugene O'Neill play.
I leave in a week for two out of town
tryouts, then Broadway.
Baby.
Isn't that exciting?
Lana,
I need to have a talk with my husband.
Of course, Mrs Smart.
Honestly, I...
Out!
She's, she's leaving
at the end of the week,
why fire the girl
if she is going anyway.
She's an actress?
Yeah, baby.
Oh, like you.
Maybe she could put a word in for you.
You want your mistress
to put a good word in for your wife.
Are you hearing yourself, Cliff?
I'm just thinking of you, baby.
You know, Cliff,
for such a big shot,
you really are stupid.
You're attracted to her because.
She's me 16 years ago.
Baby that ain't true,
she can't hold a candle to you.
It is Cliff, she's living my life.
She gets to be the big star
while I'm stuck here teaching
kids to do what I should be doing.
God damn you Cliff,
you really know how to hurt a lady.
Well, I ain't trying to...
Don't.
Just don't Cliff.
I hurt too much.
Well,
what can I do, you want me to tell her
to leave right this moment
because I'll do it?
No, no Cliff.
Let your floozy stick around,
because the only thing I want.
Is the last 16 years of my life back.
Don't talk that way.
When I was a little girl,
I used to dream about what
my life would be like.
One thing I knew for certain.
Was that I wanted to be somebody?
I wanted more than
those four dark, damp walls that trapped
me as a child and I wanted more than
my mother's loneliness
and disappointment.
I just knew I needed more.
I would dance around in my room.
Arms extended, imagining I was
I was up on a stage,
a vaudeville show or movie
picture, I didn't care.
I just knew I needed more.
And then I met you.
Happiest day in my whole entire life.
And I thought to myself.
Could this be my more
to be this handsome man's wife
and I thought and thought.
And as much as I loved you,
I knew I just couldn't
give up on that part of my dream
with you.
You said all the right things
to ease my mind.
Do you remember,
do you remember what you said to me
when we first got together Cliff?
I said I could make you happy.
You said that
my dreams, my ambitions
would always be as important as yours,
that we would help each other
and support each other in it.
I remember thinking perfect.
Now I can be whole.
But you never, never
helped me or supported me,
not in any way that matters,
because you thought that eventually
I'd give up on that part of my life.
And I would just learn to be silent
and just become your wife.
Baby that ain't true.
It is Cliff.
When have you ever taken me Hollywood?
I have been asking you
for 16 years, but still
you've never taken me.
Baby, you don't need
Hollywood to be a star.
I know that.
But I need it to make me one.
Jesus, how the hell did I end up here?
Now.
Just stop that.
This ain't a bad life
you got for yourself here, Veronica.
Oh, Cliff.
These past few days have just confirmed
everything that I already knew.
You don't want me to have my more.
But you sure as hell want to have yours.
So that's it.
We even gonna talk?
Not now, Cliff.
I may say something that I truly regret.
Well.
Will, I see you at home later?
Go for a long walk after work tonight.
Maybe a couple of drinks,
because I really need some time
to figure out what it is that I want.
It ain't no mystery
that the youths who live in the slum
side of town lived a life of risk.
Some of the kids like Riff
didn't live with their parents.
For them it is the street.
Some have to work
their fingers to the bone,
sacrificing an education to pitch in.
Sure, the boys had a few run
ins with the law, but
it was petty stuff, mainly
just to put a hot meal inside them.
But these were good kids,
living in surroundings that could easily
take them down the wrong path.
That night, Jimmy
joined Riff by the Docks,
a regular hangout
for the undesirables of the city.
So what you get?
Two bucks and a coupon
for canned meat.
Damn it Jimmy, I can't keep doing this.
Doing what?
Pickpocketing, breaking
into people's houses.
Well you know what to do Riff.
I can't stay with you.
I ain't going to be a burden to nobody.
Riff you ain't no burden,
your my best friend.
I want to help.
Jimmy, your old man can
barely afford to keep you,
he ain't looking for
no new kid in the house.
I gotta have a future Jimmy, I just gotta.
This can't be it.
I know just how you feel Riff, but.
Well, that's a problem for another day.
No, it ain't, we're sixteen now Jimmy
there's a whole world
out there, opportunities you know.
Sure thing Riff, but that's a whole world
you and I ain't ever going to see.
Don't say that.
It's been one year
since my parents die.
Jeez.
I didn't even realise.
I'm sorry.
One year since the fire.
God, that one moment in my life
and I lost everything.
You know.
You are my family.
I know.
I mean, it is great.
But I mean, it's not the same.
After seeing Veronicas house
I got this aching feeling all over me.
What do you mean?
I got jealous?
All that money, the house,
all those rooms.
My house burns to the ground,
taking my parents with it and here I am.
When did we get chosen
to be the failures?
We ain't living in a world
that wants to hear what we got to say.
You know, people would rather
just walk past us, pretend we don't exist.
Why does it have to be final?
People must find a way out of this.
I mean, Jesus Jimmy,
my shoes are falling apart,
I haven't slept well
in a year, and I'm hungry.
I'm hungry all the time.
The only time I get to eat is at school.
Whatever happened to the American dream?
The thing with the American dream is
most of us wake up.
We move on.
Not everyone can be a success.
No.
Riff the streets are paved
with shit and poverty.
The gold, It's rare.
Now, we may never get the gold,
but we just got to avoid
the shit, you know.
So what, I just sit here
and hope some shlep
gives me a dime or two?
God bless America.
I can grab you something from my house.
Or I could.
Help.
You know.
If I gotta take something
heavy on, I'm doing it alone.
I'm fine, really Jimmy.
You just go home, I'll see you tomorrow.
I promise.
Alright.
You be careful out here,
you hear me.
Jimmy leaves Riff on the docks,
but as Riff follows him away
See you tomorrow Riff.
He sees a man walking down the docks.
Alone.
You need to eat Riff.
But as the figure gets closer.
Well, how could he know?
How could he have known the man
approaching was Cliff Smart,
wandering the streets,
thinking about his failures as a husband?
Hey, step aside.
Not so fast, mister.
I'm going to need ten,
I mean five bucks for you to pass.
A tax, if you will.
I said, get out of my way.
I ain't in the mood.
I ain't gonna ask you again.
Look at
you ain't getting anything from me.
So why don't you run
on home to mommy and daddy
so they can teach you some respect?
What did you say?
I said move.
I just need some money for some food...
Ain't interested in your sob story, kid.
Jesus.
Your parents sure as hell failed you.
Oh, you are dead!
I just wanted to eat,
why couldn't you see,
I ain't a bad kid, I swear.
I'm sorry, Mr.
I'm sorry.
Cliff.
What happened to you, are you ok?
Sure, act like you care, Veronica.
What a cold thing to say.
I ain't in the mood to argue.
Come here.
Let me see it.
Oh, that looks like a nasty gash,
I think we're going to have to call
Dr. Morgan out just to be safe.
I don't need that quack.
I'll be fine as soon
as my head stops spinning.
Well,
what happened to you?
It looks as though you were attacked.
I took a walk after work
down by the waterfront.
I went down through the tunnel
where the street kids live.
One of them hit me with a bat
and took my money,
son of a bitch.
If I ever lay my eyes on him again, then.
He ain't going to see his next birthday.
Why would you go down there?
I was trying to clear my mind.
You told me to take a walk.
You needed time.
But down there.
The police should take out
a gun and get rid of the vermin
who do nothing but dirty up the city.
Cliff, most of them are children
who have fallen on hard times.
Not everybody was
as privileged as you were.
Wait, your defending them?
No, no.
It's just.
Some of the kids I teach live down there,
you know, school is all they have
at given them any kind of a shot.
I just feel sorry for them.
Well they ain't getting a shot.
God don't pay no
attention to those kinds.
You really can be so cruel.
Hey, it's my head split open here.
So these boys, what do they look like?
All these street kids
look the same to me,
although I do know
that one of them was called Riff.
Riff? Yeah.
One of his friends shouted at him,
slipped up and used his name.
Degenerates.
He could have killed you.
Some say that the kids
never stood a chance.
They were broken,
searching for something more and easily
manipulated by a woman
who took advantage of it all.
I say, I guess that's for you to decide.
But one thing is undeniable.
She certainly shook things up all right
and she spun a web
that a vulnerable person could
easily fall into.
And Vivian, did.
You have been out after school
every evening this week,
where are you going?
I am not telling you mother,
because you'll only judge.
Fine.
Then you won't be leaving
this house tonight.
Vivian Pierce.
I am not a child anymore.
I'm fifteen.
A child is exactly what you are.
You're out with those boys again.
Do you think I don't know that
you can't outsmart your mother.
Ha!
Then you're wrong.
Vivian!
I've been going to see
my new teacher, actually.
Mrs Smart?
The lady I met?
Yes.
She's been teaching me all about
how to make it in Hollywood.
Private lessons for free.
Oh, mother.
She's one of the most fascinating
people I've ever met.
Acting, no.
But mother, it's
something I want so bad that it hurts.
Oh, Vivian,
you are not going to be a movie star.
You are far too plain looking.
No, no, I'm not,
I've got great bone structure.
Veronica told me.
I don't know what's going on
with you, Vivian, but I don't like it.
Why can't you just be happy?
Because I've lived Vivian.
I know the dangers
and I want to protect you.
I am going, mother.
It's a scary world out there.
And people's motives aren't always
what they appear to be.
Living with that fear
is not living, mother.
Now.
I'll be home by ten.
Don't wait up.
My dad doesn't show love.
He hates me.
No.
It's cool.
Sometimes you're not supposed
to like your parents
or they're not supposed to like you,
I guess.
That's tough.
Jimmy, what scares you?
I guess, turning out like him.
Staying in this town
my soul rotting away
until there's nothing left.
Just a black hole.
You can always leave.
And go where?
It's a pipe dream,
I'm never going to have
that kind of money.
Well, all I can do is
wait for the old man to meet his maker.
Maybe I'll get the house, you know,
sell it and leave, but.
Until then I guess I just.
stay still.
Motionless.
Like a car without an engine.
I guess we all get stuck
from time to time in a position
that we just can't get out of.
Your husband?
I feel like I'm drowning
in my own personal hell.
Then why don't you just leave him?
It's not as simple as that,
he owns everything, the house,
the cars, the money.
I have nothing.
Material stuff isn't everything.
It is Jimmy.
You can't live without money.
I should have been somebody by now,
but he's always held me back,
he's never let me be who I should be.
You know what, if this is it for me
now, what if my....
what if my time is done?
It doesn't have to be.
Oh would you listen to me?
I'm so sorry, I shouldn't
be putting my problems onto you.
Can you forgive me.
You have done nothing to be forgiven for.
Jimmy?
Would you excuse me for a moment?
I'll be right back.
Veronica gets up and leaves the room,
leaving Jimmy alone.
What is she doing?
What is she up to?
Everything about it was calculated,
you see, every word,
every gesture, every move.
When she walked back into the room,
her motives were clear.
But as Veronica seduced
Jimmy in her marital bed,
both had failed to notice
that Vivian had arrived and she saw all
she needed to see.
Honey,
I'm home.
Cliff, another night with Lana?
No, I was with a friend,
a man can have friends, you know,
And what a good friend she is.
And, uh, what about you, my dear wife?
How did you spend your evening?
Well, I thought I'd invite
some men over and start
a torrid affair behind your back.
That's funny.
Oh, I'm drunk.
So I see.
What the hell is this?
What?
Don't tell me
the several guys
who came to visit with you, right?
Yes Cliff.
That's exactly right.
Have you got some guy Veronica?
Yes, actually,
his names Jimmy.
Oh,
and Riff,
and Vivian.
Two guys
in my house with my wife.
Are you completely insane?
Oh, relax, Cliff.
It's just three students
that I teach over at the school.
I'm giving them private acting lessons.
Why didn't you tell me?
Would you care?
I care,
I always care.
God we used to laugh.
We used to make love all night.
We used to talk until the early hours
of the morning, but
now I.
I barely get a hello.
Godammit Veronica,
I'm hurting, I'm hurting real bad
and if your not ready
to forgive me then...
What?
What Cliff?
Oh, God damn it Veronica,
you are milking this for all you can.
How do I know that
you ain't cheating, huh?
I mean, you said you've
had these kids over, but
how do I know that ain't a cover
and you've been stepping out on me?
Veronica, steady as a rock rises
slowly out of her chair.
Has the cat got your tongue Veronica.
Hahaha.
Where the hell are you going Veronica?
Veronica!
God damn,
what the hell are you doing Cliff.
(Motorcycle Sound)
(Thunder)
Jimmy, thank God you came,
I didn't know who else to call.
Of course I came.
You sounded scared.
I knew something was wrong.
Of course you did,
because you get me, Jimmy.
I knew it from the first day we met.
Oh, God.
Jimmy, what am I doing?
Talk to me.
Wipe your tears and talk to me.
What happened?
Jimmy, he was so angry
when he came home tonight.
It was like his face changed
into something I'd never seen before.
What did he do?
Jimmy, the violence in his eyes.
He hit you?
And then Veronica lied.
Yes, I think he wanted to hurt me.
After he struck my face,
he just started yelling at me.
He called me names that no woman
should ever be called.
That son of a bitch.
He started ripping at my clothes
like a wild beast would do his eyes,
they were so black, blacker
than the darkest of nights.
How can a man put his hands
on a woman like that?
I mean, I know that I'm not perfect,
but even I know that when a guy meets
a girl like you,
she should be treated
like the queen that she is.
Oh, Jimmy.
Jimmy your words, I love your words.
But I think Cliff thinks...
What? What does he think?
That maybe I talk about
a certain student too much.
Perhaps I'm looking at him with eyes.
I used to look at my husband with.
Jimmy, do you look at me that way?
Veronica, I can't
stop thinking about you.
The other night...
But this is wrong.
Everything about this is wrong.
I'm your teacher.
You're only sixteen.
Men have done great things
at sixteen I told you
I'm more mature.
Yes, I see that, I see it all,
that beauty, God such beauty.
Jimmy, what are we doing?
I don't know, but
I don't want it to stop.
I can't stop thinking about kissing you,
your arms wrapped around me tight.
Veronica.
To look into your beautiful eyes
as you make love to me
all night long again.
I want to kiss you so bad.
But I ain't about to cause
you any problems.
Oh, Jimmy.
You're not my problem, don't you see?
You're my bright, shining light.
The two kiss passionately
as the rain pours down,
maybe to wash their sins away.
It was a point of no return.
Love, lust, desperation, manipulation.
Nobody knew at that point,
least of all Jimmy Flynn,
a sixteen year old boy
whose fantasy was coming to life.
So what do you think, Betty?
I think your mothers going to send you to
a convent in a dress like that.
Where did you get it from?
Oh, Veronica gave it to me.
She said I should really start
to dress to be the person I want to be.
A bar room hooker?
No Betty, a movie star.
I don't even know why you think
she's so special.
She's hardly a young starlet.
You don't understand, Betty.
Her husband stopped her
going into the movies anymore.
She used to be somebody.
Oh, really?
Is that what she told you?
Why aren't you happy for me?
You know, Veronica said
you should really
surround yourself with people
who believe in you.
Jeez.
Are you trying to say I'm not supportive.
I just think you could embrace
my new look more.
I would if Veronica wasnt trying
to turn you into
something that you ain't.
I would if I wasn't
losing my best friend to her.
Oh, that's rather dramatic, Betty.
Really?
You were supposed to stay at mine
last night but you never showed.
Oh, jeez, Betty.
I'm so sorry.
I completely forgot.
It's like you love her.
I admire her.
And I just want to be like her.
I mean, what kind of life do I
really have after school huh?
Veronica's just showing me a new way.
So I see.
Mother, I...
What on earth do you think you are doing?
It's just a dress Mother.
You look like one of
the girls who frequent the men's clubs.
Mother,
I am changing.
You need to understand that.
You are a little girl playing dress up.
Now, take it off
I don't want to see you in that again.
No, mother.
This is the new me.
And if you can't accept that,
then we really don't
have anything else to discuss.
How dare you talk to me in that way?
Your father is going to hear about this
and then you will be sorry.
Stop trying to turn me into you.
I want more from my life
than what you have,
and I'm sorry, mother,
but if this was my life,
I would kill myself.
Vivian.
I should go.
Ah, Jimmy, hey, pass me that wrench.
OK, but it's midnight dad I gotta go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, woah.
Help me up.
Where the hell do you think you're going?
To meet my friends, I told you.
Not tonight.
Dad.
I said not tonight.
I need you here.
I don't want to work here, dad.
I got other dreams
that I want to achieve,
and I've been here all day.
It ain't like I'm getting paid.
You have a roof over your head
and hot meals on the table.
I'm your son.
I ain't some employee.
Don't you want more for me?
What I want is for
you to watch your mouth
and get back to work.
Dad, please.
I've really got to see someone tonight.
Who?
Who is more important than your old man?
You wouldn't understand.
A broad,
you want to skip out with some dame?
This ain't some broad dad, she's special.
She makes me feel
I ain't the disappointment
you keep reminding me I am.
Jimmy. You ain't going.
Yeah, watch me.
Oh, what? What?
You going to beat me again, huh?
Old man,
I ain't gonna let
you knock me around anymore.
Why you always got to see me
as the bad guy, Jimmy.
I'm just doing my best to guide you.
Guide me?
You mean destroy me.
You know, I'd have more respect
if you told me that you hated me.
I don't hate you Jimmy.
I just know what's best for you.
You don't even know
what's best for yourself.
Jimmy!
Get back here now!
Veronica was like a whirlwind,
she was already leaving her mark
and what a mark it was.
But that night as clouds
rolled over the city,
things will take a turn, a dark turn
that will change everything.
It's nice, isn't it.
Us being able to do this.
These past few weeks with you
have been incredible Veronica.
They sure have and you're right,
it is nice.
I just wish it could be
like this all the time.
Yeah.
Wake up in the morning,
take a ride on my bike
wherever you want to go.
Hollywood.
Hollywood, it is.
We could watch the sunset
over the City of Angels.
We could hold each other tightly wrapped
up, nice and warm in a blanket.
Do you think it could
ever happen, Veronica?
That you leave Cliff.
If I had the money, the security.
I would in a heartbeat Jimmy.
I have a little saved.
That's very sweet,
but a little saved,
won't get us very far.
If only Cliff wasn't around.
Yeah.
If only.
I don't think you're old enough
to be drinking my liquor.
Who the hell are you?
The man of the house.
Oh, Mr. Smart.
Wait a minute, I know you,
Oh, shit!
it's you, the kid with the bat.
Mister I didn't know
you were Veronica's husband.
You are dead!
Get the hell of him Mr Smart, run Riff!
Why are you in my house?
We know your wife.
She's teaching us, asking.
Where's my wife?
She's upstairs.
Do you want me to go get her?
Is she alone?
Alone?
Is my wife alone?
Get the hell out of my house.
Now, and you tell your friend
I'll be seeing you again Riff, real soon.
What the hell is this?
Cliff, I didn't expect you home tonight.
So I see.
So when I'm gone, you
have kids over to get drunk in my house.
These are your new......
friends?
I told you Cliff,
I'm giving them acting lessons.
Oh, yeah.
So what's this?
Some kind of love scene
in my bed?
Excuse me?
Jimmy, you should go.
Yeah, Jimmy,
maybe you should leave my bedroom,
that I share with my wife.
We were just talking, must
you act like such a brute.
Mr Smart, Veronica and I....
There ain't no Veronica and you kid, now
run home like a good little boy.
Cliff.
Get out of my house.
I said, get out of my house.
What's wrong?
Do you not hear too good?
I said, get out of my house.
Cliff!
Stop it, stop it.
You've been looking at my wife?
Touching her?
If you're man enough to go near her,
you're man enough to fight me.
Cliff!
If you don't leave him alone
I'm going to call the police.
I know your type, Jimmy.
Oh, you think you can get
what you want from her. Huh?
Maybe you should stick
to the slum side of town
because I don't ever want
to see you around here again.
I'm going alright .
I'm going.
Stay away from my wife, Jimmy.
Or I'll rip you to pieces,
limb by limb,
do we understand each other?
How dare you?
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Don't.
Don't talk to me.
We were just working Cliff.
And the kids downstairs?
Students.
The boy that attacked me
with the bat, that was him
that sewer rat was in my living room.
But I'm sure he didn't know who you were.
He could have killed me
and what would you have done then, huh?
One of your students attacks
your husband, bashes his skull in.
Jesus, what kind of company do you keep?
Cliff wait.
Do you want me divorce you,
leave you with nothing?
No Cliff, you're getting it all wrong.
Good night,
my dear wife.
Now, here is the thing.
This dame ain't going to do
well in poverty.
Poor is not a style she wears well.
Well, this is the part
you may not believe, but I assure you
every word is true.
Veronica slammed her face
against the hard wall.
Why?
Well, after a quick phone
call to a distraught Jimmy and a late
night meeting arranged,
a bruise would sell Veronica's
story perfectly.
Oh, God.
Jimmy, Jimmy, are you OK?
Son of a bitch.
Your face, what did he do to your face?
I told you, Jimmy.
He's a violent brute of a man.
I never wanted you to get hurt.
Forget about me.
We need to get you away from him.
He can't do this to you.
But how?
Just, just leave him.
Who cares if he leaves you with nothing?
You have me.
We have each other.
Jimmy, you're young.
You don't understand
how much living can cost.
We would be broke, unhappy
and resenting each other in no time.
Face it Jimmy.
I'm stuck with him until my dying day.
No.
No, we have to think of another way.
I can't live another day without you.
I love you.
Jimmy.
Do you love me?
Everything about this is wrong,
and yet I have never felt more safe
in anyone's arms as I do in yours.
I want to go back there and show him
who's the man around here.
Jimmy,
I just had a thought.
A horrible thought.
What is it, Veronica?
Tell me.
I couldn't.
It's too awful.
Yes, you can just
just say it.
Well, the way I see it
is that only Cliff and the lack of money
stands in the way of true happiness.
OK.
But if Cliff wasn't around,
if Cliff died, I would get everything.
We would have everything
we need to have the
perfect life together.
But he isn't going anywhere.
You saw him.
He's as strong as an ox.
Jimmy, I could pay,
I could pay anyone who helps.
I mean, think about it, Jimmy.
This is New York.
People die all the time.
We could say that
it was a robbery gone bad.
Nobody would suspect you.
Why would they?
Nobody knows about us
other than those two.
And they won't say a word.
I will make sure of that.
Think about it, Jimmy.
Think about it, this could work,
we could be free.
What are you saying, Veronica?
Jimmy,
I want you to kill my husband.
(Thunder Crashes)
What's all this?
I did you the favour of packing
your bags for you baby?
You're absurd Cliff.
Look, I don't want to hear it Veronica,
seeing you sat on our bed with
that kid was one thing,
but it was the look in your eyes
that told me everything.
What are you talking about?
The betrayal was in your eyes.
I saw it the moment
I walked in the bedroom.
Oh, you're talking in circles Cliff.
Why aren't you listening to me!
Cliff!
I want you gone Veronica.
I am done.
You lie, all you do is lie.
I can't trust you, I can't trust a word
that comes out of your mouth.
You strung me along for years.
You never had any intention
of becoming a mother.
I see that now.
Now you're painting yourself
as a victim Cliff.
Again, you cheated.
This isn't about that.
Look I haven't got a future with you.
I see that now baby, you've made
that perfectly clear.
You son of a bitch.
Well if you think I'm
walking away from this marriage
with nothing but a few cases of clothing?
Well, there it is.
Money, belongings and things.
That's all you care about,
right, Veronica?
You won't get away with this.
Big words, but we both know that I will.
You are making a mistake, Cliff.
You know, um.
That
kid, Riff, the kid that was in my house.
What about him?
Look, just a pretty small world ain't it.
Just one of the kids
that you've been hopelessly
flaunting yourself in front of
like some cheap whore.
Just happens to be
the kid who attacks me.
What are you saying?
Did you put him up to that Veronica?
God,
how could you even think that?
Oh,
well, here we go.
Bring on the tears.
Why don't you save them
for one of your teenage lovers?
I'm sure they'll eat em up.
You're insane, sick,
thinking that I would
sleep with a student.
You know, the fact
that you even suggested
it says more about you.
Well, I know you, Veronica,
and I know when you lie.
You cannot divorce me.
Oh, really?
Why don't you watch me?
Cliff, I never slept with anyone else.
Lies!
I had nothing to do with Riffs attack.
Please wait.
We just ,we got to talk.
I'm done talking.
No Cliff, please.
I said I'm done Veronica.
Please Cliff, I have
something to tell you.
Oh, Veronica, she never misses a trick.
Cliff.
I'm pregnant.
Where the hell do you think you're going?
I told you,
I have a date with my lady, tonight.
Jimmy, you've been seeing this woman
for the last three weeks, but tonight,
tonight, your working.
Dad please,
I've really got to see her tonight.
Jimmy.
Who the hell is this woman?
Just somebody, you don't know her.
Well, whoever she is,
she's got you acting like a damn fool.
Why dad?
Because I'm in love.
Because I don't piss my life
down the drain like you.
You think I never knew love
before your mother.
I remember falling all over myself
for this one broad.
Patricia.
Oh, I never seen a lady like that,
and make no mistake, she was a real lady.
I fell so hard for her, my first love.
At eighteen,
I started planning my future around her,
believing everything she said.
Life was perfect.
I was happy
and happiness was hard to come by you know
when I was a teenager.
And one day, out of the blue,
I found out she got
married to another guy.
I had no idea that she was
stepping out on me,
and she she never let slip.
The pain was too much.
I was left picking up the pieces.
Then I met your mother.
Look, it ain't worth it,
just just focus on your work.
That is something
that will give you a future.
I don't want to be like you dad,
I'm sorry,
but I have bigger plans for myself.
Oh, yeah, what plans?
Plans. Plans.
You're lliving in La La Land, Jimmy.
You think somebody like
you becomes a somebody?
They don't.
Look around you, Jimmy.
Your whole future is mapped out.
Well, I want more.
You're a fool Jimmy Flynn,
and this world ain't kind to fools.
I love her.
I love her dad.
You're sixteen.
You have no idea what love is.
Now get ready to be down at the garage
at six thirty, it's an all nighter again.
Dad.
Please.
I'm dressed.
I said six thirty.
Jimmy.
Jimmy!
Well, it really is beautiful here, Jimmy.
I can see why you like
to come here and think.
It's hard to find peace in a city
that's always moving.
But when I was little,
my mom used to bring me up here.
She used to say that we had to pretend
that we're not in the
big city anymore, but
just on some small island
away from everything and everyone.
Your mother sounded like a smart lady.
They spoke for hours.
It was like nothing else mattered.
The question haunting both of them had
simply vanished.
Veronica and Jimmy felt free
and opened up their souls.
Jimmy spoke about how his mother
had skipped out on us.
I've never felt so unwanted before.
I remember crying my bedroom days
just waiting for her to return.
He went on to say how he hated his
father for making her leave us
and how he dreamed every day of
of travelling the world,
seeing things that you can only see
in Life magazine.
Veronica was playful.
She laughed and giggled like
she was experiencing her first crush.
She spoke about how she
dreamed to become a movie star.
You know, I wanted it
ever since I was a little girl.
And now she fell in love
with the pictures on the big screen when
my father would take me
to watch one movie a week.
I remember sitting there
and looking up at that big screen
and just wanting to walk right into it,
imagining that if I did,
I would be transported
right there into that movie picture.
Jimmy laughed.
Veronica laughed, to anybody who saw them,
they would have looked
like the vision of happiness.
Do you believe in one man
and one woman together forever?
Of course I do.
If it's right.
It's forever.
Then maybe it's true.
Maybe there is one
perfect person out there,
I mean, I know I believe that.
I know that I hurt so much
when I'm not with you.
An unbearable pain.
That has to mean something, right?
That's love, Jimmy,
the pain of love.
Jimmy was feeling the pain of love,
alright.
All he saw was her.
All I see is you.
And all I see is you Jimmy.
And as the sun started
to set on a perfect day
in a perfect bubble.
The question.
That question came back, and this time,
the dame wanted an answer.
You know,
you never did say much after my suggestion
that night, erasing Cliff permanently
cementing us together eternally.
At that moment, a reality hit Jimmy.
His mood changed
and he turned away from her.
I can't do it.
I can't kill Cliff.
Jimmy.
Trust me,
I want to get you as far away
from that son of a bitch as possible,
but killing him.
I mean,
there's got to be another way.
There is no other way, Jimmy.
The only way to get the money
that we need to leave is
is to make sure that Cliff is dead.
No, I refuse to believe
that we still can't be together
and run away together.
People do it all the time.
It won't work, Jimmy.
We'll be living on
the streets in no time.
I love you.
With things falling apart.
Veronica, worked fast
to get Jimmy back on track.
Jimmy, you know,
I wasn't going to tell you this,
I didn't want to frighten you.
Veronica, what are you talking about?
Jimmy.
I'm pregnant.
What?
I'm having your child, Jimmy,
you're going to be a father.
A father?
We can do this Jimmy.
You, me, our child, a family,
a family, Jimmy.
I know how much you've always
wanted to be part of a real family.
Jimmy arranged the pieces
of information in his head,
the thoughts of a future
with the woman he loved.
I know it's a big step Jimmy,
but I know that with our love,
we can do anything we want.
I love you.
I love you so much.
And?
Jimmy?
I'll do it.
I'll kill Cliff.
Another victory for Veronica
and now, well,
the deal was sealed.
Cliff Smart
would have to die.
She asked you to kill him?
Things are bad Riff.
He's beaten her so badly,
I mean, you saw the bruises on her face.
But killing him?
He ain't a good guy.
We ain't talking about
some churchgoing hero
here, we're talking about a man
who lays his hands on a woman.
Oh, man, you got it bad Jimmy.
I mean, loving someone is one thing but
bumping off the competition?
Well, that's cockeyed.
She's pregnant.
With a baby?
No with a flock of sheep Riff.
Jesus Jimmy. A baby?
Are you sure it ain't her old mans?
It's mine.
Her and Cliff don't,
you know, practice anymore?
She's offered to pay
a thousand bucks to anyone who helps.
Woah!
That's life changing.
I need you to help me.
I can't do this alone.
I don't know Jimmy, murder?
We would get the chair if we get caught.
We ain't gonna get caught.
Why can't she do it herself?
I mean the lady looks like she would be
with a meat cleaver.
The first person, the police suspect
is always the partner.
This way, Veronica
could be at the school or,
or out when the murder takes place
and nobody will suspect us, because,
why would they?
This is crazy talk.
We're talking about
murdering Cliff Smart.
Why can't she just leave him?
Because he'll take everything
and leave her with nothing.
She would be out on her ass
with no place to call home.
Jeez.
If Cliff dies, Veronica gets everything,
and Cliff is a very wealthy man,
even more so when he dies.
And then
Veronica gets it all.
We could do this, I know we could
and just think then we can
all get the hell out of here.
What, the two of us and you new lady?
Sure, why not, go to Hollywood,
start again?
Riff you've been living on the streets,
you said it yourself,
you can't keep doing what you're doing.
This could get you out.
Yeah.
It's just that easy.
And I could get away
from my dad, for good.
I'm not built for this life.
I deserve more.
I deserve love.
In that moment the boys face a choice.
Two sixteen year olds wrestling with life
and death.
A thousand dollars Riff,
a thousand dollars.
No, no, I can't do this,
I'm sorry, Jimmy.
You need to look in a mirror.
This isn't you.
Riff I ain't got a choice,
I gotta defend the woman I love.
You're just listening
to what she's telling you.
How do you know what
she's saying is true?
What are you trying to say Riff?
Oh, come on, Jimmy,
you know I like Veronica,
she's a fun time with a good heart.
But that woman ain't no saint Jimmy.
Hey don't disrespect her Riff!
Do you know for sure she's pregnant?
Do you know that cliff really beats her?
Riff, you saw the guy,
you saw how angry he got
you said that his head nearly exploded.
I'm just saying, it's a lot to risk
without all the information.
Information.
Who are you, a detective?
I ain't going to say anything,
but I can not be involved,
and I pray you don't go through this
Riff, wait.
What, Jimmy?
I need your gun.
If you ain't gonna help,
you can at least do that.
I ain't got it on me.
I let a friend borrow it.
Riff.
Damn you Jimmy Flynn for telling me this.
Fine.
The night you're going to do the deed
I'll meet you before
and let you borrow it.
Thank you.
You know, you really are my best friend.
Whatever you say Jimmy.
I got to go.
My future is calling.
They say the road to hell
is paved with good intentions,
and maybe that's the best way to describe
Jimmy's decision.
Cliff was now a dead man walking.
That night, out clearing his head,
Cliff stops dead in his tracks
when he sees Riff in front of him
warming his hands.
You!
After a moment Riff's eyes lock on Cliff.
It was like a showdown
from the Wild West.
But who would flinch first?
We still have unfinished business, kid.
Mr. Smart.
It's so different.
You look...
Glamorous?
Older.
Well, good.
Hopefully people start
to see me as a grown-up
rather than some dumb kid.
Has your mother see your transformation?
Oh, she's out.
She'll see it when she gets back.
I'm sure she'll think it's fine.
Have you met your mother?
And Vivian,
how did you manage to afford this?
Oh, Veronica paid, she said,
I remind her of her when she was my age.
She's always getting me
little gifts we're even talking
about going to Hollywood together.
Hollywood?
Vivian,
your mother nearly has heart failure
every time we go camping,
and that's usually in your backyard.
Do you think I should go blond?
I mean, Veronica says the dark suits me,
but I'm not so sure.
You do realise that
all that comes out your mouth now
is about Jimmy's new girlfriend.
Girlfriend is a stretch Betty.
He's just some teenage crush.
Veronica and I,
we have a true connection, like
on a deeper level, you know.
Not really.
Plus, it's nice to have grown up
conversations for a change.
So what am I just some dumb kid?
No, you're just different.
What we have is our thing and what I have
with Veronica, is...
Better?
Betty.
You promised that I wouldn't be
replaced by your new glamorous friend,
but I hardly see you anymore.
Why aren't you happy for me?
You know what, you're supposed
to be my best friend.
When it suits you.
I'm changing Betty and you better get
used to it or sit down
and stay the hell out of my way.
Goodbye, Vivian.
I know when I'm not wanted.
I just didn't think it would be you
that didnt want me.
Betty!
Betty?
Kids.
My name? Oh,
it's Vivian, Vivian Pierce.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Did I tell you that I was an actress?
Yes, I've starred in several movies.
Actually, one critic
even called me "dazzling".
What on earth have you done to yourself?
Mother?
Take that stuff off your face.
You think going to church
looking like some teenage
Jezebel is appropriate?
It's just make up mother
and a new hairdo.
Why did you have to be such a drag?
And I'm not coming to church.
I feel like you're changing right
in front of my eyes
and I can't reach you.
I keep trying but
you keep pushing me away.
You need to stop worrying about me.
You've done your job, mother.
Now it's time for me to take over.
Vivian, I think it's time
I put my foot down.
You would have to take it off my throat
first mother.
You listen to me.
No, you listen to me.
This constant need
to turn me into you is nauseating mother.
I don't want to be Vivian Pierce.
There's nothing wrong with her.
She's so black and white.
I want to see the world in color.
I wan to be like those ladies
who can just click their fingers
and get whatever they want.
Well, that is not the real world Vivian.
No, that is not your world, mother.
Look at you.
You give up the day you got married.
Vivian, your father will...
What?
Go ahead and call my father.
I'm not scared of him.
You know, you can't think
without a man telling you what to do.
If it's not father, it's God.
Is this because of that woman?
I've seen her around town,
you know, your actress friend.
Flashy is not attractive
on a woman her age.
And jealousy is not attractive
and a woman of your age.
Give me that dress.
Give it back mother.
This is not you Vivian.
Give it back now.
What has gotten into you?
Keep your hands off of my things, Jean.
Please respect that.
Vivian.
You don't need to be
in such a rush to grow up.
The world is not always kind to women.
Do you think I didn't have dreams?
I wanted to open my own sewing shop.
Atlantic City, near the boardwalk
that's where I dreamed of opening it.
But life isn't a dream Vivian,
do you think this lady
is going to turn you into a star?
She's not.
That doesn't happen for girls like you.
You gave up your dream
because you're weak.
Good morning, sweetheart.
What's all this?
Breakfast.
You know, now we've got our own
little bundle of joy on the way.
I thought I ought to learn to do
my part around here.
Well, crazier things have happened,
I suppose.
I told my mother.
You told your mother?
I couldn't wait.
It was bursting out of me.
I specifically told you not to tell her.
It's still early.
And as you pointed out,
I'm an old shrew now.
So this is clearly a delicate pregnancy.
Well, I never called you a shrew.
Coffee?
Thank you.
Now, Cliff, please don't go
sharing our news with anybody else,
especially the boys at work.
Don't think I don't know you can out
gossip the ladies at the markets.
I swear on all the Saints.
I can't tell you how excited I am.
I can't sleep anymore
knowing that the day I dreamt
about is so close.
It's a new start.
We still have time, Cliff.
Let's not go wasting all of our joy.
We'll have none left for the child.
You um, you are
excited about our baby aren't you?
I can hardly wait.
That's what I needed to hear.
Now,
do you need anything else before I go?
Cliff I'm not even showing yet.
I think I'm perfectly capable
of looking after myself
whilst you're at work.
After all, I have done it
for the past 16 years.
OK, baby.
Have a good day, Cliff.
Oh, and
Veronica.
Yes, Cliff.
You are starting to show a little.
It's beautiful.
What?
Bye baby.
The moment Cliff left the room,
Veronica jumps up
and heads for the phone.
Operator, connect me to New York,
seven, three, two, four please.
Thank you.
Is that you?
Oh, Jimmy, we have to do this soon.
His temper is out of control.
My face still stings.
He ain't ever going to learn is he?
He's just bad, bad to the core.
Oh, Jimmy, Jimmy, I am scared.
I'm scared for the life of our baby.
Don't worry.
I'm ready when you are.
Oh, Jimmy.
Every time I hear your voice, it's
like the rain clouds lifting.
I can see clearly,
I can see our future so clearly.
When should we do this?
Tomorrow night, Jimmy.
We have to do this tomorrow night.
Tell me you love me.
Jimmy, I gotta go.
Vivian, well, don't
you look like a knockout?
I knew that dress would suit you.
Oh, thank you Veronica.
You look beautiful, too.
Why thank you.
Now Vivian, what are you doing here?
Not that I'm not delighted
for your visit, of course.
Well, since we didn't
meet this week after school,
I thought I'd stop by and say hello.
That's what friends do, isn't it?
They pop by and say hello.
And we are friends, aren't we, Veronica?
Of course Vivian.
In fact, I'm delighted you stopped by.
Really?
Sure.
I mean, I think it's about time
we had another acting lesson.
Only this time let's do it away from here
or or the school.
Let's make it more like
two girls out on the town.
Oh, Mrs. Smart.
I would love that.
We could go to a bar and well,
I could teach you all about
how to audition for a movie picture.
A drink?
In a bar?
Sure.
Oh, Mrs. Smart.
I would love that.
But I'm only fifteen.
But in this dress, Vivian,
you look like a beautiful woman.
Every bar in town
will want you to light
up their establishment and it'll be nice.
Just us girls.
Just us girls?
You and I?
A sweet gesture, a blossoming friendship.
No, Veronica was lining up
alibis like a professional crook.
Poor sweet Vivian
was caught up in Veronica's web.
Mrs. Smart.
I would love that.
I, I want to learn everything from you.
And I will teach you everything
that you want to know.
I've never had any real friends before.
Oh, well, except Betty, and she's well,
she's just a kid.
I've never really had anybody
that truly understands me.
Everybody just
passed me by.
I hope you know how much
I value our relationship.
Oh, as do I, Vivian.
So why don't we say
eight thirty tomorrow night?
Perhaps you could tell your mother
you're staying at a friend's place.
My mother doesn't control me.
I want to be like you.
Strong. Confident.
I'm afraid.
I don't feel very strong lately.
Vivian.
What do you mean?
My life is is complicated.
Mr. Smart?
You know, I used to be like you, Vivian.
I dreamed of a life in the spotlight.
People calling my name
surrounded by glamour
and most of all, friends.
But the day I married Cliff,
I think I let a part of that die.
No, no, it's still in there.
Perhaps. But
I think every time
Cliff strikes my face,
he takes a little more of me.
Veronica.
You don't need a man.
I mean, why do any of us
need men, really?
They always ruin everything.
My father's idea of raising
a child is shouting at it
when called on by my mother.
Maybe...
Maybe what sweetheart?
Maybe we can move to Hollywood together.
Two girls ready to
take on the big screen.
Oh, Hollywood won't know what hit it.
You could leave Cliff.
We could just drive there together.
Oh, Veronica, imagine.
Well, that sounds wonderful, Vivian.
A dream, but wonderful.
It doesn't have to be.
Cliff is so awful to you.
Why can't he just drop dead?
Oh, Vivian, you shouldn't
say such a thing.
Well, you'd feel positively awful
if something were to happen to him now.
I doubt it.
Look, Vivian,
I need to head into town, so.
Oh, oh.
Sorry, I'll go.
Oh, shall we say.
Eight thirty tomorrow.
Outside the front of the school?
Sure Veronica, I can um,
I can hardly wait.
Why don't you, uh
come sit on my lap,
let daddy take care of you.
OK, baby,
you like that daddy?
I do indeed.
So
how are you
going to make your old man happy?
Whatever you want me to do,
you're paying.
Don't talk like that.
Don't talk like a whore.
OK baby.
Jimmy.
I thought I told you
stay away tonight, I had company.
Hi dollface, I'm the company.
I'm sorry.
I forgot.
Are you trying to be lippy with me?
Look dad, I've had a tough day.
I want to go to bed.
Tough day?
My kid, sixteen, at high school.
Thinks he's had a tough day.
You don't even know what a tough day is.
You try breaking your back
every day at work.
Then you can tell me about a tough day.
Look, I should go Harvey.
Sit down!
You're not going anywhere tonight.
I'd get out of here if I were you.
He likes to use his fists
to beat the women around him.
Harvey, I'm out of here.
Do it, go on.
Let me tell you something, Jimmy Flynn.
I have protected you from this for years.
I will not let you talk
that way about me.
Your mom was a drunk.
She would come home every night
starting a fight throwing things,
hitting me.
That's a lie.
She left you outside of church
when you were just seven months old.
She wanted to go to some bar,
but you were in the way.
So I came to get you again.
Why are you lying?
She screwed every man
without a single thought of you and me.
So, yeah, you may see me
as the bad guy, and yeah,
I ain't perfect,
you know what,
I'm still here.
No, no, no.
You pushed her away.
Women lie Jimmy, always
remember that, women lie.
No dad, that's you.
Life is easier without them.
I got mine back when she left.
And look at you, dad.
You're an embarrassment.
Spending all the money
that you make on booze and whores.
I never, ever
want to turn out like you.
Jimmy.
I know love.
I've found love,
I'd kill for love and I tell you
I've never felt more alive.
So if you want to fade away,
then that's fine.
But I ain't going down with you.
Do you hear me, old man?
I ain't going down with you.
(Train Sounds)
Ha!
Well, you look like
you've got the weight
of the world on shoulders.
Now that I could handle.
What's going on?
Why aren't you with Jimmy?
We're not joined at the hip you know.
No, but you seem to share a brain.
Haha,
you should have been a circus clown.
Riff!
What happened to your face?
I walked into a fist, it's New York City,
what are you gonna do.
Well, are you OK?
Honestly, I'm fine.
Vivian, can I ask you something?
Sure,
as long as it's not asking me on a date.
Not a date, fear not.
Do you trust Veronica?
What do you mean trust her?
You know, the thing
she says the things about Cliff.
He's a monster Riff.
Veronica is one of the most honest
and trustworthy people I've ever met.
DIal it down, you sound like you
run her fan club.
Well, Veronica cares about us.
I mean, she's more of a mother to me...
Yeah, but...
Yeah, but nothing Riff Randall.
I mean, Veronica has taught me so much.
I mean, she stopped and gave me,
gave us the time of day.
I mean, what other adult
wants to listen to us, huh?
Like really listen.
Oh Vivian, I'm wrestling
with something real bad.
What are you talking about, Riff?
Can I trust you
that no matter what I say,
it stays between us.
This is serious, Vivian,
and it isn't some silly, childish thing.
I don't know if you've noticed but
I've done a lot of growing up recently.
So I swear to you,
I'll take it to the grave.
Veronica has asked Jimmy to kill Cliff.
What?
Jimmy's asked me to be involved as well.
And it's a thousand bucks,
which is more money than I ever
thought I'd see.
But I can't, can I?
Woah Riff.
Slow down.
I know he beats her.
At least that's what she says, but
murder is just so final, you know,
I mean, how could I live with that?
When is this supposed to happen?
Tomorrow night, he's gone girl crazy.
It's like he thinks that
if he kills Cliff, Veronica
will fall madly in love with him.
The whole thing is just hairbrained.
Jeez, killing her husband
to prove his love for her.
Ain't that something.
Should I call the police?
Should I try to stop him? No, no, no.
He'll go to prison Riff.
You need to be there and stop him
from making a stupid mistake.
He won't listen to me.
I've already tried.
Well, if he doesn't,
then go to the police.
Just, just stop it.
This could ruin his life and Veronicas is
if they get caught.
We can't allow that to happen Riff.
Vivian, you better
not be down by the tracks.
She is driving me crazy.
God, killing Cliff.
Riff, you need to stop it.
We can't allow Veronica to get hurt.
She could get sent away
if she gets caught,
and that's not the way for her
to get away from Cliff.
Veronica, you worried about Veronica?
I've got to go.
I'm sorry.
Vivian, but that's not the whole story.
I still have more need to say, Vivian!
(Train Sounds)
It's 7:30 a.m. on the big day, Cliff.
Well, Cliff
wakes up to a life
he could only dream of.
Cliff stands and stares
at Veronica for a few moments
as she prepares breakfast.
I want to remember this moment.
Oh, Cliff, you startled me.
I feel like I'm looking at a new you.
What's the occasion?
It's just breakfast.
I'm already late.
I've got a big day,
but I can take it to go.
You're always on the move.
Oh, and
Veronica.
I always loved you.
Whatever happened,
I wanted you to know that.
UInexpectedly, tears
form in Veronica's eyes.
These ain't no acting tears.
Veronica appears moved,
moved by Cliffs words.
The man she's about to have killed.
Veronica.
Jimmy, Jimmy you startled me.
You having second thoughts?
What?
No, no Jimmy, it's
me and you from now on.
Our future begins tonight.
When can we leave for Hollywood?
A week, maybe two.
I just don't want it
to look as though I'm
fleeing.
God, I love you Veronica Smart.
So you get here at eight o'clock.
Cliff would have just
come home from work,
you'll catch him off guard.
I have an alibi in place.
There is nothing that can stand in our way
Jimmy.
Hey, Sal Salazar's fighting tonight.
Why don't you and I have a night in.
Watch the fight, have a couple of beers.
I can't dad,
I've got something I need to do.
I'm trying here Jimmy.
You have no idea how it feels to be
invisible, do you, mother?
You know, I sit
and watch the movies
and see these beautiful women,
so full of life,
their eyes sparkle like diamonds,
and they seem happy.
Really happy,
and then
I look in the mirror and I see,
me.
Dad.
That woman you said you loved,
Patricia?
What about her?
Why didn't you fight for her?
How do you know I didn't?
Well, did you?
How could I Jimmy.
She made a choice
as soon as she let
that other guy into her bed,
it was all over.
Those women on the screen
aren't like that in real life.
They have the best makeup
people and the best gowns.
And I want that.
I hate my life.
I just want to be beautiful,
why is that so wrong?
Oh, Vivian you are beautiful.
Stop it, mother.
Veronica is making me beautiful.
Look at me.
Maybe.
Maybe she made a mistake,
got married for the wrong reasons,
maybe she was waiting for you
to come and save her.
Jimmy?
What is this all about?
You listen to me.
You are 15 years old.
You haven't even fully
blossomed as a woman yet.
But I see you,
I see you are beautiful
and you don't need to hide behind
this paint to show that.
Nothing that I got to go, Jimmy.
Should I be worried about you?
What do you mean?
Well,
this woman, are you serious about her?
I've never been more serious
about anything in my life.
You have to find your own way,
you can't just become somebody else.
That's not true.
Veronica said that many movie
stars come from lives like mine.
They get to change their name and
they're weight and their hair.
You know how many girls feel like you?
All wanting the same thing.
So should I be worried?
Worried.
About love?
No dad you don't need to be worried.
I know that she's the one.
Veronica...
Ahh, Veronica!
I don't want to be your enemy
and I want you to succeed.
But we have few options
in life as women, Vivian,
so we have to work harder,
and that's all I want
you to do is work harder.
You know, that is the first time
you have told me her name.
Yeah.
Veronica, Veronica.
I don't think I know her.
Well, apart from your teacher.
Well, I am working harder mother,
but this time
it's for me.
Not you.
Oh, Vivian.
Mother I have to go.
Please tell me you're not involved
with your teacher.
I have to go and find Riff,
and if I can't find him
I have to find Veronica and stop...
Stop what?
What are you talking about?
I got to go, I won't be late.
Jimmy please.
Jimmy stop.
Jimmy!
Riff, Riff?
Is that you?
So have you got the gun?
I'm sorry Jimmy I ain't got it.
The guy never gave it me back.
And he's vanished.
Damn it Riff. I need that.
You don't have to go through with this.
You really don't have it?
Sorry.
Oh, well, that's perfect Riff.
To hell with it, I still got my bat.
Don't do this.
You'll ruin your life.
If I don't do something,
and he hurts my baby
how am I supposed to live with that?
You think your some kind of mobster
now cause you are gonna kill a guy?
Oh Riff, go home
if you don't want to help,
you ain't got to be here.
Jimmy.
Jimmy, look at me.
all the things you could
do with your life.
I don't need anything else
just her and my kid.
You're a kid yourself.
Jimmy, how are you going to raise a kid?
Riff, go home,
please.
Once you're marked by the devil Jimmy,
you can't come back from that.
Believe me, I know.
Some things are worth it.
I'll call the police, Jimmy.
No, you won't Riff, that ain't you.
Jimmy, please just listen to me.
I really needed that gun.
Call it off.
No way.
It just means that
I have to do this myself.
Like a man.
Jimmy please.
It's going to be fine Riff.
Trust me.
In a few hours,
all this is over.
Dammit Jimmy.
I'm sorry.
A plan.
A man ain't a man without a plan.
It's February 13th,
just after 7.30 that same evening,
silence washes over the neighborhood.
A figure seen at the back of the house
heads towards the back door.
The figure stands in front
of it for a moment
and then knocks on the door.
As the door opens, however.
Well, it's not Cliff, It's Veronica,
and it's not Jimmy stood
there, it's Riff.
Riff, what are you doing here?
You're early.
I have to leave first,
and then you come back when Cliff's home.
Jesus, I thought
Jimmy went through the plan with you.
Mrs Smart.
Where is Jimmy is he not with you.
Is that the gun?
I thought you gave that to Jimmy.
In fact, I thought you said
you didn't want any part of this.
Mrs Smart.
Now run along Riff,
I need to get out of here,
go and meet Vivian.
Riff?
Riff, what are you doing?
Aaahh!
Yes, Riff.
What are you doing?
Let's go back to the moment
Riff and Cliff came face to face.
It was like a showdown in the Wild West,
but who would flinch first?
We still have unfinished business kid.
Mr. Smart.
Did you really think
I was going to let
you get away with that kid?
Please Mr Smart, I'm sorry.
You think you can jump
me, you little punk?
It was a mistake, please.
I didn't know you were Veronicas husband.
You made a joke out of me
for the last time.
You're nothing, street trash.
I should do the world a favour
and put you out of your misery.
Please don't do this.
I'm a good kid, I didn't mean to hurt you.
You ain't a good kid Riff.
Please, please, please.
Oh God, oh God, oh God!
So tell me Riff,
are you sleeping with my wife?
No, no.
Why would you think that?
I think you are.
Now, Is it just you
or is it Jimmy as well?
You got it all wrong.
Ahhh, it's Jimmy.
Jimmy's stepping out with your wife,
not me, I swear.
Give me a Bible and i'll swear on it.
Jimmy, that son of a bitch!
Please just let me go.
I ain't going to cause you
any more problems.
You give me one damn reason I should.
Because I'm just 16.
I ain't moved.
Your wife has hired Jimmy to murder you.
You're lying.
No, I ain't, he is supposed
to do it this week?
She wants your money and Jimmy,
I swear to you,
I ain't stupid enough to be lying
to you right now.
No, no, she's having my baby.
She said the same thing to Jimmy.
Veronica, you've made a joke out of me
for the last time.
Oh God, what have I done?
You just saved your own life kid.
Now
you're working for me.
Do you understand?
Everything I tell you to do you do it
or I will kill you kid, you and Jimmy.
Do you understand me?
Yeah, I.
Yes, sir.
So, she wants to be dead.
Aaah. Riff!
Riff, look at me, we're friends,
why would you do this?
Cliff knows Mrs Smart,
he knows all about your plan.
How, how does he know?
I had to tell him
he was going to kill me.
Why, oh God.
What have you done.
I've got to do this Mrs Smart.
No, no, Riff, don't you see?
He's trying to set you up for my murder.
He is going to kill me.
Do you hear me, he's
going to put a bullet in my head
and not just mine, Jimmys as well.
This way, this way, he said,
he is going to leave us alone.
There's got to be a way out of this Riff.
I'm so sorry.
I guess this was my path.
You could flee.
You could just pretend
that you killed me.
What about Jimmy?
What about him?
He loves you.
You would just leave him?
He's a sweet kid.
He's young.
I don't want him on the run,
he's got the rest of
his life ahead of him.
Oh God, Mr Smart was right.
He said that you didn't love Jimmy
because you couldn't
love anybody but yourself.
And you needed us to play
a part in your husband's murder?
Riff, no!
I wish he'd never met you.
I wish none of us had.
You ruined everything.
Don't you see that he's
poisoning your mind against me?
You know,
the moment my parents died, I knew,
I knew that my life would mean nothing,
that I would mean nothing.
Something like this was
inevitable, I guess.
No Riff, no!
Goodbye Mrs Smart,
and may God forgive me.
Nooooo! Oh,
(Riff Sobbing)
It's OK.
The hard part's done.
Cliff, help.
Help me.
And why would I do that, sweetheart?
After you tried to have me killed.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I know just how sorry you are.
My God, all I ever asked from you
was for you to love me,
and to give me a child,
you couldn't even achieve that.
Have you ever, really loved me Veronica?
I love you.
No, no, no, you don't.
Those are just the desperate words
of a dying woman.
I never loved Jimmy.
I love you.
No, because you lie as often
as you breathe baby.
You get out, you get out of town.
I don't ever want to see you
around here again.
Oh, and Riff.
Leave the gun here,
I'll get rid of it,
I ain't leaving anything to chance.
Now, get out of here!
Police.
Oh God, please.
There was just some crazy kid here.
He shot my wife,
and then he shot me as well.
Please!
Oh, God.
Oh, God, Veronica.
Who did this to you was it him?
JImmy?
Is that you?
Go....
I ain't going anywhere.
I won't let anybody hurt you?
Take care of you, hold on Veronica.
No, no, wake up Veronica, wake up?
You can't.
You can't die.
You can't leave me.
Oh God!
You see, Jimmy.
I always win.
I always have and I always will.
You killed her.
You son of a bitch, you killed her!
No you killed her Jimmy.
If you want to be a man
you've got to be able
to take a shot and not miss,
and you missed Jimmy,
it's never wise to miss.
Give my love to Veronica.
Wait!
Oh God!
Oh my God.
I thought I told you to go.
No, no!
You know what your problem is Riff?
You care too much.
Why would you do that?
You promised.
Nobody outwits Cliff Smart.
Now, I um, I tell the police
that you and Jimmy just just burst in
and he was screaming
at her to leave with him, but no,
she wanted to stay with me
because she still loves me.
But he wouldn't have any of that,
so he shot her,
but then I shot him,
in self defence of course.
Jimmy, Jimmy come on.
It's too late for him, but you can run.
I'm letting you run.
You murdered him.
He would do anything for her, anything.
I'm telling the police.
You're trying to set him up.
And implicate yourself.
You ain't stupid enough for that kid.
I should kill you, right now?
I don't think your aims that good kid.
To hell with you Cliff Smart!
That boy attacked my wife!
Stop or I'll shoot!
As I walked around the crime scene,
I saw Veronica's body
laid on the floor next to Jimmys.
A table next to the chair, had an ashtray
on and a half smoked cigarette.
Veronica had been caught by surprise,
Jimmy's body laid next to her
with his eyes wide open with fear.
I feel like I died alongside her.
Does that sound normal?
I notice that Cliff didn't have
a single tear in his eye.
I feel empty.
I've seen the pain etched in the faces
of those left behind,
as reality dawns on them
that death has changed
everything for them.
This should have been
another routine visit,
but something about it felt off.
And it all came down to Cliff Smart.
Now, Mr. Smart,
can you tell me if you have any idea
why these two young men would want
you and your wife killed?
Yeah, but
I don't want to tarnish
the memory of my wife now.
She's...
Dead?
Yeah.
I mean,
well, you see,
she's been spending a lot of time
with the kid, Jimmy.
I think he'd fallen in love with her.
I'd, um, suspected for a while.
She used to teach him see,
she gave him private acting lessons.
And every time I saw him, like
I saw the way he looked at her,
I mean, I hate to say it, but
at times my um, my wife didn't
dissuade his flirtations.
Were the two, intimate?
Yeah. Yeah,
I think so.
I think he thought
they'd be together in the future.
You know,
there was something real strange
about this kid Detective.
He had something real dark in his eyes.
He was clearly, very troubled.
Did he say anything
when they turned up tonight?
He just stormed in in a rage
and just kept screaming
that Veronica had to go with him.
But Veronica just kept saying
that he was just a little boy and that
she was married
and she loved me,
but he wouldn't accept it.
He just kept screaming his love for her.
Eventually he said,
if I can't have her, then nobody can.
Oh, God.
Then he shot her.
I mean, I tried to shield it,
but he shot me as well.
Lucky for me I managed to fall
near the drawer where I keep my gun.
So I just about managed
to let off one shot.
Straight through the heart.
I just shot.
I didn't aim.
I just wish I could have saved her.
Still no tears, an actor Cliff was not.
What about the other boy?
Oh, yeah.
He didn't say much.
I mean, once I'd managed to kill Jimmy,
in self-defense, um, he, he,
he ran out of the house,
and then you fine men turned up.
I see.
Well, it all seems
pretty straightforward to me,
but you might want to get
that wound looked at.
If you ask me, you're very lucky
it just grazed you.
God must have intervened.
Indeed.
Vivian, please sit down,
I've got something to tell you.
Mother, I have to go.
Veronica never showed last night
and I can't find Riff.
I need to make sure that he stops...
Stops what?
Teenage drama mother.
You don't need to know everything.
Vivian, please.
It's terribly important.
I said I have to go.
Mrs Smart.
She's dead.
Vivian, oh Vivian.
Jimmy's also dead, and Riff, well,
it's not looking good
for him, he's in a coma.
What?
They were murdered
last night at her home.
They say... What?
What do they say?
They say that Jimmy was in love with her.
She turned him down
and Jimmy shot Veronica.
Cliff got off one shot
and then shot Jimmy dead?
No, you're lying,
Cliff is dead, Cliff Smart is dead.
Cliff's fine. No, you're lying.
I don't lie Vivian.
How could she be dead,
and how could Jimmy kill her,
he couldn't, he wouldn't kill her.
Sometimes you don't see what's going on
even with the people
that you're closest to.
Riff, oh, God.
Riff why didn't you stop it,
why did you join in?
Oh Vivian, what can I do?
He took her from me.
From us.
Jimmy was obviously very confused.
She was my only friend.
She was the only person
who ever believed in me.
That's not true.
I've always believed in you.
How can she not be here anymore.
Oh God mother, it hurts.
it's OK.
It's OK.
It's OK to be sad.
Sad?
Sad, he took her from me.
Oh, no, my head is spinning.
God, mother
she was my ticket out of here,
she was going to make me a star.
Let me get you some hot tea.
I don't need hot tea.
I need to make him pay.
Jimmy paid with his life, Vivian.
Jimmy?
Oh mother, you have no idea
what you're talking about.
Then talk to me, please.
Mother, I need to be alone.
Vivian, please.
I said, get out, mother,
get out, get out, get out.
I never want to see you again.
Get out, I never want to see you anymore.
No.
Oh God. No. No.
How can he do this.
The innocence of youth was lost.
The paths they took
led to their own downfall.
Veronica had destroyed
everybody to get what she wanted
and if she went to hell, I'm
sure even the devil
wouldn't recognize her.
It's two days later
and Cliff was finished
playing the grieving husband.
In fact, Cliff had a secret of his own.
Get over here, baby.
I got you a brandy darling
just how you like it.
God, I'm so grateful
to have you at my side.
So, Cliff, Veronica never knew.
She never knew that we didn't break up?
Never had a clue.
Went to her grave, none the wiser.
I still can't believe
she was murdered in this house.
Yeah, tough break.
I mean, we had our disagreements, but
I never wanted her dead,
even after all she did.
You are handling it so well.
It can't be easy for you.
The pain will always be there.
And that's because you're such
a good man, Cliff Smart.
And you're going to make
a wonderful father to our baby.
A little Cliff running around.
Or Lana.
I'm so grateful
you decided against doing your show.
Now you're with child.
No wife of mine will be
burdened with work.
You're a housewife and a mother.
The greatest job there is.
Are you expecting anybody?
No.
Don't you move, I'll get it.
You'll do nothing of the sort.
Let me get it.
I'll be waiting in the bedroom for you
Cliffy.
Lana.
I ain't going to waste
my second chance at love, baby.
Cliff reached out for
the door and opened it,
and so his surprise, he sees Veronica
stood there with her back to him.
He's taken aback,
but a moment later,
the woman turns around
and it's not Veronica.
It's Vivian, dressed
in a killer red dress,
she looks just like Veronica.
What the hell do you want?
Why are you dressed like that?
Well, Cliffy, I have a message for you.
Who is it, sweetheart?
Well what the hell kind of message
would you have for me?
It's simple, Cliffy.
It's from Veronica.
Veronica's dead.
Yes Cliffy, and she's real mad about it.
LANA!!
Aaaahhhhh!!!
Vivian would be arrested
and sent to a mental institution
where she would remain for years.
Vivian Pierce, this sweet girl
with a bright future ahead of her
had now vanished.
All that was left,
a broken shell of a girl
who soul seems to have been
completely removed from her body.
Her mother and loyal friend
will be her only visitors.
And even then, Jean never gets to truly
see her daughter.
It would be a week later,
when Riff opened his eyes, and his mouth.
Yeah, he told us the whole sordid story.
It was only at that moment
that everything fell into place.
The affair, the murder
plot, thedouble cross.
It was something that
even the best Hollywood writers
ccoudn't have dreamed up.
Riff would be sent to jail for 10 years
for the murder of Veronica Smart.
But he's using the time
to better himself,
to learn himself a trade.
God, please let one positive come
from this tragedy.
In all my years,
I had never seen a more
twisted or tragic story
from one teenage boys fantasy
and one manipulative woman's motives came
the murders of Jimmy Flynn,
Cliff Smart and Veronica Smart.
The tragedy wouldn't end there, however,
the implications were far and wide.
It would be too much for Harvey.
He will blame himself for how hard
he had been towards his son, a charge
he was sadly guilty of.
So on a cold winter night,
Harvey Flynn took a large drink
from his bottle of whiskey,
picks up his pistol,
aimed it at his head and.
Well, he didn't pull the trigger,
stopping himself
becoming the latest victim
of this tragedy.
As for me, well, I left the force.
The case lingered over every move I made.
This ain't like the movies,
the detective doesn't always get his man.
So now I write pulp detective novels
like this one you witnessed, it's
cathartic in a way, it helps me release
the nightmares I see
in my sleep to the page.
It helps me to put them to bed for good.
Now it's your nightmare.
You see, the city is a scary place.
nobody is what they seem.
Evil doesn't always hide around
dark corners, and innocence
doesn't automatically mean innocent.
People are far more complex than that.
In this case,
they showed me the horrific acts
that people can do to one another
over a beautiful
but unworthy woman.
See, nobody is truly bad
or good, right or wrong.
Human existence is far
more complicated than that.
And that's the scariest thing of all,
because you can never see it coming.
This is my city,
and I prided myself on
solving every case
that came across my desk.
Well, apart from one,
the case of Veronica Smart,
a woman who destroyed
everything that got in her way.