Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
c musi)
♪ So I'm coming home ♪
♪ Home ♪
♪ I'm coming home ♪
♪ So tired, tired
of being alone ♪
♪ So I'm coming home, home ♪
Look at me.
Hold, hold, hold.
Okay, go search, go search.
Hey, sweetie.
Good girl, Maxie.
Come here, baby.
Good girl.
Wow, that is one talented dog.
You must have a strong scent.
You know, when you asked me
to spend the morning with you,
this is not what I had in mind.
Well, you have the
eternal gratitude
of the entire Kenai
Mountain Rescue Team.
Why don't you
show your gratitude
by having a drink with me?
It's seven in the morning.
I don't mean
like a drink drink.
I mean like a coffee
or a hot chocolate.
Yeah, I would love to.
Yeah?
Great, then it's a date.
Well, I got to
get to the cafe.
Gotta help my mom
'cause my sisters are actually
coming in from New York
for my mom's birthday.
Another time then.
I don't know.
The locals might start talking
if they knew that I
was dating the guy
renting my parents' guest house.
Dating?
I'm just talking
about getting a drink,
but if you want to date.
You excited to see your sisters?
Yeah, I am.
It's also complicated.
You're talking
to an only child.
Has it always been complicated?
No, we were really
close when we were little,
but I don't know.
Maybe it's normal for
siblings to grow apart
as they get older.
It doesn't help that we live
on other sides of the country.
So what are they like?
How to describe my sisters?
And finally, I would
suggest a line item accounting
to ferret out any redundancies.
To be competitive, you're
going to need to streamline.
That is, if you decide
to bring your business
to Crest Financial.
Thank you for walking
us through that, Hannah.
We expect to make our
decision in the next week.
Very good.
Just curious if
you could share more
of your longterm strategy?
Well, that would
be much more complex,
but I would be happy to work
out a more expanded analysis.
I could get started
on that right away.
Well then, we'll look
forward to reading it.
Thank you for coming in.
Are we celebrating
a new account?
Not sure, but I think
we have a good shot.
Still have work to do.
Where is everyone?
A bunch of folks cut out
early to get drinks at O'Brien's
for Charlie's birthday.
Oh, that reminds me, did you-
Checked you in for
your flight to Anchorage,
upgraded you to business class,
and I got a car to pick you
up when you land in Alaska.
Great.
Oh, and I need to get
a gift for Suzanne.
60's a big year, it needs
to be something special.
You're getting excited
to spend some time
with your sisters?
Yeah, it should be good.
Speaking of,
Beth called to see
if you're meeting at her
place or at the play.
The play.
Oh.
You want me to get
her on the phone?
No, no, I better call her.
Okay then, I'll see
you when you get back.
Call or text anytime.
Okay, I will.
Good afternoon,
doctor's office.
Is Dr. Vogel in?
Who's calling, please?
Hannah McBride calling.
The line is busy,
would you like his voicemail?
No, no, just if you could
have him give me a ring back,
that would be great.
As soon as possible.
- You got it, bye now.
- Bye-bye.
- She isn't!
- She is!
Girls, girls.
Melly.
Okay, just...
Hey, Hans, can you
hold on just a sec?
Melly, stop, please.
If you pull the ears like that,
you're going to rip it off.
Thank you.
Hi, sorry.
That doesn't sound good.
No, they're fighting
over Bugsy again.
Bugsy?
Stuffed animal.
Are you coming here or we going
to meet you at the school?
Listen, Beth, I hate
to do this last minute,
but it looks like I'm going
to have to do a rain check
for the play tonight.
No, are you serious?
They're going to
be so disappointed.
Melly's the lead, but
this is Ruby's first play.
I know, I know, but
work's been so crazy.
I just...
I just flew in from San
Francisco late last night
and I'm trying to land
this really big client.
This is twice you've
canceled on us this month.
I know, I'm sorry.
But I'm going to
see you tomorrow.
Okay, I'll make it up
to the girls, I promise.
I'll take them for the day.
I mean, no offense, but
they'll eat you alive.
Besides, I'm not
putting much stock
in your promises these days.
Look, I...
I said I was sorry, I
don't want to fight.
I just want to get
through this trip, okay?
Just can we put everything
aside for Suzanne?
Can you not call her Suzanne?
You do realize this birthday
is the 25th anniversary of...
Yeah, I know.
This time of year, it's
all I can think about.
Gotta go.
How's it coming, guys?
We're almost there, right?
It's so
beautiful up here.
Gosh, we don't get mountains
like this in upstate New York.
Yeah, we get a ton of
clients from back east.
They all say it's
worth the trip.
Fabulous way to spend
your birthday, Suzanne.
Yeah, I got it pretty good.
So how long have you
guys all known each other?
The four of us went
to Michigan together.
Been friends ever since.
Suzanne guided us on
our first ever summit
when we were sophomores.
Wow.
So you and your husband
been doing this for a while?
Yeah.
I run people up and
down the mountain.
Stewart runs the business
and our indoor climbing
classes for kids.
So, next section
gets pretty steep.
I'm going to need
to put you on belay.
Whatever you say, captain.
Looks like we have
some clouds moving in.
There was snow up
top early this morning,
but the forecast said
it should be clear
by the time we get up there.
What was that?
Suzanne?
Suzanne!
Suzanne, are you okay?
You drifted off.
Yeah, I'm fine.
What's up?
Well, I'm headed home.
Gotta sort the rooms
for our special guests.
I'm about done
here too, I will join you.
Great, I'll meet you out back.
You're okay, right?
Honey, I am fine.
Will you quit worrying about me?
Well, I just want to make sure
that the birthday girl is happy.
Sweetheart, my birthday
is still a few days away.
Please, don't rush
me out of my fifties.
Come on, 60 is the new 40.
I heard 60 is the new 30.
Yeah, well, I wish.
Nope, 60 is still 60.
And you are as beautiful and
vibrant as the day I met you.
Liar.
It's true.
So how was everything
today, gentlemen?
The service and the food was
perfect, Suzanne, as always.
Thank you.
How about a dozen
of these cookies
for the Polar Bear Club?
You got it.
Keep the change.
Here you go.
Be sure to say hello
to Hannah and Beth for me
when they get in.
We will.
Having you girls together is
all she's been talking
about for months.
Oh, don't I know it.
Oh, okay.
Your dad and I are headed home.
Still need to get
the house in order.
Oh, and if you have time,
the monthly invoices
still need to be balanced.
Right, got it.
You know, there is this thing
called software, just saying.
Yeah, well, after we retire
and you're running the cafe,
you can do the invoices
however you want.
Until then...
Abacus, parchment,
paper, and quill?
Very funny.
Ha ha.
You told her to let go.
He was mine first.
You did give him to Ruby.
But I miss him,
I want him back.
Well, sweetie, that's not
really how gift giving works.
We could share.
That's a really good
idea, isn't it, Melly?
Doesn't matter, he's ruined.
One quick trip to
the stuffed animal vet
and he is good as new.
Hmm?
Hey girls, this is
Mommy's old boss.
You guys run upstairs
quick, quick, quick
because Daddy's going to
be here any minute, okay?
You start getting ready.
Hello?
Beth, how are you?
I'm good.
Good.
Well, it's been a minute,
so I thought I'd check in with
my favorite former colleague.
Yeah, wow, it has.
It has been a minute.
How, how are you?
How's the company?
We're both amazing.
Both very busy.
Beth, does the name Anna
Bellingham ring a bell?
Yeah, she's the CEO
of Regal Beauty, right?
Well, we just got out
of a meeting with her
and we were discussing
marketing their new beauty line.
That's huge.
Congratulations.
It's a little early
for congratulations,
which is where you come in.
Okay.
I thought to myself,
who would be the perfect
point person for this account?
The great Beth McBride.
Yeah.
Maybe in my former life.
Which makes you
perfect for this.
Their target demo is moms
in the workforce or at home
who want to look their best
but don't have the
luxury of time.
I'm flattered, I am.
But I just, I have a lot on
my plate with the family, so.
Don't you ever think
about getting back to work?
Wait, are you
offering me a job?
That's the plan.
But first Anna wants
to see a strategy
on how we would reel
in our target market.
I...
Thank you, but now's not great.
Mull it over.
I'll touch base in a day or two
and you can give me
your answer then.
Okay, yeah, I'll
think about it.
Deal.
Thanks, Corinna.
I'm home!
Daddy, Daddy!
Hi, hi.
Get in here.
Oh, wow, look at you.
Okay, what's happening?
Melly broke Bugsy.
I did not.
Oh no.
But looks like
she's in good hands.
- Can I have one?
- Me too.
Oh, okay.
Those are supposed to
be for after the show.
Sorry.
But at least I don't have to
talk to you about cavities.
Do I?
Sorry.
So, how was your day?
Well, it was interesting.
Care to elaborate?
Later.
All right.
So, who wants to
go to the theater?
- Me!
All right, let's go, let's go.
Hand, hand, hand.
Who's driving?
You driving?
Okay.
Hey, should I
bring this scarf?
Hannah?
Yes, yeah, sorry.
Yes?
Scarf, should I
bring the scarf?
Sure.
Yeah.
The scarf.
Everything all right?
It's just, you know,
this trip couldn't have
come at a worse time, right?
I think that I bit off
more than I could chew
with this account.
Anything else?
It's just I know
that being with family can
sometimes be stressful.
Well, there is that.
And Beth is mad at me.
Again?
Yeah.
Well, look, it's
only for a few days,
so why don't we try and
make the best of it?
Promise?
I promise.
As long as you promise
not to take the bait
and get in another chess
battle with my dad.
Trust me, I'm not
falling for that again.
The man is a shark.
Oh.
Whoa, you okay?
You look a little pale.
No, I'm fine.
I just skipped lunch.
I'm going to pack, or repack.
What'd you want
to talk to me about?
I know that it's
not the best timing,
but with the girls
getting older,
I think I'm ready
to take on more.
And I know this is something
that we've talked about before,
but I've been thinking
a lot about it recently
and it just, I feel like...
Wow.
I was not expecting this.
I know the timing's not great.
Oh, the timing
is never perfect.
I think it's a great idea.
Oh, really?
Yes, yes, we can adapt.
Remember when we were
planning to have Ruby,
we thought two kids
would do us in.
You don't think the
girls are going to feel
like they're not enough?
I don't want them
to feel that way.
Are you kidding?
They're going to be thrilled
to have a younger
sister, or brother.
Um...
We're not talking
about the same thing.
No, we're not.
We're not talking about
the same thing, sorry.
I...
Corinna reached out to me.
As in formerly the bane
of your existence Corinna?
She wants me to
be the point person.
And this is an
amazing opportunity.
Okay.
And work was a
huge part of my life.
It was.
And with Ruby going to
preschool, I have more time.
Okay, but when we had kids,
you wanted to stay home.
What made you change your mind?
I...
I just feel like you're the,
you know, you get to go to work
and you get to do what you love.
and then you come home, you
get the best part of them.
You get to be the fun
dad, and I'm just this,
the person that says
no all the time.
I need balance.
Mom!
Stop it!
Wait, hang on, let's
finish this conversation.
I can't.
I gotta break up a fight
and then I gotta sew an ear
back on a stuffed animal.
So just...
Maybe you're just burnt out.
What if tomorrow
you head back home
and the girls and I
will stay back a day?
Give you, I don't
know, a little break?
That would be nice.
Hey, girls, girls, girls.
Flight 662 to Chicago,
urging passengers to
proceed to gate B14
for immediate boarding.
Can I bring either of
you something to drink
before your flight?
Oh, champagne?
I'll just have some
water, bit of a headache.
Thank you.
Make that two.
Hey, we've got a long flight.
Maybe see if you can
catch up on some sleep.
Good idea.
Fingers crossed we won't
encounter any screaming kids.
Got my eye on a potential
troublemaker over there.
Speaking of which, are you
prepared to talk babies
when your mom inevitably
brings up the subject,
she wants grandkids?
You know, she
has Melly and Ruby
and who knows, one
of these days Posy.
It's not that
uncommon for couples
to decide not to have kids.
Ladies and
gentlemen, flight 783
to Anchorage, Alaska will begin
pre-boarding in 10 minutes.
Please make your
way to the gate.
I'll get those waters to go.
Thanks.
This is Dr.
Vogel returning your call.
I have your test results.
Please give me a call back.
Hannah, I had another bad
dream, can you read to me?
Sure.
Come on.
"It was a bright
and sunny morning
"and the window
stood wide open."
I'm trying to sleep.
Can we start at the beginning?
Posy, if we keep
starting at the beginning,
we'll never get to the end.
Mom and Dad would start over
as many times as we wanted.
I wish they were here.
Me too.
Okay.
"There once was a
velveteen rabbit
"and in the beginning
he was really splendid.
"He was fat and punchy
as a rabbit should be."
Hey, sorry.
Hey, sis, welcome home!
Thank you.
Hey!
Jason, the kids,
getting their bags?
Nope, just me flying solo.
Wait, what?
They'll be here tomorrow.
I'm so confused, why
didn't you say anything?
I didn't want you to worry.
You know, kind of like
you're doing right now.
I'm not worried.
You know, it's just different.
Well, Jason thought I
could use some quality time
with my sisters, so he's
giving me some space.
Details, please.
Can we just talk
about something else?
Lots of women are
mothers and have careers.
Well, yeah.
It's not selfish
of me to want more.
Did he say you
were being selfish?
No, he just can't
understand why now.
I mean, I love being
a mother and a wife.
I just, I want more.
Yeah, okay.
That's great.
But yeah, why now?
Talking to Corinna
woke something up in me.
I mean, I miss being out
there with adults, you know,
doing something that I'm good at
that doesn't involve
cleaning or making lunches.
I miss the hustle.
And let's be honest, I mean,
the girls are gonna
grow up, right?
And they're going to
be out of the house
and then who's going to hire me?
I mean, an 18 year gap tends
to stick out on a resume.
I mean, I'd be un-hireable.
I think you're getting
ahead of yourself here.
And in Jason's defense,
change is hard.
Maybe he just likes
things the way they are.
Yeah, but he didn't
seem to have a problem
when he thought it was
about having another baby.
He said "We'll
adjust, you know."
Wait, you want another baby?
No, that's not about
having another baby.
Oh, because you
mentioned a baby.
No.
Wait, are we having one
of those I should just
listen conversations
or you want my
help conversations?
Both.
Okay.
Well, to be honest,
I'm pretty surprised
that you're even thinking about
working with Corinna again.
I mean, you couldn't get
away from her fast enough.
People change.
Everybody gets to do
what they want in life.
I mean, you get to spend
time in the mountains
and you'll have the cafe.
And Hannah, you know, she
leads her jet-setting life.
And then there's me.
You shouldn't compare
yourself to others, you know.
Things aren't always
as simple as they seem.
I'm just...
I'm happy to be home.
I'm excited to see Mom and Dad.
They are so happy you're here.
Does she ever talk
about it, the accident?
No.
Talking about the accident is...
It's not really our
family's strong suit.
What an awful thing
to be reminded of
every single birthday.
I think this is the
first time in five years
that you, me, and Hannah have
been home at the same time.
Should be interesting.
Really interesting.
Oh, there they are!
Welcome home, honey.
Oh, oh, sweetheart.
- Good to see you.
Good to see you.
Hello, kid.
Dad.
Oh, I'm so happy to be home.
We've been counting the days.
Yeah.
Wait, where's
Jason, the girls?
Oh, slight change of plans.
They'll be coming tomorrow.
Oh, well, we'll just
get your bags inside.
We set up your old room for you.
Thanks, Dad.
So you must be exhausted.
Do you need a hot
shower or a warm cookie?
Both.
That's my girl.
Posy, can you show your
sister to her room?
I think she knows
which room, Mom.
This brings me back.
Did I ever tell you how
much I miss your cooking?
Well, I miss
cooking for you more.
You spoil us.
Sometimes I get jealous that
Posy gets to live next door.
Seriously, I wish I was
half the cook you were.
I think Jason and the
girls definitely agree.
Oh, come on.
I'm sure you're great.
No.
Well, all it
takes is practice.
Posy here used to want
nothing to do with baking
and she's turning
into a real pro.
Oh.
That's quite a casserole.
Yeah.
Well, Hannah and Adam
will be here soon
and I wanted to take
some to Luke too.
Who's Luke?
He's been renting the guest
house the past few weeks.
He's a travel writer.
Oh, speak of the devil.
Hey.
Okay.
You didn't want to tell me
that there was a cute writer
living on the property?
It never occurred to me.
Uh huh.
And he is a very
nice young man.
In fact, he is
writing a travel guide
about the great peaks
of North America.
All of which I hope
to summit one day.
Actually, Mom,
why don't you let Posy and
I run this over to him?
- Yeah.
- I would like to meet Luke.
You think this is funny.
What a nice surprise.
I hope we're
not bothering you.
You're not bothering me.
Mom whipped up one
of her specialties.
Have you eaten?
No.
Oh, this is my
nosy sister, Beth.
I've heard a lot about you.
New Jersey, married, two kids.
That about sums it up.
I have heard a
lot about you too.
Really?
Yeah, Mom filled her in.
Oh.
You guys want to come in?
We would love to.
Except that we can't
because our other sister
is arriving any second.
That'd be Hannah, right?
- Yeah.
- That's right.
So how long will you be in town?
I'm not really sure.
I've got a few climbs I
want to get under my belt
and a few sights I'd like to see
before I head back
home to Chicago.
He should come to the
Lumberjack Games with us.
We're going to the
Lumberjack Games?
Yeah, it's a family tradition.
Okay, well, I'm sure
Luke has work to do.
Actually, one thing you
should know about writers is
we do just about anything
to avoid writing.
Well, it's a plan.
All right, I
look forward to it.
Tell your mom
thanks for the food.
I will.
Bye, Luke.
Family tradition?
Okay, I might've
gotten carried away,
but I feel bad,
he's all by himself.
You're just like Mom,
always playing matchmaker.
Posy!
- Hey!
Hi!
So good to see you.
Hey.
Beth.
How was the flight?
Oh, it was great.
Except for the kid that
was kicking my seat.
Oh, it wasn't that bad.
He was just being a typical kid.
Here's
the weary travelers!
Oh, you made it!
I'm so glad to see you.
Hey, Adam, welcome.
- Welcome home.
Okay, let's get inside
and we are going to
go make some tea.
Come on, girls.
You have anything stronger?
I may have a single malt
scotch around here somewhere.
Follow me.
These are delicious.
I am definitely quitting
my diet while I'm here.
Mom, I love your food.
Mom, sit down, relax.
Oh, it's just so good to
have all my girls here again.
It's a miracle we could do
it with your busy schedules.
Did you really think we'd
miss your 60th birthday?
Okay, note to everyone.
No need to keep
reiterating it's my 60th.
Just say plain old birthday.
How are things at the cafe?
Oh, Posy here has just
really taken over the reins.
She's a natural.
It's almost like Stewart
and I don't even need
to be there anymore.
It gives us such
peace of mind knowing
that it is going to be in
safe hands when we retire.
Well, speaking of retiring,
I think I'm going to go to bed.
No?
Yeah, me too.
I'll be up just as soon
as I beat your dad here.
I have him cornered.
Checkmate.
- Seriously?
- Every time.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
You've had a long flight.
We'll play again when
you're not so tired.
Dad, you're making it worse.
Well, I...
Next time, sweetie.
Let's go.
Live to fight another day.
- Yeah, good night.
- See everybody tomorrow.
- Night.
- Nighty night.
You know, I think I
will turn in as well.
I'm going to give Jason
and the kids a call
before I read a book
and drift off to a peaceful
uninterrupted slumber.
I'll help you up.
I'm fine.
Sure, yeah.
That'd be great.
- Night, Mom, Dad.
- Night, girls.
Good night, girls.
Just the thought of
working at the cafe
for the rest of my life
scares me to death.
I want to travel,
I want adventure.
I want to climb new peaks.
I know, but it's beautiful
here and the people are nice.
And Mom and Dad have
done so much for us.
I mean, it's their dream to
keep the cafe in the family.
What is this?
I don't think I've
ever seen this before.
Me either.
I can't believe we
still have a VHS player.
It must've been Hannah's.
I think that about does it.
Let's go.
Girls.
What do you think, girls?
You excited?
Your first overnight
hiking trip.
Isn't it gonna be freezing?
I'm starving.
I need to go to the bathroom.
As you can tell,
they're all very excited.
Mom sure was beautiful.
Yeah.
She sure was.
No colds, no one gets
colds on this trip.
The same age
as Melly and Ruby now.
Yeah.
Sometimes I do wonder how
different life would be
if Mom and Dad were alive.
Me too.
I also think about what
it would've been like
if Suzanne and Stewart
hadn't taken us in.
Yeah.
So much
for sleeping in.
Sorry, I know
it's early for you,
but I'm just dying
to get your answer.
Corinna.
Jason and I talked
and we just don't think
it's the right time for us.
I think that's
a mistake, Beth.
This is a golden opportunity.
Believe me, I know,
but I'm going to have to pass.
I appreciate you thinking
of me for this though.
Good morning.
Hey, there's coffee
if you want some.
Where is everyone?
Oh, Mom and Dad
are at the cafe,
Adam went into town, and
not sure where Hannah is.
Funny.
So what's on the
agenda for today?
I'm actually going
to go into town too.
I wanted to get a few
extra little things
for Mom's birthday.
You want to join?
Sure.
I'd love to.
- Great.
- Hannah, you want to come?
I would really love to,
but I have to get
through this proposal.
I'll catch up with
you guys later.
And miss a day out
with your sisters?
Don't make me feel bad.
I didn't say anything.
You don't have to.
So just you and me then.
Yeah, guess so.
Have fun.
We will.
Hey, Beth, how about this?
No.
Pretty sure she would hate that.
Oh well.
Luke!
Hi.
Posy, look, it's Luke.
Yeah, I can see that.
I saw you guys through the
window, I wanted to say hi.
What are you up to?
Oh, we're trying to find
a little extra something
for Mom's birthday.
How about you?
I was going to go to Keystone
Canyon, get some climbs in.
I hear there's some beautiful
waterfalls up there.
Oh yeah, some of my favorite
routes are up that way.
Why don't you guys come?
Oh, that's more Posy's domain.
You should go.
Oh, we just got here.
Yeah.
Go, I can keep looking.
And leave you all alone?
Oh, you say that
like it's a bad thing.
Jason arrives with
the kids today,
so this might be the only,
you know, me time I get.
What do you say?
Yeah, yeah, I'd love to.
Great.
Bye, Beth.
- Bye, Beth.
This is beautiful.
Yeah, this is home.
Aren't you so lucky you got
Denali right in your backyard?
Yeah, but you get to
climb all over the world.
What's been your
favorite so far?
Matterhorn.
I mean, it's not the tallest,
but it's definitely a challenge.
Yeah, man, I would love
to climb in Switzerland
or, gosh, anywhere in Europe.
Well, someone of your
skills, you definitely should.
Yeah, I was thinking about
going back there this summer.
Could use a companion,
like a climbing companion.
Oh, I'd love to, but work.
I mean, your parents
would understand
a little climbing excursion.
My dad maybe, but my mom,
I think she'd rather
I took up something
a little less dangerous,
like scrapbooking.
Over-protective, huh?
Yeah.
But I can understand.
My birth parents and
one other couple,
they were killed in an
avalanche on Denali years ago.
I was four years
old at the time.
Sorry, Posy.
That's an impossible
situation to deal with.
We're still dealing with
it, each in our own way.
Posy, I...
Oh gosh, I don't
mean to bring you down.
No, what I want to say-
Oh, you don't have to
say anything, really.
It's a lot to lay on someone.
Most people don't know
how to react, it's fine.
We came here to hike,
let's get to it.
Well, I think they
are great together.
Well, they do have
a lot in common.
I say we stay out
of her business.
Oh, come on.
You guys realize I'm
standing right here?
And I agree with Hannah.
Thank you.
We just want you
to be happy, honey.
Grandma, we made it!
Oh, there's my
two favorite girls!
I missed you guys.
My turn.
Auntie Posy!
We almost missed our plane.
Well, I'm glad you didn't
because I missed you.
Come here.
- Mommy!
- Where is your Daddy?
Freezing out there.
Oh.
Wow.
I kind of didn't
know what to pack,
so I kind of packed everything.
Yeah, good man.
So, who is hungry?
We had pretzels, two cookies,
and a candy bar on the plane.
Traitor.
Well, let's get
your coats off at least.
Come on.
I'm glad you're here.
Me too.
How was your flight?
Well, we were a little slow
getting out of the house,
but we made it.
That reminds me, actually,
not all of us made it.
Daddy lost Bugsy.
- Oh no!
- Daddy lost Bugsy.
What?
Yeah, Daddy lost Bugsy.
Well, sweetie, he
might be on the airplane.
I'll call the airline.
Hey, girls, you know what?
I didn't get my hug.
Who wants to hug Auntie Hannah?
Aunt Hannah!
Hi, sweetheart.
Hello, you two.
It's so good to
see you girls again.
Think we'll ever
see Bugsy again?
'Course you will.
Oh.
I gotta get this.
Be right back.
Well, are you sure you're sure?
100%
Congratulations, Hannah,
you're going to be a mother.
Oh, look!
Hey, Socks.
Wow.
Can we ride her, Mommy?
Not right now.
I can walk 'em
around really slowly.
Maybe when you're
a little bit older.
But last year, you said
wait until next year.
It's already next year.
I've got helmets.
You know what, I'm
going to have to say no.
Hey, you know what?
I bet you he would love it
if you gave him a brush.
Oh, that's a good idea.
A brush.
It's pretty safe, you know.
I'd make sure they didn't fall.
Why chance it?
He's got a perfect record.
Not one accident.
I don't think anybody
plans on getting hurt, Posy.
That's why they
call it an accident.
Come on, you don't
want them growing up
being afraid of everything.
Not everybody's a daredevil.
Our parents were.
Yep, and look what
happened to them.
You know, Mom worries about
you when you go climbing.
What, am I supposed to
stop doing what I love
just because it makes
someone nervous?
Well, it's not just someone.
It must be nice to
have your freedom.
What freedom?
I have my entire future
mapped out for me.
You and Hannah get to live
the lives that you want
while I'm stuck here,
working at the cafe.
You don't think Mom
and Dad felt stuck?
Do you think their plans
involved raising
three little girls?
Sometimes you have
to make sacrifices.
We all do.
Good job, girls.
Nice and gentle.
What is that?
That's a snowman.
I thought it was a turtle.
Is he making fun of Pudgy?
You named your snowman Pudgy?
Well, it's definitely accurate.
Gosh, I remember this
like it was yesterday.
- Let's see.
- Look.
These girls were best friends.
Oh, it's my favorite
picture of you girls.
Look, they are at
the fairy creek.
They have fairies here?
Oh, yes.
You can't come all the way
here and not go to fairy creek.
Can we go?
Please, please, please?
- Please?
Sure.
But Auntie Posy would
have to be the guide.
I don't think I would
remember how to get there.
I would love to.
Thanks.
Dad's promised Paul
Bunyan over here
that we would go to
the Lumberjack Games,
so we're in for that.
Oh yeah, we're in for that.
And I gotta be honest,
I'm very excited.
Adam, you in, buddy?
Sounds good to me.
Hannah?
Where's Hannah?
I'll be back.
Look at this blue hair.
Hey.
Everything all right?
Yeah, I'm great.
Why don't you come join us?
Posy and Luke are going
through old photo albums
and I think I'm close to
checkmating your dad, so...
I'll be in, in a minute.
Okay, what is it?
It's just...
It's just a headache really.
No big deal.
I just...
You have working too hard.
It's supposed to be
a time to unwind.
Yeah.
Okay, listen, I have an idea.
What if, after I wrap
up this next case,
you and I go on a real vacation?
I don't know.
Hear me out, hear me out.
We'll go somewhere secluded.
No kids.
A small island, just you,
me, and endless margaritas.
I don't think a vacation
is in our immediate future.
Why?
Adam, I-
We're going to start charades.
Do you guys want to play?
Count us in, yes please.
I can definitely beat
your dad at charades.
Okay.
Sorry, I cut you off.
What were you going to say?
Um.
I was just going to remind you
not to get so
competitive with my dad.
Charades.
First new message.
Hi, Beth,
it's Corinna again.
Look, I know you're busy,
but I emailed you
the brief anyways.
Just look at it.
You don't want to look
back years from now
and regret not doing this.
Call me.
Beth, we're
starting charades!
Coming.
This is where
real fairies live?
That's right,
but they only come out when
there's no people around.
Do they have magic powers?
Oh, absolutely.
In fact, if you can find
a little round stone,
make a wish, toss
it in the water,
and your wish will come true.
What'd you find?
Can I wish for
Bugsy to come home?
I don't see why not.
Let's get you one too.
Okay, now I'm going to take
you girls to the wishing spot.
Oh yeah, okay.
They come right over here.
Okay, close your
eyes and make a wish
and throw it in the water.
That's so good!
It's gonna come true, good job!
My wish, Mom, I made a wish!
Good job, sweetie.
Well, here we are
on the magical bridge!
Here we are.
It seems way bigger back then.
Yeah, well, we were just kids.
Hey, you know what?
We should recreate that photo.
Oh, that's a great idea.
I'll take it.
Posy, give me your phone.
Yours is way newer than mine.
Now take a seat,
Hannah in the middle.
Oh, we don't have to
actually sit on the ground.
I think you'll live.
Do we really have
to sit on the ground?
You're so pushy, come on.
Squeeze in close.
I just don't understand
why you have to do that.
Why I have to do what?
Tell her to make
a wish for Bugsy.
Now she's going to
be disappointed.
Look on the bright side, at
least your daughter's going-
Girls!
Hey, can we not do this now?
Big smiles.
Hannah, I think your arms
were around your sisters.
Hold on.
Beth.
- Oh, oh!
Sorry.
You startled me.
I didn't mean
to interrupt you.
We are leaving in five minutes.
Okay.
On your marks, get set!
What are they doing, Grandpa?
Well, this is the cross
cut saw competition.
The teams are racing each other
to see who can cut through
the logs the fastest.
I want to show Luke
the wood carving.
I want to try my hand at
a little speed chopping.
What?
Well, there's a
lot to see here,
so why don't we just split up
and meet over the hot saw
competition in about an hour?
And we'll take Melly and
Ruby over to the kids area.
How about that?
Good?
Let's go.
We'll go this way.
Thanks for coming along.
I'm sure you'd much
rather be climbing.
No way, miss this?
I love this stuff.
Plus, there's always
time to go climbing.
Oh, you are leaving next week.
Unless of course you
want to extend your trip?
Is that an invitation?
Maybe.
What do you think
about Luke and Posy?
They seem pretty
good together,
from what little I've seen.
They both love climbing.
Shared interests
are always good.
Thank you.
They're both adrenaline junkies.
You used to be a bit like that.
I think you're talking
about someone else.
Oh, come on.
When we first met, you were
into all sorts of things.
It was you that talked me
into going cliff jumping
at the lake that summer.
I blame you for my
fear of heights.
I was a
different person back then.
You know, I guess there was
things that used to scare me
that don't anymore.
And then there are things
that I thought would scare me,
maybe to the point that I
never wanted to do them,
and I think now maybe
I would like to.
Okay, you lost me a little
bit back there, but...
But whichever Hannah this is
and whatever scary thing you
want to do or not do, I'm in.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Come on, come on, you
got it, you got it, yeah!
What do you say, Mr. McBride?
You want to give it a shot?
Oh, do not challenge him
'cause he might just do it.
No, but I have another
challenge in mind.
Oh no, now you've done it.
What'd I do?
Be afraid.
Okay.
What are we playing for?
Playing for chili?
Well, not just any chili.
Loser has to eat the
five alarm chili.
Oh.
You're on.
No, no, no, Luke, listen.
You don't have to, really.
I'm feeling pretty
good about this.
Plus I got a cast iron stomach.
Oh gosh.
Come on, Luke, you got this.
Go, Luke!
Good, that was good.
That was pretty good.
All right, come on, Dad!
What ever happened
to "Come on, Luke?"
I don't know, he's family.
Iron stomach.
Nice one, Dad.
Did I ever tell you
guys about the time-
That you won the blue
ribbon at the chili cook-off?
And held the title for two
years until Francis Miller won
with what you thought
was a stolen recipe.
Yes.
Dad, we got it.
Oh man, I just love this.
Mr. North's chili is
always my favorite.
How you doing
over there, Luke?
I'm going, I'm going.
Luke, don't worry, mate,
the first aid tents
are right over there.
Just in case.
It's not bad.
Oh man!
This should be illegal, I
think my tongue's going numb.
Good, because you have
to finish the whole bowl.
Dad.
I'm kidding, I'm just kidding.
Are you crying?
No, it's still burning.
Hey, you
just missed the guys.
Oh yeah.
I'm gonna meet up
with them later.
Beth and I promised the girls
we'd make special cookies
for grandma's birthday.
That's sweet.
Wow, somebody's phone
is really blowing up.
It's Beth's.
She's still sleeping,
I'll drop it off to her.
Huh.
Everything okay?
Yeah, fine.
Good morning.
Where are the girls?
Playing in the living room.
Why didn't you tell me?
I can explain this.
I thought we put
that behind us.
You lied to me.
I just sent a few ideas.
Jason, wait.
Hey.
Where is everyone?
There are a lot of us.
Can you be more specific?
Mom, Posy.
Posy's heading to work.
Mom's being pampered.
It's just you here?
Yes.
Can you...
Can you watch the
girls for a little bit?
Watch them do what?
Oh my...
I'm joking.
Of course I will.
What is going on, Beth?
Jason's upset.
I may have not told him
something important.
I think there's
a word for that.
No.
No, I did not lie, okay?
Okay.
Maybe a little.
Fine, go.
I've got the girls,
unless of course you think
they're going to eat me alive.
Go, Mom.
Thank you, Hannah.
Wow.
Thanks for walking me to work.
You didn't have to do that.
I wanted to.
How's the book coming?
Good.
I hit a bit of a snag.
Oh, writer's block?
Yeah, something like that.
I'm sure it'll
come back to ya.
So how many rescues
have you been a part of?
Not too many since I started.
Luckily nothing too serious.
Must get a lot of
satisfaction from it.
Might sound crazy,
but I feel like it brings me
closer to my birth parents.
Swear I can feel them
with me sometimes.
How does Suzanne feel
about you doing this?
I know you said that she's
not crazy about your climbing,
but I can imagine that'd
be hard for her too, right?
Sure she'd rather I didn't,
though she'd never say it.
It's normal.
She just wants you to be safe.
Yeah.
It's more than that though.
I didn't tell you
the whole story.
Suzanne was actually
leading the expedition
on the day that my parents died.
Her and my mom
were best friends.
They were a little ways
away from the summit
and rocks triggered
a slide and...
Posy, sometimes
it's no one's fault.
Yeah, I know, that's what
we keep trying to tell her.
She won't hear it.
So they were still in
Michigan at the time?
Yeah, yeah.
They were just working
here for the winter,
working as guides.
This is where my dad, I mean,
Stewart's family is from.
And so after they adopted us,
they knew they needed help,
so they moved here to
be closer to family.
And it worked out.
They helped out with the cafe
and his parents
helped out with us.
The cafe was in the family.
Yeah, they were so happy
when he took it over,
and one day I will do the same.
Well, thanks for the walk, Luke.
You sure don't want
to come inside?
I can hook you up with
our famous blueberry pie.
Well, if you're
going to twist my arm.
There you go.
Thank you.
What do I owe you?
Oh, it's on the house.
Oh, in that case, I'll take
three more of these to go.
Don't press your luck.
Actually, I would like
to make a contribution
to the mountain rescue fund,
so could I get a dozen
of those cookies?
That I'll happily
charge you for.
Great.
Oh, table three
needs their check.
Oh, hey, Posy.
I wanted to say thank
you for inviting me out
with your family yesterday.
I had a great time.
Yeah, it was really fun.
Everyone really likes you.
Maybe we could do
it again sometime.
Yeah, I'd love that.
- Great.
- Yeah.
But if people see us
hanging out together,
they might get the
impression that we're dating.
I don't worry about
what other people think.
I don't think I believe you.
Believe me now?
I told her I wasn't
interested in taking the job,
I promise.
But the next thing you know,
she's convinced me to take a
stab at a marketing proposal.
Convinced.
More like manipulated.
But Beth, we've always
told each other everything.
Why not this?
I don't know, I guess
I just wanted to know
if I still have what it takes.
Of course you still
have what it takes.
You're great at
everything you do.
I guess I just thought that
maybe after all these years,
I've lost it, you know?
I mean, Jason,
if you had to give
up your career and be
a stay-at-home dad,
you would've felt the same way.
When we decided to have kids,
it was your decision
to walk away.
I know.
If you really want
to go back to work,
even if it is for
Corinna, I'll support you.
We'll figure it out.
You really think we
can make this work?
I do.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
By the way, who's watching
the girls right now?
Good job, girls.
Your mom is going
to be so impressed.
Aunt Hannah?
Mm-hm?
Do you think Bugsy will
ever find his way home?
Sure.
Did you ever lose someone
you love more than anything?
Yeah, I did, honey.
I have to get this.
We're going to have
a little break,
but don't eat the product.
All right?
Hello?
Okay, sounds good.
Oh, and heads up, they
don't make them anymore,
so you're going to have
your work cut out for you.
Tell you what, drop
everything you're doing,
make it a top priority.
Sure, let me do some digging.
Great.
And Lexi, I know that I
don't do a very good job
of telling you this, but
I really appreciate you.
I know, but it's
also nice to hear.
All right, bye.
Melly, Ruby!
We're home.
I'm a cookie.
So how are my little
cookie monsters?
Oh, wow, I am so sorry.
I only left them
for like a minute.
Hey, girls, let's go
get cleaned up, come on.
Okay.
It only takes a second
for them to get into things.
Well, thank goodness
it was something harmless
like frosting.
That's not the point, Hannah.
What is your point?
I asked you to watch them,
not let them run wild while
you took care of work.
I said I was sorry.
You know what?
This is my fault.
I should have known better.
Hannah, what I mean-
Oh, I know what you mean.
Hannah.
I only left them
for like a minute.
Yeah, not good.
We were having so much fun.
It was like I was the
cool aunt for once.
Well, let's be clear,
I'm the cool aunt.
Yeah, that's true.
You know, Beth is right,
I'm not made for kids.
Well, then you and Adam
are perfect for each other.
You know, not
everyone wants kids.
I'm pregnant.
That is exactly
the reaction I had.
I'm trying to picture
you with a baby.
Posy!
Oh my gosh.
You're going to be a great mom.
I get to be an aunt again!
Oh, congratulations.
You?
I mean...
I mean, you did seem
a little preoccupied,
maybe a little bit distant.
I mean, more so than normal.
Sorry, that didn't
come out right.
What did Adam say?
Well...
Hannah.
We weren't going
to have children.
This is something I made very
clear before we got married.
I know, but
circumstances change.
You have to trust that
things are gonna work out.
I have always
loved that about you.
You've loved what about me?
You go with the flow.
You're like water.
I'm more like-
A brick wall?
Well, I might've
said more like a rock.
That works too.
But yes.
Posy, I don't know if I have
what it takes to be a good mom.
When we moved here after the
accident, I was so terrified.
Everything we'd
ever known was gone.
I'll never forget
how comforting it was
to have you as my big sister.
Really?
Yeah.
And that's how
you'll be as a mom.
I'm just a little scared.
Yeah.
Sure.
Hi.
Hey.
Welcome.
Yes, sorry, I was
knocking for a while
and I just let myself in.
- That's great.
- Good.
So one for the adults,
one for the kids.
And there was a
package out front.
That's for me.
Checkmate!
It looks like
you're just in time
to watch history be made.
Thank you for these.
I won.
New chess master.
Yeah!
Thank you very much.
Oh, please, no,
it's no big deal.
We all came
running into the room
and there was Posy,
just standing on top
of the refrigerator.
What was she, about
five years old?
Her first official summit.
You were like a
little mountain goat,
climbing everything in sight.
Oh, it was like
she had no fear.
You know, one of my favorite
memories of her as a kid is
when we got snowed
in at Christmas.
Do you remember that?
Right, okay.
So it snowed three days straight
and we couldn't leave the house.
So Posy's coming down the
stairs with a little toy shovel
saying she's going to
tunnel her way out.
I believed her.
We all did.
That's been fun.
Enough Posy stories.
No, no, no, I love
this kind of stuff.
What's your favorite
childhood memory?
Easy.
10th birthday, my aunt
gave me my first real tent.
So I camped out in the
backyard every night,
but I pretended I
was on Half Dome.
I thought to myself, I
could live like this.
And you do.
You live your dream.
Been very lucky.
Suzanne and I spent an
anniversary bivouacked
on Half Dome.
What's bivouacked?
Well, sometimes it
takes more than one day
to complete a climb,
so you sleep hanging off
the side of the rock.
Why?
My question exactly, Melly.
You really did that, Grandma?
Mm-hm.
Your grandma was
quite the mountaineer.
Why don't you climb anymore?
Oh, it was a long time ago.
Yeah.
Who's ready for
her birthday cake?
That sounds great!
Great idea.
- Beth, will you help me?
- Yeah.
So Luke, what's the next stop?
Chicago.
Promised my aunt I'd be back
for the annual Whitaker
family reunion.
- Oh, that sounds nice.
- Yeah.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Mom ♪
Yay!
Happy 30th times two.
It's perfect.
Okay.
Here we go.
Thank you.
Wait, Whitaker.
Luke Whitaker.
I knew you seemed familiar.
Hannah, what are
you talking about?
A few months ago,
I got some messages
from a Luke Whitaker
who wanted to know
about the accident.
Wait, I got those
phone calls too.
Was that you?
What are you
guys talking about?
I can explain.
Explain what?
That's a new low.
It's not that simple.
See, we've had people
chase this story before,
but none of them have
moved into the guest house.
A lot of people die climbing.
Why is our story so
important to you?
Okay, girls.
We are going to go upstairs
and get ready for bed.
What about cake?
Well, we are going to
have cake after, I promise.
Yeah, great idea.
I was going to get
ready for bed too
so then later we can have
some cake in our PJs.
Okay.
I'm not just some
guy chasing a story.
My real last name is Palmer.
Cheryl and Brett Palmer?
My parents were
the other couple
that died that day on Denali.
a.
Posy, if I could just explain-
Excuse me.
- Posy.
- Honey, wait.
Sit down, young man.
I was going to tell her.
It wasn't supposed
to happen like this.
I'll pack my things and
be gone in the morning.
I thought about you.
All the time.
I didn't have the
courage to reach out.
I couldn't face you.
I understand.
I just thought
you'd be better off
without me as a reminder.
The woman who ruined your life.
Luke, I'm so sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
It wasn't your fault
and you didn't ruin my life.
I've had an amazing life.
I wanna hear.
Everything.
Hi, Colin, can we sit here?
Of course.
The McBride sisters,
together again.
What can I get you ladies?
White wine, please.
Bring the bottle.
I'll just have
a water, thanks.
Coming right up.
How could I be so gullible?
It's not your fault.
I really liked him.
Oh.
We don't know the whole story.
Oh, come on, you
can't be serious.
Maybe he's
looking for closure.
I mean, if anyone
can be sympathetic
to what he's going
through, it's us.
No, no, no, I can't
believe I'm hearing this.
He lied to her.
Okay, I admit I like
this new side to you.
Yeah, well, somebody hurts
my little sister, I get angry.
I'd do the same for you.
Okay, I saw that.
What?
You don't think
I'd stand up for you.
I don't think you
think about me much.
Can we not argue?
No, let's have it out
right here, right now.
So how's your
evening going so far?
Not now, Colin.
Right.
You know what?
Hannah's right.
I'm so tired of us all
tiptoeing around everything.
Why did we stop being
honest with each other?
Don't you think it's weird
that we never talk
about the accident?
We don't talk about it
because we are protecting Mom.
But why?
Why do you think everyone
needs protecting?
Mom, Melly, Ruby?
Can we leave the
girls out of this?
I'm just saying that
they'll never have a chance
to skin their knees.
A few bumps and bruises
are good for kids.
Says the woman with no kids.
It's not that you're
just overprotective.
You catastrophize everything.
I catastrophize everything
because bad things do happen.
Posy, they happen to us.
Beth is right.
It is so scary to bring
a kid into the world
that is so uncertain
where parents could just
be swept away like that.
They need certainty
and stability.
Sorry, Hannah, I
love you, I do, I just,
I just don't think you
know what's best for kids.
Beth.
I have lost count of how
many times you have canceled
on Melly and Ruby.
Have you thought about
how that makes them feel?
It's just, I-
Please don't say
that you're busy.
Do you want to know the truth?
I love those girls, but I...
What?
It's just too hard.
They remind me of
you and Posy when...
When Mom and Dad died.
And you, I will never
forget how afraid you were.
And I wanted so badly
to save you from pain,
but I didn't know how.
You did.
Yeah.
I don't know what
I would have done
if I didn't have you to lean on.
Hannah, you were
just a kid too.
That wasn't fair to you.
I just,
I never considered how hard
that must've been for you.
I'm sorry.
Sounds a lot like motherhood.
No matter how you felt,
you were always there for us.
That's why you'll
make a great mom.
Oh my...
You're pregnant.
I think she's blown a fuse.
For the record, I'll
still be the cool aunt.
I've made a career
writing travel guides
related to climbing.
But I decided that I
wanted to shift gears
and write about
something different.
So I set out to write
a survival book,
not just for climbers
that survived accidents,
but for the people
that were left behind
by climbers that
weren't so lucky.
People like you all.
Like Hannah, Beth, and Posy.
People like myself.
I thought it might
bring some closure.
We could all use some closure.
I don't blame you, Suzanne.
After all the research that
I've done about that day,
nothing points to anything
other than a random
act of nature.
There are always signs.
Yes, but my parents chose
to go up there that day.
As climbers, we know
there are always risks
and we calculate those risks.
And it's not my
place to say this,
but it seems to me like the
best way to honor my parents is
for you to forgive yourself.
Thank you.
Oh, I swear, this
woman never sleeps.
She's constantly
calling me, texting me.
Hannah, what are you doing?
You're going
to get me fired.
She can't fire you if
she hasn't hired you.
She is using you.
Beth, if you want to go
back to work, that's great.
There are plenty of places that
would be lucky to have you,
places that won't
make you miserable
like working with Corinna.
I know, but it's
been seven years,
I wouldn't even know
where to start, Hannah.
Well, I'll help
you if you'll let me.
Okay, but only if you let
me help you with the baby.
Count on it.
Bye, Corinna.
Bye.
I feel good.
Congratulations, you are free.
Okay, now that
we've dealt with that,
let's deal with you.
Oh, I'm good.
My life is here,
I'm cool with that.
No, no.
You deserve to be happy.
What about everything you
said before about sacrifice?
I was wrong.
I'm sorry if I made you feel
like Mom and Dad's happiness
was your responsibility.
Shouldn't live your life
according to what
someone else wants.
They've done so much for us.
Yeah.
But you should
pursue your passion.
And if that means venturing
out, then so be it.
Mom and Dad will understand.
Can we make this a tradition?
Every year, the McBride
sisters get together
and really be honest
about their lives?
I'd really like that.
Me too.
I really love you guys.
Is it safe?
Yes, Colin.
I'll take it, I'll take it.
All right.
Little sis, paying the bill.
- Thanks, Posy.
There's still one more thing
you need to take care of.
What are you going
to do about Luke?
Oh.
Hey, Mom.
Hey, are you okay?
Yes, I'm so sorry I ran out.
You didn't get to
do your presents
or your cake or anything.
The girls got into the cake,
so we all just joined in.
Can I get you girls some?
- I'm okay.
I'm going to go
tuck the girls in.
I love you.
I'll see you upstairs, hon.
Yeah, sure.
- Night, Mom.
- Night, sweetie.
- Girls.
- Night, Dad.
Okay, come here.
So Luke and I had
a really good talk.
We talked about the accident.
Mom.
I can't tell you
what a relief it is
knowing he doesn't blame me.
It's like I can finally
see through this cloud
that's been hanging over my
head for the past 25 years.
Mom, that's so
much to carry around.
I think Luke is the
best birthday gift
I could have asked for.
We also talked about you.
Now, I'm not playing matchmaker,
but I know his feelings
for you are genuine.
Just I don't know how I
could ever trust him again.
Forgiveness is a good start.
You seem made for each other.
I've never seen two people
who loved the mountains
more than you do.
It's your calling.
Look at me.
The cafe will survive, honey.
But you and Dad, you
have plans to retire.
If there's one thing
I've learned for sure,
it's plans change.
You need to follow
your heart, Posy.
And if that leads you to the
peaks of Europe, then so be it.
Yeah, but you and Dad,
you guys didn't get a
chance to have that freedom.
You need to
understand something.
Our lives have been so
much richer because of you.
Sometimes you find your calling,
but sometimes your
calling finds you.
Raising you girls was ours.
Thank you.
I was thinking.
I could talk to Paul
about working from home
a couple of days a week.
He's a reasonable guy.
Don't hate me,
but I have decided not to
go back to work for Corinna.
Oh.
I think I'm going to wait
for something
that's a better fit.
And Hannah has said she'd
helped me find something.
Oh, wow.
Why the change of heart?
What started as
excitement, I don't know,
turned into anxiety.
Started to remember why I
was happy to leave there
in the first place.
Good.
But I think I'm going to try
and work from home a
couple of days anyway.
I mean, the girls aren't
going to be young forever
and I'd like to be around more.
I'd like that.
Hey, how's Posy?
Oh, she'll be fine.
She's tough.
You know, we talked.
Like really talked,
and having it out with
those two was like,
it was like getting a gift
I didn't know I needed.
Yeah, those are the best kind.
I'm pregnant, Adam.
I'm going to be a dad?
Yeah, you're not disappointed?
Disappointed, what, that
we're going to have a family?
I couldn't be happier.
I don't know,
we always said we weren't
going to have kids.
Yeah, well, things change.
They're gonna change a lot.
You're not worried?
Hey, do I look worried?
Little bit.
Do I?
Little bit?
I love you.
The end.
One more?
And then you promise
you'll go to bed?
Okay, go pick one.
What do we have here?
Oh, yes.
Do you know that Hannah
used to read this
to Posy and me when
we were your age?
Hey, I just wanted
to say good night.
Will you read with us?
Is there room?
Get in here.
Wow, you're still up.
Yeah, we're just about to
read our favorite bedtime story.
Come on, we'll make room.
I would love to, but girls,
there was somebody that was
just sitting in the hall.
The fairies heard our wishes!
They sure did.
Thank you.
Of course.
You mind?
Do I mind?
All right, girls.
You ready?
Yeah.
Okay.
"There was once a
velveteen rabbit
"and in the beginning
he was really splendid.
"He was fat and punchy
as a rabbit should be."
Hey.
I didn't think
I'd see you again.
Yeah, well,
my mom said something last
night about forgiveness
and I put myself in your shoes
and it turns out they
feel a lot like my shoes.
Guess we share a tragedy.
Yeah.
I'm really sorry you
lost your parents, Luke.
You had every
right to be upset.
Luke, I have to ask,
if I hadn't found out,
were you ever going to tell me?
My intention was to research
the accident for the book,
but then everything changed.
I fell in love with this place.
The mountains, your family.
I fell in love with you.
Every time I worked up
the courage to tell you,
I would talk myself out of it
because I didn't want to risk
ruining our relationship.
I'm sorry.
I don't blame you if you never
want to talk to me again.
I accept your apology.
Hey, I have to get
back to the house.
Call it Mom's birthday 2.0.
Do you want to join?
Are you sure?
Say yes before
I change my mind.
Yes.
One, two,
three, open your eyes!
Surprise!
Come here, we have
a chair for you.
Sit down, sit down, here you go.
So since last night
got cut a little short,
we thought we would
try this again.
You guys.
This is from me,
Beth, and Hannah.
Oh, girls, you spoil me.
Oh.
I love it.
It's going on the mantle.
Look, honey.
Thank you.
Okay, Adam and I have a
little something for you.
Actually, it's for both of you.
Okay.
"Dear Mom, surprise!
"Baby on the way."
Are you kidding me?
Oh, honey!
Are they crying?
These are happy tears, honey.
We're going to be
grandparents again.
Your Auntie Hannah
is having a baby.
You and Ruby are going to
have a little cousin soon.
Congratulations on
becoming an aunt, again.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming in here
and disrupting our lives.
If the offer still stands,
I would love to go to
Switzerland with you.
Nothing would make me happier.
All right, I would
like to propose a toast.
To family.
Even the ones who aren't with
us who we miss every day.
Michelle and Jerry gave
us the gift of a lifetime.
You three beautiful girls.
Thank you.
Cheers!
Cheers.
- Cheers.
Cheers, Grandpa.
- Let's hug it out.
- Okay.
Get over here, girls!
Oh.
Happy birthday, Mom.
I love you girls.
♪ Here's to the good times ♪
♪ Forget the bad times ♪
♪ These are the best
days of our lives ♪