Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
What a beautiful day!
Yeah, you know what'd be really beautiful?
Some breakfast.
Hey, why don't you
find us breakfast for a change?
Oh yeah? Maybe I will.
I'd like to see that.
Yeah, you could
if you'd get out of my way.
-Get out of your way? I'm under your way!
-Yeah, you're always under my way.
That's because
you follow me wherever I go.
I can't help it. I'm kind of fixed to you.
Why do you always have to be so prickly?
-You finished?
-No.
I got it.
Oopsie.
I gotcha. Here you go.
One, two, three, four.
One, two…
Attention, Octonauts.
Please report to HQ for roll call.
The Octonauts and the Ring of Fire.
Calling all Octonauts.
-Kwazii!
-Peso!
-Shellington!
-Inkling!
-Dashi!
-Tweak!
Tunip!
Good morning, Octonauts.
I hope you all had a good night's sleep.
Aye, Captain,
but I had the weirdest dream.
I dreamt that I went to the kitchen
and ate 17 kelp cakes.
Actually, maybe that wasn't a dream.
Tunip says that soon we'll have
more kelp cakes than ever,
thanks to the Vegimals'
sustainable seaweed farm.
A seaweed farm will provide
lots of delicious seaweed for us to eat,
and it's a home
for all kinds of sea creatures.
Yes, the seaweed harvest starts today.
Well done, Tunip.
Sounds like the seaweed farm
has been a big success.
-Super!
-Any other updates?
Shellington and I have one, Captain.
Listen.
Welcome back
to the Octonauts video training series.
Lesson 27: Basic accordion tips.
Playing the accordion is
a lot easier than it seems.
Dashi?
Whoops. Wrong file. I've been organizing
all the old Octonauts training videos.
This is what
we really wanted you to listen to.
What are we listening to, matey?
A singing sea banshee?
Even better.
This is a recording of an Omura's whale.
A whatter's whale?
An Omura's whale.
They're one of the rarest whales on Earth.
We've been trying to find one for years.
One of our Octo-recorders in the South
Pacific picked up these sounds last night.
So today, Shellington and I are going
to look for the whale that made them.
I'd love to get a picture of it.
It sounds like you're on the right track.
Good luck with the search.
I'm going somewhere today too.
These are my cousins,
the chinstrap penguins.
More penguin cousins?
How many have you got, matey?
A lot. And these cousins live here,
on the Sandwich Islands near Antarctica.
The chinstrap penguins are
in the middle of their egg-laying season.
Captain Barnacles,
Professor Inkling, and I
are going down there to check up on them.
Anyone's welcome to come along. Kwazii?
Thanks, Captain,
but I've got big plans for the day too.
I'm taking the GUP-B out for a
little high-speed action on the high seas.
I mean, I've got to make sure
the old engine's working fine and all.
Funny you should mention that, Kwazii.
As a matter of fact, I'll be checking
on all the GUPs' engines today.
Huh? What do you mean?
What I mean is, I'm taking all the GUPs
back to the Octo-repair station
for a full tune-up.
But we'll need a GUP
to check on the chinstrap penguins.
And we'll need a GUP
to search for the Omura's whale.
We need a GUP for the seaweed harvest.
And Tunip says
he needs a GUP for the seaweed harvest.
And I need my GUP
to drive around really fast in.
Calm down. Tweak already has a solution.
I sure do.
Come on down to the launch bay
and I'll show you.
Everybody, I give you the Z-GUPs.
Z-GUPs!
-Wow!
-Oh wow!
The Z-One, the Z-Two,
the Z-Three, the Z-Four, and…
The Z-Five!
That's right! The Z-Five.
Super, super!
Shiver me whiskers.
You made five new GUPs!
Think of ‘em as proto-GUPs, Kwazii.
GUPs in progress.
You mean they're not even finished yet?
Well, they're mostly finished.
Besides, sometimes you just gotta work
with what you got.
Just one little thing.
Whatever you do, don't push the Z button.
Okay, but what does it do?
Probably fires off the kelp cannons
or launches
the sailfish speed boosters, eh, Tweak?
Let's just say it's a new feature
I haven't been able to test out yet.
Understood, Tweak, and thanks.
These Z-GUPs should be perfect
for today's missions.
Octonauts, let's do this!
Aye-aye!
Octonauts, it's going to be
a very busy day.
Tweak's taking the GUPs
to the repair station…
Wait up, matey!
Wherever the GUP-B goes, I go too!
Dashi and Shellington are heading
to the South Pacific…
If the Omura's whale is out there,
we're going to find it.
Tunip and the Vegimals are working
on the seaweed farm…
And we're going towards Antarctica
to check on the chinstrap penguins.
Safe travels, everyone.
Bye-bye! Goodbye.
Thirty-three, thirty-four,
thirty-five, thirty-six.
This Z-One slowpoke
can barely do 36 loop-de-loops.
In the GUP-B, I can always do at least 67.
Well, once the GUP-B
gets a proper tune-up,
you can do
as many loop-de-loops as you like.
Here we are, the Octo-repair station.
Come on, help me park the GUPs.
In you go.
See you later, Z-One.
Last one.
Not so fast, matey.
I'm not letting the GUP-B out of me sight.
Suit yourself.
Watch the paint job, mateys!
Watch the ears too.
Kwazii, you've got nothing to worry about.
The GUP-B is in good hands.
And you don't need your helmet
or air tank in here now.
It's as dry as a stale fish biscuit.
Wow! I've never been
in this part of the repair station before.
Come on, I'll show you around.
We're on the highest level now.
There are two more below us.
Well, I'll be a sea monkey's uncle.
This place is even bigger
than I remember it.
What are those?
Those are air shafts. They run
through the entire repair station.
Without them, we wouldn't have air
to breathe down here.
And what's in there?
An Octo-Max suit.
I keep one on every level
for heavy lifting.
What?
Number 87.
Polar bear strength training.
With the right attitude, anyone can
have the strength of a polar bear.
What's going on?
It feels like a little tremor. You know,
when the sea floor starts shaking?
Happens all the time down here.
Do they always turn on
old training videos?
Must've messed
with the electrical system or something.
Sometimes all it takes is
a little polar bear strength.
Dashi, look! The Octo-recorder.
It's been picking up
more whale songs all morning.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's look for the Omura's whale.
I mean, let's listen for it.
Hear anything, Shellington?
Nothing yet.
I hear waves crashing.
Crab claws clacking.
Sardines burping.
Dashi, listen.
That's the Omura's whale, all right.
It must be close.
Shellington, wait.
Hurry, before it swims away.
No, Shellington, listen.
I don't like the sound of that at all.
Just sounds like a tremor to me.
Tremors happen all the time down
on the seafloor. Now, come on, let's--
Shellington, it's not just one tremor.
It's lots of tremors,
coming from every direction.
Something strange is going on.
I think you're right.
Captain. Come in, Captain.
Come in, Dashi.
How's the whale search going?
It's going fine, Captain,
but we're picking up
a lot of unusual activity down here.
Activity? What kind of activity?
We're hearing all kinds of tremors.
Much more than usual.
Captain, look!
Our scanners are picking up tremors too,
lots of them.
Here, here, and here.
They're all over the place.
Oh, strange. Very strange indeed.
The tremors seem to be in a ring shape,
all around the Pacific Ocean.
You don't suppose it's the--
Captain, what was that?
Captain?
Flappity flippers!
That seamount just exploded.
That's no seamount.
It's a volcano.
And it's shooting hot lava!
Peso, activate manual steering.
Aye, Captain.
Everybody, hang on.
Steady. Here we are.
That's it.
That was close.
Captain? Are you okay? Captain?
Dashi, another tremor. A big one.
Whenever there's a tremor this big,
there's bound to be…
A tsunami wave!
Jumping jellyfish!
Hurry, back to the ship.
Hang on!
Oh me, oh my, now that's a big one!
Tweak, look out!
Oh no!
Run, matey!
Huh?
Oh no.
-Uh-oh.
-That can't be good.
Captain, what's going on?
I don't know, Peso.
It feels like every volcano
in the whole ocean is erupting at once.
You're not too far off, Captain.
All these volcanoes are part
of the Ring of Fire.
The Ring of Fire?
The Ring of Fire is a group of volcanoes
that stretches
all around the Pacific Ocean.
Some of the volcanoes are underwater,
and some are above it.
How many volcanoes
are we talking about, Professor?
Approximately 452.
-Four hundred and fifty-two?
-Uh-huh.
What we're seeing now is a chain reaction.
That's when a big eruption
on one part of the Ring of Fire
causes eruptions, tremors,
and tsunami waves all around the Pacific.
Flappity flippers!
I'm afraid this is only the beginning.
More eruptions are on the way,
and they could be even bigger.
Even bigger?
Captain, what about the rest of the crew?
We have to warn them.
Calling all Octonauts.
This is an emergency.
Come in. Kwazii? Dashi? Anyone?
Captain, the communication network's down.
You mean, we can't call the others?
This is the biggest disaster
the Octonauts have ever faced,
and we'll all have to face it on our own.
Let's just hope
everyone remembers their training.
Captain? I think we'd better hurry
and get to the chinstrap penguins.
Peso, I think we may have
to put that on hold
until we've dealt with
all these volcanoes.
But that's the problem, Captain.
The chinstrap penguins live
right on top of a volcano.
On top of a volcano?
It usually helps keep their eggs warm,
but according to the map,
it's about to erupt.
Say no more.
Full speed ahead.
All right, then.
Dashi? What do we do?
Well, we stay calm, that's for sure.
I'd say our first problem is
getting down from this tree.
Well, that's taken care of.
What's our next problem?
Now we've got to figure out where we are.
Looks like a deserted island.
Oh, look. That tsunami wave carried us
a very long way from the water.
I guess our next step is to figure out
how to get this back in there.
Better call for backup.
Dashi to Octopod. Come in, Octopod.
Can anyone hear me?
Dashi to Octopod. Come in, Octopod.
A coconut crab!
I'm stuck. That big wave really tossed me.
Here, let me give you a hand.
We coconut crabs live on land,
and we can't swim, you know?
There you go.
Thanks, Mr. Octonaut, sir.
How does he know I'm an Octonaut?
Tweak. Do you read me, Tweak?
Any luck?
Not yet.
Whatever caused that tsunami must've
shut down our communications network.
Isn't there a backup system?
Shellington, wait!
We don't know what those buttons do.
Now we know what that button does.
Shellington, you did it.
The Z-Four has a land mode.
We'll be back in the water in no time.
Not very fast, is it?
Well, Tweak did say
the Z-GUPs weren't finished.
Sounds like the engine's
about to give out.
I don't think that came from the engines.
Listen.
It's something outside.
Come on, we'd better check it out.
It's coming from that hill.
Strange. There's nothing here.
Another tremor.
It's not a tremor.
It's the Omura's whale!
Hello. Sorry to bother you.
Bother us? We were standing on your back.
I didn't mind. But, as you can see,
I do seem to be in a bit of trouble.
The tsunami wave washed you ashore too!
I've always wanted to see
an Omura's whale, but not like this.
We have to get
you back into the water, fast!
Please, don't go out of your way
on account of me.
I'm sure you must be very busy and…
Pardon me, I'm just feeling a bit dry.
Don't worry. We're here to help.
Now that's a tremor!
And I see what's causing it.
A volcano!
The lava's heading straight for us.
We've got to get out of here.
I really don't mean to sound pushy,
but do you think we could please hurry?
Hurry, matey!
Quick, in there.
We can seal the doors to stop the…
Tweak!
Kwazii, I'm stuck!
I've got you, matey.
Kwazii, hurry.
This just needs
a little polar bear strength!
Let's get out of here!
That was a close one.
Polar bear strength, huh?
Gotta remember to thank
the captain for that one.
If we ever want to see the captain again,
we've gotta find a way out of here.
That isn't good.
That isn't good at all.
The station's flooding fast.
Then let's swim our way out.
We don't have our air tanks, remember?
Right. No swimming.
What about the GUPs?
The GUPs are all okay, aren't they?
The GUPs are fine,
but the hangars they're in look like this.
There's no way to launch them.
Wait, the Z-One's hangar is still okay.
The Z-One? Not that old slowpoke.
That old slowpoke
is our only hope for escaping,
but it won't be easy to get to.
It's up here on the top level
where we are,
but the hallway's blocked.
To get to it, we have to go
all the way to the bottom level,
make our way around,
and then come all the way back up.
And how will we do that?
Well, that's the tricky part.
I suppose we could…
That wouldn't work,
but we might be able to…
Tweak? Do you smell that?
Not now, Kwazii. I'm busy.
I could try
to short-circuit the breakers, or--
Fire!
Fire?
-We've gotta get out of here!
-Quick, through that door!
Yow!
How do we get through that?
Oh me, oh my.
Look out! Yow!
Yeah.
Right.
Tweak, what are you doing?
Just thinking like an engineer.
That was cool.
Let's go!
After you.
This way.
The elevator ahead might be able
to take us down to the lower levels.
Nope!
Oh me, oh my. We're trapped!
Maybe not.
What about in here?
Kwazii, you're a genius.
This chute'll take us down
to the lower level. Come on.
I can't believe I didn't think of it.
That's ‘cause you weren't
thinking like a pirate, matey.
Where does this chute come out?
The compost room.
The compost room?
I thought that chute smelled funny.
The only way out of here is up there.
-What's that sound?
-Uh-oh.
That's the compost grinder.
It makes anything that's too big, smaller.
I like myself the size I am.
How are we going to get up there?
Sometimes, you gotta work
with what you got.
I gotcha.
Thanks, matey.
To get to the Z-One,
we have to go through here.
Looks like we're swimming after all.
Yup. Come on.
Help!
Help! Help!
Oh no!
Gotcha.
Thanks!
What are we gonna do?
Octonauts video training series,
lesson nine.
Dealing with disasters.
First up, whirlpools.
Whirlpools can really take you for a spin.
What you need to remember is…
Next, all about algae blooms.
Too much algae
can make for a really slimy situation…
And finally, lava rescues.
Lava rescues.
When dealing with lava, first construct
a barrier, if you can, to stop the flow.
Barrier.
Then, search the area for creatures
or plants that might be in danger.
Remember,
they may be frightened and confused,
so they'll be looking to you
for leadership and courage.
Leadership and courage!
Vegimals, let's do this!
Okay.
I got it!
Vegimals, build a barrier.
Protect the crop.
Faster!
Okay, Vegimals, now pick up the seaweed.
Help!
Easy now. I’m coming.
Out you go.
Faster!
Vegimals…
Barrot! Kelpa! Kelpa!
Everybody, hold on.
Hey, what about me?
Yeah, and me!
You gotta save us!
Hang on!
Save us!
Oh man, that was a close one.
Now, what's for lunch?
Lunch? Is that all you ever think about?
That one almost got us.
Captain, we're arriving
at the chinstrap penguins’ island.
Or should I say their volcano?
Thanks, Professor. Surfacing now.
Volcano straight ahead.
Getting onto that island won't be easy.
We'll have to get past
all those big, jagged rocks.
And that's just the first problem.
We'll still have to find
a way to get all the penguins…
And their eggs.
…and their eggs off the volcano
and into the Octopod.
There's no way
they'll all fit into our Z-GUPs.
What about the life rafts?
We've got plenty of those.
There won't be time
to launch enough rafts,
but if we launch them all at once…
If we connect all the rafts together,
we could make an evacuation slide.
Captain, that's brilliant.
Peso, prepare to launch the Z-GUPs.
Aye, aye, Captain.
Professor, gather up
as many life rafts as you can find.
You're in charge of the Octopod.
Me?
In charge of the Octopod?
Careful, Peso. The waves
are slamming us into those rocks.
Steady.
We'll have to find
another way onto the island.
Hello!
Captain, look!
This way.
There's only one way onto that island.
The penguin way!
Follow me!
The penguin way.
I'll have to remember that one.
Peso!
Hello, there.
Good to see you too.
Oh my, you've grown tall.
Captain, these are my cousins,
the chinstrap penguins.
Yes, pleased to meet you.
I wish there was time to chat,
but you're all in very great danger.
-Oh no!
-I knew it.
I knew something was wrong.
These volcanic cracks
usually keep our eggs nice and warm.
But lately they've been too warm.
Our poor little eggs were almost cooked.
That's because
this volcano is about to erupt.
Erupt?
Don't worry. We're going to get you…
And your eggs.
…and your eggs
off this island safe and sound.
But where are we going to go?
Barnacles to Inkling.
We're ready to begin the evacuation.
Oh dear.
Professor?
Octopod standing by.
Launch the rafts.
Yes, Captain.
It'll just be one moment.
Professor, we don't have much time.
The volcano could erupt at any moment.
Yes, of course, Captain. Just need
to raise the ship up a bit first.
There.
Now to launch the rafts.
Why must there be so many buttons?
Let's try this one.
Goodness.
Oh, which button?
That one? No.
Lesson 23: Computer systems made easy.
That's not it either.
The Octopod systems may seem complicated,
but they're actually quite simple.
Just ask Dashi.
Ask me what, Captain?
Oh, sorry. I'm so used to being
on the other side of the camera.
Should I talk about the computers or…
Professor! The rafts. Are they ready?
Almost, Captain.
If only Dashi were here.
She always knows what button to press,
and she always stays so calm.
Calm. Just stay calm like Dashi.
Professor, launch the rafts now!
Already on it, Captain.
Good work, Professor.
We have to hurry.
Everyone onto the slide.
Good job.
Everyone keep moving.
Single file. Mothers and babies first.
You're doing great.
My egg!
Oh no, it's going over the edge!
Oh no!
Gotcha.
Oh, bravo!
Uh-oh.
You've got a crack.
Let's get you bandaged up.
There.
Here you are.
Thank you, Peso.
Well done, Peso.
Professor, retract the slide.
Now, let's…
Run!
Jump!
Are all eggs accounted for?
They're all tucked in
to their heated beds, nice and cozy.
Your egg will be fine if it stays warm.
Thank you. I don't know what we
would've done without your help.
We made it out of there just in time,
but there are still volcanoes erupting
all around the Ring of Fire.
I just hope everyone else is okay.
Hit it, Dashi.
This isn't working.
We're not gonna make it
back to the water in time.
And not to keep going on
about my problems,
but my skin's getting really dry.
Really, really dry.
How about some coconut water?
That's much better.
That's them, Dad. The ones who helped me.
Hello, down there.
You're Kwazii's mates, aren't ya?
Yes, but who are--
We're the coconut crabs.
I'm Claude, this is Claudette,
and there are our little ones,
Clem, Clyde, and Clarence.
But our friends all call us…
The Claw!
You helped my little Clarence,
and now we'd like to help you.
Times like this,
we've all got to help each other.
Everybody ready?
Ready!
Crack those coconuts!
Keep it coming, please.
We've got to keep moving.
Lesson 77. Emergency engineering.
When it comes to engineering on the fly,
Tweak has a saying.
Oh, right.
Sometimes you just gotta work
with what you got.
Coconuts.
Dashi, I don't think
now is a good time for a snack.
How are we going to move the whale?
Maybe these coconuts can help us.
It's like Tweak says, "Sometimes you gotta
work with what you've got."
And right now, we've got coconuts.
But how--
That's it.
If we put coconuts under the whale…
We can use them as rollers
to tow you to the water.
I have to say, I really like that plan.
Me too.
Let us lend you a claw.
Here comes the lava!
Oh no!
Here we go!
It's working!
That kind of tickles.
Thanks, coconut crabs!
Shellington?
I'm sure you must've already noticed,
but I'm running out of coconut rollers.
No problem!
Keep going, Shellington!
I don't know how much longer
I can keep this up.
Shellington…
Catch!
Claude? You should be
back with your family.
Oh, don't you worry about me.
After all, times like this,
we've all got to lend a helping claw.
We're almost there.
We're here!
Prepare to dive.
But what about Claude?
Coconut crabs can't swim.
Excuse me, but maybe I can help with that.
Like you said, "We've all gotta
help each other," right?
Hop on to my tail.
Righty-ho.
Where's your family?
Up there in those trees, where it's safe.
Well, then, if you don't mind,
prepare to fly.
Fly? But coconut crabs can't fly.
Thanks, mates!
Goodbye, coconut crabs.
Thanks for all your--
Shellington, climb on!
We made it.
And just in time too.
Guys, I really hate
to ruin the celebration, but look!
Every volcano's erupting at once.
Jumping jellyfish! It's a chain reaction.
I still stink of that compost room.
We almost there, Tweak?
The main air shaft's
at the end of this hallway,
and if we can get to it, we can get up
to the top level and escape in the Z-One.
You make it sound so easy.
No way through.
Think we can swim under it?
Only one way to find out.
I'll go through first with this rope.
When I give it a tug, that means it's safe
for you to follow me through.
Got it.
Here I go.
See you on the other side, matey.
Made it!
Tweak! I found a way through.
Tweak?
Can you hear me, matey?
Oh no!
What in the seven seas?
Hey, Kwazii.
Look what I found.
I found you this air tank too.
Thanks, Tweak.
You really saved my whiskers.
Things look pretty bad up ahead,
but I can bash through
with this Octo-mech suit.
Now you're talking, matey.
Follow me.
Yeah!
Take that!
And that!
Look! There's the door to the air shaft!
This shaft will take us
back up to the Z-One.
And how will we get up there?
With a good, old-fashioned grappling hook.
I gotta get me one of those.
Going up.
We made it.
And there's the Z-One.
Tweak to Octopod.
Come in, Octopod.
Communication network's down.
Can you fix it?
We gotta let the others know we're okay.
There might be a way
to reboot it from here.
Anything I can do to help?
Well, actually, yeah.
See that emergency supply kit over there?
What do you need?
A wrench? A screwdriver?
Actually, I was hoping
for an emergency carrot.
Sure thing, matey.
Not bad.
There!
Welcome back to a very special installment
of the Octonauts video training series,
lesson 352: A field guide to fish burps.
Everyone knows
the sound of a sardine burp,
but many other species of fish
are known to burp as well.
Let's listen to a few of them.
Not another training video.
Hang on, let me try that again.
Okay, systems rebooting.
This ought to get their attention.
Shall we?
Sound the Octo Alert!
Tweak, Kwazii? Is that you?
Yep. Got the whole crew here.
Dashi and Shellington reporting in.
Hello.
Octonauts! It's good to see you all again.
Is everyone okay?
We're fine, Cap,
but what's going on out there?
And where'd all them penguins come from?
It's a long story,
which involves a massive chain
of eruptions all around the Ring of Fire.
The Ring of Fire!
So that's what caused the tsunami wave.
And the tremors.
And the lava.
It's caused major problems
all over the Pacific Ocean.
And it's not over yet.
Most of the eruptions are dying down,
but there's still one more on the way,
and it's going to be big!
I'm seeing it here too.
Looks like a big old undersea volcano
off the coast of Japan.
The biggest I've ever seen!
Jumping jellyfish.
That volcano must be home
to all kinds of sea creatures.
We have to rescue them before it erupts.
Aye! But how are we all
going to get there in time?
It'll take days to fix the repair station
and dig out all the GUPs.
And the Z-GUPs
aren't exactly the speediest.
Well, there is still one GUP we can use.
Is there?
Everybody, hop in your Z-GUPs now.
Goodbye!
Z-helmets on.
Y'all remember that Z button
I told you not to press?
Yes?
Yes, indeed.
I sure hope this works.
Okay, y'all, press it!
Hey!
It's actually working!
Yow!
Tweak, the hatch is still closed.
Yup. It's jammed.
Jammed?
Don't get your whiskers in a twist.
I got a plan.
Yow!
Now that's thinking like a pirate.
We made it.
Incredible.
Hi, guys.
That was cool.
Yeah.
It's not over yet. Tweak?
Okay, everyone,
prepare for transformation.
Transformation?
In five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
Transformation complete.
Octonauts, welcome aboard the Mega GUP-Z!
-Shiver me whiskers.
-Oh wow!
Very impressive.
Tweak, it's amazing.
It should have everything we need
to deal with that last volcano.
Looks like you modeled it
after the vent shrimp.
They can withstand
the hottest temperatures on Earth.
Good eye, Shellington.
Like a vent shrimp,
the Mega GUP-Z is heatproof,
and it's perfect
for scooping up sea critters.
Impressive, Tweak.
Thanks, Cap!
Ready to take the driver's seat?
-Ready.
-Activating Z-Seat swap.
Wait a minute, how--
It's gonna take all of us
working together to operate it.
Everyone ready?
Ready!
Here we go!
Next stop, the volcano.
Jumping jellyfish.
That's the biggest volcano I've ever seen.
And it's completely covered
with sea creatures.
Dashi, how much time
do we have before it erupts?
Not long, Captain.
The lava's building up inside the volcano,
and when it reaches the top…
Kaboom.
Then we've got to get all the creatures
away from here before that happens.
Attention, sea creatures!
This volcano is about to erupt.
Erupt?
Oh no!
If you can swim away,
you should do so immediately.
We're out of here!
Wait for me.
You don't have to tell us twice.
Everyone else, sit tight.
The Octonauts are coming to the rescue.
Activating suction claw.
Snails straight ahead.
Help us!
Hello!
Don’t worry!
Got you.
Oh no!
Over there, a spider crab!
Got you!
Thanks.
Cap, look.
Help!
Sea urchins above you, Peso!
Save us!
Help!
What was that?
The rocks are sealing us in.
We need to get out of here!
I can't see!
Activating extra bright lights.
An opening straight ahead.
We made it!
Scans show the volcano is
clear of creatures, Captain.
Well done, Octonauts.
Captain, we've got to clear out
of here ourselves.
The volcano is about to erupt.
Octonauts, prepare to--
Captain, wait!
Peso, what is it?
I just saw something down there,
inside the volcano!
Inside? Are you sure?
Yes, Captain.
All right. Here we go.
Flappity flippers!
-Yeah!
-Oh me, oh my!
Creatures living inside a volcano.
Fascinating.
They're just swimming around in there
without a care in the world.
Attention, creatures!
You must leave the volcano right away.
What? Leave the volcano?
Why would we do a thing like that?
Yes. We like it in here.
Though it is
feeling warmer than usual today.
Yeah, and shakier.
That's because the volcano's about to--
Explode!
Captain, the eruption is starting.
These chaps were right.
Let's skedaddle!
Hot!
We're trapped!
We've got to rescue them!
Can't get through.
What do we do?
Cap, cover my controls!
Tweak, what are you…
There's one more thing
the Mega GUP-Z can do,
and it just might help us.
Trouble is, I've never tested it.
Never even made a button for it.
Gotta turn it on another way.
Oh dear!
Whatever it is, we need it now!
Get ready, Cap!
Tweak, hurry!
Hit that button!
Mantis shrimp mode, go!
Wow!
Mantis shrimp?
Those little mateys are tough!
Tweak, it's perfect!
I see you already got the hang
of the spear claw, Kwazii.
In mantis shrimp mode,
we can spear and hammer the rocks away.
Hammer claw, go!
Good one, Peso!
That's how we've got to do this,
as a team!
One little problem, Cap.
Mantis shrimp mode uses a ton of power.
When our power runs out,
the five Z-GUPs will all blast apart.
Then there's no time to lose.
Into the volcano.
It's getting really hot in here.
Sure is.
How about some super heat shields?
Thanks, Tweak.
I can barely see them, Captain.
Activating mantis shrimp vision.
There they are. Straight ahead.
Kwazii, incoming!
Got it!
And that!
Peso, behind you!
Got it.
The creatures are just
on the other side of this lava.
Activating mantis leap!
Get us out of here!
Help!
Don't worry. We're here to help.
Octonauts, let's do this.
-All clear.
-Thanks.
Thank you!
Over there, Cap!
We're coming!
Thank you!
I'm stuck!
Don't worry.
There you go!
-Thank you!
-Thanks, Mister!
Oh no!
Let's get out of here!
-Cap!
-Uh-oh!
Oh no! No!
The power warning!
We're running out of time.
Oh no! Help!
Oh no!
A family of sharks!
Hammer claw, go!
Tweak, status report.
Not much power left, Cap.
Dashi, any more creatures to rescue?
All clear, Captain.
We'd better… Hold on.
I’m picking up a few last creatures.
-Up there, on that rock.
-Help us!
They're going to fall into that lava.
Oh no, they're not!
Shellington! Mantis leap!
Aye, Captain!
Gotcha!
Uh-oh.
It feels like this whole place
is about to blow!
Octonauts, let's move out.
Oh no!
Captain, down there!
That was some ride!
Just a little further.
Cap, we're almost out
of mantis shrimp power!
We won't make it out
of the volcano in time.
What do we do with these creatures?
Yeah, what about us?
Shellington, what's that noise?
Is that…
Yes! The Omura's whale!
Excuse me. Maybe I can help.
Time's up.
We're blasting apart in ten, nine…
I mean… Hey! Toss them over here!
Hang on!
-Six, five…
-Gotcha!
…four,
three,
two,
one!
Well done, Octonauts.
We made it.
Tunip says,
"Welcome to your new home."
You'll be nice and safe here.
Wonderful.
Home, sweet home.
Hey. No lava. I like it.
I'll tell you what I'd like. Some dinner.
Dinner? You know what, pal?
That sounds pretty great. Come on.
There you go.
Thank you.
Thanks for all your help back there.
I really didn't do much.
Just returning the favor.
After all, in times like this…
We've all got to help each other!
Captain, good news.
What is it, Professor?
Have all the eruptions stopped?
Oh, well, yes, actually they have.
The Ring of Fire is returning to normal.
But that's not what I was calling about.
The chinstrap penguin eggs.
They're hatching.
Captain, we can't miss this.
But how will we get there in time?
And all the Z-GUPs are out of power.
Don't worry, Dashi.
The Octopod is heading to you.
Right. Now we just need to…
Yes!
Oh dear!
Oh my.
They're so cute.
Just one egg left.
It looks like that little eggy
took a real beating.
I just hope my chick is okay.
Oh dear.
My baby!
Hooray!
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
But where are all these penguins
going to live now?
After all, their island
was destroyed, right?
I think the Ring of Fire
might provide us with a solution.
Volcanic eruptions can destroy things,
but they can also create things.
Even new islands.
All right!
Wow!
Tunip, this island's perfect
for the chinstrap penguins.
But it's not on any of our maps.
How did you know it was here?
Follow me.
Bye!
Bye-bye!
Wow.
This is where the seaweed farm used to be.
The volcano created a whole new island.
We name it "Vegitoa."
Yes. The Vegimals named it "Vegitoa."
Vegitoa!
Let's do this!
Come on, Octonauts.
Now that we're all back together again,
it looks like we've got
some seaweed to plant.
You know, Cap,
even though we were apart today,
it still felt like we were
all working as a team.
It did, didn't it?
Yeah. It was almost like you were
right there with us, Captain.
But there's just one thing.
Well, what's that?
You really, really need to update
those training videos.
Welcome to the Octonauts
video training series, lesson 43:
Octo-aerobics.
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four!