Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
If you make smart,
strategic choices
you can maximize your efficiency
every single day.
If you save 10 minutes a day,
that adds up to 41 hours a year.
We're implementing
Nicky's strategic plan
and you'll all be receiving
a little extra gift
in your paychecks.
Christmas bonuses.
Congratulations.
And you'll notice that we
finished 10 minutes early.
Thank you all
for your attention.
Happy Holidays.
Excellent presentation, Nicky.
Thank you so much.
Oh, I'm so glad.
You know I could've spent more
time on goal setting, but...
No, it was perfect.
What's your availability
like in January?
I'd like to bring you back.
I'm free.
You're going to be busy.
That's me!
I can't wait to see you.
I know, I'm so excited.
Oh, hey!
Hi Nicky.
Anthony, is that you?
How tall are you now?
Five six and a half?
Your mom told me that
you made the JB team.
Yup. Youngest on the team.
Yeah. He eats all the time.
Oh, get the pie out.
Please?
Hey, so we're on for Friday,
right?
Yes. Uh, we will meet
at the flower shop.
I will order some lunch.
Can't wait to see you.
I love you.
Love you, bye!
Bye.
I'm serious, you're going
to spoil your dinner.
I'm making pork chops.
We're just going to grab
a pizza.
Oh.
Jeremy's taking me and Chad
to work on free throws.
I thought I mentioned it.
Nope, but that's fine.
It's just fine.
That's Chad. I'll get it.
Okay.
-Hello beautiful.
-Hi.
Mwah.
-How was work?
-It was fine.
You're taking the guys
to the gym?
I thought you had to work late.
No, the presentation got
postponed just like I predicted.
Right.
Oh, it's my mom.
She probably wants
to tell us
what day she's coming
for Christmas.
Well, I'd really like
to know that
so I have time to mentally
prepare.
She'll leave a voicemail.
Really not going to help me
that much.
-Hey Anthony, you ready buddy?
-Yup!
Oh, I'm going to show these kids
how it's done.
-I'll see you tomorrow, babe.
-Yeah, bye.
I hate this kitchen.
-Thank you so much.
-Happy Thanksgiving.
Hi! Mom!
You're here.
Hey sweetheart.
It's so good to see you.
Hi Dad.
Hi honey.
Let's get inside.
It's cold.
-Here, let me get your bag.
-Okay, yeah. Absolutely.
Thank you so much, Dad.
Okay.
So, how was your trip?
Hey, hey, hey.
Come in here.
I got it.
It's a done deal.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
We can surprise her
at Christmas.
No way.
What did I miss?
Uh, nothing. Um, we were...
We were just talking about
how great the table looks.
Oh!
Yeah, that thing in the middle
is very cool.
It's fun, right?
-Yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Uh, I'm going to get the turkey.
Me too.
They're being helpful.
Nicky, why don't
you start first?
Oh, okay.
Well, I am grateful to be
spending Thanksgiving
with my two favorite people.
I am grateful that we were
both able to retire this year.
Yeah.
And embark on a whole new phase
in our lives.
Wherever that takes us.
Near or not so near.
Why do I get the sense
that you two are trying
to tell me something?
Honey, um...
Your mom and I have decided
to downsize.
We're selling the house.
We wanted to tell you
in person.
This is the house
that you grew up in
and well we weren't sure how
you were going to take the news.
I think it's terrific.
You do?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
I think it's great.
Good for you.
You know what?
You should travel to Europe.
You, you could take that trip
to Alaska
that you've always dreamed of,
that cruise.
You should do all the fun things
that you want to do
that you worked so hard for.
Thank you so much
for your support.
We thought that you might feel
like you're losing
a piece of your childhood.
What? No.
My home is wherever
you two are.
Aw.
But I have a great idea.
You know what?
You should go look at property
up in upstate New York.
I love it there,
it's so close.
It would be beautiful.
Woah, woah, woah, woah.
We're not leaving Marsden.
We love it here.
We just need something smaller.
Oh. Yeah.
Of course.
Okay. Well, uh, I'll help
you find a local realtor.
We hired one.
Simone's fiancé has a friend,
Derrick.
Wow. You two are further along
than I... than I thought.
Honey, if you really wanted
to help
maybe you could stay
a little longer.
We've got a lot to pack
and purge.
Of course, Mom. I would love
to help.
That's wonderful.
I'm so excited, you'll be here
for Christmas.
Christmas?
What? What, what are you
talking about?
No, no, no. I said I would
help, you know.
A couple days I would stay,
speed pack.
And then you two can come
see me on the 22nd.
Your mother and I thought
it might be nice
to have one last Christmas
in this house.
For old times' sake to go
and pick a tree
at Jensen's farm together
and decorate it.
Just like when you were little.
I would love that.
All right. To Christmases past.
And new beginnings.
-Cheers.
Oh no, Mom.
I was such a nerd.
I can't believe I kept
all my old textbooks.
You said you wanted to reread
them over the summer.
No wonder no one wanted
to hang out with me.
Come on over, we'll redo
our trig assignments.
Yeah.
Well, it's not like you had a
whole lot of time to socialize.
You were in math competitions
almost every weekend.
I mean... look.
Look how many you won.
Yeah. I...
Mom, why did you frame
my Valedictorian speech?
So, it wouldn't get ruined.
You thought I would want
to keep something
to remind me of literally
the worst day of my entire life?
So, a few people didn't connect
with your speech.
It came from your heart.
I loved it.
Mom, half the kids laughed
and the other half thought
I needed to be
under observation.
I think that's just because
they didn't expect you to sing.
Yeah, I wasn't expecting
that either.
No. That is when I learned
not to trust my instincts.
Oh! Look.
This is from when Simone
lived next door.
You two decided that you wanted
to dress exactly alike
that entire year,
so I just gave up
and started buying
two of everything.
Oh, honey, nobody remembers
that speech
and you were not an outcast
in high school.
Why did I even keep this book?
I tested out of...
What's that?
I don't know.
-Who's it from?
-I don't know.
Uh, it's not signed.
"Dear Nicky.
"I guess I'm too shy to tell you
this in person,
"so I figured an anonymous note
is the way to go.
"You're an amazing person,
I hope you know that.
"The time you complimented
my drawing
"and when you congratulated me
last week
"on winning against
Mountain Point
"it really put a smile
on my face.
"Hopefully this card
makes you smile.
"Merry Christmas".
And, and there's a phrase
written in it.
"With love's light wings
did I o'erperch these walls,
"for stony limits cannot
hold love out."
Hmm. What a beautiful sentiment.
Oh, oh honey.
No, it's, it's just that whoever
wrote this was right.
It's true I never smiled, ever.
I just don't know how
I missed it, you know?
I really needed to have
found this then,
to know that someone felt
this way about me back then.
Maybe you needed
to find it now.
Maybe.
Oh, my gosh,
you are here!
I have missed you so much!
Wait, let me see it.
Oh, yeah.
It's beautiful.
I can't wait to see you walk
down the aisle.
You are going to give a toast at
the reception this time, right?
What? No.
You don't need me to do that.
You have a Best Man for that.
How many speeches
do you need?
You are the Maid of Honor.
Besides, if you don't do it
it'll just be Jeremy's
gym buddies.
Please, please, please. Please?
Yes, of course.
Of course, I will.
If you want me to make a speech
I'm going to make a speech.
-I can do it.
-Yes, you can.
You have waited so long
to find someone like Jeremy,
and I want to do whatever I can
to help you make this wedding
the most perfect day ever.
Thank you.
Oh, love you.
I love you too.
Well?
I know. Look at this place, wow.
You have made it so fantastic.
There's so much more here
than there used to be.
I know, I'm on track to do twice
as much as I did last Christmas.
Wow, look at you.
I know.
Well, I want to help out
or whatever I can do.
Okay.
But I have something
to show you.
"With love's light wings
did I o'erperch these walls,
"for stony limits cannot
hold love out."
Whoever wrote this clearly
thought a lot of you.
I know.
That's what's so hard
to understand.
Why is that surprising?
You remember me in high school.
Mm-hmm.
I was the kid that wasn't
in the play, you know?
I'm always on the sidelines.
Everybody felt that way back
in high school, Nik.
And there she is.
-Hi.
Oh, it's so nice to see you.
Good to see you.
I thought you guys might be
getting hungry.
Yeah, we were.
And where's Anthony?
Uh, I told him I'd pick him up
at his buddy Chad's house
and pry the video game
controller out of his hand.
Thank you.
Of course, yes.
Uh, so I'll leave you two
to, to dish.
Okay.
And I'll have Anthony back
at 9:00.
Oh, 9:00?
I'm done at 6:00.
Maybe we could all have dinner.
Oh I... I'm sorry, babe.
I... You know, I told Anthony
I'd take him Christmas shopping
for your gift.
Oh.
But uh, we'll grab some food
at the mall.
I'll make sure he eats
real food.
Or, you know, at least
the most real food
you can get at the mall.
Ok. bye.
Okay. Well, I'll see you at home
then, I guess.
All right. Bye.
He's really leaning into
this parenting thing, huh?
Yeah. He is definitely
the father figure
I always wanted for Anthony.
I mean, he even spent every
weekend over the summer
teaching him how to rebuild
the engine of an old Mustang
Jeremy bought.
That's great, right?
Yeah, it is.
But between Jeremy and
basketball and his friends
I just, I don't see him
very much.
Aw.
I know.
Derrick, hi.
Welcome home, boys.
Oh man I... I can't believe
it's actually ours.
Well, guess what?
It's going to feel a whole lot
more real once we're inside.
These are for you.
Closing docs and insurance.
Great.
And I will let you do
the honors.
Oh.
Woah!
Or of course, Anthony.
After you.
Age before beauty, bud.
Two ovens?
Mom's going to love this place.
So, what now?
We list my condo.
But don't go public with it till
after the Christmas surprise.
You know I can keep a secret.
I do, yeah.
How about you, buddy?
Won't breathe a word.
Can I go pick out my room?
Yes.
Do you remember the look
on my dad's face
when he sipped that eggnog?
He was trying so hard
not to hurt our feelings.
We had no idea what tempering
eggs meant.
You still have the stockings
that we made for your hamsters?
Yeah.
I mean, come on, they're cute.
I couldn't let them go.
Of course not.
You couldn't let
this go either?
I know.
I... I just kept that in case
Anthony wanted it one day.
Does he ask about Ryan?
Uh, no.
The last time was, uh, right
after Jeremy proposed.
He wanted to know if Jeremy
would leave us
the same way his dad did.
What did you say?
It caught me so off-guard
I just said, "No, Jeremy's
in it to win it."
Well, he is.
Jeremy is such a good guy.
He was even in high school.
And you deserve that.
So, does Anthony.
Thanks.
Hey!
Hey, come and say hi
to Nicky.
-Hey bud!
-Hi Nicky.
Oh, look at you.
So good to see you.
Where are you off to
in such a hurry?
Snack.
Oh, uh yeah.
Well, go get it.
Help yourself.
And that right there is why I
will never be able to retire.
He eats all the time.
So, are you going to try
to find him?
Who?
The guy who wrote the mystery
card obviously.
Aren't you curious?
Of course, I'm curious.
But how am I supposed
to figure out who it is?
There were 250 people
in our graduating class.
Well, um, okay.
I think he was an athlete,
right?
Because he said that
you congratulated him
on the win against
Mountain Point.
Hmm. That's very good, Sherlock.
And it was a Christmas card, so
I mean, probably a winter sport.
Football.
Oh, my god.
Only you could go to high school
for four years
and not know that our
high school football team
never won against
Mountain Point.
But I bet you it was basketball.
Yeah.
And obviously he knew
about literature
because that last quote,
it was...
it could have been out of
a Jane Austen or something.
You know, I could look it up.
-Yes, yeah, okay.
-This is fun.
Yeah. This is fun.
Okay.
Um, "With love's white wings
did I o'erperch."
From Romeo and Juliet.
Oh!
Shakespeare's most famous story
about unrequited love.
That's telling.
Maybe it was Reggie.
Do you remember how cute
that boy was?
Reggie Green.
Oh, he was cute.
Or Treyton Vega.
Damian Wenzel.
Do you remember him?
He worked part-time
at that bakery and he...
he always gave you those um,
the free...
-Crullers!
They were very good crullers.
Hey. The good news is
that you have a whole month
to figure this out, right?
What?
Come on. What is it?
Well...
What?
What if I find him and...
and he forgot that he wrote it.
I mean, I just don't want to put
too much stock in this
in case it... it doesn't mean
anything, you know?
Hey Nick, you're more memorable
than you realize.
And nobody is going
to have forgotten
writing a card like that.
Even all those years ago.
It was Shakespeare.
Obviously, he really loved you.
Okay, okay.
We'll try to f find him.
-Okay.
Yeah.
Okay, here it is.
My favorite house.
I know, I know,
they usually have
way more lights up
at this time.
Usually they have it all done
by Thanksgiving.
They're incredible.
I just can't believe that
you dragged me out here
in the middle of the night
to look at a house
that isn't even for sale.
Shut up, a girl can dream.
Yes.
Yes, you can.
And you should dream.
Thank you.
But just don't turn
into a stalker okay?
I can't afford the bail.
Well, you know,
they could report me.
It'd be worth the jail time.
I'm serious, I love this place.
Remember when we were kids
and we used to play house?
This is exactly the type
of house I dreamt about.
I love it.
Okay.
Now, you have to take
me home,
because I think my parents
are going to start selling
my old math awards
for their retirement trip
around the world.
I love you so much.
They're not going far.
They're not going to go far,
yeah.
But we are right now,
let's go.
Let me get your stuff
out of the car.
-Okay, let's do it.
-Okay.
We're here.
We made it.
All right. We get...
-Woah, these are-
-Oh, oh! Let me help you.
These are bigger and heavier
than I had intended.
Okay.
No, they're perfect.
They're perfect and it's going
to look so great on the mantle.
-Thank you so much.
-You're welcome.
Perks of the trade, you know.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah. I got it.
I got it now.
-I love you.
-Love you too.
Mwah! Bye.
-Goodnight, drive safe.
-Goodnight.
-It's so nice to have you back.
-Oh, it's so nice to be back.
Oh, hey. Oh, thank goodness.
-Good timing too.
-Yeah.
Yeah, anything to make
this house have
a little holiday pizzazz
is great.
Sorry, um, who are you?
Oh, I'm the, I'm the realtor.
Yeah, the homeowners are
on the way back from dinner
but I've got a buyer swinging
by here in about 10 minutes,
so, this'll be really helpful.
You know, it's amazing.
I can't believe Simone sent this
to us so late.
She's amazing.
Oh, I gotta get rid of this.
This has got to go.
What are you doing?
Oh, I've just got to elevate
this room a little bit.
I mean, look at this painting.
Isn't it beautiful?
Oh, I love the snow on the trees
and the interplay of light,
I like how the, the flurries
descending.
It's almost like you can sense
the movement, huh?
Movement. Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Movement.
Um, yeah. It's like, whether,
you know,
whether it's Baroque or Rococo
or Luminicsm like this piece is.
Luminicsm.
Yeah.
Sure, yeah.
Tell me more.
Well, uh, it's uh, this is
a really good friend of mine.
He's extremely,
extremely talented.
Mm-hmm.
His name is Reggie Green.
I think his goal...
Reggie Green?
I went to school with him.
He's on my list.
Huh.
What do you, what do you mean
"list?"
Oh uh, nothing.
I didn't mean to say that.
Uh, you're...
We're home.
We brought cake.
Hey Derrick, I see you've met
our daughter.
Yeah. Sure did.
We'll make coffee
while you do the showing.
Okay.
Come on, honey.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
Okay.
-Thanks so much for coming by.
-Alright, thank you, Derrick.
-Okay, goodnight.
-Goodnight.
Well, that went very well.
I think they may make an offer.
Good.
There's a cup on the counter
if you want some coffee.
Holiday blend.
Do you take cream?
Yeah, no. It's very kind.
No, I'm, I'm uh, I'm fine I...
Oof, it's getting late.
I should get going.
But there is a condo I want
you guys to see, okay?
I talked to the owner.
They said we should swing by
Monday at noon.
How does that sound?
-Great.
-Yeah.
All right.
You're welcome to join us
if you'd like.
It's Nicky, right?
Yeah. Do I know you?
I, I saw your name all over
your awards in your room.
I'll take those down before
the next showing, I'm sorry.
No, it's, oh, it's fine.
Um, text you the address
for Monday, all right?
Thanks Derrick.
Right. Goodnight.
Have a good night.
-Okay.
-See you Monday.
Yep.
What a great guy, huh?
Bradley Duncan,
Damian Wenzel.
Hmm.
Um, should I just make
some more?
Because it doesn't look like
we'll have enough for the tree.
You know what this weekend is,
right?
The next Cavaliers game.
Oh! Yeah, Sunday night.
That's great. But you know
what else it is?
It is the first weekend
of the craft fair.
And you know what that means?
We get to have our famous
Christmas card photo taken.
What? No, you promised last year
I'd never have to do it again.
Oh, come on.
Everybody loves to
get a Christmas card
with you and Santa.
Okay, this was the first one.
Aww!
Look at his little
chubby cheeks.
Okay, see this?
Look at that.
You wouldn't let go
of Santa's beard
and everybody was laughing.
Oh, what a sweetheart.
Why don't I... why don't I bring
my camera over
and take a photo of you two guys
in front of the tree together?
Yes, that's a way better idea.
You know what? We can take
that picture
but for, you know, for
the Christmas card
I'd really like to stick
with our tradition.
Well he's 15, he's a...
a little old.
What if someone from school
sees him?
Exactly. It would take months
of therapy to get over that.
The tree is a perfect backdrop.
I vote for the tree.
You know, if you guys have
this handled,
I think I'm going to go make
some popcorn.
I'll talk to her.
I'm sorry for getting involved
in that.
I shouldn't have.
I want you to be involved,
I just don't like being
teamed up on.
But, you know, that's going
to happen, right?
I mean, if I take your side
then that's how Anthony's
going to feel.
And most of the time I'm going
to take your side.
You know, our picture
with Santa.
I know that it's silly
and it seems ridiculous
but it's always been
our Christmas tradition.
I know.
But he doesn't want to do it.
And since there are
so many things
that he doesn't want to do
that he has to do,
maybe you can let him
off the hook on this one.
You can't keep him
little forever.
Jeremy, I have three years
left with him.
Three years before he goes
off to college and,
and everything changes.
And it just doesn't need
to change yet.
I don't want it to change yet.
his 20th wedding anniversary
last month.
Pictures were all over
social media.
That doesn't mean he couldn't
have written the card.
He married his
high school sweetheart.
Oh, okay. Yeah, that does
rule him out.
But it means the search
continues.
No, I am getting carried away.
I don't think I should do
this anymore.
Let's talk about you.
All right.
Um, what are you going to get
Anthony for Christmas?
Well, I was going to get him
a guitar
but apparently he told Jeremy
that he wants to go to
snowboarding camp.
Well, that sounds fun though.
-Yeah.
Here we are.
Reggie's exhibit.
What? No.
I thought we just agreed that I
wasn't going to do this anymore.
No, we did not agree to that.
This isn't a good idea.
I think this is a great idea.
In fact, I think that he
probably wrote the card
because he's artistic.
Just let the conversation
flow naturally.
You're not 17-year-old Nicky.
You are successful,
well-adjusted
adult Nicky, right?
I feel like the first thing.
Oh, come on.
Thank you so much.
I'll have it delivered tomorrow.
Okay, take care.
Um, your favorite season
must be summer.
Well, I... I find the winter
scenes tend to sell
a little better during
the holidays.
Oh, that makes sense.
Yeah. Of course.
Yeah.
Uh, I really like the interplay
of light in this one.
Yeah, it's... it's subtle.
I'm surprised you picked up
on that. Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm a big fan of
the luminicsm style.
You know art?
A little.
What's your favorite period?
Um... a favorite?
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I mean,
if I had to pick a favorite
I guess it would be, it could be
the ro... coco. The ro-
-The Rococo.
-The Rococo style.
-Yeah.
-Yeah same. Yeah, it's great.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it is great.
I mean, what I love about it
is how it's so...
Artistic.
Yeah, it is. Yeah.
Excuse me. Hi.
I think that gentleman
over there
has been trying to get
your attention.
Yeah him.
-Okay, excuse me.
-Sure.
Psst.
What are you doing?
Trying to find
something in common with him.
He doesn't even know
who I am.
I don't even
know who you are either.
Just... just be
a normal person.
Just breathe in and out,
deep breath.
And out.
You're foxy.
Okay.
Oh, hey, um, you know
what I just realized?
I think we know each other.
That maybe we went to
high school together.
I'm Nicky Beaton.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah. You were valedictorian,
right?
Yeah. Yeah, I was.
It's nice to see you again.
How have you been?
I've been great, uh,
thank you.
Yeah.
I'm here just visiting my
parents for the holidays.
I live in New York now.
No way. I... I just spent three
years on the Upper West Side.
Really?
-Yeah, I loved it.
-I love it too, yeah. Excellent.
I'm at 86th and Broadway.
-Oh, so nice.
-Yeah.
I'm actually just about
to move to Paris.
That is the home of
the Rococo...coco coco.
-Right.
-Yeah.
It's famous.
Yeah. I've... I've just always
wanted to live there
and I figured why not
give it a shot
rather than wonder
"what if?"
Yeah.
Yeah, those what-if's
will kill you.
Yeah.
I, um, I wish that I had known
you were in New York.
Why, would you have
looked me up?
You didn't even remember me.
I didn't recognize you.
There's a big difference.
I remember, I remember
a lot of things about you
from high school.
We definitely had chemistry.
I thought so too. You know,
I really thought that-
It was the hardest class
that I've ever taken.
And I remember you got
straight A's.
That class was hard.
Mrs. Epp, she was so tough.
I was always...
I was always envious of
how easy that was for you.
I would study for hours
every night
and I could not get better
than a B.
You were envious of me?
Oh, yeah.
You're good at everything.
Weren't you on
the basketball team?
Yeah, until I blew my knee out
during the summer.
Oh.
Yeah, I didn't play at a single
varsity game after that, so.
Wait, you didn't play against
Mountain Point our junior year?
Uh, nope. Why?
No reason.
Wait, wait, wait!
Your mom.
Hi guys.
Hey.
You finish up, okay?
I'll help her.
Thanks, love you.
Good to see you.
Mwah.
You too.
Hey kiddo.
How was practice?
Good.
Nice.
Hey, do you think I could
go over to Chad's tonight?
Why don't you have him
come over here?
I could make you a big pot
of spaghetti
with the pink sauce you like.
I... I think he's looking after
his little sister
so, we have to study there.
Sure. Next time.
I'll go call him.
Okay.
Yeah, of course.
I will just...
Come on.
-Hi.
-Hey sweetie, how was it?
Oh, it was super fun.
It was really nice catching up
with Reggie
but he definitely did not
write the card.
So, I haven't made any progress
with that.
But I did find lots of fun stuff
at the craft fair.
Well, he may not have written
the note,
but whoever did is left-handed.
How do you know that?
I might have done a little
sleuthing online last night.
Here, let me show you.
Have you got the card?
Oh um, yes, of course.
Yeah, I have it right here.
See, people who are left-handed
cross their T's
from right to left,
not left to right.
So, it looks like this.
Wow, yeah. I can see
what you're saying.
That's great Mom,
thank you.
Jessica Fletcher has nothing
on your mom.
Yeah.
-Okay, so... well hey.
-Hi.
All right, so what do you
guys think?
Two bedrooms, two baths,
upgraded kitchen.
-I love it.
-Yeah.
Are you looking
at another house?
Derrick wanted us to look at one
more before we made our offer.
It does have everything
we want.
Yeah. I mean, it's my listing
but it's not officially on the
market till after Christmas, so.
You have photos?
I'd love to see it.
Oh, it's beautiful Mom.
I love it.
Isn't that Jeremy's place?
Uh-huh.
e news.
Uh-oh. What?
It's not bad news.
Well, when you have good news
you say you have "good news,"
when you have bad news,
you say you have "some news."
Well, Mom's coming on Thursday.
On the 23rd?
Okay, okay.
Well, it still gives me time
to prepare for her
and, you know, make sure
everything is just as
she likes it.
This coming Thursday.
What?!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Your brother has a party
on the 18th, remember?
Tasha's parents are flying in.
And you know how mom feels
about Tasha's mom.
Yeah.
Exactly how she feels
about me.
Not even close. She despises
Tasha's mom.
Mm-hmm.
Look, with the wedding coming up
I think it's a good opportunity
for her to spend some time
getting to know you
a little better.
Let her teach you how
to bake a ham.
I know how to bake a ham!
Well, pretend you don't.
It... that worked for Tasha!
Seriously?
Listen, I know that my mom
can be somewhat opinionated.
Uh-huh.
I want you to feel good about
your soon-to-be mother-in-law.
It will mean something to me.
So, covering a ham keeps it
from drying out?
That's fascinating!
But we may want to reign it
in, you know, just a little.
No. I just want to see it.
She's been my best friend
since I was five years old.
I know, I know. And that's
precisely why
I don't want to show you
the house, okay?
Oh, you can trust me.
I promise you I'm not going
to say anything to Simone.
Besides, Christmas spirit.
Please help this man see sense.
Okay, fine.
Yeah, you can't argue
with the Christmas spirit.
Yeah, well...
Are you driving?
Uh, it's kind of my car.
Fantastic.
Are you serious?
This is it?
Simone loves this house.
I know. I know she does.
And Jeremy says
they always drive by
every time they're
in the neighborhood.
Yeah.
I figured, you know,
why don't we find out
if the owners want to sell,
so I put a note on the door.
And it was just that easy?
Well, I wouldn't say
it was that easy.
First time they called me
they said that they
weren't interested.
But then after that snowstorm
we had in October
they called me again
and they said,
"You know, we've had
a change of heart.
"I think we're going
to move to Phoenix."
So, I said "Okay, well I'll show
you some listings."
And I negotiated the sale.
Wow, you're really good at this.
I don't know about that.
I think there might be
someone here.
Well, I hope it's Jeremy.
Hey man. How's it going?
Hey, hey, listen.
Are you at the new house?
No, no.
Because we just heard,
uh, a noise inside.
I hired a plumber
but he's not going to be there
until next week.
-Well...
-Okay hey, hang tight, okay?
I'll be there in five minutes.
All right buddy, thanks.
Hey hon.
Uh, what are you doing?
Um, uh...
Anthony, Anthony
forgot something
and he needs me to bring it
to him.
Really? Why didn't he call me?
Because the thing he needs
is in my truck,
and so, I'm just going
to run it over to him.
I'll get my coat, and on the way
back we can go to Damian's.
I really like those
hot chocolate cupcakes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
You, you...
Tell you what, okay?
You stay here, okay?
And I'll get the muffins
and a latte,
and I'll... I'll be back soon.
Oh, there's definitely someone
in there.
-Yeah, come on.
-What?
-Let's take a look.
-Don't you think it's dangerous?
This is Marsden Ohio Nicky,
not New York.
-I'm sure we're fine.
-Okay.
No, no, no, but maybe we
don't want...
Shhh!
Anthony!
Hi. Can you help?
This is kinda heavy.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Oh.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
I wanted there to be a tree
in the new house
when we surprised mom.
The guy said it should just
screw into the stand
but it keeps falling over.
Wait, you brought this tree
in yourself?
One of the seniors on my team
has a car.
But there's still two weeks
till Christmas
so, I hope it doesn't die.
Anthony trust me,
it'll be just fine.
Does anyone know
you're here?
They think I'm at a friend's.
Anthony!
What? How else could I keep
it a surprise?
Well, Jeremy's on his way.
You called him?
Of course, I called him.
Come on.
Wait, what are you two
doing here?
Oh, I asked Derrick to bring me.
I want to check out
your new house.
You weren't supposed
to say anything.
I know. I know.
Come on, we had a pact.
Buddy, I'm sorry,
but I just- it slipped.
I'm not going to ruin it,
I promise.
All right.
I really like your tree.
Your mom's going to love it.
You brought in all
these decorations.
I don't know, I...
I don't think I have enough.
Hmm, really?
Maybe I can help you
with that.
Derrick, these candles are real.
Yeah, they lived a lot
more dangerously
in the Victorian age.
How do you know
about this place?
Well, this store's been here
for about six years.
Yeah, Genevieve the owner,
started it in Connecticut,
and when she moved here
she brought it with her so.
I actually hire her sometimes
to stage the homes I'm selling.
This is a mid-century modern.
Wow.
That over there would be
Pennsylvania Dutch.
Oh, here we go. This is what
we want right here.
Oh.
Look, bubble lights.
Yeah.
These were popular in the '40s
when they were introduced
all the way up into the '80s.
You know what?
Tell me what you think.
I thought this might be
kind of cool
to decorate Simone's new home
the way she was
when she was a kid.
What do you think?
-She'll love that.
-Yeah.
It's a great idea.
It's a bit like going back
in time, right?
Yeah, it really is.
How do you know all this stuff
about time periods
and Christmas?
I mean, it's not like that's
a course they teach
in real estate school, right?
Uh yeah. No, no.
Actually, my... my ex-wife
was an interior designer
so, I learned it from her.
I, uh, didn't know you were
divorced, I'm sorry.
No, no, no, don't be sorry.
It's for the best.
Six years ago,
we both realized
we were not as compatible
as we thought.
Right.
Um, do you want a coffee?
-Sure, yeah.
-Yeah.
-Two.
-Thank you.
Why do we do that?
Fall for the person
that's totally wrong for us?
I don't know, it's um...
For me personally,
Jess and I just... we just
weren't friends, you know?
I really believe that you can't
love someone
if you can't ask yourself you
like them in the first place.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's really perceptive.
Yeah. Well, I had a lot of time
to think about it, so.
So, um, well what about you?
I mean, married, divorced?
It's complicated?
Single, single and single.
Oh.
You know, I guess I'm just
working on myself
so, I can be the right partner
for someone else.
Mm.
That sounds like a little bit
of an excuse.
It actually sounds like
that parable of that writer.
What do you mean?
Well, she's the perfect author
who never sends out
her manuscript.
And as long as she keeps
working on it
she'll never have to feel
any rejection.
I send out my manuscript.
Sometimes it just gets lost
in the mail.
Oh, yeah.
But you said you don't.
You said you don't,
you're not confident
you'd be a good partner.
No, no. You're just twisting
my words.
I think you might be a little
afraid of rejection.
Ah.
I'll just uh, yeah.
Can you believe that he actually
said that to me?
Like I'm afraid of rejection?
Please.
Well, you kind of are though,
right?
What?
I'm not saying that you don't
take risks because obviously
starting up your own consulting
business was a huge risk.
But, I think, Derrick's right,
when it comes to
your personal life,
if you think that somebody's
going to reject you,
you back away.
I love you and you know me
better than anyone,
but I think you are
way off base here.
All right. Well then, come
to the Christmas party
with Jeremy and me
on Wednesday.
Okay fine. I would love to.
Thank you.
Fine.
My last few hours of freedom
before Jeremy's mom gets here.
Oh.
Hey. Maybe some of those guys on
the list will be at that party
and I can finally figure out who
wrote me that Christmas card.
That's a great idea.
All right. It's at Yvette
Tipton's house.
Yvette Tipton?
The cheerleader?
That was 20 years ago.
She owns a hair salon now.
Well...
People move on Nik, right?
They've had some bumps
in their lives too.
Right. Of course.
Good.
Okay.
But you're going to have
to pick me up
because my parents have
the car that night.
Sure.
Do you have a curfew?
Really lovely, yeah.
Yeah, beautiful.
-And here we are ladies.
-Oh hi.
-Christmas cranberry coolers.
-Lovely.
I hope they're made correctly.
You know, it's been a while
since I was a bartender.
I'm sure they're great.
Thank you.
All right.
Cheers.
Yes. To the search.
Mmm.
Ooh, these are very good.
Yeah.
Oh, there's Derrick.
You could talk to him.
No? Okay.
Hey wait.
Is that Treyton?
Which one was he again?
Remember, the really cute one.
He could've written the card.
Yeah. Yeah, he could've.
-I'm going to ask.
-Do it.
-Okay.
-You got this.
-Okay, okay.
-Okay.
-I'm doing it. It's happening.
Nicky Beaton?
Hi.
Merry Christmas.
You look fantastic.
You haven't changed a bit.
Well, I don't know about that.
I've definitely changed
a little.
But you look exactly the same,
Treyton.
Well thanks.
I do my best.
How long has it been?
Last time I saw you
was at graduation.
That's probably right.
Yeah, yeah. I remember
the speech you gave.
I remember it too.
The one where you sang a song
about following your dreams
and discovering who you
truly are.
Yeah. Yvette.
Oh, I felt so bad when everyone
started laughing at your song.
I didn't laugh.
It was inspiring.
But it was no surprise
you'd come up with something
like that.
Thank you.
Oh, well, I... I didn't mean
that everyone laughed.
I mean, besides... I could never
even give a speech
in front of that many people,
so.
Well, at least it was memorable,
right?
Yes, it was.
Feel free to help yourselves
to the hors d'oeuvres.
We have vegan, vegetarian
and fruititarian options.
Oh, great.
And I should circulate.
Okay.
Thank you for saying that.
That was really,
really nice of you.
I meant every word.
Treyton, can I ask you
a really weird question?
If you don't mind
a weird answer.
I don't mind.
It's about a Christmas card.
That is it. No more work calls,
phone is off.
This is Nicky, a friend
from high school.
Nicky, this is my fiancé,
Richard.
Hey, nice to meet you.
It's really nice to meet you.
Hi.
Nicky was just inquiring
about a Christmas card?
Yeah, yeah.
Um, I was just... I was going
to ask if you had written me
this romantic Christmas card
in high school.
Not unless your name
was Jeffrey.
Okay. Well, do you mind if I,
um, show it to you?
Maybe you would recognize
the handwriting.
It's definitely someone we went
to school with.
No.
But listen, I'm not surprised
someone would write you
something like that.
You're always complimenting
people and lifting them up.
Thank you.
Wow.
Well...
-Merry Christmas.
To you both, and congratulations
to you both.
-Thank you.
Okay.
-Okay. This is not going well.
-Talk to me.
-Definitely not.
-All right.
He was really sweet-
So, look who I found.
Hey.
Hi. Derrick.
-Hi.
Simone, Andrea's here.
Oh, right.
I have to talk to her
about the flower order.
-Really?
-Yep.
Okay.
-Okay. We'll see you in a bit.
-Bye.
Uh, listen Nicky,
I hope I didn't offend you
with what I said about you
not sending your manuscript out
I just that conversation...
No. No, not at all actually.
You gave me something
to think about and...
and I appreciate that.
You're right. I do need to
put myself out there more.
-So, thank you.
-You're welcome.
I mean, look at you, you're
here, you're at this party.
-Exactly.
-Yeah.
Manuscript published.
Manuscript published,
that's good.
Did you see the hors d'oeuvres?
-Woah.
-A little like, scary.
-Yeah.
Slightly.
It's like everybody
that knows Yvette
is either on a starvation diet
or they're allergic to food
that actually tastes good.
I think it might be both.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Listen, you want to um,
you want to bail
and go have ourselves some,
some real Christmas fare?
I'd like that.
I'm actually starving.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
Me too. Who knew?
Mexican?
Well, you know, nothing says
Christmas like a great tamale
in my opinion.
Well, thank you for leaving
to bring me here.
It was my pleasure.
You know, I overheard Yvette
say something
about a graduation speech?
Yeah.
Well, as you probably gathered
it was a disaster.
You sang?
-Derrick.
-Hi.
I have your table ready.
Thank you very much.
Is there no one in this town
that you don't know?
Well, I found her a terrific
little bungalow
down on Riverside.
You stop trying to change
the subject.
Fine.
I didn't start singing,
you know,
it was just a traditional speech
about closing one chapter
and opening another one.
And I had written this song
which is weird because I can't
even read music.
And in a complete lapse
in judgment
I, I just decided to sing it.
Just like that, like right there
in the moment.
Yeah.
Off the cuff and acapella.
Okay. Wow.
See, in my mind, it was going
to be really touching
and it was going to bring
people to tears.
But, in reality, it brought
people to, you know,
tears of laughter after
a very awkward silence.
Okay. So... so what did you do?
I stopped singing.
Uh-huh.
And then I just rushed
off stage.
Ouch.
-Yeah.
In high school nobody knew
who I was.
Right.
Unless you went to like,
a math competition.
And when they asked me
to do the graduation speech
I just thought this was
my chance.
Mm-hmm.
You know, for my classmates
to really know me.
Right.
I put all this pressure on
myself to make it really good
and it just wasn't.
You know? It wasn't that good.
And about halfway through it,
it came to me that I could,
that I could sing that song.
And I did.
And I humiliated myself.
Well... I will tell you that
on the humiliation scale
I'll give you a nine,
nine-and-a-half.
-Well, thank you.
-You're welcome.
But I got a solid 10.
-What?
-Yeah.
All right, let's hear it.
What do you mean,
like right now?
Yes.
I just poured my heart out
to you.
I just gotta make sure no one
was in my high school here.
Okay. Alright.
Here it goes.
Um, when I was in high school
I was on the debate team,
right?
So, one night before
this big debate
I decide I'm going to go home,
I'm going to stay up all night,
I'm going to study,
I'm going to be super prepared
and obviously very tired.
Mm-hmm.
The next day when I got
to the debate,
Nicky, I was so exhausted.
I fell asleep.
And you snored?
Uh, no. Worse.
Yeah, way worse.
I had a dream about my mom.
And in my dream
while I was sleeping,
I said "I love you too, Mom."
The whole auditorium
heard me say it. Everyone.
Yeah, boom.
The next day I walk down
the hallway
and everybody's looking at me
going "I love you son!"
I mean, it was brutal.
It was like...
I was like "Oh my.
This is the worst."
No, that is
the worst, that is actually.
I was just hiding
in the back...
-Hey!
-What is this?
This is pozole.
Wow.
When I was growing up in Mexico
this is what we would have
after coming home
from caroling on Nochebuena,
Christmas Eve.
Oh.
It's good for the voice
after singing.
Oh, perfect for Nicky.
Thank you, Elvira.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you so much.
Provecho. Thank you.
All right.
Well, after those two stories
I think I'll make a toast.
To being humiliated
in high school.
I'll drink to that.
Don't mind if I do.
Ah, ah, ah!
Hands off.
Not until Miriam has the first
one and then you get three max.
Ugh. So many rules.
Yeah. That's the way it is.
Now, Miriam lives
in a perfect house,
so, for the next two weeks
we are going to pretend
that's the way we live too.
Don't you want Miriam
to see the real us?
Hmm?
And don't call her that.
Not unless she says it's okay.
It's Mrs. Winters, huh?
Oh, that's her.
Here we go.
Miriam, hi.
Come on in.
Grandma M.
You must be Anthony.
Jeremy told me you're a pretty
decent point guard.
Maybe even better
than he is.
Hardly. He destroyed me
the other day on the court.
Don't worry, sweetheart.
He'll age out soon enough.
We are so happy that
you decided to come early.
I didn't have much of a choice.
Well, the roast
is almost finished
so why don't you make yourself
at home?
Oh, good.
You know, you have to cook it
right or it gets tough.
Everything is delicious, honey.
It really is.
Thank you.
You wouldn't happen to have
a steak knife, would you?
Oh sure, Mom.
Anthony?
So, Mom realized in the car
that she forgot the gifts
that she was going to send
to Tasha and Jason.
I could just kick myself.
Well, I'm sure
they wouldn't mind
receiving them
after the holidays.
Actually, Mom wanted to buy
them something new to send,
so, I thought that maybe
you could take her
to the craft fair on Sunday.
Uh, you know, honey...
I would love to but Anthony's
game is on Sunday.
Well, you can't miss that.
Jeremy will take me.
No, I have to be there
to videotape it, remember?
Jeremy's making me
a highlight reel.
It's kind of a big deal.
You basically need one now
to get a scholarship.
Yeah, you do.
Sure.
Yeah, you two go to the game
on Sunday
and Miriam and I
can go shopping.
Great.
Good.
It really is.
Oh no, Dave. Don't pack
the red tablecloth.
We'll need it for Christmas.
Red tablecloth, check.
Mom, what's in this?
Those are the extra decorations
you said you wanted
to look through?
Oh.
If you don't want
to deal with it now
we can just ship it
to New York.
No. Actually, if you don't mind
I have someone I'd like
to donate these to.
Are you sure?
I have plenty of decorations
in my apartment in New York.
And really, I shouldn't be
holding on to a bunch of stuff
that I don't even have room for.
This is good quality.
Oh yes. Very, very good.
Very, very, very cute.
Perfect for Tasha.
Good.
I'd get you some,
but I don't get the sense
that you cook much.
Really? I cook all the time.
Oh.
Usually when I phone Jeremy
he says he can't talk
because you're going out to eat
and they won't hold
your reservation.
Oh, thanks Jeremy.
Thank you.
...Come and take a picture.
Is there any place
we can sit down here?
Oh, yes of course.
Just right over here.
Maybe we could get some hot
chocolate or something to eat.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.
-Glad you found a table.
-Mm-hmm.
I must say that these
cinnamon rolls look so nice.
I might have to steal a bite.
Oh, well, they certainly
are big enough for both of us.
Hmm.
Okay.
Mm. Ours were better.
Cinnamon rolls were a Christmas
staple at our house.
Really?
When Jeremy was little he and I
used to get up 5:00 AM
on Christmas Eve and bake,
oh, about four dozen.
And then we'd take
them around
to all our friends
and neighbors.
That was sweet of you.
Mm, I miss those days.
Yeah. Me too.
Anthony used to, he used to bake
with me when he was little.
Anthony's at that age now
where he wants to do everything
on his own.
Yeah. And that's okay.
You can't baby him forever.
Well, I like to think that
wanting to be
a part of my son's life
isn't babying him.
The worst thing a mother can do
is to hold on too tight.
You don't say.
It was all I could do
to remain civil.
I mean, who is she to tell me
that I'm hanging on too tight.
It's not like she's the most
amazing mother in the world.
Jeremy barely takes her calls
half the time.
Well, maybe that's why
she's saying it,
from experience, you know?
She knows that she was
hanging on too tight
and that that's why Jeremy
keeps his distance.
Yeah, but she's also overbearing
and she complains all the time.
Look it's not about her, right?
Yeah.
Maybe you have been holding on
too tight to Anthony lately.
Don't you think?
No, no I'm not.
I have three more years
with him.
Three, and then he's gone.
There is nothing wrong
with wanting to make
those years count.
Of course, there's not.
But you put so much pressure
on the time that you spend
with him.
Trying to force these memories
to happen
instead of just letting them
happen naturally.
Don't you think if you
relaxed a little,
you and Anthony would have
more fun together?
But there is no together.
He doesn't want to spend time
with me.
He's always,
he's off with Jeremy
and they don't include me.
You know, for years
he needed me.
And now Jeremy comes
into the picture and he-
I just... I can't compete
with that.
You don't have to compete.
Listen to me,
your son loves you more than
anything in the world.
And Jeremy loves you
just as much.
So, maybe, you should think
about just taking a step back
and letting them create a bond
with each other.
You know I figured you
of all people
would understand
where I'm coming from.
I do.
I don't think so.
Simone.
Thank you so much.
Hello?
Oh wow! This looks great.
Hey Nicky.
You know what's funny?
Derrick was just talking
about you.
Oh?
Actually, I mentioned
your parents.
Yeah. I just got off a call
with the seller's realtor.
He accepted your parents' offer.
That's fantastic!
Oh wow!
Can we go tell them right now?
Of course. Absolutely.
Jeremy, you should tell her
about the party.
Oh yeah. Anthony thought it
might be fun to have some people
over here on Christmas Eve
when we surprise Simone.
She would love that.
That's a great idea.
Hey, you know,
maybe you can sing.
I so regret telling you
that story.
Okay.
We'll be back in 20 max,
all right?
-Okay. Come on.
-Okay, bye.
Bye. Have fun.
-Thank you. I appreciate this.
-No problem, are you kidding?
Does Derrick...
Does Derrick like Nicky?
What makes you say that?
Sometimes the way
he looks at her.
It's the same way
you look at Mom.
Well, you pick up on a lot
for a 15-year-old.
Hey. 15-and-a-half.
All right. 15-and-a-half.
Gotta be specific.
Look at that.
-Oh, yeah.
-That's great.
Doesn't that look good?
A couple of hard workers here.
Mom?
What are you doing here?
Oh, I figured I'd come see
your big surprise for Simone.
I heard you two on the phone.
Couple of spies you're not.
Well, what do you think?
It's pretty awesome, huh?
Oh, it's a beautiful home.
Although it looks like
you've lost a bulb up there.
Oh, yeah.
Sometimes it's easier
to see things
when you're not so close
to them.
Hmm.
I think it's really nice what
you're doing for Simone.
I'm sure she'll love it.
I hope so.
We spent a lot of time
getting it ready.
-Maybe too much time.
-What do you mean?
Well, you think she'd be
any less surprised
if you didn't take time to do
all these decorations?
Not really.
She might even like helping
you out.
Spending time working
on it together.
I don't know Simone that well,
but no one likes to be
left alone.
Especially during the holidays.
She's right.
We've been skipping out
on a lot to focus on this.
I guess, we should've thought
about that before.
Well, like I said, it's easier
to see something
when you're not so close to it.
Hmm.
I haven't been to a Christmas
concert in forever.
Well, you're going to see
something really special.
Ring out wild bells,
to the wild sky
The flying cloud,
the frosty light
The year is dying
in the night
Ring out wild bells,
and let him die
Ring out the old,
ring in the new
Ring, happy bells,
across the snow
The year is going,
let him go
Ring out the false,
ring in the true.
Woooo!
-Wow!
-Amazing, right?
Yes.
Amazing for an eight-year-old,
huh?
I bet you helped her parents
find a house.
Well, not yet, but
I'm working on it.
Mm-hmm.
No, no. Truth be told,
actually her mom and I
graduated from high school
together so...
Oh, yeah?
Where'd you go?
Lakeview.
Yeah, same as you.
Were you there when I...
No, no, no. I graduated
a year before you.
Oh. Right.
You're right-handed, right?
Yeah, yeah, I am.
Why?
No. I was just curious.
I've meant to...
Oh!
Oh no. I got it, hey.
That's ok, I got it.
No problem.
Uh, this is uh...
It's old.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, it's nothing.
It's just a Christmas card
someone gave me a long time ago.
And you, uh, you've been
carrying it all these years?
No, no.
Oh, my gosh.
No. Um, I mean, I have it now.
It just... it's that I found it
at my parents' house in an old
box and so I just...
I don't even know why I have it
with me really, to be honest.
It's just... It's that,
it's the thing.
Never mind. Anyway um,
I'm going to donate.
-Right.
-If you don't mind.
Oh, uh, listen.
Sorry, listen, I gotta
take this.
It could be about your
parents' house.
-Oh, yeah.
-Yeah great.
Hello? Derrick here.
Hey.
You're going to need
more icing than that.
Okay.
Here, let me do it.
You know what?
Thank you, Miriam. Thank you.
Hey honey. Are you going
to go to the gym
and practice basketball
with Jeremy?
Actually, I was wondering
if you wanted to go
to the Handmade Holiday Fair.
I haven't been and it's
the second last day.
I would love to, honey,
but Miriam and I have
to finish this up.
Oh, no, no, no. Please.
You two go.
I'm more than happy
to do this on my own.
Are you sure?
Positive.
I'll mix up another batch.
Okay. Thank you.
I know Christmas is only
a couple days away
and it's too late for
a Christmas card
but if you'd really like
a picture of me with Santa
we can do it.
Really?
What made you decide that?
You love that tradition.
I do. But I love you more.
I just want to spend time
with you.
We don't need
to include Santa.
Really?
Because I'd rather go look
at snowboards
and skip the whole craft fair.
Okay, snowboards it is.
And maybe grab lunch afterward,
just you and me?
Yes.
Honey, these are the things
that I'm going to miss
when you're gone someday.
Just 'cause I leave doesn't mean
I'm gone, Mom.
Aww, kiddo.
I just styled it, Mom.
But it's so pretty.
Ugh.
You never let me touch
your hair anymore.
-Santa's here.
-Hi.
Okay, okay.
Woah! Yeah!
Are these all for us?
-Yeah.
-Thanks.
Well, my mom and I went
shopping yesterday.
Aww.
And also, it's a bit of
a peace offering.
Our last conversation
was a little tense.
No, you were absolutely right
about Anthony and Jeremy
needing space. It's fine.
Yes, you were.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Yeah.
Um, Miriam and I
are playing trivia.
Want to come on in?
-Yes, I do.
-Okay.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to interrupt your game.
Perfect timing. I was
losing anyway.
Uh, Miriam, this is
my best friend, Nicky,
also the Maid of Honor.
Nicky, this is Jeremy's mom.
Oh, it's a pleasure to meet you,
Mrs. Winters.
Call me Miriam, please.
Here honey.
Sit down and play this Christmas
trivia game with us.
Oh.
Simone, we have to start over
now that we have a third.
That is convenient.
I'll just have to beat you both.
I need to find a game
she isn't good at.
Oh, I've tried.
-Yeah. Good luck with that.
-Yeah.
Nik, we have been discussing
how difficult it was
when Jeremy and Jason
went away to college.
Oh, I missed them both
like crazy.
Now Jason, he phones
every couple of days.
But Jeremy on the other hand,
if he doesn't
feel like talking
he just doesn't answer
his phone.
It's true.
At least I have
the pictures.
Oh, yeah.
Miriam says she has old photos
I haven't seen yet.
Photos from when Jeremy
was young?
-Yes.
-Mm-hmm.
You know, if they're
embarrassing
we could put them up on the wall
at the rehearsal dinner.
That would be great.
When I get home, I'll find
the box they're packed away in.
Perfect.
Mm. Speaking of things
packed away in boxes,
did you find out
who wrote that card?
Nothing yet.
Card?
It's just an old Christmas card.
No, it is an anonymous
love letter from high school.
Oh!
You have it, don't you?
Oh, Miriam you have to see it.
I just wasn't able...
It is so sweet and sincere.
He even quoted
Romeo and Juliet.
Let me see.
Oh.
What?
Nothing.
No, really, tell us.
Well, uh, it's just that...
I recognize the writing.
You do?
Whose is it?
It's Jeremy's.
Um...
wrote this?that Jerey
It can't be.
It is.
I spent weeks working with him
on his penmanship.
See how he makes his R's?
Never did get 'em right.
He does do his R's that way.
Oh, no. I'm sure lots of people
do their R's like that.
And he is left-handed.
My fiancé was in love
with my best friend. Great.
Okay. No, no, no, no, no.
We are not jumping to
conclusions here, okay?
What we're going to do is we're
going to ask Jeremy.
Ask him what?
What's going on?
Hi, um...
Did you write this?
Oh.
Oh, yeah, I did write this.
I'd forgot all about it.
No. No, no, no.
I mean, yes. Yes, I wrote
the card.
But I uh... someone gave me
this card,
and they, they gave me
a piece of paper
with what I was supposed to copy
down and asked me to do it.
Why in the world
would he do that?
Uh, because they had
terrible writing.
I mean, you would've needed
a degree in hieroglyphics
to decipher it.
So, uh, who was it?
I can't tell you that.
I... I promised I wouldn't.
Wha?
Oh, come on, honey.
Nicky's been trying to figure
this out for three weeks.
She really wants to know.
I mean, it's been 22 years.
Yeah, I know.
But, I uh, I made a promise
and I keep my promises.
See? That's the boy I raised.
Thank you, Mom.
I'll talk to him tonight.
Listen, I know that you said
you weren't going to tell Nicky,
but I am your fiancée. So...
I promised I wasn't going
to tell anyone.
She felt like an outsider
in high school.
It would be really nice
for her if she,
she knew that somebody
liked her.
It would just... it would mean
a lot to her, you know?
Yeah.
I think that Nicky should focus
less on the past
and more on the present.
What do you mean?
Well, Derrick seems to have
taken an interest.
Really? He's such a great guy.
I know.
But Nicky doesn't seem to be
picking up on the signals.
Oh, well. I'll just talk to her.
It'll be fine.
-No.
-Yeah.
No.
I know you love her,
but this is something they need
to figure out on their own.
But, you know,
the thing with her is
she just needs a little nudge,
like the tiniest little...
Ugh, fine. I will stay
out of it.
You're not any fun.
So.
So, how'd it go today?
Was Nicky here to run
interference?
No, actually.
Your mother and I are getting
along quite well.
I think I understand her
a little bit better now.
Yeah. Um, in fact,
I think that you could be
a little bit more attentive.
-Me?
-Mm-hmm.
I'm attentive.
Yes, of course.
But, you know, this week
I have spent more time with her
than you have.
Well, in my defense we didn't
expect her this early,
and I've been...
I've been busy.
Okay. Well, why don't you
take her calls?
I... I love talking to her.
I just... she always calls
at the worst possible moment.
And when would
the right moment be?
Because you know,
you're always at work
or here or with Anthony.
And she gets left out.
You're right.
A mother needs to spend time
with her son.
That sounds a little familiar,
yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
Hey!
Happy Christmas Eve, kiddo.
What do you want
for breakfast?
I'll make anything you want.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
Anything?
Yes. I think it's time
that we come up with
some new Christmas
traditions together.
Waffles? Omelettes?
How about both?
Yes!
Womlettes, waffles.
Wafflettes! Huh?
Okay.
You get to crack the eggs.
All righty.
Okay.
-The best part.
-I only need...
-Two?
-Careful.
All right.
This goes in at 350.
-That gets turned down to 275.
-To where?
-The prime rib.
-275.
And then what...
-Don't burn the house down.
-Did you?
I just touched that.
Oh. We need to get the cake
out of the fridge.
Right.
And then once the water's
boiling then we do the crab dip.
I gotta tell you, Nicky.
I love your efficiency.
Well, it is my job.
It's also who I am.
Alright. I hope you don't mind
if I drop and run.
I got a mammoth to-do list.
No problem.
I was able to get the roasting
pan out of the house
without Simone cluing in.
Fantastic.
Are you guys sure everything
will be ready by 7:00?
I told her we have reservations.
Guaranteed.
Okay.
Oh, and don't forget to turn
the outside lights on
so that she can see them
when we pull up.
Jeremy, Jeremy, calm down.
We got it.
All right.
Thank you guys both
so much.
I mean, there is no way
I could've pulled this off
without you two.
All right, I am off to pick up
dry cleaning and a tree skirt
and about 900 other things
left on my to-do list.
Jeremy, we got it.
Okay.
And Nicky, I just, I wanted
to say again how sorry I am
I can't tell you who,
who wrote that card.
I understand.
A promise is a promise.
Okay. I'll see you guys tonight.
Yeah.
Drive safe.
Okay.
That was uh... was Jeremy
talking about that card
that fell out of your purse?
Yeah, he was.
You know, I know you said
earlier that it was nothing,
but it sounded like
there's a story there.
I shouldn't have said
it was nothing.
It was really sweet, actually.
In high school someone
slipped a Christmas card
into one of my school books.
Uh-huh.
It was actually more of
a love note.
And, um, anyway I just found it
the other night.
Wait...
you just found it?
On Thanksgiving.
Can you believe that? Yeah.
Anyway, I was trying to figure
out who had given it to me.
Jeremy knows and he
won't tell me.
Will you hand me the stars?
Uh, yeah, yeah. Sure.
You got some, some cranberry
on there.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
So, if you can't get it
out of Jeremy
how are you going to find out
who this person is?
I'm not.
I was just trying
to figure it out
because I wanted to
have something good from
high school to remember.
It doesn't matter now.
What changed?
Me.
I changed.
I realized that high school
wasn't as bad as I thought
it was.
Can we put those on
the other tray?
Right, yes.
Yeah.
Um, so, let me get
this straight.
So, you... you're totally okay
with not finding out
who wrote you the card?
Yeah.
I really am.
Hmm.
I have to get
the crab dip going.
Right.
Okay, let's see.
How's, how's that look?
Perfect.
You know, I forgot how much
fun this is.
We better get going on
those deliveries.
You don't want to be late
for your big surprise.
Right.
Anthony, come on.
Jeremy and Miriam are waiting.
Right.
Oh, honey. You made
it almost on time.
Don't want to miss
our reservation.
Oh, good.
Hey sweetie, do you think
we have time
to drive by my favorite house
on the way?
Yeah. I think we can.
-Thank you, love.
-Yeah.
-All right, let's go.
-Yeah. Let's go.
You are going to love
this house.
I'm telling you, it is probably
one of the best houses
I've ever seen.
Oh, look.
They changed their decorations
this year.
I love what they did.
Yeah. Yeah, me too.
We should tell 'em.
What?
Come on, we should tell them
we like their decorations.
No, I don't...
-Jeremy, what are you doing?
-Come on, let's go tell them.
This is a horrible idea.
Jeremy, you can't just pull
into somebody's driveway.
Yes, you can.
It's, it's Christmas.
Come on.
Your son may be losing
his mind.
It was only a matter of time.
Okay, let's go say hi.
No.
Come on!
Come on, Mom.
Like Jeremy said,
it's Christmastime.
Oh, my gosh!
This is crazy.
We don't even know
who lives here.
Yes, we do.
No, no, no, no, no, Jeremy.
I really don't want to do this.
The joke is funny but it's-
Oh, this is humiliating.
Okay. Come on.
Let's just go say hi.
Ok. You ready?
Oh, my gosh.
You are actually in.
I mean, my goodness.
It is exactly as I imagined it.
What are you doing?
Surprise!
What is happening?
What?
Jeremy, what is this?
It's your Christmas gift, Mom.
What?
For the last two years you've
made me drive past this house
every time we've been
in the neighborhood.
I know you've dreamt about it
for a long time,
and I've dreamt about having
someone as incredible as you
and Anthony in my life for,
for just as long.
It seems like the perfect place
for us
to start our new life together.
-I love you.
Well, I couldn't have done it
without this guy.
Oh, my sweet guy.
You were just putting up
with mama, right?
He's so weird.
And, of course, Derrick.
He went to such great lengths
to get this house.
Thank you.
And Nicky, who somehow managed
to keep it a secret.
-I'm so happy for you.
-Thank you.
Oh wow, I'm just so happy
and overwhelmed
and I don't know
what to say but, yay!
Mom, come check out
my room.
Have fun!
Thank you everyone.
Eat, drink, enjoy yourself.
What do you think?
You think she likes it?
It's hard to tell, right?
Just a little bit.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
And then the look on her face
when she came through that door.
I mean, I couldn't believe
she was so surprised.
Hey Nicky!
Come here.
Oh, excuse me.
I want to take a picture
with you in front of
the Christmas tree.
Yeah.
Honey, can you take
a photo?
-Oh, yeah.
-Great. Thank you.
-Isn't this so exciting?
-Yes.
Okay, at least we're not
wearing matching outfits
like we did when
we were kids.
Yes. There's definitely
been progress.
Okay. On the count of three
say Christmas.
One, two, three.
Christmas.
-Love you.
-Love you too.
Watching for Santa?
A star to wish on?
Well, they do both bring you
what you want.
I was just thinking about that.
But I have everything I want.
I don't need to keep striving
for more.
I should just learn to be
grateful and enjoy it.
What about someone
to enjoy it with?
If the right person came along,
yes.
Oh, okay.
And what would make him
the right person?
Would he have to write you
a romantic Christmas card?
Because, um...
I don't like to be upstaged.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
What...
If you can't read my writing
it says "Love Derrick."
I can read it.
But you didn't... you didn't
write anything.
At least I signed it
this time.
"With love's light wings
did I o'erperch these walls,
"for stony limits cannot
hold love out."
You? That was...
Yeah, I probably should've
put it in your physics books
instead of your calculus.
I tested out of calculus
in the first semester.
Of course, you did.
Look at those two.
But you weren't on
the basketball team.
That's true, I wasn't.
And, and you're right.
Mountain Point did have
a great basketball team.
But they weren't so good
in debate.
I beat 'em every year.
You were right.
They needed to work
that out themselves.
Yep. Yep.
Sort of, yeah.
Wait a minute.
What did you do?
Well, sometimes Derrick
needs a nudge.
Just a little, little
tiny nudge.
You!
Why didn't you say
anything at the church
when the card fell?
What was I supposed
to say, Nicky?
I mean, I was stunned.
I still couldn't believe
that we were spending
all this time together
and that you were still
holding onto a card
I wrote to you years ago.
It was overwhelming.
Nicky, 22 years ago I,
I didn't have the courage
to tell you how I feel.
But I do now.
Well, 22 years ago I probably
couldn't have heard it.
Maybe not seeing that card
back then
gave us a second chance, huh?
Nicky.
I've always believed that
you were special and amazing,
and that you deserve
to be happy.
I'm so glad that it was you.
And I am so glad
that it is you.
-Merry Christmas.