Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Where is the video she recorded?
You will be punished!
Stop!
Boss!
The girl is rigid!
This is a high-quality one who sends herself.
If it is broken,
you will be responsible.
Take her to the laboratory.
- Ask your people leave.
- Dad!
- Hurry up!
- Mom!
- Wu Wei!
- Just leave!
Sir!
- Kneel!
- Dad!
- Mom!
- Hurry up!
Kneel in a hurry!
Dad!
Wu Wei!
Let me in!
Dad!
Yuan yuan, don't be afraid!
Dad is fine.
Dad won't let them hurt you!
Kill him!
Yuan yuan!
Dad!
Wu Wei!
Now that you take off the suite today,
you can no longer go back to the camp.
Do you know?
Sir!
I am a solider for all my life.
No matter where I am,
I will not betray the mission of the soldier.
Let him go!
Who are you?
Why are you here?
Let him go!
Zhilan?
Liu Xiao!
Doctor Au!
Have you left with Uncle Pei?
Uncle Pei has something to deal with, and
he can't go for the time being!
Our plan will not change.
You'd better go first,
and let's meet at the wharf.
OK!
See you!
Wu Wei!
My bag!
Thanks!
Fortunately, it's still here.
What happened?
Why did they do this to you?
Sir!
How is your health?
Never mind!
It doesn't matter.
Mr. Pei,
we are really jealous of you!
There are not only capable persons like Miss Zuo
on your side,
but also excellent talents like Doctor Xu.
PE Group
is really powerful.
Mr. Chen,
don't flatter me.
R hemagglutinin
is a new breakthrough of your company.
But it is stopped suddenly,
it is a great loss of the medical industry.
No matter there is R hemagglutinin or not,
PE Group
is always the top medical organization in China.
Doctor Xu,
nice to meet you!
Excuse me.
Sir!
Manqing!
I am leaving with Zhilan.
You
should take care of them.
Don't worry!
I got it!
Are Liu Xiao and Doctor Zhao
noticed?
I have arranged everything.
As a matter of fact,
I am not a good father.
My health
is getting worse.
This time,
do take the boy back.
Mr. Pei, don't worry.
Liu Xiao and Kaiwen grew together.
He should persuade him.
In addition,
Doctor Zhao will go together.
Everything will be fine!
I am rest assured
of you!
Zhilan,
this is
all information of R hemagglutinin.
It originally belonged to you!
You can deal with it as your wish.
What smell?
Does my chariot have the oil leakage?
Gosh!
Stop. Stop the car!
Stop it!
Run!
It is going to explode!
My car!
Liu Xiao! Get on the car!
Get on the car!
I can't move!
Shall we have a rest?
You have a rest
The cellphone has been damaged!
Indeed,
I am only a private doctor.
I just come to make up the number.
I don't want to stay here!
And I have even lost my life!
Why am I doing this?
Mr. Wu!
Would you please send me back in the first?
Doctor Zhao,
as I know,
Mr. Pei has multiplied your
consultation fee for one hundred times.
If you breach the contract now,
I am afraid you will have a bad time
in the rest of your life.
Mrs Xu,
I am talking to Mr. Wu.
It's none of your business.
The yacht is out of oil.
If you don't mind,
you can swim back.
I...
Zhilan,
You stay here with Doctor Zhao.
I will investigate the
environment here with Liu Xiao.
Before we come back,
you should not leave!
Do you understand?
No!
We!
No! Nothing!
Come on!
Take it to protect yourself.
Let's go!
Watch out!
Look!
Wait for me here!
- Let me have a look in the first!
- OK!
Nice work!
Brother, where are you from?
Tell me your name!
Tell me!
Who are you?
Why do you come here?
Let me go!
Stop!
Everyone, stop!
Liu Xiao!
Why are you here?
Kaiwen!
Really you!
You run about,
and fight heavily.
Brother!
You are quite unique!
Wild and fashion!
Combined with the beautiful dreadlocks
on your big hair.
What shall I say?
Are you a forest wolf,
or a trenchant man?
Zhilan!
Zhao Ren!
Where are you?
I know where they are!
I am not interested to the married woman.
I come to save you!
Go! Go! Go!
Brother!
Where is the washroom?
Do you want to escape?
No, no!
We...
just want to go to the washroom.
I will come back soon.
Back soon!
Run!
Don't let him go!
Stop!
My face!
Stop, everyone!
Just a misunderstanding!
They are Kaiwen's friends.
- Are you OK?
- Fine!
Kaiwen!
How did you get into this?
A long story!
Kaiwen!
Mr. Pei is in poor health now.
He and the Group need you urgently.
I can't leave.
I have to find Zhenzhen.
Your girlfriend?
What's wrong with Zhenzhen?
One month ago,
Zhenzhen found a clue of human trafficking.
I came to Angela Mountain with her.
However, she disappeared
a few days later.
At the very beginning,
I thought she was working.
But one week ago,
I found this picture accidentally.
I know she is in danger now!
It's him!
Wei!
He is Duxie,
an international A wanted criminal.
He killed many of my
teammates!
Unexpectedly,
he would hide here.
I remember,
I have seen this guy.
On 15 every month,
he would lead a group of people to meet Duxie
on the island.
What day is it today?
It's 14.
It's her?
Zuo Manqing?
Why are they here?
What are they doing here?
No more than the blood experiment.
Blood experiment?
Do you see those people on the boat?
They are for the experiment.
They can't live long.
Is it
the R hemagglutinin experiment?
Isn't it finish?
Yes!
Because the cost is very large.
Such serum
can cure blood disease,
and even delay senescence.
However, for every piece of serum,
it is required to swab off
the blood marrow of five people!
Are you Killing people?
So, I was strongly against of it.
Is it possible that Zuo Manqing
has stolen the research scheme,
and done the experiment silently here?
Impossible!
The confidential documents of the Group
have always been controlled by Mr. Pei himself.
There are some rats on the island once again!
Eliminate them as soon as possible!
Angela Mountain!
No one
can leave here!
Zhenzhen,
Zhenzhen must be in danger!
Jinzi!
We need your help!
What do you want me to do?
We want to dive into the base of Duxie.
We want weapons!
Interesting!
Let's go!
Lead you to Tudie!
Tudie
is the famous leader of Angela Mountain.
He is also the great man
whose power could contend against
Duxie on the island.
Tudie!
Who are you?
Why do you break my dream?
Dad!
Is this my little girl?
Tell me!
Did you betray my mom
in the dream just now?
No, no, no.
I dreamed of your mom just now!
Who are they?
It's none of your business.
Dad!
- Give me the key of the arsenal.
- Ah?
Listen to me!
Liu Xiao and I will go deep into the workshop
to collect evidences.
Kaiwen and Jinzi,
you two
Are responsible for the search,
finding Zhenzhen.
Zhilan and Zhao Ren
should leave outside for the coordination.
Remember,
no matter what happens,
after fifteen minutes,
we must come out.
Zhilan,
you shall be responsible for the outside.
Kaiwen, Jinzi,
It's 11:30 now.
No matter what happens,
after fifteen minutes,
come out immediately.
- OK!
- There!
Go!
Whose product is it?
The product of Zuo!
Boys, thanks for your hardworking.
Zuo!
Discharge!
Liu Xiao, go!
Doctor Zhao!
Where do you think is the power supply system
for such large-scale workshop?
What, what do you want to do?
No!
Mr. Wu said,
We should coordinate outside.
You want to make troubles.
Don't let me get involved.
Come down!
Come down! Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Go!
Run over!
Hurry up!
Come back!
Go over!
Hurry up!
Do you think where is Zhenzhen?
It is out of my expectation that
you are spoony!
Rest assured!
No matter where is Zhenzhen,
I will help you find her.
Go!
OK!
Go inside!
Hurry up!
These are blood samples!
They are devils!
We have to
save them!
Who are you?
Take... take me out!
Zhenzhen!
Who are you?
Your gate is not closed,
SO we come inside to have a look.
Let's go!
You!
Go!
This way!
- Are you OK?
- Stand up!
Tell me!
Where is the master of the bracelet?
You take me out!
Come out!
Do you know the master of the bracelet?
Where is she?
- You take me out!
- Kaiwen!
Go! Go!
Hurry up!
What's going on?
They're
not rates,
but tigers!
Interesting!
Capture them!
I want the alive ones!
Kaiwen!
Hurry up!
This way!
Come inside in a hurry!
Hurry up!
My old friend,
we meet once again.
Your brothers must miss you very much!
I will send you to join with them today!
Kill them!
Wu,
what shall we do?
Rush outside together!
Follow me!
Someone has destroyed the power system!
Check right now!
Yes!
Wu Wei, get on the car!
Go!
Hurry up!
Chase after them!
Who are you on earth?
Why are you there?
Tell me
where is the master
of the bracelet?
It's the girl!
Do you know her?
Where is she?
She is a journalist!
I know where she is.
Where is this?
Death place of Angela Mountain!
She is in it.
Zhenzhen,
Where are you?
Zhenzhen!
You cheat me!
Where is she on earth?
Tell me!
They are really here!
All people of the island are under the forest!
You trick me!
If you don't believe in me!
You can excavate!
Impossible!
Zhenzhen,
where are you?
Zhenzhen!
Kaiwei!
Let it be!
Let him alone!
Zhenzhen!
What's going on?
How could those who
are captured to Angela Mountain
still stay alive?
The ghosts of those people who were
dried of the blood clotting factors
are all under the earth.
Zhenzhen!
Zhenzhen! It's my fault.
I didn't expect that such a beautiful place
would hide so many evils.
All beautiful things in the world
have the price.
But the price of the forest
is so cruel.
Life is fragile.
The live people
should cherish the present world.
Zhenzhen!
Snake!
- Kaiwen!
Kaiwen!
Zhenzhen!
Doctor Zhao, come to save him.
Kaiwen has been attacked by the snake.
I am afraid of the snake. I can't do it!
Why are you afraid of snake?
Brother, I am afraid of snake.
Come on! Hurry up! I will accompany you!
I am afraid of snake!
- Where did it bite?
- Here... here...
Have to inject serum immediately,
otherwise he will die.
There is the serum in the cottage.
Wu Wei, he is running away.
Take them back.
I will chase after him!
OK!
Come on! Stand up!
Why do you escape?
Don't come over!
Why?
I am on the landmine.
Let me help you.
No!
I don't want you to die with me.
I am a soldier.
Saving people
is the responsibility and mission of the soldier.
Although I have put off the uniform,
I will the soldier
for the whole life.
This is the responsibility
and honor of the soldier.
Believe in me!
Quickly,
try to recover the power system
as soon as possible.
The experiment should not be stopped.
And the rates
should be eliminated soon.
Don't disappoint me.
Go!
Why are you still here?
You go first!
Go!
Wu Wei!
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Why are you here?
Didn't I tell you to leave in the first?
My name is Gao Tianming.
I am a policeman of Meng State.
I have been undercovering at
Duxie's side for two years.
I just want to investigate
his criminal evidence.
This
is the experimental report of Duxie,
which records
the name of the subject,
and the death time.
During the period,
I could here crying every night.
They are struggling and
asking for help.
It seems that they are
telling me
they should not die.
I originally thought
I can't wait until the day.
But the evidence keeps on reminding me,
justice will
always come.
There is certainly hope
on the other side of despair.
I finally wait until the day.
Do take it out!
Thanks!
- Gao Sir!
Gao Sir!
Brother!
Lift up!
Doctor Zhao!
Hurry up!
Watch out!
What's going on?
Because of being imprisoned
and tortured for a long time,
his body has been damaged seriously.
He must be sent to the hospital immediately,
otherwise he will be in danger at any time.
The most important thing now
is to contact the outside,
and send those evidences out.
But there is no signal at all on the island.
How can we send the signal out?
The signal source on the island,
has already been cut by Duxie.
Duxie's base is the only place
that can contact the outside world.
Signal room.
Duxie is coming.
Ready for a combat.
Hurry up!
Brother!
Little scorpion!
How could you dare to make troubles on my place?
It will be your last day today!
Watch out!
Go!
Hurry up!
Go away!
Dad!
Dad, what's wrong with you?
Fine!
I'm fine!
Stand up, dad!
They
have a too strong firepower!
Evacuate to the rear mountain.
Hurry up!
Dad! Let's go!
Kaiwen!
Come to help us!
Gao Sir!
We have rushed out!
Zhilan, go!
Go!
Retreat
Dad!
Dad, come over!
Chase!
Dad!
I... I am dying.
Leave me alone.
No, dad!
I can't leave you alone!
Go!
No!
Dad! I can't.
Kaiwen!
Help me take care of Jinzi!
Hurry up!
Go!
- Go!
- No!
- I can't,
- Gao Sir!
Take them to the bridge!
Go!
Hurry up!
- Go!
- Dad!
Go!
- Hurr y up.
- dad!
Hurry up!
Brother, hurry up!
I will bring up the rear.
Liu Xiao!
Go!
Chase!
Go! Hurry up!
Go!
Evacuate!
Sir,
R hemagglutinin
will be succeeded soon.
Be rest assured.
PE Group
will become stronger.
By the way,
Kaiwen
will go with you soon.
We don't capture the rats.
They escape!
Go!
Go to capture the child!
Mom will come back a few days later.
- Grandma.
- Yuan yuan.
Yuan yuan!
Leave her alone!
Brother,
I want to revenge for my dad
and my clansmen.
I also want to revenge for Zhenzhen and Liu Xiao,
as well as those dead ghosts,
and my teammates.
We have to
revenge!
Just us?
How could us make it?
I think
we should get contact
with the outside world in the first!
If we still wait here,
we will die soon.
Gao!
Where is the signal room of Duxie?
At the back of the base!
Do you want to attack when they are not prepared?
Yes!
At 5:00 in the morning,
they have the most loose vigilance.
This is the best opportunity.
Since you're familiar to
the environment in the base,
you'd better take us there.
I have been waiting for the day for a long period.
Everyone,
we have to revenge
and save the people.
Where are they?
Why do they disappear?
Where is the monitor?
Be destroyed!
Originally, he has been ready!
Boss!
I have found the private signal of Zuo Manqing.
Jinzi,
Go!
How about?
It's the signal room in the front.
- Zhilan, handle this.
- OK!
Gao Sir! Let's rescue them.
Doctor Xu, hurry up!
Come for death!
Come out!
Jinzi!
Help me keep it!
Doctor Xu, how long it still has to take?
Succeed!
Sir,
it is Kaiwen calling for help
and criminal evidence of Zuo Manqing.
Send it to the police right now.
What's going on?
It is the one-way communication set here.
- It can only be sent to Angela Mountain.
- Hurry up!
Connect to our own signal source,
and send the message out.
Yes!
You have no chance!
Manqing!
I have been kind to you!
How could you become this?
I become this
because of you!
I devoted everything to PE Group,
and even got sick.
You exactly know R hemagglutinin
could save my life,
but you refuse to continue the research.
The danger of R hemagglutinin
is clear to you!
I have no other choice!
Really?
What a sanctimonious hypocrite!
When you know you are sick,
you intentionally disclose
the scheme of hemagglutinin
to me!
You know I will continue the research,
and you maintain the important data.
When I am going to succeed,
you are going to kill me with the force
Dispose of
Then,
you can enjoy the fruits, right?
You
firstly kill two birds with one stone
and then have the mantis stalking the cicada.
Really resumed all your efforts.
Nonsense.
- I indeed...
- Enough!
It's too late.
Both Kaiwen and you should die.
Zuo Manqing,
I didn't expect
you should be so vicious.
Now that,
it's not my fault.
Lou Yi!
Take actions!
You thought you arranged Lou Yi beside me,
then you can control everything.
People will change!
Your trick
has been out of date.
Mr. Pei,
sorry!
Manqing!
Manqing! Manqing!
Don't kill me! Don't kill me!
Don't kill me!
The Group will be yours.
For our emotions of several years,
please let my son and me go.
The Group is certainly mine.
The same is the life of your son
and you!
Gao!
Hold on!
I fulfill my task!
Take them out!
Gao!
Where is Jinzi?
We are going to save them!
Don't be afraid!
We come to save you!
Where is the little boy?
Where does he go?
I don't know!
The laboratory!
Go!
Doctor Zhao!
Save!
OK!
Have a look!
How?
Can be saved!
Wu Wei!
Your beloved daughter is with me!
She is very lovely,
and really thoughtful!
If you don't want your daughter to die,
take Kaiwen
and data of R hemagglutinin
to Manjing Temple.
If I couldn't see you at 4:00 pm,
you will never see Yuan yuan.
Yuan yuan is in danger.
I want to save her.
Calm down!
I will go to save my daughter!
Don't worry!
She will be fine!
I promise, OK?
Wu Wei!
Do you want to save her alone like last time?
I don't want her to be hurt!
Wu Wei!
Do you know the family?
The daughter is in danger now.
She needs us.
She not only has your blood,
she is also my treasure.
No matter what danger we come across,
we should confront together.
Brother!
I want to exchange with Yuan yuan.
Listen to me!
What Zuo Manqing wants
is not only your life,
but also the PE Group at your back.
I won't let her succeed.
Brother!
Stop!
Listen to me!
You stay here,
and protect them!
Doctor Zhao!
Take them leave here as soon as possible!
I will save Yuan yuan with you!
Let's go!
Yuan yuan!
Put down the gun!
Where is Kaiwen?
Why hasn't he come?
It seems that,
you don't want to meet the old friend.
Right?
Zuo Manqing!
Come at me!
Don't bully the child.
Give me the thing!
Yuan yuan!
Today!
Your dad
and mom
have both come!
You reunite!
Quite warm, right?
Yuan yuan!
Dad is here!
Don't worry!
Don't be afraid!
Today, aunt wants to play
a game with you!
Do you want
dad to die,
or mom to die?
You have to choose one!
If you choose,
I will let you go right now!
OK?
Zuo Manqing!
I have given you what you want.
Why are you still bullying the girl
a little child?
Let Yuan yuan go!
I will give you whatever you want!
Come to me!
Right!
Your dad is a soldier,
he is not afraid of death.
Then, let's shoot dad.
Kill dad, OK?
Kill him! Come on!
Give me the hand!
Take the gun! Come on!
Take it!
Shoot at dad!
Align!
Don't move!
Wu Wei!
Yuan yuan is really clever!
But you didn't align.
Come on!
Shoot Dad again.
The stubborn girl
will be punished.
It seems that
you don't want mom either.
Wu Wei!
Doctor Au!
It seems that
your life is meaningful.
You have a man who loves you so deeply
and is willing to die for you.
You can die in peace.
Wu Wei!
- Wu Wei, don't leave us!
- Dad!
- Mom!
Dad!
I miss you!