Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
-
- Hi.
- Are you done in there?
- Yeah.
Oh, rent on Friday, right?
Yeah, I get paid Thursday.
Awesome.
Hey, bud, time to get up.
Son, come on, time to get up.
I gotta go to work, let's go.
Come on.
Hey.
- You have to go pee?
- Yeah.
Okay, here.
Go pee and brush your teeth.
Um, not that shirt.
What shirt do you want?
Red one.
Okay, go pee
and brush your teeth,
and I'll get your red shirt,
okay?
Here, take this.
I'll get your red shirt, go.
Hurry up!
Here you go, bud, red shirt.
I'm gonna get our lunches
ready,
do you need help
with your shoes?
- No.
- Okay.
Hurry up, come on we gotta go.
Hey.
Do you need a snack
before daycare?
- Yeah, cereal.
- No time for cereal.
How about a banana?
- No, juice.
- Juice.
GREYSON:
There you are.
Lunch.
Alright, let's go.
JAMES:
Don't forget our book.
Oh, right.
Alright, come on, let's go.
- GREYSON: Morning.
- Good morning, James.
Good morning.
GREYSON:
Hey, I put some breakfast up
in here, too.
He wanted cereal,
but we didn't have time so...
No worries.
Maggie, can you put this
with the rest?
MAGGIE:
Of course.
Who's picking him up
this afternoon?
Your mom's gonna com
pick you up later.
That'll be fun, huh?
I want you to come get me.
I know you do,
but it's just gonna be
for a couple of days.
I promise.
SARAH:
You should go.
- Don't wanna be late.
- Okay.
Alright, have fun today, bud.
Thank you.
Fuck!
JOHN:
Yes, this is Tech Fix.
- Good morning.
- : Morning, Zoey.
- How are you?
- Late.
JOHN:
Yes, like I instructed you
to use.
Morning.
You're late.
I know I just had to drop
the kid off on my--
Fourth time this month.
I know.
So what are we doin' about it?
I'm working on it.
And?
And it's just hard, because
I have to get the kid ready,
and I have to drive him
all the way over to daycare.
Yeah, you gotta get
the kid ready,
you gotta take him to daycare.
"I got to, I got to--",
look, I don't care.
We all have problems, okay?
But we all manage to get here
on time
and I don't want
any more excuses, alright?
I'm sorry, it's just--
Grey, just say "alright".
No more excuses, got it?
Alright.
Fuckin' animal, calm down,
we're tryin' to work here.
Good morning.
Thank you for calling Tech Fix.
My name is Greyson.
How can I make you happy
this morning?
Hey, guys!
Kate and I are making a run
to Anthem Coffee.
Does anybody want anything?
- Jim?
- No.
Hey, let me get something.
Hey.
What do you want, John?
Um, we got a caramel macchiato.
- What size?
- Uh, grande.
Thanks.
Go strong with the sugar.
BRODY:
Yeah, Zoey, can I get
a white chocolate mocha?
Venti.
Thanks, Brody.
Oh, I bet it tastes like shit.
Hey, Grey.
Do you want any coffee?
- I gotta pass, thanks.
- You sure?
Give the guy a break, Zoey.
He's a loser tryin' to support
a kid on $12 an hour.
He can't afford coffee.
That.
You're an asshole.
You say that now.
Fucking don't.
ERIC:
Who's in there?
Yeah?
Is that you, Grey?
GREYSON:
Yeah.
Dude, you better not be
jerkin' off in there.
Fuck no.
ERIC:
Come on.
All yours.
-
TRENT:
Yeah, thank you for calling
Tech Fix.
Mmhmm.
I guarantee you.
Okay.
Mmhmm, yes, yes,
it's great to know.
Alright, chop-chop, teammate.
Get back to work, okay?
We're losin' time
and not makin' a dime.
Grey, where are you goin'?
I just gotta talk to Zoey for--
Look, you should've taken
care of it during lunch, okay?
Instead of jerkin' off
in the bathroom?
- Yeah.
Oh, speaking of--
dropped your porn in there.
It's not porn.
Yeah, I don't care, man.
I care about the environment.
Come on, Zoe,
you're slower than mud.
Let's go.
Happy hour only lasts
till 6:00, you know?
Right behind you.
BARNES:
Hey.
- You wanna go out Saturday?
- No.
Why not?
What's the problem?
The fact that you don't know
why not.
Bye!
Is it Grey, is it?
Great, well, I'm glad that
I could help you out today?
Is there anything else
that I can do for you?
Awesome.
Again, my name is Greyson.
If you have any further issues,
please don't hesitate
to call back.
Thank you for calling--
Hello, sir?
Sir?
- LIAM: Hey, cuz.
- Hey.
LIAM:
Want a beer?
Yes, please.
Awesome.
Oh, thank you.
Don't mention it.
Oh.
You have to work late tonight?
Nah.
Actually,
took off a little early.
Went shootin' with a friend
of mine.
A dude named "Winslow".
"Weird Winslow",
they call him at work.
Hmm.
He picked up
his badass machine gun,
did some simple conversions
to it.
The thing goes full auto now.
It was crazy.
A guy they call "Weird Winslow"
has a machine gun?
LIAM:
Yeah.
Weird Winslow
has a machine gun.
Say it with me.
LIAM:
Yeah, he's alright.
He's just a little--
Anachronistic.
Um-- yeah, I don't know
what that means, but--
Weird Winslow
has a machine gun.
-
Anyways, we're goin' again
Sunday afternoon,
before I head to Janice,
if you wanna go?
No, I can't, I have James.
- You sure?
- Mmhmm.
LIAM:
Hey, you already eat?
Yeah.
LIAM:
No James, tonight?
No, not till Wednesday,
but then just for a little bit.
- LIAM: Like usual.
- Yeah?
LIAM:
Sorry, man.
Me, too.
Listen, hey, dude um--
You know, I just wanna say...
...thanks for letting me
and James stay here.
As soon as I get back
on my feet, I--
Nay.
You're family, man.
Blood's thicker than water.
You stay here as long
as you need to.
Okay?
James, time to get up.
Buddy, come on, time to get up.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Um, thank you for the latté
yesterday.
I wanted to come by and say so,
but Eric's--
anyway, I can give you
some money
as soon as we get paid
on Thursday.
Grey, if you wanna pay me back
you can always buy me coffee
after work.
or dinner or both.
Are you asking me out?
I mean, come on.
I've been tryin' to get you
to ask me out for months.
But you haven't quite picked up
on it.
So, yeah--
I'm asking.
A girl's gotta take care
of herself sometime, right?
I have my son on the weekends.
So Thursday then?
6:30 p.m., Anthem Coffee.
Coffee date?
Okay.
This isn't a prank, is it?
No, no prank.
I like you, Grey.
Why?
It's 'cause you're different.
And I need different in my life
right now, I think.
Um--
- Oh--
- Oh.
- You should go clock in.
- Yeah, I should clock in.
Yeah, um.
- Grey.
- GREYSON: Yeah?
Can you come in here a sec?
Is everything alright?
ERIC:
Yeah, just come on.
Have a seat, Grey.
Jen, from upstairs,
says I gotta write you up
for being late the other day.
Eric, it was just
a few minutes, I was--
Look, I like you, Grey,
I do, okay?
But the company policy
is clear.
You have to be at your desk,
you have to be logged in,
and be ready to take calls
by 7:00 a.m.
I know.
Look, I gave you a verbal
warning last time, okay?
So I have to write you up
this time.
It's not a big deal.
It just states that
we spoke about it
and that if it continues,
further action,
up to and including termination,
could occur.
Now, nobody wants that, Grey.
Just sign there.
It states that you understand
the company policies
as laid out
in the employee handbook.
I didn't get
an employee handbook.
Well, you're tryin'
to be difficult?
No.
Sign then.
Here.
Alright.
ERIC:
Alright, thanks.
Yeah, I got it.
That's it.
- That's it?
- Yep.
So it won't happen again, okay?
Look, the next time,
there's a three-day suspension,
and time after that is well--
you know?
I understand.
Good.
You can go now.
Hey, Grey.
Why don't you smile more, huh?
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah.
BARNES:
Once again, my name is Barnes.
Thank you for callin' Tech Fix
and I hope
you have a wonderful day.
Grey, pick up the phone!
Thank you for calling Tech Fix.
This is Barnes,
how may I assist you today?
Thank you for calling Tech Fix.
This is Greyson.
How can I help you today?
:
The forecast, showers
and thunderstorms today
with strong southwesterly winds
to 37 miles per hour.
We'll have a high of 59 degrees
with the temperature dropping
rapidly towards this evening.
The showers and thunderstorm's
expected to continue
until tomorrow morning.
The overnight low, near 38.
Rain tapering off to--
Button Grey slowpoke over there.
Oh yeah.
Fuck Grey.
BARNES:
Yes, ma'am, I understand.
What I'm tryin' to tell you--
Yes.
Okay, ma'am--
Ma'am, please--
Yes, what I'm-- what I'm trying
to tell you is that if-
if you just-- hello?
Hello?
Hey.
So we're still on
for tomorrow night, right?
Yeah, if you still want to.
Yeah, I-- I still want to.
- Okay.
I should go.
I gotta go pick up James
by like 4:30, so--
Yeah, no worries.
I will see you tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Really?
What?
Grey.
Yeah, Grey!
I like him.
Isn't he like-- what,
20 years older than you?
No.
So what?
My dad's like 10 years older
than my mom
and they're happy, so--
Oh, doesn't he have a kid?
Yeah, so?
All I'm saying is be careful.
Divorced, single dad,
works here--
Oh.
He's probably damaged goods,
Zoe.
Okay, why do we say those things
about single dads,
'cause like
we call single moms "brave"?
"Ooh, look at her raisin'
that baby all on her own."
But when it comes to single dads
we're like,
"Oh, look at him,
he is a loser"
and that's bullshit, Kate--
- Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Because we don't know--
Whoa!
Point made.
Jeez.
- All I'm saying is be careful.
- Oh.
There's something a little off
about him.
He's weird.
- He's shy.
- Weird.
Shy!
Same thing.
So I'm shy.
Does that make me weird?
Um, yeah.
But I love you anyway.
Come on happy hour calls.
Oh my God!
Daddy!
Hey, bud.
How was daycare today?
You know, what we did today?
What'd you do today?
We painted pictures
with our fingers.
Really?
Can I see?
Hey.
Had them finger-paint outside.
GREYSON:
Wow!
This is very good.
You did this all by yourself?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
This is very pretty, son,
you did a good job.
Is this for me?
No, for mommy.
I'm sure she'll love it.
JAMES:
I made you, too.
I put "to dad" on it,
so you would know
which one's yours.
That's great.
I think we should go home
and hang it right up.
Come on.
Uh, this is his stuff.
Oh yeah.
Hold your bag.
And Marilyn wanted me
to remind you
it's your week to pay.
I get paid on Thursday, though,
so I don't--
I don't have it at the moment,
but I can give it to you
right after they send it.
That's fine.
Thank you.
Alright, let's go.
See you tomorrow, James.
- JAMES: Bye.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
One kid scoop
of birthday cake ice, please.
Okay, is that a cup or a cone?
How much more is the cone?
It's 30c.
- Okay.
Here you go.
Okay, it's a buck, 45.
Thank you.
There you go.
Uh, you said it was a buck, 45.
SHOPKEEPER:
Yeah, sorry,
I only have pennies.
- That's fine.
- Okay.
JAMES:
We're savin' up our change
to go to Disneyland.
We put it in a jar at home,
and when it's full,
we're goin' to Disneyland.
Oh, I don't think 5 pennies
is gonna get you very far, kid.
JAMES:
Daddy says, "When you workin'
towards somethin'
every penny matters".
That's right, son.
Yeah, every penny matters.
There you go.
You want a bite, daddy?
No, that's all you, dude,
but you have to promise me
you're gonna eat some dinner
tonight, okay?
Okay, what's for dinner?
Dad, can you help me?
Sure thing, buddy,
just a minute.
Oh, you're gonna give him
purple stripes?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's cool.
That's a good idea.
- What do you think?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
What else does it need?
- Anything?
- Mmm.
- I think it's pretty good.
- Yeah.
Yeah, that looks like birthday
cake ice cream, right?
- Definitely.
I'll just shade it
in a little bit more.
MARILYN:
I thought I heard you.
Oh my gosh, that's amazing!
I did it myself.
Is that me
with the blonde hair?
- Yeah.
- Oh, I love it.
Thank you so much, sweetie.
- You're late.
- I know.
We were workin' on our book.
So is your mother just gonna
let you have her car?
Yeah, she said I could keep it.
Good for you, Grey.
What am I supposed to do,
tell her "no"?
Hmm, somebody always comes
to your rescue, don't they?
Hey, go on inside, mister,
dinner's about ready.
- JAMES: We ate.
- Oh.
What'd you eat?
Daddy's scrambled eggs.
Okay.
You need some real food.
Go on in.
Here, take this painting.
Thank you.
He needs more than eggs
for dinner.
GREYSON:
I know.
I'm gonna go buy some fruit
and stuff for this weekend
after I get paid.
Yeah, about that--
What's up, mister?
I forgot to say "bye" to dad.
- Can I?
- Of course.
I'll see you this weekend, okay?
Alright, go back inside.
So what were you gonna say?
Nothing.
Just have a good weekend
with him, okay?
GREYSON:
Shit.
Hey, Grey.
Hey.
No gym today?
Uh...
No, my free trial expired.
- Lame.
- Yeah.
Oh, hey, this is Winslow.
Winslow Danny,
meet Greyson Bell.
It's nice to meet you Mr. Bell.
Hi.
What's with the machine gun?
Well, this is what
those cream puffs
would call an "assault rifle".
Winslow was just showin' me
the conversion work
he did on it.
- Did all the work himself.
- Hmm.
I'm thinkin' about buying it
from him.
WINSLOW:
You shoot, Mr. Bell?
By shootin' I mean you ever
fire a weapon.
Not in anger, though.
No one should ever fire
a weapon in anger.
You can just call me "Grey",
but-- no,
I mean I don't even know
which end to-
I know which end, I'm j-
I'm just sayin' like no,
I wouldn't.
Well, then, sir,
would you like to learn,
because I am in fact
a certified safety instructor
and licensed dealer
for that matter.
Liam and I, we're goin' out
shooting Sunday after work.
You know, it'd be a pleasure
to have you come join us
in celebratin'
our Second Amendment rights,
in true red-blooded
American fashion I might add.
Yeah, absolutely.
You guys are gonna celebrate
by shooting a machine gun?
Yeah.
I own several of 'em.
It's our God-given right.
I have a kid, so I can't--
I can't do it you know.
Well, there you go.
That's an even better reason
to learn.
Gun safety is important
if you have children.
Picture the scenario,
your kid finds a gun.
Thinks it's a toy.
Can you imagine
the consequences
of somethin' like that
happenin'?
Downright unthinkable.
Here, check this out.
- Whoa, oh, no, no, I can't.
- It's alright, safety's on.
Just don't put your finger
on the trigger,
- it's uh, right there.
- Okay.
It's alright,
ain't gonna bite you.
Alright.
Whoa, Jesus Christ!
Oh, s-- I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to.
- Dude, I'm sorry.
- Listen.
You never ever point a gun
at somethin'
you don't intend to kill.
You understand what I'm sayin',
Mr. Bell?
GREYSON:
I'm sorry.
Well, I'm just sayin'
if you remember anything,
remember that.
Gun's not a toy.
It should be treated
with respect.
I got it.
Jesus.
Well, I believe you, but here.
- The safety's right here--
- No.
And you just make sure
that sucker's on first.
No, I shouldn't.
That's alright.
Here, take it.
No, we don't--
you just hold it right there.
Yeah.
Alright.
Now, listen,
when you pull the trigger,
this thing is gonna kick back
at you.
That's gonna cause the barrel
to climb,
so you have to kinda just--
Here, there you go.
Just like that.
Feels good, doesn't it?
Ugh, no, I-- here.
I'm never gonna shoot
anything like that.
Yeah, I understand.
A gun that size
can be intimidating.
Kinda like the young
college girl
havin' her first sex encounter.
She's really kinda hopin'
she gets somethin'
she can handle.
If you catch my drift.
Yeah.
WINSLOW:
I won't hold it against you.
LIAM:
Hey, you want a beer?
Yeah.
Hey, somethin' American
and/or domestic, please.
LIAM:
Yeah.
How about we start
with somethin' small.
That's small?
Comparatively, yes, sir.
It's a revolver, simple.
Just point and pull the trigger.
Kinda like a dart gun.
You know, those little kid toys
with a plastic dart
and a suction cup on the end?
Kind I used to shoot
my little brother
in the forehead
with all the time.
Did you ever have
one of those dart guns
when you're a kid, Mr. Bell?
GREYSON:
Yeah, sure.
Everybody did.
I do believe you are correct,
sir.
I reckon about every boy did.
Well, this ain't that
much different than those,
really.
Although,
this shoots real bullets
instead of a plastic little dart
with a suction cup on the end,
which is considerably
less dangerous.
And this is quite
a bit heavier, too.
Is this thing loaded?
That is not, but this one is.
A man must be prepared
to defend himself
against all enemies,
foreign and domestic.
You just point
and pull the trigger,
and you got a dead body
on the other end.
Simple and neat, as you please.
I don't wanna shoot anybody.
Pacifist.
I get that.
Path of least resistance
is a tough one to walk sometimes
and deserves its own respect
for the difficulties therein.
Not everyone's a warrior,
Mr. Bell.
I accept you for who you are.
Why don't you come with us
this weekend, Grey?
We'll be shootin' cans
and stuff, it's fun.
GREYSON:
Shooting cans?
Yeah.
Yes, sir, Mr. Bell.
Mexicans, Africans,
Puerto Ricans.
It's not even
a little bit funny.
I'm sorry, I was just jokin',
Mr. Bell.
Fact is we've got
a serious immigrant problem
in this country anyways
and it should be dealt with.
I'm not sayin'
I advocate shootin' anyone.
Well, that would be just wrong.
They oughta just pass
some legislation
to keep 'em out
in the first place.
Build a friggin' wall
or somethin'.
Dude, can I borrow
a couple bucks for gas
to get to work tomorrow?
I can pay you back as soon
as I get home.
I'm all tapped out till Friday,
man.
- Sorry.
- Shit.
I could arrange a small loan
for you.
Or I could just give you
five bucks
of my hard-earned money.
If takin' a handout would suit
your democratic mindset
a little better.
Hey, don't say shit like that
around here, okay?
Grey's dealin'
with a lot of shit
and he's family.
Money's tight, that's all.
Shit, Liam, I was just joking.
I know that, but he doesn't.
- Just give him a break.
- You're right, of course.
So I go forth and apologize?
No.
Just-- here.
Let me see that 9.
You really carry that thing
around loaded?
I do indeed.
Fuck!
Pump 2.
Really?
Good morning.
Morning.
I gotta--
Yeah, go get to work.
Yes, and if it does happen
again um, please call back,
and you have
my direct extension,
and we can take care of it.
Okay, great.
Yes.
Oh, again, my name is Greyson,
thank you so much
for calling Tech Fix,
and have a great rest
of your night.
Okay, you too.
- Hey.
Change your mind yet?
Nope.
- You?
- Nope.
So what's the plan?
I just gotta go cash
my paycheck,
and run a few errands,
and then I'm gonna go home,
and get ready.
Do you wanna go out to dinner
or somethin' after coffee?
Yeah, I would like that.
- Yes, um--
- Okay.
Okay.
- I should go.
- Uh, yeah.
I will see you in an hour?
- 6:30, yeah.
- 6:30.
- Okay.
- Alright, see you.
See you in an hour.
GREYSON:
Fuck.
Hey.
You showed up.
Yeah, I'm sorry I'm late.
I was starting to think that
you wouldn't.
Oh, no, I just--
I didn't know what to wear.
Well, I mean you look great.
Thanks.
Just you know,
it's been a long time
since I've been on a date
with the work, and the kid,
and you know,
you look great, too.
Buy me coffee, Grey.
Alright.
Alright, the big question.
Uh-oh.
It's just a question.
Alright, go ahead.
What do you keep workin' on
in the break room?
What's in that sketchbook?
Oh, it's--
It's just somethin'
I'm workin' on with my son.
- Aw!
- Hey, guys.
- How are you two, today?
- Good.
- Oh, good, thank you.
Can I get you guys started
with anything to drink?
Um, may I please have
a 12 ounce vanilla latté?
Sounds good.
- For you?
- Um, can I get a tea anything?
Like a London Fog?
Okay.
- Alright.
- Thank you.
You'll like it.
Okay.
I don't know what that is.
Okay, so?
So--
It's a book.
What kind of book?
It's nothing.
What?
It's just I never really shared
with anyone and...
...no one's ever asked me
about it before actually.
Well, I mean I'm asking.
Okay.
It'll probably be easier
if I just showed you though.
Yeah, okay.
What?
Where are you--
Just-- I'll be one second.
Alright, here are your drinks.
Oh, thank you.
Thanks.
So?
This is really personal.
Okay.
Yeah, it's just me and my son,
we really put a lot of work
into this, and normally,
I would never share this
with anyone.
Grey, you said that already.
I'm not gonna tell anyone,
I promise.
These are all originals
and they can't be replaced,
so I'm trusting you.
ZOEY:
Grey.
Okay, okay.
These are really good, Grey.
Really.
Have you always been an artist?
It's the only thing
I ever wanted to be.
I've been drawing
ever since I was a kid.
Hmm.
Even went to a pretty good
art school, got a degree,
started my own business,
you know, but--
But?
But then James came along.
We just--
We were not ready at all,
we-- we were totally not ready.
And you know,
I had to look for a real job,
somethin' with insurance.
Had to sell our supplies,
and all my paintings,
and stuff to buy diapers.
Turns out that
an art school degree
doesn't really translate
to the real world.
Before we knew it,
went underwater
and lost everything.
And now you work at Tech Fix?
Yeah.
Now, I work at Tech Fix.
They were hirin'
and I just needed a new job.
What's it about?
It's called "The Bumbling Ogre"
and it's about a little boy
who doesn't have any friends
or at least,
he thinks he doesn't have
any real friends,
because they're always playing
on their phones
and on their computer,
and he wants to go out
and play in the woods.
And he wants to explore
and have adventures.
His mom works all the time
and she's never home.
So one day he's all by himself
and he decides,
"I'm gonna head out
in the woods and play".
So he does.
But the woods are dark, scary,
and way bigger
than he imagined,
so he finds himself lost,
and then it starts raining.
So the little boy sees a cave
and he thinks,
"I'm gonna go into the cave
and wait until the rain stops."
But as he gets closer
and closer,
he hears a terrible roar.
And he gets scared.
But then an ogre
sticks his head out
and he sees the boy,
and he says,
"I wasn't roaring,
I was snoring."
GREYSON:
And he tells the boy
he can come in
and take shelter in the cave
until the rain stops,
because he knows what it's like.
You see,
there once was a dark wizard
who told the ogre to do
bad things and he did them.
And he's sorry
and now he's an outcast,
so he understands
what the boy feels like and--
and he wants to fix it.
So the two of them sit
in his cave around a campfire
and they-- they eat marshmallows
from the boy's backpack
and little by little,
that boy is less
and less afraid.
When the rain stops,
and they go outside,
and the woods seem less dark,
and less scary,
because the boy
has a real friend now.
And the boy asks--
he asked the ogre
if he wants to play,
and they smile at each other,
and the ogre,
after all that time bein' alone
in his sad cave
as nobody understands him
and he's an outcast,
he's so happy to have a friend
and someone to play with,
he runs out into the woods,
and the two play, and play,
and play,
and have a-- a grand old time.
And then night comes
and the boy asked the ogre
if he can stay.
And the ogre knows that
the boy's mother will be worried
and that the dark wizard
could come back at any time,
so he tells the boy
that he has to go home.
And the boy, he cries,
and cries, and cries,
because he thinks
he's never gonna see
the ogre again,
but the ogre tells him
he'll always be there
when he needs him
and he will always be
his friend.
In the end, the boy convinces
the ogre to go live with him,
so they journey together
through the woods
towards the boy's house,
leaving behind
the wizard's voice,
and leaving behind
the ogre's dark cave,
and the boy hides him
in his closet,
and they have many grand
adventures together, but...
...the ogre's clumsy.
He's always breakin' things
and screwing things up.
Even though he tries so hard
and it makes him feel
really bad, but--
But the boy loves him anyway.
And the boy teaches him
that that's what love is.
It's to accept someone
for who they are,
and he helps them
to finally break the spell,
and they leave the dark wizard
behind forever.
And the two live happily
ever after.
Uh, the boy
and the bumbling ogre.
You're not an ogre, Grey.
I know.
Just a story,
it's a kid's book.
But duh, the wizard's real.
It's a great story,
and the artwork is amazing,
and the moral is important,
and um--
I bet you're a really great dad.
My ex-wife doesn't think so.
What?
Dinner.
I'm hungry.
Everybody else seemed
to actually like,
"No", like they were following
along with the events.
They knew
it was a used cough drop--
Mmhmm.
He had smacked
out of his mouth, um--
Except for me, 'cause like
when I hear like noises goin'
I tend to just like you know,
move my--
Is that me?
Good morning.
So we probably shouldn't go
to work together.
Yeah.
We've already talked too much.
Do you wanna drive me back
to my car?
- Okay.
-
- Alright.
Let's go.
I had a great time last night,
really.
Me, too.
Okay.
Oh.
We should do this again
sometime.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Just um, don't tell anyone
at work about this, please.
- You're embarrassed?
- No!
It's just--
I don't want people talking
about it.
I don't want either of us
to get in trouble and--
- People are already talking.
- Hmm.
You know, office gossip, it's--
Okay.
What?
I said, "Okay".
Don't okay me on this.
I mean it.
GREYSON:
Zoey!
Do you regret it?
No.
Neither do I.
So let's just go to work
like normal.
What kind of a router
are you currently using
right now?
Good morning.
Go clock in.
- Yeah, I should--
- Yeah.
Oh.
I think you dropped this.
Thanks.
Morning, Kate.
Hmm.
Hmm?
- What?
- Nothing.
- Keep up.
- Yeah, it's over.
- Anyways--
- Yes, I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry about, man,
I am so sorry.
Mmhmm, I don't know
to be honest,
but here's what we'll do.
- Here's what we'll do--
- Why don't we--
-
Why don't we start over again
and let's just-
let's just take--
So?
Yeah, you, Grey.
- What?
- She suck your dick?
- Zoey.
- The office slut.
- Don't call her that.
We went out, and we had coffee,
and-- and dinner,
- we had a nice time.
- It was nice.
What's your problem?
You weren't her first, Grey.
I already tapped that shit.
- You're lying.
- Am I?
She was mine first, Grey.
Think about that next time
you kiss her, bitch.
Hey.
Hey yourself.
I'd like to see you after work
on Monday.
Maybe we can get ice cream
or something?
Yeah, ice cream.
I like ice cream.
Good.
- It's a date.
- Okay.
Monday.
Hey, Grey, you know,
you can text me, right?
Like over the weekend.
I don't care what people say.
Yeah, now, it's not really
the time or the place--
Well, I just want you to know
I don't care.
I'm tired of caring
what people think.
You look pretty today.
Thank you.
Bye.
I'm here, I'm here.
I'm sorry I'm late, I'm sorry.
Hey.
I'm here.
SARAH:
James stayed home today.
Didn't you get Marilyn's text?
Sorry.
Oh.
Yeah, here it is.
I must've just not seen it.
Okay, uh, bye.
Fuck, fuck, fuck,
fucker, fucker!
Hello?
- Mom?
- Grey.
GREYSON:
What are you doing here?
I thought
I'd come see my grandson--
- Hey, daddy!
- Oh, hey, buddy.
How are you?
Why don't you get
your backpack ready, little man?
- Okay.
- Go upstairs.
What's going on?
Grey, why can't you just
try harder?
CAROL:
James is such
a wonderful little kid,
he needs a father.
He has his father.
CAROL:
Oh, does he?
You know, I love you, Grey,
I really do,
but we never should
have had you.
I let you down, Grey.
That's my legacy.
Now, you're doing
the same damn thing
with your family.
I'm doing the best that I can.
That's what concerns me.
I'm a good dad.
You know, what they um,
called kids like you
when I was still teaching?
"Wasted potential".
Still drawing pictures
and telling stories.
I like drawing.
It makes me happy.
Doesn't happiness count
for anything?
James likes my art,
we're makin' a book together.
And how's that working out
for you?
Oh, you're such an angry
little kid.
And you're still angry.
Maybe that's your real
fucking legacy, huh?
Well, maybe it is.
You are responsible
for your actions.
for where you are in life
not anybody else.
No, the world
doesn't owe you anything.
It doesn't owe you shit.
Sometimes I can't even stand
to look at you.
CAROL:
Stand up and be a man
for God's sake!
Hey!
Why don't you uh, go out
and play some baseball
and get some exercise.
Hey bud, ready to go?
Yeah.
But stay away
from that damn book.
Come on, let's go.
Good job, buddy.
You can put that in the jar
when we get home, okay?
"And then Prince Ernest
and all the prince's men
raced across the drawbridge
into the castle
where Princess Emily
was waiting,
but she had a surprise."
Aww!
That's it for tonight, bud,
it's past your bedtime.
But what happened next?
We can read more tomorrow.
It's time for sleep.
Okay?
Okay.
Alright, goodnight, buddy.
Goodnight, dad.
Love you more than ice cream.
Love you more than cake.
Love you more
than ice cream cake.
That's not your thing.
You're makin' that up.
Yeah, it's time for bed.
We can go to the fair tomorrow,
okay?
Okay.
- Goodnight.
- Night light.
Yeah, I'll put it on right now.
JAMES:
Dad.
Yeah?
JAMES:
We're not going to Disneyland,
are we?
Yes, we are, I promise.
JAMES:
It's okay
you can't afford it, dad.
James.
Son, look at me.
We're going to Disneyland.
I promise.
We just have to save up
for it first.
Every penny matters.
That's right, son.
Did you take the money, daddy?
Go to bed.
I don't know, I want 'em all.
Well, you better get
what you can
while you got a chance
before the laws change,
'cause it's really only
a matter of time.
Hey.
Hey, Mr. Bill, how you doin'
this fine evenin'?
Yeah, yeah.
Fine.
What's all this?
WINSLOW:
This is my fine selection
of firearms.
We're gonna be shootin'
these on Sunday.
Like I said before,
it'd be really cool
if you could join us.
We will have a good time.
- Are these things loaded?
- LIAM: No, no.
Because my son is right there
and I really don't feel
comfortable with you guys
having these in the house
- and I'm--
- LIAM: No, no.
Only gun I ever carry loaded
is right here in my holster.
You guys are shooting
all of these on Sunday?
Yes, sir, we are.
Every damn one of 'em.
- You should come.
- No, I can't.
Well, I'm buyin'
the assault rifle on Friday.
I think it'd be good to have
a firearm around
for the protection, you know?
For home protection?
You need one of these
for home protection?
From what, a bear?
We do live in uncertain times,
Mr. Bell.
Liam, my son is right there.
I don't feel comfortable
with you
having this in the house.
I'm also buyin' a trigger lock
and a locking gun case.
WINSLOW:
Safe as rain, Mr. Bell,
I guaran-damn-tee it.
Hey, I'm gonna step out
for a smoke.
You guys cool?
Yeah.
Awesome.
So you buy and sell
these things?
I mean you got a shitload
of guns.
You interested in purchasin'
a firearm or sellin' them,
- for that matter.
- No, no.
Well--
It's my card, as they say.
Got all my complete
contact information on there.
All that pertinent information
is located right there
in front of the card.
And on the back of the card.
That there's a picture
of an M1 Abrams tank.
I know.
Give me a call if you change
your mind, Mr. Bell.
I'd be here within the hour
with guns in hand.
Or cash to buy
if you're sellin'.
Okay.
What about background checks?
What about 'em?
Hey, I also carry about
10 grand in cash
at all times for that
more discreet customer.
I do have some very important
business to discuss
- with my compatriot Liam.
- Mmhmm.
You'll excuse me Mr. Bell.
I'll talk to you later.
You got my card,
you can give a call
if you change your mind.
Okay.
What do want to do, bud?
Yeah.
Oh, look at this one,
that's a goat.
- Do you see him?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
"And Prince Ernest knew
what he must do.
Climb to the top
of Midnight Mountain."
That is it for tonight.
- Time for bed, okay?
- Okay.
Here, lay down
and get all covered up.
Alright, got your dinosaur.
- Good?
- Yeah.
Alright.
Love you, buddy.
Goodnight, dad.
Love you.
Love you more than ice cream.
More than birthday cake
ice cream?
Yeah.
Alright, goodnight,
go to sleep.
Get your backpack, James.
Don't leave it out here.
Go on inside
and put it your room.
- Hey.
Did you guys have
a good weekend?
Yeah.
Good, I'm glad.
Sorry, we're late.
That's okay.
It's--
- Is my mom still here?
- No.
What was she doing here?
She was helping me pack.
Pack, for what?
Come on inside, Grey,
we need to talk.
Grey, close the door.
James, go to your room, honey.
Mommy wants to talk to daddy
in private for a minute, okay?
So what's going on?
- We're moving, Grey.
- Oh, okay.
Um, you need my help
moving stuff or--
It's California.
My job had a management opening
in San Pedro, I applied,
I was a perfect candidate,
and I got the job.
Okay, it's a good job,
it's a huge salary increase,
and they'll help pay for us
to relocate.
I can finally take James
to Disneyland.
I was gonna take James
No, you weren't, Grey.
You've been stringing him along
for two years now.
Putting pennies in a jar?
Are you for real?
He knows you're broke, Grey.
He's not stupid, okay?
He knows.
I'm looking for another job.
Stop it, okay?
Just stop!
You're not looking
for a better job,
you're not taking him
to Disneyland.
You're breaking his heart
and he loves you.
Okay, I don't wanna fight
about this anymore.
We're workin'
on our book together.
As soon as it's done,
then we're gonna sell it,
- and I'm gonna--
- Your book?
- Your-- your stupid ogre book?
- Yes, our--
The one that you
you've been working on
- since he was born?
- Yeah--
- That book?
- Yes, that book.
We're workin' on it together--
And as soon as it's finished,
we're gonna sell it.
Grey, just stop and listen
to yourself, okay?
I can't wait for you anymore.
Grey, I have waited for you
for almost two years.
I have sat here day after day
and night after night,
watching you break
our son's heart
by being a failure
who can't even afford
to take care of his family.
Look at you!
You can't even take care
of yourself!
And I've given up on you, Grey.
I have finally realized that
this is who you are.
I am sorry, but we are moving
and we're never coming back.
I told you that I'm lookin'
for another job.
I'm gonna figure something out,
okay?
I can start paying more towards
his daycare if that helps.
It's too late, Grey.
Are you taking your meds?
No, I-- I can't afford 'em.
You can't afford them?
Tell me, Grey,
what can you afford, huh?
What can Mr. Greyson Bell,
fabulous artist, afford?
I'll be fine.
I just have to make it
through a couple of weeks.
MARILYN:
A couple of weeks?
Didn't you say
a couple of weeks last week?
And this week,
and then next paycheck,
and next month?
What about now?
I'll start paying child support.
- Is that what you want?
- I don't want child support!
I don't want anything from you,
I never have.
All I wanted was you
to be a man, and a father,
and to provide for his son!
MARILYN:
I wanted you.
I'm trying.
No, you're not!
Don't you dare say that!
I don't you dare put this on me!
MARILYN:
This is on you, Grey, you!
This is who you are, this is all
you'll ever amount to.
Are you happy?
Are you fuckin' happy?
Okay, I said it.
- I can't--
- No.
Yeah, well, neither am I.
Why are you looking
at your phone?
It's not like you've paid
your bill in months,
you don't even have service!
This is exactly the kind of shit
that I'm talking about!
You can't just go on pretending
everything's okay
like nobody notices.
Please.
Please, don't take my son away.
Please, he's the only good thing
I have left in my life, please.
Please, don't take him away.
No, we're moving to California,
you can come visit him there.
I can't afford that.
Then get a better job!
I'll get an attorney.
You can't even afford
to feed your son
and you're threatening me
with an attorney!
Go to hell, Grey!
He deserves a better father
than you.
Don't say that!
JAMES:
Daddy, stop, don't hurt mommy.
MARILYN:
Grey, please go away.
Don't ever, ever come back.
Just go.
Go!
GREYSON:
Yes, I understand that
it's closed on the weekend,
but this is an emergency.
Yes.
Well, how much would that cost?
Wait--
It costs how much to--
to file in court on Monday?
No, I--
No, I don't have any money.
I don't know what else to do,
please, I need help.
She's gonna take my son.
Hey, Mr. Bell.
How you doin' this fine evenin'?
Where's my partner in crime?
My dear friend and colleague
Mr. Brady,
where's he at tonight?
Oh man, we had a hell
of a time shootin' today.
It's a damn shame
you couldn't make it.
He's with Janice.
WINSLOW:
No shit.
Well, he is quite
the ladies' man.
As I'm sure you are, too,
Mr. Bell,
speakin' of the ladies.
You can almost fit
this little bastard
in your boot.
Check that out.
That's pretty good convenient.
Hmm.
What about one like yours?
My 9 mil?
It's got some decent
stoppin' power in this one.
I got a couple in my selection
right now
if you're interested.
Can I see it?
Have a hand at it.
Use two hands,
you'd be more accurate.
There you go.
Wanna close that left eye,
sight that sucker.
Uh-huh.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Do you have more bullets
for these?
WINSLOW:
Hell yeah, I got some out
in my truck right now.
I can get you some ammo
for that HK.
Enough rounds for that bad boy
to take you
right through the apocalypse,
reliable.
Cash is okay?
WINSLOW:
Cash is legal currency,
Mr. Bell.
Okay.
I want one like this,
and some bullets for it,
and bullets for the--
the one that Liam got.
We're going shooting.
No shit!
Well, fuck it, hey.
I'll go get some ammo
out of my truck right now.
You sit tight.
You know, Mr. Bell,
I do gotta ask though,
you sure this is a good idea?
You got enough cash for this
here transaction you know,
'cause I have been led
to believe that times
are kinda tough
and cash ain't flowin'
so well anymore.
I don't have any money,
but you do and I need it.
I'm taking my son to Disneyland.
Oh, Mr. Bell.
No, just wait a minute.
I don't actually ha--
-
You're broken, daddy.
You're right, son.
Grey.
Are you okay?
Are you sick?
No.
I can hear the wizard.
Dude, answer your phone!
Putting pennies in a jar?
Are you for real?
He knows you're broke, Grey.
He's not stupid, okay?
You're breaking his heart
and he loves you.
You're not looking
for a better job.
You're not taking him
to Disneyland.
Sometimes I can't even stand
to look at you.
The world
doesn't owe you anything.
It doesn't owe you shit.
Stand up and be a man
for God's sake!
BARNES:
Grey, you fuckin' freak!
Pick up the fuckin' phone!
I got six calls on hold!
I can't wait for you anymore.
You're not taking him
to Disneyland.
BARNES:
No.
No, ma'am, I'm -- I'm sorry.
Hold on.
This is who you are.
You can't even take care
of yourself!
I am sorry, but we are moving
and we're never coming back.
Grey!
God, fuck this!
Did you take the money, daddy?
We're not going to Disneyland,
are we?
James?
Dad.
Buddy.
It's too late, Grey.
He needs more than eggs, Grey.
You're breaking his heart.
I'm trying, honey.
No, you're not!
All I wanted was you
to be a man, and a father,
and to provide for his son!
Go to hell, Grey!
He deserves a better father
than you.
I can fix this.
I'm not an ogre!
Get out of the way, Barnes.
Dude, you need to stop
whatever the fuck you're doin'!
I mean it.
What the fuck, man,
just answer your phone, please.
Sorry for the hold,
we're a little short-staffed
at the moment, ma'am.
ERIC:
I need a raise today.
I'm taking my son to Disneyland.
Grey, I'm on the phone.
Hey, can I call you back again?
Yeah.
Alright.
Hey, thanks.
You know what?
Why don't you have a seat?
BARNES:
Hashtag gorgeous.
- Oh.
- JAMES: It's red.
- Looks like Shrek's--
- Yeah, it is.
JIM:
Looks like Shrek's dick.
BRODY:
Oh my God, he is so full, man.
- BARNES: My name's Zoey.
- JIM: Oh, oh.
I like coffee and suckin' dick.
BRODY:
Shouldn't it be green
if it's Shrek's dick?
What are you doing?
Oof, mind your own business,
Zoey.
This is Grey's!
Yeah, I know.
So it's his personal book
and you have no right to it!
Aw, you seem to know
so much about it.
Get the fuck out of my way!
Oh, come on!
Just talk to me.
It's a children's book
he's writing with his son,
you fucking asshole!
You'd know.
What the fuck
is that supposed to mean?
Come on, Zoey, just let it up.
- Everybody knows.
- Everybody knows what?
That we went to coffee?
So fucking what?
And that you've been fuckin'
him.
- Fuck you!
-
You already did that.
Come on, Zoey,
like why can't
you just give me
another chance?
- I need a raise today.
- Hmm.
So I can take my son
to Disneyland,
so I can be a better dad,
so my wife won't leave me.
I thought you were divorced.
What's your problem?
I do a good job.
I never call in sick.
I answer all my calls.
Why can't you just pay me
what I'm worth?
So what if I fucking am?
Oh, you fuckin' suck his dick
on the first date, too, Zoe--
I was fucking drunk!
Oh, you really weren't
that drunk.
Just fuck you!
What's he got that
I don't have, huh?
Fuck you!
You already did that,
sweetheart.
I like him!
And he likes me
and that's all I want.
Oh, come back.
What's he have
that I don't have?
An ogre dick?
All that fucking matters to me
is to be a good father
and you won't let me do that.
Why don't you just pay me
what I'm worth?
I think you should clean out
your desk, Grey.
- We're done here.
- No, no.
- You give me a raise.
- We're done here.
You give me a raise, today.
Hey, you gotta get out there
right now.
Barnes is just flippin' out.
About what?
I don't know
but Zoey has Grey's book.
Tell me how to help you, please.
- Please.
-
He ruined it.
Just-- just tell me
what happened?
- He ruined it.
- It's okay.
Hey, take a deep breath, okay?
Come on now,
just take a deep breath.
Are you alright?
Can I have my book, please?
No, no.
No.
GREYSON:
Zoey.
I'm so sorry.
No.
Loser.
You're all alone.
No.
There is no Grey.
Do it.
Do it, Grey.
Why?
You ruined it!
You ruined everything.
I thought you were different
and you're just like them.
Grey, I didn't, please.
Don't, you're scaring me.
It was my one chance
and you ruined it.
And now I have nothing.
Grey, I'm sorry.
I didn't do it, I promise.
- Please, stop.
- And you.
Fuck you!
Why can't you just pay me
what I'm worth?
Why can't you just pay people
what they need to live?
Look at me.
Look at this.
I'm fuckin' dying here.
You made me break my promise
to my son.
There's no food.
He doesn't like eggs.
And it's your fault.
- Grey, please, don't--
- You're just like them.
Please-- please, no, stop it.
- You're just like all of them.
- Stop it, you're scaring me.
You're in on it
like all of them.
You're all in on it!
All of you!
Grey, please.
There's no food.
He doesn't like eggs.
He doesn't like--
Do it.
Do it, Grey.
ERIC:
Kate.
- Kate!
- KATE: Yes.
ERIC:
Why don't you call the police,
huh?
No, please!
He doesn't mean it,
he's not like that, please,
he just needs a chance, please.
Guys, get back to work.
- Please, don't.
- Zoey.
- Don't.
- Come on, bitch.
- Leave him alone!
BRODY:
Run!
ZOEY:
Grey, no!