(gentle music)
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
- [Linda] Do you mind if
I ask about your father?
- Oh, yeah, he lives on the
north end of town by himself.
I haven't seen him in over a year though.
(background chatter)
- I know it must be hard.
- Why would I want to
see the devil himself?
- He's not the devil. He's your dad?
- Well he sure seems a lot like the devil.
I didn't ask for him to
push me around as a kid.
I didn't ask for him to hit my mom
and scream and cuss at me.
I'm, I'm sorry. I shouldn't have yelled.
- It's okay.
I never told you about my father, have I?
- No, you haven't.
- Daniel, tHere's a reason
why I've never said a
word about my father.
- You never told me how you got that.
- My father was abusive, also.
He would cuss at me and push me down.
When I was about 10 years old
I came home from school one day
to see my dad screaming at my mom.
He's dropping every cuss word imaginable.
He had her pinned up
against the wall in tears.
He was choking her.
I was so angry.
I threw my bag on the
ground and I ran to my dad.
I jumped on his back to
try to get him off my mom.
I was so angry.
I just wanted to protect my mom
but it was clearly no use.
He grabbed me and threw me down.
My face caught the corner of the table
and it cut it clean open.
I was so angry though.
I stood up right there
with blood everywhere.
I just wanted to protect her.
My dad started walking towards me again.
My mom stepped between us.
He struck her right in the face,
turned, walked right out the door.
I never saw him again.
- Melinda, I am so sorry.
- I know as much as I hate
my father for what he did,
I can't but wonder where he is today.
Even if he's okay.
I honestly don't even know if he's alive.
I gotta get to work.
- With all this work
are you going to be able to keep up
during the fall semester?
- I'm not sure I'm going to be taking any.
- What do you mean?
- It's a long story. I'll tell you later.
- It's okay.
Will you at least be
at Bible study tonight?
- I don't think so. I have
somewhere I need to be.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Thanks for meeting me again.
Same time next week?
- I wouldn't miss it.
(both laugh quietly)
(Daniel sighs)
- I'll beat you to the
tip one of these days.
(knocking on door)
- Daniel.
- Hi dad.
- Hey.
I'm sorry, come on in.
Can I get you something to drink?
- Err, no, thank you but
thanks for the offer.
- [Daniel's Dad] Okay, all right.
Um, do you want a chair?
- Thank you.
- [Daniel's Dad] So,
er, how have you been?
- Um, I've been fine.
How have you been?
(sad music)
- I'm doing all right.
- How come I don't hear from you anymore?
- What do you mean?
- I don't hear from you anymore, dad.
- You don't come around to see me.
- Well, I shouldn't have to.
- Look, it's not the best situation.
- When is it ever?
You know, you know what's really sad, dad?
I'm having a hard time remembering
the good times we have.
- Son, listen, there was
something I was wanting,
wanting to talk you about.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I can't.
(door slams)
- Sweetheart. You need to
take some time to rest.
- Unfortunately, taking
time off of work to rest
is not the best idea for me.
There's nowhere else for me to go.
You raised me half my life,
the least I can do has
help support you now.
- I don't want you worrying about me.
- Grandma, my worry for you
is what's keeping you alive.
My worry for you causes me to work
as much as I can to help you.
- You're worrying is not
what's keeping me alive.
You know what is.
- I'm thankful that God
is keeping you alive,
but the hospitals still
need to be paid for.
- Of course, but paid or
unpaid, God has a plan.
And if it's for me to go
home soon, well then...
- Grandma.
- You need to be willing
to follow God's plan,
whatever it is.
You've heard the doctors.
You know, they said I haven't long.
- Grandma, you can't...
- It's, since your grandfather died
God showed his love and mercy
for me by giving me you.
I don't, I don't want to
take away from your life.
I just, I want you to promise one thing.
I want you to be here when I pass.
I know the Lord will be with me,
but I want you here too.
- Does anyone know if Melinda
is going to make it tonight?
- As far as I know she isn't coming.
- She hasn't been able to
come for almost a month now.
Any news on her grandma?
- I haven't heard anything.
- From what I heard, not well.
- [Pastor[ I think we should Pray.
- [Daniel] I agree.
- Heavenly father, we all
pray for Melinda right now.
She's facing a lot with her grandmother.
Father, we want to help her out.
We just ask that you would show us
what you'd have us to do.
Lord, we just pray for
your will to be done.
We ask that you would show
Melinda what you'd have her,
whatever you ask of her,
show it, show her your will.
Guide her Lord.
Pray, Lord, your peace and
comfort and rest on her.
We ask your healing hand
on her grandmother, Becky.
Guide them, guide us all in
your mighty name, we pray. Amen.
- Oh please, Lord, not like this.
Lord, if it is your will
that I go home to you soon,
let it be so, but please don't take her.
- [Doctor] Hi Becky, it's
going to be all right
but we need to get you
back to your rook, okay?
- There's someone I need you to call.
- Hello.
I'll be right there.
- Guys. I need to go.
Melinda's in the hospital.
- Visiting her grandma?
- No. Well, she was, she got hit by a car
in the parking lot.
Sorry Daniel, I need to go.
- Are you Pastor David?
- Yes, is she okay?
- She'll live. A couple of
bruises and a concussion.
- Is she okay?
(sad music)
- Yes, she is lucky to be alive.
Her injuries could have
been much more severe
given the circumstances,
but she will never be able to walk again.
- Does she know?
- [Doctor] Yes.
- May we see her?
- I'll give you some time.
- Is she okay?
- Thank you.
- She's lucky to be alive.
- I heard what happened. I'm so sorry.
- Thank you guys for coming to see me.
- Look Melinda.
I know this must be difficult.
- You wanna know what's
going to be difficult?
I haven't been to study in a while
because I've been working.
I'm the only one paying for
my grandma's medical bills
and Medicare can't cover all of it.
- Why didn't you tell us we,
we could have helped you.
The church could have a fundraiser.
- I didn't want to have to do that.
- There's nothing wrong
with asking for help.
You need help.
- Now I have to go through
some physical therapy
to help me get used my
legs not functioning.
- Did they say how long
the therapy would last?
- Believe it or not only a few weeks.
That's including all
of the boring paperwork
and figuring out the housing situation.
(knocking on door)
- Daniel, come in.
What brings you the most here?
I was worried I might not
see for a while there.
- Um, I wanted to apologize.
I'm very angry with you,
but I realized something.
Last night God showed
me the value of life.
I almost lost my best friend.
- I heard what happened. I'm really sorry.
Here, why don't you have a chair.
- Thank you.
I wanted to come and talk and at least try
and if I'm being honest,
I don't want to try.
I want to walk out that door,
(sad music)
but I know if I do,
I won't be ever, be
able to forgive myself.
- Therefore do not be
anxious about tomorrow
for tomorrow will be anxious for itself.
Sufficient for the day is its own trouble.
Matthew 6:34.
- How did you know that?
(Dad sighs)
You just expect me to
believe that you changed.
- I know I can't expect you
to just believe my words.
I have to show you that I'm different.
I'm a new creation.
- How did this happen?
(sad music continues)
- Now that my son is a long story.
I met very sweet lady and
she helped point me to him.
- So you went on a date with a lady?
- No. Oh no.
Not a date.
- What was it then?
- you could say we're good friends, now.
- Dad, I'm, I'm speechless
and quite frankly, I find
this hard to believe.
- I know son that this is
completely out of the blue for you,
but I've been reading this
and it's absolutely incredible.
It's like every type of hardship,
every difficult situation in life.
It's like, there's an
answer for it in here.
- I, I just, I.
I'm sorry I have to think
and, and pray about this.
I hope you understand.
(door closes)
(background chatter)
Hey, it's good to see you.
- It's good to be back.
I figured you'd be here at our usual time.
- Really? How?
- What if I don't say.
(both laugh)
- Um, can I get you anything?
Coffee or something?
- Yeah. That'd be great if
you could get me my usual.
- Perfect.
- Thank you.
(phone vibrates)
Hey uncle Tom.
- Hi Melinda, how are you?
- Doing my best. Considering
the circumstances.
- I understand.
Your aunt and I have been praying for you.
- Thank you.
I really appreciate that.
- So, er, you're
messaging me about Daniel?
- Yeah. I just wanted your advice.
I have a few minutes before he
comes back with the coffees.
- Let me tell you something, Melinda.
There's nothing wrong with having
a good Christ centered
friendship with Daniel,
but if you want to take it a step further
then you need to let
the Lord lead the way.
- But what if he doesn't like
me, because of, you know...
- Remember what Isaiah
chapter 40 verse one says,
"But they who wait for the Lord
shall renew their strength.
They shall mount up wings like eagles.
They shall run and not be weary.
They shall walk and not faint."
Wait for the Lord, Melinda.
- Thank you Uncle Tom.
I got to go.
- Take care Melinda.
- They'll bring it up.
- It's nice to be back here.
- Well, it's nice having you back.
I've been getting really
lonely sitting here every week.
- Daniel, why?
(Daniel laughs)
- I can't, I can't explain it.
- Okay.
- Hey, so actually some of us
are meeting up at the church here
in a little bit.
I was about to head out there
myself when you showed up.
- Wait, why?
- Oh. To discuss ideas.
- Ideas?
- Yeah, ideas on how to pay
for your grandma Becky's bills.
- Ah, I don't even know what to say.
- Well, if you have any
ideas, we'd love to hear them.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Perfect.
- Can you give me a ride to the church?
- If your wheelchair can fit my car.
- Of course it'll fit.
- Ah, one of these days.
(calm music)
- Hey, glad to see you out and about.
- Ow, still a little sore.
- Oh, I'm, I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
I'm glad to be out.
I could only take so much
of that hospital food.
(all laugh)
- That's fair. I can safely
say we're all glad you're here.
Okay guys. I have a
visitor to join us today.
- Hello there.
- Hi grandma.
(grandma laughs)
- Hello, sweetheart.
Did your uncle Tom get hold of you?
- He did.
- That's great. It's good.
So I have some news for you.
It's hopefully good news.
- I could use some good news.
- Well, your hospital bills
and your physical therapy pills
have all been paid for.
- What?
Who paid?
- I haven't a clue,
but apparently the Lord
decided to help out.
- So now all we need to
do is focus on your bills?
- Exactly. Which is where the,
I hope it's good news, comes in.
- All right, I'm listening.
- Well, there's a, a
technique and a strategy.
Actually, it's a kind of
surgery that they can do
and if I go through with it,
it will put me on the road to recovery,
but it's a long shot.
- That's amazing.
(grandmother sigh heavily)
- Yes, but, well, it's
sort of experimental
and so Medicare won't pay for it.
Can't pay for it and it's very expensive.
I, er, I don't know.
I think perhaps it's just
time for me to go home.
- No, please don't say that.
- It's, what am I supposed to say?
I am, I am an old woman.
The point being that...
Well Pastor Dave has said the team,
that you need to work
together to raise the funds.
And well, I'm not going to go
through with this procedure
if it's going to put you in debt.
- So what you're saying is
in order for you to go
through with the procedure,
we have to come up with at least
a fair amount of the funds?
- Exactly.
- Please go through with the procedure.
- Sweetheart, I'm more than grateful
that Pastor David is going
to help raise the funds.
What I need you to do is trust the Lord.
- I love you Grandma.
- I love you too, sweetheart.
- So, now it's just
race against the clock.
- That's one way to put it.
- I forgot to ask her how
much we need to raise.
- Holy cow. That's a lot.
- Yes, it is.
Your grandma didn't
want to put you in debt.
If she were to go through
with the procedure,
you would be the one legally
responsible to carry the debt.
Which is why we need to raise the funds.
- How much time do we have?
- Not much. A few weeks at the most.
- Thank you guys for doing this.
I really appreciate it.
- You're our sister in Christ.
We need to be there for each other.
Let's get to work.
- So it's basically a
race against the clock
because she will not get the treatment
unless she knows she has all the money.
- She doesn't want to put Melinda in debt.
- Well, how come she can't
just get the treatment
and then you guys paid off and work at it
like you've been doing?
- Well, honestly, it's looking like
we're not even going to get
close to the amount we need.
Also, she's not even guaranteed
to survive the operation.
- How much money do you need?
- The operation itself
costs over 50 grand.
- Oh, my.
- Yeah.
We've started a GoFundMe in
hopes that people will donate.
Hopefully whoever paid off
Melinda's hospital bills
will help out again.
- Who paid off her bills?
- That's the thing. We don't know.
- Prayer.
- It's hard sometimes.
- But it's the answer, isn't it?
- Yeah.
We're doing a couple of
freewill donation events
at the church next week.
Hopefully that will at least
get some of the money we need.
- So what's a GoFundMe?
- Oh, it's a website where
people can go and donate money.
It's nice because we can
put it up on Facebook
and other social media sites.
- So you can share a website to Facebook?
(Daniel laughs)
- Nevermind dad.
- No, really.
I mean, I mean, I want to know,
is it like a miniature
version of the website
on Facebook inside there or...
(Daniel laughs)
- It's nice to be out.
Thank you for this.
- No problem.
Ho has it been trying to adjust?
If you don't mind me asking.
- It's been difficult.
I have a sudden urge to stand.
Legs won't move.
I can never be a famous athlete.
- Is that something you wanted to be?
- No, thankfully,
- Thankfully our lives here are temporary
and we shall one day be walking
in Heaven with the Lord.
(background chatter)
- I can't wait to walk again.
- Not only walk, but run.
- That's true.
- But as of right now, you
must trust in the Lord.
So, what do you think of Daniel?
(Melinda laughs)
(piano music)
♪ I want to know that You're near me ♪
♪ I want to feel Your presence over me ♪
♪ I want you to tell me
that You're with me ♪
♪ Always and forever ♪
- What do you want me to do Lord?
♪ Here with me ♪
- Hello Daniel.
- I hope I'm not disturbing you.
- Oh, well yes, but nevermind.
Come sit down.
Daniel, have I told you the story
about how Melinda helped a stranger?
- I don't believe so.
Since this is the first
time we've ever talked,
I've only seen you before.
- Of course, of course my
memory isn't what it used to be.
(both laugh)
Well, but, well,
the story is that we were in a store
and the clerk was trying to get something
off the top shelf for a customer
and he couldn't quite reach it.
So he went off to get
a ladder or something
and I turned my back for just a moment
to pick something off a shelf,
turned back and Melinda
was climbing the shelves
to the top shelf to get
the package for the clerk.
- [Daniel] How old was she?
- Oh, I don't know. Seven or eight.
(Daniel laughs)
But the point being Daniel
is that she's always had her
heart in the right place.
- Yes, she has.
- And she has a very tender heart, Daniel.
Don't break it.
- What do you mean?
- Well I see the way you look at her
and if you do end up together, I just,
I just want to make sure that
she'll be safe and protected.
- Is it that obvious?
- Oh, yes.
Now I'll tell you a secret.
I think she feels the same
way and I see it in her too
when she looks at you or talks about you,
the two of you together.
I mean, when you look at each other
and you talk about each other.
- [Daniel] You're going
to have to make a choice.
- Daniel, what are you talking about?
- Are you going to choose the cross?
(running footsteps)
- Get off her.
- Get off me child.
(sounds of struggle)
Fucking kill you.
(running footsteps)
(dramatic music continues)
(music intensifies)
- You've ruined everything.
I never wanted you.
I had hopes, I had dreams
and you ruined it all.
- No.
- You were a mistake.
- You are a mistake
- No.
- You ruined my life. You ruined it.
(distorted) You ruined my life.
(Melinda cries)
(Melinda pants)
(background chatter)
- Hey, are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm okay. Sorry I'm late.
I was trying to get out
of bed and I fell out
and needed to get help.
- Oh, oh I'm sorry.
- I should have been more careful.
(phone vibrates)
Hello?
I'll be right there.
- Is everything okay?
- Can you please take mt to the hospital?
- Yeah, let's go.
- [Becky] Hello sweetheart.
- Doctor, what's going on?
- Melinda, her condition
is dropping rapidly.
She may only have a few more days to live.
- I'm sorry it's come to this.
- Grandma, please take the treatment.
- Oh sweetheart,
I've been in such pain for so long
and now it's at such a point
the treatment probably
wouldn't help at all.
- Grandma, please.
- Sweetheart, sweetheart,
let God wipe away your tears.
- You're the only family
I have left, please.
- I'm not the only family you have left.
You have the greatest Father of all.
- Grandma, I haven't
seen my father in years.
My father is, he's gone.
- Not that father. Your heavenly father.
- Jesus came to Earth to save us from sin.
God sent his son Jesus to Earth
to be the ultimate sacrifice
to save us from his sin
so that we could someday
sit by God in Heaven.
- Grandma, please.
- It is well with my soul.
- [Daniel's Dad] How much
longer does she have?
- Maybe a couple of days at most.
- Well, I will definitely keep praying.
- Have you been praying?
- What?
- I just, I just, I'm just trying
to wrap my head around it Dad.
I've seen you following Christ
these past couple of weeks
and it's been amazing.
I just, I just don't understand.
- [Daniel's Dad] Son.
- For years, dad. For years you abused me.
You even hit mom a number of times.
If I'm being honest,
how can I forgive you?
(Daniel cries)
(Daniel's Dad sighs heavily)
- I abused you and your mom for years.
(Daniel's Dad cries)
I treated you horribly.
I Know that there is nothing I can say
or do can even show how much I'm sorry
but, I want you to know
I am so, so sorry.
I am sorry for everything I've done.
(music swells)
- I've seen Christ working through you
these past couple of
weeks and it's amazing.
(Daniel cries)
Thank you.
(sad music)
- Why God?
Why is this happening to me?
(Melinda sobs)
- [Daniel] Melinda.
Are you okay?
- Thanks.
- [Daniel] Melinda, what's going on here?
- I'll tell you what's going on.
God decides that he wants
to take my grandma away
and my ability to use my legs.
That's what He's doing.
- Melinda, I know it's hard.
- You have no idea.
- You're right, but I
know one thing for sure.
God has a plan.
- Are you guys okay? What's going on?
- I know what's for sure.
God is going to take my grandma away
and there is nothing, absolutely nothing
that I can do about it.
- You're right.
God is the only one that can do this
and you know this Melinda.
- He put me in this position.
- And why do you think he did that?
Until we submit to God.
Until we do things His way
we will forever be wandering.
(Melinda cries)
- I surrender Lord.
(moving music)
(Melinda laughs)
(music swells)
Oh my, what?
- Melinda you're walking.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh, I have to tell Jamie.
Oh my gosh, I have to tell my Grandma.
Oh my gosh.
(running footsteps)
- Err, I was her ride.
- I don't think she wants a ride.
(uplifting music)
- Praise Jesus.
(indistinct)
- Okay, Becky we need to...
- Hi, Dr. Walter.
(chart and pen clatter)
- Uh, you're standing.
- I am.
- Yes. That's, that's not possible.
- Anything's possible through Christ.
- Oh my gosh.
- I know. Caught me off guard, also.
- This can't be happening.
- God is good.
- All the time.
(background chatter)
(phone vibrates)
- Oh, sorry, one sec. I got to take this.
- Hello?
- [Doctor] Ready for another miracle.
- I'm getting another one?
- [Doctor] You're never
going to believe this,
but your grandma's surgery has
received the remaining funds
from an anonymous donor.
- What? Who paid?
- [Doctor] I have no clue. It
was from an anonymous donor.
Someone that paid your bills,
apparently he or she just goes by J.
- J?
- [Doctor] J. Anyway we can
begin as early as tonight.
Your grandma has even
said yes to the procedure.
She says, "God has provided the money."
- [Becky] Yeah.
- Okay. Let me come see her real quick.
Then I'm going to get a group of friends
to go to the church and pray.
- Hey guys, this is my father.
Is it okay if he joins us today?
- Absolutely. The more the merrier.
- Yeah, sent out an email
blast to the entire church.
We have a lot of people praying right now.
Right now is the most crucial moment.
- Just so it's out, I'm going
to be leaving in a minute.
I made a promise to my grandmother
that I'd be there for her.
- Let's pray.
- Let your will be done Lord.
- Amen.
- Hello.
(phone clatters)
- Melinda.
(dramatic music)
- [Voice] But they who wait upon the Lord
shall renew their strength.
They shall mount up
with wings like eagles.
They shall run and not be weary.
They shall walk and not faint.
(music builds)
- You ruined my life.
(Melinda cries)
- I'm not a mistake.
I'm a child of God.
Lord I submit to you.
I'm yours.
(Melinda cries)
(rain patters)
(thunder crashes)
(music swells)
I told you I would be there
for you when it was time,
but I failed.
(birds twitter)
I shouldn't have gone
to the church to pray.
I should have just come to see you first.
I'm sorry.
Daniel.
- Melinda.
- Daniel, I know.
- What?
- I know how you feel about me.
- Oh, oh, I, uh. I wasn't
actually gonna bring that up.
- Oh, sorry, that's...
- You're, you're, you're fine.
So how'd you know?
- My grandma told me.
- Your grandma told me that you liked me.
(both laugh)
- That little snitch.
- So, who paid for the
rest of the hospital bills?
- We don't know.
I thought it was my dad
cause he has the money,
but it wasn't.
- Well, if it wasn't your father
then who was it?
- [Melinda's Father] It was me.
- Dad?
(gentle piano music)
♪ I want to know that you're near me ♪
♪ I want to feel your presence over me ♪
♪ I want you to tell me
that you're with me ♪
♪ Always and forever ♪
♪ Be with me ♪
♪ Surround me with your presence ♪
♪ Surround me with your arms ♪
♪ Surround me with your faithfulness ♪
♪ Surround me with your grace ♪
♪ Be with me ♪
♪ Surround me with your presence ♪
♪ Surround me with your arms ♪
♪ Surround me with your faithfulness ♪
♪ Surround me with your grace ♪
♪ Surround me with your presence ♪
♪ Surround me with your arms ♪
♪ Surround me with your faithfulness ♪
♪ Surround me with your grace ♪
♪ Surround me ♪