Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
The ocean is Earth's life
support system.
No Ocean,
No Us.
My name is Sylvia Earle.
For most of my life,
I've had the joy of exploring
the sea,
studying the living systems
that make our lives possible.
But what I've seen in mylifetime is slipping away.
It's now a race against time
to find solutions.
Today, a new generation ofheroes are showing us what needs to be
done
to restore health to the ocean,
creating a perpetual planet
for generations to come.
Fantastic.
This is where I first fell inlove with the ocean as a kid.
It was here
that I first breathed air
underwater.
And for me,
it was transformative.
I thought,
“This is going to be so great,
I can get to see the fish
and watch them and see what they
do.”
And what happened was the fish
came over
and started looking at me.
I thought, “Wait a minute,
it's supposed to be
the other way round, right?”
Since I first breathed air under
water,
I've been a part of the greatestera of exploration
in the history of humankind.
I've lived underwater
for weeks at a time.
She has witnessed first-hand
parts of our planet
most could barely imagine.
I've helped design and build
submersibles
to explore further and deeper
than ever before.
For the first time,
a woman walks the seafloor
beyond 1,000 feet.
It's a pleasure
to introduce a scientist, an
engineer,
a teacher, and an explorer.
And founded organisations
to explore and protect the sea.
Her Deepness, Dr Sylvia Earle.
But this era of discovery
has been accompanied by immense
loss.
If we continue business as
usual,
we're in real trouble.
We used to think the ocean was
too vast
for humans to harm.
We were wrong.
We've squandered
the treasures of nature,
pushing the ocean
to the brink of collapse.
But I still have great hope.
Across the globe, a network ofscientists are building on my life's
mission -
to save the ocean.
For me, Sylvia Earle is an
inspiration.
We all are following in her
footsteps.
She's allowed for so many morepeople from my generation to move
forward
and advance their work.
Their pioneering work
has taken our knowledge
to new heights - and depths -
of understanding.
Now we know what previousgenerations could not know.
We're entering
another mass extinction,
we're losing species
at an alarming rate.
We are the scientists
who know what's going on
and it's our responsibility
to make people aware
for the sake of the planet
and our own future.
Together, they are creating
a global movement
and we all can be a part of it.
Protecting the ocean
as if our lives depend on it.
Because they do.
When I first began exploring,
I marvelled at the abundance oflife that thrives in healthy coral
reefs.
But today, coral reef systems
around the world are
disappearing.
This is about as bad as it gets.
It was like looking at the fae
of climate change. There it is.
Reefs are dying,
and this is evidence of it right
here.
If we don't act now,
coral reefs may be gone
by the end of the century.
Seen from space,
the Great Barrier Reef
is the largest living structure
on Earth.
The corals here are among
the most diverse in the world.
But in recent years,
the impacts of climate change
have wiped out up to 30%.
Coral Biologist Dr Emma Campwitnessed these tragic events first-hand.
I feel that I have aresponsibility to speak up for coral reefs
that's been my area
of passion and research
and do what I can
to protect and guard that
ecosystem.
Climate change
and other human activities
are destroying coral reefs
globally.
Warmer, more acidic, low oxygenseawater is threatening their very
existence.
Whilst we are rapidly changing
the environment,
we're, with that, learning howcorals can or cannot survive with that
change.
To help save what's left,
Emma and her team have set up
the first multispecies coral
nursery here
to restore coral abundance and
diversity.
Coral fragments are carefullytransplanted onto metal frames.
This has been really successful.
We've had, I think now, over
14,000
corals out planted in just under
a year.
This method of transplantingcoral cuttings has already been
adopted
on other reefs around the world.
The only long-term solution to
save corals
is mitigating climate change.
Until then,
these coral nurseries help buy
reefs time.
A few years ago, Emma and herteam made another extraordinary
breakthrough
in the fight to save coral
reefs.
They found corals thriving
in extreme conditions.
One area where we found corals
surviving,
where we wouldn't normally look,
was in mangrove lagoons.
It's unusual because theconditions are warmer, more acidic
and have lower oxygen.
That's what we're predicting tointensify under climate change.
Finding these corals
that have some enhanced
resilience
gives me some much-needed hope
that we can have at least somecorals into the future.
These ground-breakingdiscoveries are already being shared
with scientists around the
world.
Working together to future-proof
this precious ecosystem
for generations to come.
I want to be able to say to mychildren and the future generations
that I did everything that Icould to try to conserve these systems
and to try and motivate and
educate,
and encourage those around us,
to also conserve these
ecosystems,
so that they aren't lost,
so it wasn't a privilege
that just us were able to
experience.
Today, the impact of climatechange is being felt everywhere on
earth.
Nowhere is this more apparent
than in the frozen parts of the
planet.
Here in Antarctica,
melting ice is opening up
this once pristine environment,
exposing marine life
to unexpected forms of pollution
we're just beginning to
understand.
It's beautiful, isn't it,
just to listen to nature.
The more diverse the soundscape
is,
the more it tells us about its
health.
Bio-acoustician Prof MichelAndre has developed pioneering
technology,
unlocking the sound of the
ocean.
Revealing a vast soundscape oflife undetectable to human ears.
Light doesn't penetrate
more than a few metres below the
surface,
so the only way the inhabitants
of the sea have to communicate,
to orientate, to get
information,
is through sounds.
Whales produce these rumble
sounds,
similar to what you hear with an
elephant.
This very low frequency rumble.
Something like... "Brr."
And it allows these whales
to communicate at very long
distances,
sometimes hundreds of
kilometres.
But as Michel learned to listen
to these voices,
he also discovered
they are drowned out by human
noise.
Contaminating this channel of communication
with noise from human activity,
in particular shipping.
If we prevent them
from exchange information,
we condemn them to death.
In the last 50 years,
noise in most of the ocean
has doubled every decade.
Shipping, industrial fishing
and surveying for fossil fuel
has dramatically intensified.
And it's not just killing the
mammals.
10 years ago,
we made a shocking discovery.
It wasn't just large marine
mammals,
like whales and dolphins,
that were impacted by noise
pollution.
Thousands of invertebratespecies may suffer and die from it.
We were totally surprised,
we could not believe it.
You feel responsible not only
to demonstrate that there is an
effect
but to propose to society
a solution for that.
To tackle the impact of noise
pollution,
Michel has developed technology
that listens live
to the sounds of the sea.
This is the first time,
this is a new device,
it is a prototype that wespecially designed for this expedition
and this little baby is going torecord the sound of the Antarctic.
This autonomous buoy
transmits data in real time,
from one of the last places onEarth with zero noise pollution.
It comes with this bittersweet
feeling
that we might not be able to do
it again
in the future.
This technology will become apart of a global network
of listening stations around the
world.
Known as LIDO -
or Listen to the Deep Ocean -
it offers the first truly globalpicture of ocean noise and its effects.
The beauty of this technology
is that it is listening to the
ocean
24 hours a day, every day,
every month, every year.
The ability to listen isrevealing exactly where we must reduce
noise -
protecting vital habitats.
I hope that this listeningstation that we are developing
and deploying around the world
will help many people
to hear the message.
My feeling is not fear.
My feeling is, on the contrary,
I believe that what we are doing
is bringing a solution,
is bringing something that
the next generation will know
how to use.
This technology
that was born in the ocean
is now monitoring biodiversity
on the land,
revealing the impact of humanactivity on wildlife around the world.
Undersea noise pollution is
like a death of a thousand cuts.
But it's just one of manyproblems facing the ocean.
In my lifetime,
industrial fishing has
eliminated 90%
of many different species
of wild ocean animals.
Some of earth's most majesticcreatures are being pushed to extinction.
But with the right protection,
species can recover,
from the smallest squid and
shrimp,
to the biggest fish in the sea.
The first time I saw a whale
shark,
it was like a bus underwater
coming towards me and I was in
awe.
You almost feel insignificant
because of their sheer size.
And yet, these animals that aremassive and they've been around forever,
are endangered.
Marine Biologist Dr Brad Norman
and his colleagues
have helped develop technology
to monitor
this highly elusive giant of the
deep.
Their numbers have declined
by more than 50% over the last
75 years.
Driven to the brink ofextinction by humans
due to hunting and ship
collisions.
If we do nothing now,
there is a big risk
we're going to lose this species
forever.
This is not something
that I want to happen on my
watch.
Magellen, this is Shark Bay
Watch, over.
Yes, this is Magellen.
Go ahead, over.
We've got a sighting of a whaleshark off the north west corner.
Just keep an eye on him,
we'll be there as quick as we
can.
Like many threatened species,
in order to protect them,
we need to understand them.
We want to know
if climate change is having an
effect,
how it's going to affect theanimals in their movements.
To answer this vital question,
Brad and his team
are using electronic tags
to track whale shark movements
and monitor their behaviour.
Tagging the biggest fish in thesea is not that easy.
You have to be very calm.
The tag is clamped harmlessly
onto the dorsal fin.
This reveals unique insights
into what they're doing
when they're out of sight.
We've recorded whale sharks
moving along the WA coast
all the way north to Indonesia
and all the way south below
Perth.
Well, that's great, guys.
Well done. Perfect.
Along with tagging,
Brad and his team have alsodeveloped a pioneering photo monitoring
system.
The spots on the skin
of each whale shark are unique.
We can identify individuals
similar to a fingerprint in
humans.
By photographing the unique
pattern,
Brad can track the returnmigration of individuals.
Anyone with an underwater camera
can now play a part
in helping
to conserve whale sharks
globally.
By adapting an algorithm NASAuses to map stars in the night sky,
Brad and his colleagues
have produced a database
with over 75,000 sightings
from 54 countries.
To be able to break new ground
on something that was so big
and so amazing,
yet so little known,
it was a dream come true really.
And this star mapping technology
is also being adapted
to help other species
on the edge of extinction.
We need to keep learning,
and as technology is advancing,
we have so many more tools
to help our understanding
of whale sharks,
of their environment,
and ultimately,
how we're going to protect them.
Saving the ocean now depends
on scientists from all
disciplines
and nations working together.
We are fighting a battle on many
fronts.
And to really win,
we must keep exploring.
There's still so much about theocean that we have no idea about.
The deep ocean, we know less
about that
than we do about space.
Even today,
we've only mapped 15% of the
ocean.
The purpose of the exploration,
it's to acquire a better
knowledge,
understanding how it works,
how species interact,
discovering new species.
Exploring the unknown is now
more important than ever.
We cannot protect what we don't
know.
Marine Biologist Dr VreniHäussermann has dedicated her life
to exploring one of the lastwildernesses on earth.
CHILEAN FJORD REGION, PATAGONIA
We were the first to look at
everything,
trying to understand
what species are living there
and how they live together.
In these remote fjords in
Patagonia,
she's been tackling
one of the biggest challenges of
all -
the threat to Earth's
biodiversity.
Diving down there in the
darkness
the first couple of metres,
generally,
it's really green and dark.
And then,
you suddenly get into a clearer
area.
There are many secrets
hidden down there.
It's our responsibility
to explore what's down in the
ocean
and to show people what we find.
Using new robotic technology,
they've gone further and deeper.
Finding previously unknownspecies that have lived here for
millennia.
When we saw the corals for the
first time,
it was like
“What is that that looks like a
coral?
Why would a coral be in the cold
water?”
We don't find them in any otherplaces in the whole of Patagonia,
so it's really interesting,
it's a very special area.
Bright lights
make everything look just snowy.
So, it was really exciting
because nobody had known they
were there.
For a biologist to discover this
is the dream of your life.
Vreni's discoveries astonished
the world.
It led to the first
comprehensive field guide,
featuring over 500 fjord
species.
Vreni had uncovered a hiddenworld no-one knew existed.
This took 10 years of work
and brought together people
from 25 countries
and they all helped to describe
the species from Chilean
Patagonia,
which was a really big effort
because there was very little
in literature about these
species.
But as Vreni has continued
exploring,
she's also witnessed
a frightening transformation.
When I first arrived
in the fjord here in 2003,
there were only three small
salmon farms.
Within about 10 years,
they were popping up everywhere.
Pollution from salmon farms
and the impact of climate change
are having disastrousconsequences on this delicately balanced
ecosystem.
The changes were really serious.
We started being really worried
about the future of the fjord.
In recent years there have been
mass die offs everywhere,
including fish, jellyfish,
starfish, and even whales.
We saw a big coral mortality.
99% of the corals died off
and they haven't
recovered since then.
What is happening in Patagonia
is taking place everywhere.
Globally a species is lost
approximately every ten minutes.
This loss of biodiversity
matters to us all.
It's like a ball of threads,
where all the species are
connected.
If we start losing species
because they are going extinct,
we're kind of cutting the
threads
and that makes
the whole ball unstable.
The whole ecosystem
can break down
and we have really
no control over what happens.
Vreni's discoveries haverevealed the true value of life in the
fjords.
Helping her prove
to the Chilean government
how vital it is
to protect what's left.
The danger really here
is that we are losing species
that we don't even know yet.
We have to start
really understanding the
ecosystems
and trying to describe thediversity so that we can start to protect
it.
Because the diversity is asimportant as the climate for the planet.
There's no planet B,
no other planet
where there's so much life.
And if we destroy this planet,
we don't have more chances,
we need to do something now.
I've spent most of my lifeexploring the deepest parts of the ocean.
I've helped design and build
innovative technology
to go deeper and stay longer
under the sea.
Here we are,
more than a thousand feet down -
it's 304.2 metres down
and it's dark, it's wonderfully
dark.
The ocean below 100 metres or
so,
makes up 90% of all space
occupied by life on earth.
And yet most of it
is yet to be seen or explored.
To understand and care for theocean we must go deeper.
And also build new technology
enabling us to stay underwater
for longer.
Like space, this environment
is not made for men.
It's a world full of mystery.
Time underwater is a unique
gift.
Offering scientists an
opportunity
to monitor and protect
our rapidly vanishing world.
There was a dream,
to create a new scientific
observatory.
To have a better understanding
of the rules that drive the
ocean.
Explorer Ghislain Bardout
is leading a four-year
scientific expedition around the
world.
Using creative technology tomonitor the negative consequences
of climate change on marine
life.
We decided to sell our house.
We sold everything we had.
But we did it, we took the risk.
We just sailed from south to
north,
we did hundreds
and hundreds of dives.
Along their 50,000 mile journey,
they have dived
under the Arctic ice caps.
And collaborated
with over 40 international
scientists.
Their latest expedition
has brought them
to the remote waters
of the South Pacific.
Since a kid I have been inspired
by pioneers like Sylvia Earle
and their work
with underwater habitats.
Ghislain and his team
have designed a capsule
that allows them to no longer
count dives in hours, but days.
We had the idea to create
a new scientific observatory
adapted to our time.
The capsule's design
leaves no footprint on the ocean
floor,
so it can be placed
anywhere in the world.
No noise, no pollution.
With this approach,
you can get a betterunderstanding of the ocean,
of what's happening down there.
Staying underwater
for days at a time
has enabled the team
to monitor previously hidden
changes.
We could see the life of thereef which is like a town.
You can follow a fish
from where he wakes up
in the morning,
how they move away
and they disappear
for a few minutes or hours
and then they come back.
The chance to live underwater,
literally.
To spend day and night living
underwater with the fish,
it's not a common experience,
it's not an easy one also,
but it's incredibly rare and
rich.
These long-term observations
are already providing vital data
for a dozen
international research
institutions.
Ghislain hopes the capsule will
be used
throughout the world
to continue to monitor
the impact of climate change.
With the capsule programme
it's only the beginning.
I do believe that our
imagination
has to be continuouslyassociated with technologies
and that way,
we can create new tools
to have a modern understanding
of the ocean
and to preserve
not only the ocean but us.
To save the ocean,
we must keep exploring.
But for change to be permanent
we must pass our knowledge
on to this generation -
and the next.
We need to start with the
children
and hand on the knowledge
and all the children
need to be aware of the
situation
and the risk for their future,
so that they can help
to make the necessary changes.
I think it's important
that the new generation learn
from what's being done
and what needs
to be improved upon
and getting kids involved
in science and ocean protection.
Our future depends on ourability to capture hearts and minds.
Do you have a question
for Shannon the Shark,
or the amazing Dr Sylvia Earle?
What sort of animals have youseen underwater while diving?
Good question.
Well, I have seen sperm whales
come back to the surface
after they've been
thousands of feet down
and they still have
squid tentacles, like spaghetti.
If every one of us learns
to love and care for the sea,
we can win the battle
to save the ocean.
In Peru this ability
to ignite passion for the sea
is helping save
one of their most threatened
species.
I remember I was out in the
water,
just looking out in the blue.
And then all of a sudden,
one of the fishermen spots it.
Giant manta rays
for me are magical.
They are so powerful,
but they are so gentle.
They're just majestic.
Marine biologist KerstinForsberg has been studying these gentle
giants.
Reaching over 7 metres in
length,
they can tell us about
the health of the ocean as a
whole.
If you see a giant manta ray,
you know that it's coming there
because it's a healthy ecosystem
that it's feeding on.
But fishing and hunting
have put them at risk.
Giant mantas are a vulnerablespecies that's threatened worldwide
that has a population
that's decreasing up to 30%
globally
and in some places up to 80%.
Kerstin's mission is to find newways of protecting this vulnerable
species
by involving every member
of her local community.
It is about connecting people
to the species,
and connecting people to the
ocean.
Kerstin and her team work
with local fishermen
to find alternative income
through ecotourism.
And to value them
as living treasures.
They're worth far more
in the ocean alive
because people will come
and they will see them
and they will want more people,
more tourists to come in
and it will build
the whole ecotourism industry.
But, to make sure
changes are sustainable,
Kerstin is doing even more.
Raising awareness
with the next generation.
Everybody can make a difference.
Everybody,
starting from a two-year-old
kid.
Working with over 50 local
schools
and engaging with hundreds
of thousands of people
throughout Peru
Kerstin has empowered the nextgeneration to lead their own campaigns.
Her success has since inspired
other youth movements around the
world.
I tell all the kids that we work
with,
you don't have to be a biologist
or a conservationist to change
the world,
you can change the world
from whatever career or path
that you decide to take in life.
In a place where mantas wereonce hunted to near extinction,
Kerstin's showing
how real change can happen.
Today, it is now illegal to
capture,
sell or eat mantas in Peru.
Protect me!
Care for me!
For me, sharing knowledge
and working together is key.
We need to be all together.
Everybody wants to live
in a healthy planet.
Everybody can make a difference.
When I was a child,
most people thought the ocean
was too big to fail.
Now we know it is in trouble
and therefore, so are we.
Currently less than 10% is
protected.
But to stand a chance of saving
the blue heart of the planet -
we must protect at least 30%.
And there is a place in the
Indian Ocean
that is cause for hope.
The Seychelles is part
of a global network of ‘Hope
Spots'.
Created by the Non-ProfitOrganisation Mission Blue,
these are places critical
to the health of the ocean
that need protection and care.
- Angelique.
- Hi, Sylvia.
- How are you?
- I'm very well thank you.
- Good to see you.
I'm so glad you're here,
you're all champions.
Each 'Hope Spot' starts
with a champion, like Angelique
who has empowered everyone
from the grass roots up to take
action.
The Seychelles often sees itself
as a laboratory.
You can test whether
something would work,
and from there we can inspireothers to say it does work,
it's your turn to take action.
There are
some impressive projects here.
Today, a youth-led beach
clean-up
is collecting tonnes of trah
washed up
from all over the world.
Elsewhere fishermen
remove rubbish from the reefs.
Others have voluntarily
stopped fishing for 6 months.
Fishers who typically would havebeen taking out of the ocean,
they want to pilot for the very
first time
a temporary fish closure
and in fact will collect data
about the impact of a closure
to be able to inform policy.
And, particularly exciting for
me,
scientists are surveying
seagrass meadows
to calculate their role incapturing and storing carbon from the
atmosphere.
What's incredible is how
the whole country has taken
action -
including the president himself.
And it just shows you the amount
of areas that we have protected.
It's paradise.
You know, when I first came
here,
you were two years old.
Wow, wow.
It was 1964.
There was no protection
for the ocean, zero.
Zero protection.
But people thought
we didn't need protection.
Today 30% of the waterssurrounding the Seychelles are protected by
law -
ten years ahead of global
targets.
Time has come for us to act.
And you have been there,
we need to listen to you
and continue to listen
to the scientists around the
world.
The people of this small nation
are showing the world
how one action times ten,
times a thousand, times a
million,
makes change.
It's great to see that there are
still fish in large numbers
here.
And not just one species,
but at least a dozen in this one
area.
It's so beautiful.
It was nice weather.
I think I want to be
one of them.
Plenty of reason for hope.
We're diving in a 'Hope Spot'
after all.
The Seychelles is just one
of a growing number of 'Hope
Spots' -
130 so far.
Inspiring people around theplanet to use their power
to restore and protect
the blue heart of the planet.
One of the latest
is where I lived as a child
in Dunedin, Florida.
Thank you, thank you all of you.
You all have a key role
using your super powers
to see the recovery
and celebrate it.
We have to cut the ribbon,
right?
3,2,1.
Declaring this
as Florida Gulf coast 'Hope
Spot'
gives me special satisfaction
because this is
where for me it started.
There are 130 'Hope Spots'
now around the world
and all of them really matter.
Our fate and the oceans are one.
With every drop of water you
drink,
every breath you take
you are connected to the sea.
It's what makes
all life on earth possible.
Thanks to a global network ofscientists - innovating, educating and
exploring -
we know what we need to do.
Trying to actually
communicate the science
so that people understand
the value of these ecosystems
and what it means if we lose
them,
is so important.
Each and every one of us
can make a difference.
I call upon all of you to do
your part.
You could be an explorer -
discovering hidden worlds
before they are lost.
This capacity to listen to sound
and to explore the environment
is allowing us to get a little
bit closer
to understanding how it works
and how we can save it.
Or you can be an inventor -
building new technology
to explore the ocean.
It's going to take
innovative technology
and the biggest and bestscientists from around the world
to protect and save our oceans.
Or you can be the teacher
inspiring others
to make a difference.
For me it's not
just about exchanging knowledge
from peer to peer,
but it's really
about exchanging knowledge
from one generation
to the other.
Or you can be the one with hope
-
showing that anyone
can change everything.
Now, there's a chance -
and that's what I'm working flatout to achieve -
that in the future
they'll look back and say
thank you 21st century humans,
you did get it.
Together we can create
a perpetual planet.