(haunting music)
(suspenseful music)
"La la la la la la"
Neverland was a world
that every child dreamed about.
A land where mermaids swam
in the crystal-clear waters...
...of the lagoon, where boys
could shoot bows and arrows...
...and play pirates aboard
the Jolly Roger.
A land where every desire...
...every wish could be granted
to the boys by fairies.
No evil darkness
hung over Neverland.
The children were happy...
...and could be friends
till the end of time.
Sleep did not exist, rules
did not exist, and above all...
...there were no parents
to tell the little boys...
...what they should or
should not do.
This utopia, this world
was offered only...
...to the most special little boys.
Peter ruled the island
having been ordered...
...by a higher being to ensure
that the best children...
...were invited to stay
in Neverland forever.
This was Peter's gift to
grant the boys their wish...
...to never grow up.
With the promise that Peter...
...would be able to join the little
boys in Neverland for good.
Hm.
Oh.
But first he had
a mission to complete.
"La la la la la la"
So, I think
that it's time for you...
...to go to Netherland, Curly.
Hm?
What do you say?
(Peter chuckles)
(haunting music continues)
(suspenseful music)
(dark ominous music)
(circus patrons laughing)
(circus patrons chattering)
Come on, Mom!
It's about to start!
Hurry, hurry.
Hurry inside now.
(circus patrons cheering)
(dramatic music)
(circus patrons applauding)
(ominous music)
(Peter hushes)
(chilling music)
(ominous music)
(suspenseful music)
(circus patrons applauding)
Right. I'm going for a shower
and by the time I'm done...
...I want you upstairs
doing your teeth.
Come on.
(James groans)
(Roxy clicks tongue)
(clothes rustling)
(shower curtain rattling)
(metal screeches)
(water splashing)
(Peter chuckles)
(floor creaks)
Hey!
Wakey, wakey.
(Peter chuckles)
(James inhales deeply)
Wakey, wakey.
(James gasps)
Peekaboo.
Oh.
Oh, don't be frightened.
I, uh, I got lost down
here, and it's really cold.
Hm.
I lost my mummy.
- You lost your mum?
- Mm-hmm.
And I'm really scared,'cause it's,
it's really dark...
...and I don't want
my mummy to be mad at me.
(water splashing)
How did you get down there?
(Peter grunts)
Well, I was walking along,
and then I...
...I slipped and fell into darkness.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, silly me.
I'm not allowed
to talk to strangers.
I'll get Mummy.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're not strangers at all.
(Peter chuckles)
Today I caught you a balloon.
Don't you remember me?
From the circus. Mm-hmm.
- That was you?
- Mm-hmm.
Indeed, it was.
Hey, I guess that
means we're friends.
(Peter chuckles)
- Let me get Mum.
- Oh, no, no, no.
You'll make her mad.
We don't need two angry
mummies now, do we? Hm.
You're a bit old to
need your mum, aren't you?
(Peter hushes)
It's late.
We should go to bed.
I'm Peter.
It's nice to meet you.
Mm?
Mm-hmm.
(Peter chuckles)
(ominous music)
I'm James.
(Peter gasps)
James.
(Peter chuckles)
Hey, I have an idea.
You could...
No, no, actually, no.
- No, forget I said anything.
- What?
No, no, no.
- I don't think you're brave enough.
- I'm very brave.
Tell me.
(Peter chuckles)
Okay, come here.
(ominous music)
There's a place
where all the kids go...
...somewhere
I could take you if you like.
Home, it's a world of dreams.
You don't have bedtimes there.
Mm.
No more mummies.
I think you'd make
the perfect Lost Boy.
(Peter chuckles)
In Neverland you're
gonna have so much fun.
- No! No, he's not!
- No, don't take him.
He's my friend!
(groans)
Get off! No! No!
Give him to me!
(food thuds)
(wood clatters)
Go! Please go!
(wood clattering)
(Peter grunting)
Fucking bitch!
You...
(Peter grunts)
(James pants)
What is it?
Take this. Take the
phone, and you'll be fine.
You'll be fine.
I'll be back, okay?
(Roxy breathes heavily)
(curtain rattles)
(air whooshes)
(cleaver thuds)
(Roxy screams)
(dramatic music)
(foot thuds)
(Peter grunts)
I need to take you with me.
(James gasps)
(curtain rattles)
(knife clinks)
(Roxy grunts)
(body thuds)
(knife clinks)
(Peter groans)
(head thuds)
(both grunting)
(fist thuds)
(metal clattering)
(Peter groans)
(suspenseful music)
(knife clinks)
(Roxy grunts)
(metal clattering)
You ruin this for me?
Mm?
(Peter grunts)
(Roxy gurgles)
(objects clattering)
(metal clinking)
(Roxy groaning)
(Roxy screams)
(flesh squishing)
(chilling music)
(Roxy gags)
(body thuds)
(ominous music)
(Peter panting)
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Stay on the line.
I'm sending police to your location.
Aren't you a wonderful boy.
(James gasping)
Would you like to come
to Neverland with me now?
Hm?
(dramatic music)
What happened to
sharing the chores, guys?
That lasted about five minutes.
You were supposed
to sort this, John.
- Mom.
- One thing.
I asked you to do one thing
and you can't even do that.
Mum, can you not see that...
- ...I'm working right now?
- Yeah, you've had...
- ...ages to do that.
- Oh no, no.
Wendy, I need you to
take Michael to school.
Perkins are taking John...
- ...but they haven't got any space.
- Yeah, that's fine. Why not.
I don't need anyone to take me.
I've got my bike.
Yeah, which you
only got this morning.
Mum.
Oh, you can practice
riding around the block...
...before you even think about
riding to school. (car horn honks)
Right, that's me. I am off.
Mum, um, could I borrow
a fiver please?
I'll pay you back next week
when Dad gives me my weekly.
You say this every week,
I never see it.
- So, what-
- I asked you to do one chore.
No, absolutely not.
Goodness sake.
It's five pounds, Mum.
(door thuds)
I heard from your dad this morning.
Can you believe it?
I hope John's not expecting him
to make an effort this weekend.
(Mom chuckles)
He's more than likely
otherwise engaged.
Oof.
Dad said he'll get
me the drone I wanted.
Oh, now, Michael, you know
that's not gonna happen.
I told you, you're not old enough.
And those things are
really expensive.
I don't think your dad's gonna
fork out for that, do you?
Michael, you need to be ready.
I don't wanna be late again, okay?
Have a lovely day.
By the way, Wendy, this
came this morning from UCL.
Why are you opening my letters?
(Mom scoffs)
I thought you were really
looking forward to going.
No, I never said that.
That's what you said.
Is this because of this guy?
(Mom sighs)
Wendy, you gotta get your
head screwed on...
...or you'll end up just working
nine-to-five in some shit job.
Wow. Maybe that's what I want, so...
Fuck.
Shit.
Aw, you too.
You're just like your dad.
(door thuds)
(Mom sighs)
Michael!
- Michael!
- Aw, no.
(Wendy groans)
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Hold that.
I've got something to say to you.
- "Happy birthday to you"
- Stop!
- So annoying, stop!
"Happy birthday"
(Wendy groans)
- Michael!
- I hate you.
"Happy birthday to you"
- Aw, I love you.
Oh, new bike.
Very nice. From Mum?
Well, she's got a point, you know.
You don't be doing
that long journey...
...to school on
your new bike, do you?
I want to ride my bike.
You're not gonna make
it in time, are you?
Come on, I'll give you a lift.
Follow me this way.
Come on, come on.
We can do car karaoke.
Hurry up, you're gonna be late.
- Sorry.
- Okay?
I forgot your birthday.
Look, I'll, I'll take you out
for ice cream after school.
Yeah?
How about that?
Wanna go Brownies?
Brownies.
Come on.
It's your favorite.
Don't leave me hanging, otherwise
I'll just have to go all...
...by myself and
sit there like a loner.
- You are a loner.
- Oy!
I deserve that.
But for me, please?
Are you still going to London?
I'm just figuring it out.
Ah, you're so obsessed with him.
Michael.
Look one day you'll meet
someone that you'll really like...
...and you'll realize
that you need...
...to do certain
things to keep them.
But...
Look, Michael, we all need
to grow up at some point...
...and at some point
we need to move out...
...and get on with our adult lives.
It's nothing to be
angry about, okay?
I'm always gonna be your
annoying big sister.
(Wendy laughs)
Come on.
(upbeat music)
Just before school. sLet's go.
Woo, woo, woo!
Scoot, scoot, let's go!
"Runaway runaway runaway from you"
(bell ringing)
(car doors thudding)
All set?
I hate Mum for this.
- Everyone will think it's girly.
- Who cares? Screw them.
Hug.
- I'm not kissing you.
- Oh, all right. Okay.
- Where am I putting this?
- Over there next to the others.
Okay, are we still going out
for ice cream after school?
(Michael sighs)
Hi, Joey. Are you all right?
- You're late.
- I know, I know.
(ominous music)
(birds chirping)
"To die will be"
"An old folly"
"You got an angel"
"To die will be"
"An old folly"
"You got an angel"
(Peter coughs)
(Tinkerbell hums)
(water splashing)
It's time to collect.
(suspenseful music)
(bugs chirping)
(chilling music)
(door rumbling)
(door thuds)
(suspenseful music)
Oh, fuck.
- She's been asking where you are.
- Oh, fuck. I know, I know.
Wendy, the time.
I know, I'm sorry...
- ...it was my brother's birthday and I
- I didn't ask for your life story.
You're late, okay? Again.
One more time this week and I'm
gonna need to dock those wages.
The letter came today.
About me scheduling my gap year.
I thought my mum was gonna flip out.
Well, it's not her decision, is it?
If you wanna do your thing,
then do it.
If you wanna go into the
city with Ronnie, go for it.
Yeah?
What's that face?
He's completely ghosted me.
I don't know what's happening.
It's like we had this plan...
...and now he's not even
answering my calls.
- Well, how long's he aired you?
- Like a day.
But he was acting off
all about it before that.
I don't know what's happening.
It's like a switch in
his brain or something...
...about the whole thing.
Well, can't you just cancel
the gap year...
...and go to Uni instead?
Mia!
No, it's very official.
Well, me and the girls are
doing a glamping trip tonight...
...if you girls wanna come.
Jamie's coming.
The phone.
(phone ringing)
For God's sake.
(ominous music)
(plastic rustling)
Aye, we're closed.
(ominous music continues)
(bear squeaks)
(suspenseful music)
(eerie music)
(sighs) You're such a pretty boy.
Would you like to come to
Neverland with me, hmm?
(ominous music)
Hi.
I'm Peter.
Mate, were closed!
You hearing me?
(chilling music)
(dramatic music)
(gasps) Freak!
You're gonna pay for that.
(Peter exhales)
(knife thuds)
(dramatic music)
(body thuds)
(knife clinks)
(sinister music)
(door dings)
(birds chirping)
(hand pats)
- So, your birthday, yeah?
- Uh-huh.
But you've not kissed a
girl and how old are you now?
Carl, fuck off.
This is our table.
Also, get your mum to
check your hair.
It's infested with
knits and it's gross.
- I think this is yours.
- Fuck off.
He's so pathetic.
How about if he does it
again, we'll get some payback.
Here you go.
You wanna go to the cinema
this weekend?
Yes.
(bell rings)
(dramatic music)
(Wendy yelps)
Ronnie!
What the fuck? Where have you been?
- [Ronnie] Yeah, sorry.
- I've been calling you.
[Ronnie] I, I, I've been busy.
Busy what?
Why have you been ignoring me?
[Ronnie] No.
(ominous music)
(sinister music)
No. Look, I, I'm not ignoring you.
Well, you are, so...
I've just been thinking, okay?
About moving to the city.
And I think I'm gonna stay.
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
But you pressured me.
- I pressured you.
- Yes...
...and I got caught
up in your excitement.
- I didn't know-
- Ronnie!
Hey buddy. Are you okay?
I'm sorry, okay?
(bike rattling)
(birds chirping)
(ominous music)
(dark music)
(suspenseful music)
(bike thuds)
(Michael shrieks)
(Michael breathes heavily)
(suspenseful music)
(sinister music)
(bike wheel ticking)
(grass rustling)
(sinister music continues)
(dramatic music)
[Peter] You need to come with me.
Get up!
(dramatic music continues)
[Michael] Help!
Come on!
(both grunting)
(dramatic music continues)
(door thuds)
Is he in detention...
- ...or something?
- I've already told you...
...he's not marked down
for being in detention.
What time should you
have picked him up?
[Wendy] (chuckles) Well,
I was there on time, I...
[Receptionist] I can
call his tutor for you...
...and see whether he's in any
after-school activities.
[Wendy] Yes, please.
(engine rumbling)
(suspenseful music)
(crickets chirping)
(dog barks)
(door clicks)
[Michael] Who, who are you?
I'm Peter.
(eerie music)
(suspenseful music)
Peter Pan.
Oh, don't be frightened.
I'm just a big ol'teddy bear.
My mother, she used to
do terrible things to me.
And when she would do
things to make me upset,
I'd close my eyes.
Can you close your eyes, Michael?
Hm?
Close them.
(sinister music)
Oh, good boy.
And I would dream of this
magical place.
Oh, it would be filled
with children our age...
...and we'd play all day
and all night long...
...and I wouldn't be scared anymore.
So when you get scared,
just think of that place...
...because it's real.
It's real, Michael.
(ominous music)
What I'm giving you for your
birthday is the greatest gift...
...a child could ever ask for.
(door clicks)
(door thuds)
(dramatic music)
[Officer] So there's
no problems at home.
[John] No, not at all. He's fine.
- He's just-
- [Mom] No, but he is a shy...
...shy, vulnerable little boy.
He wouldn't just run away,
you know that.
He's not off on some adventure.
Maybe he's just out
with his friends, Mum.
He hasn't got any fucking
friends, John.
Christ.
This is from the school.
(Mom exhales)
[Wendy] Oh, look.
(Mom cries)
[Mom] Oh, my God. There he is.
- [Wendy] I didn't see him.
- [Mom] How could you not see him?
Where did he go?
I mean, if you wasn't
actually there, Wendy.
It's okay.
[John] Wendy.
No, I was there,
I was just distracted.
What?
You were just, you were distracted?
What do you mean,
you were distracted?
- I can't, I can't do this.
- [Mom] Distracted?
I can't do this.
(Wendy pants)
(phone ringing)
I'll get it.
Hello?
(upbeat carnival music)
(ominous music)
Hello?
Who is it?
Is it Michael?
(Wendy gasps)
Hello?
(upbeat carnival music continues)
Who is this?
Who are you?
(flesh squishing)
[Peter] Don't worry about Michael.
Please. @@
I'm gonna take him to Neverland.
Who are you?
This isn't happening.
This is not happening.
You sick fuck.
(phone clatters)
(keys jingling)
(door clicks)
(door slams)
(Wendy gasps)
(sinister music)
(door squeaks)
(Peter breathing shakily)
[Peter] Hey, kid.
I can't sleep.
You awake?
I know you're awake.
You want to play a game?
Oh, a game's always fun, isn't it?
Let's see.
Oh, how about a good
old game of Marco Polo?
You know that game?
I'll go and hide,
and you have to find me.
Are you ready?
Close your eyes.
Count to 10.
One, two, three...
...four, five, six...
...seven, eight...
...nine, 10.
(eerie music)
(Michael breathing shakily)
[Michael] Marco.
[Peter] Polo.
(suspenseful music)
(Michael gasping)
(ominous music)
Marco.
[Peter] Polo.
(dramatic music)
(Michael gasping)
(foot tapping)
(glass clinking)
(Michael breathing shakily)
(wood rattling)
(glass shatters)
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
Marco.
(Michael breathes shakily)
(plastic rustling)
Polo!
(dramatic music)
(Peter coughs)
(Peter panting)
(sinister music)
Oh.
Oh, are these your friends?
He, he's my friend.
Joey.
Oh, Joey.
Oh. Would, would you like it
if I brought Joey here too?
No, no, no, no.
- I, I don't want him here.
- Oh, oh.
Oh, now, Michael, you're
a special, special boy.
I see great things for you,
hm, in a place where you...
...can be a little boy for
the rest of your existence.
Living the most incredible life.
Mm.
And I could let Joey come with you.
Hm.
(Peter coughs)
(upbeat carnival music)
You know, my mother used
to play this song to me...
...and the other
little boys at school.
What happened to your mother?
(sniffs) No, you don't
need to worry about her.
I won't let her touch my boys again.
(ominous music)
[Tiger] Is it true what
they're saying about-
Yeah.
We got the same call.
[Tiger] It's crazy.
They all thought he was
dead, but he's back.
Peter Pan.
They always said
he was out there...
...but everyone forgot
about it and moved on.
Oh, got to go T.
Mm.
Call you later?
(thunder rumbling)
I've looked and looked, I just...
...I just don't know
where to look next.
I've been calling around.
Look, Mum, why don't you go to bed?
Get some rest.
If anything happens to him...
...I'll never forgive myself.
(birds chirping)
Look, none of this is
your fault, okay?
- Seriously.
- No.
It is.
I wanna help bring him back.
Don't tell Mum.
I'll call in school and
say you're sick.
So where are we going?
I found an address of somebody
in Ashdown who experienced this...
...so I'm gonna see who they are...
...and see what they know.
(ominous music)
(engine rumbling)
(car door thuds)
(doorbell rings)
(birds chirping)
Incredibly sorry for
what you're going through.
Back then we'd leave
the doors unlocked...
...in our houses like there
was nothing to fear.
It was a safe community.
The police never found his,
his body after that...
...awful incident
with that boy's mother.
[Wendy] What happened if I may ask?
When Timmy went missing,
what do you remember?
(Steven sighs)
It was the autumn time.
In the evening, Timmy
asked if he could walk over...
...to his friend's house a few
streets down, and so we agreed.
Then it got later and later
and, uh, he didn't come home.
So I called the friend's home.
They told me that he had never
arrived in the first place.
So I, I was thinking,
where'd he been all that time...
...if he hadn't been there?
I mean, that's where
he said he was going.
Then...
Then you got the call.
(ominous music)
[Peter] I'm going to
take him to Netherland.
(door creaks)
He always told us he felt
like a little girl inside...
...and his mother believed him.
My Timmy was always such a,
a kind child.
I still can't after
all these years...
...bring myself to pack
this room away.
I still feel one day there'll
be a knock on the door...
...and my little Timmy
will come home.
I hope they find
your brother, Wendy.
(suspenseful music)
Really, I do.
(bell rings)
(children laughing)
(suspenseful music)
(birds chirping)
(engine rumbling)
Look at this.
Right on time.
(Peter chuckles)
Oh, come on, mate.
All right, kids, stay put.
Let me see if I can help this guy.
Sir, if you need a hand
moving it to the side.
Huh.
(ominous music)
Oh.
Oh, uh, these old vans,
you know, uh...
...always acting up and they're
completely unpredictable.
(driver grunts)
(knife thuds)
(body thuds)
(sinister music)
(water splashing)
(eerie music)
[Child] Hide.
(sinister music)
Well...
(ominous music)
(Peter breathes heavily)
Who wants to come to
Neverland with me, hm?
(Peter chuckles)
(children screaming)
(sinister music)
(door clicks)
(door thuds)
(glass rattling)
Oh.
Thank you.
I'm Tinkerbell.
He coughs a lot.
He isn't well, is he?
Oh, he's close to Neverland.
And this is his sign.
That's why he must act now to
take the children with him.
Before it's too late.
[Michael] How long have
you been here?
[Tinkerbell] I was
the first to be chosen.
He keeps you here, doesn't he?
(chuckles) He, he doesn't
keep me here.
So you can leave whenever
you want then.
He's not gonna let me go, is he?
Where Peter takes the
children is a place more special...
...and spectacular than
anyone could ever dream.
Why hasn't he taken you there then?
Because I'm different.
And I've always been different.
I'm a fairy.
(hand rustling)
One day I'll be a bigger
being, something magical...
...where I can be and
do whatever I like.
I just need to follow his guidance.
Same for you.
I'll be back soon.
My family.
They'll miss me...
...if I don't return.
I don't wanna be anywhere else.
I was happy.
(door clicks)
(door thuds)
(crickets chirping)
(door rattling)
What's wrong?
(John breathes heavily)
Is it Michael?
- [John] He-
- Is it Michael?
- Have you seen the news?
- No.
What is it? Where is he?
What's happening?
Sit down, sit down, sit down.
(chilling music)
Tell me.
Michael's friends.
They found their school bus...
...but they found
the kids in the woods.
(dramatic music)
It's okay.
[John] He's dead.
No, he's not. No.
John. John. It's okay.
You're okay.
Just breathe.
(door squeaks)
Mum?
(ominous music)
Come on.
He's gone.
No.
He isn't.
You can't say that.
I think you should go to your dad's.
(Wendy sniffles)
(ominous music)
(water splashing)
(sinister music)
(metal clatters)
(mumbles indistinctly)
(Peter cackles)
I'll send him to you tonight.
(Peter gasping)
(ominous music)
(dark music)
What are you doing?
Where do they really go?
You know where they go.
I told you.
You don't believe me? Hm?
You think I'm lying?
I always believe you.
(Peter grunts)
Yeah.
- Yes, you do.
- Yeah.
(Tinkerbell moans)
(Tinkerbell grunts)
Don't you ever fucking
question me again!
- Do you understand?
- Yes, I'm sorry!
(Tinkerbell cries)
I'm sorry.
(suspenseful music)
Don't.
Stay!
Don't go.
(suspenseful music continues)
(metal clangs)
What did I tell you about
making a fucking noise?
(object thuds)
- Honestly, fuck being around that.
- Thanks.
But no, it's okay.
I need to be there.
I just needed somewhere to...
...you know.
You done with these, girlies?
Right, I'm gonna hit the sack.
Joey.
Let's get you to bed.
'Night, Wendy.
I'll pray for Michael tonight.
Goodnight, ladies.
Look Wendy, if, if there's
anything we can do...
Thank you.
Right, there's, um, blankets
in the downstairs cupboard.
Do you know where they are, T?
Yeah, I'm gonna let Wendy
stay in my room tonight.
I don't mind staying on the sofa.
- Good girl.
- Right.
Sleep well.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Thanks, T.
His first victim, Timmy Carter...
...who was taken when Peter
was just 17 years old.
Reporting from the town of
Norwood where 11 children...
...were taken from their school
bus and brutally murdered.
This comes a day after a
local boy went missing.
The boy cannot be named,
but his family spoke...
...of receiving a haunting
phone call from a man.
(phone dings)
(Wendy sighs)
(fire crackling)
(footsteps tapping)
(hand thuds)
(window squeaks)
(curtain rustles)
(eerie music)
(suspenseful music)
(Peter hushes)
(knife thuds)
(flesh squishes)
(Tiger screams)
(bag rustles)
Phone charger.
- Get out!
- Get out of my house!
(Tiger screaming)
Get out of here!
(Miles shouts indistinctly)
Get out of my house!
Now! Now!
(indistinct screams)
(ominous music)
(Miles groans)
(loud thudding)
(indistinct screams)
(door creaks)
(Miles groans)
(sinister music)
(Miles coughs)
(dramatic music)
(knife thuds)
(sinister music)
(Wendy panting)
(bag rustling)
(door thuds)
(suspenseful music)
(sinister music)
(Peter breathes rapidly)
(ominous music)
(suspenseful music)
(Wendy breathes heavily)
Tiger, no.
No, no.
(door rattles)
(door thuds)
(Wendy gasps)
(dramatic music)
(Wendy shrieks)
Untie me.
(indistinct talking)
Okay.
- Okay.
- Where is he?
Where is he?
(dramatic music)
Go!
Go save Joey!
(dramatic music)
(Mel screams)
No!
(muffled screaming)
(sinister music)
(tape rustling)
(Mel gargling)
(Mel gags)
(door thuds)
(Wendy gasping)
(curtain rustling)
(car door rumbling)
(Joey groans)
(ominous music)
(body thuds)
(Wendy groans)
(ominous music)
(Wendy gags)
(engine revving)
(keys jingling)
(engine rumbling)
(Wendy groans)
(tense music)
(upbeat rock music)
(Peter cheers)
(Peter coughs)
(dramatic music)
(door rattling)
(Wendy breathes shakily)
(ominous music)
(Wendy moans)
(Wendy breathes shakily)
(door thuds)
(suspenseful music)
(door creaks)
(door thuds)
(suspenseful music continues)
(door rattling)
(Peter coughs)
(sinister music)
(sinister music continues)
(animal roars)
(door clicks)
(Joey gasps)
Oh...
...now you have a little friend.
(ominous music)
(Peter giggles)
There's no need to be frightened.
Oh!
Do you want to hear a story?
You're going to hurt us.
He's going to help you.
Just do as he says.
Tonight...
...one of you will...
...get to go to Neverland.
Oh.
No need to be afraid.
At Neverland,
oh, anything you can dream.
Oh,
once you accept my invitation...
...a wealth of dreams
will be given to you.
So...
...who wants to go first?
Eeny...
...meeny...
...miny...
...moe.
Hm.
Aren't you the lucky one?
You gotta say yes.
You won't hurt me?
Oh, no, of course not.
(suspenseful music)
Okay.
No.
No, don't.
Don't.
No!
(body thuds)
(Michael grunts)
You're lying.
You're lying to me.
Stop it.
Come on now, stop.
Get away from me.
I wanna go home.
I wanna go.
Don't fight against this,
Michael.
(ominous music)
(objects clattering)
- Yes. - Where do you think
you're going?
(Wendy panting)
(ominous music)
(Wendy gasps)
(silverware clinking)
(footsteps tapping)
(ominous music)
(Wendy panting)
(sinister music)
(ominous music)
Birthday.
- (Wendy gasps)
- Who are you?
Please.
Please (indistinct).
I, I just want my brother back.
Michael.
Is he down there?
I, I won't tell anybody.
Please.
(Wendy whimpers)
I just want him home.
(Wendy sniffles)
I'm begging you.
(Joey groans)
Please. Please.
(Wendy sniffles)
Let me go!
- Let me go!
- Please!
Go!
(door rattles)
(Joey groans)
Let me go, let me go.
(Tinkerbell breathes heavily)
(Wendy breathes heavily)
(ominous music)
Michael?
Michael!
(Wendy breathes heavily)
I thought you were dead.
It's okay.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Okay?
(Tinkerbell gasps)
(Peter coughs)
verything okay?
(Tinkerbell sniffles)
(Peter sighs)
Hm.
(lighter clicks)
You know what I'm doing
is for the best.
Right?
I can't stop.
See, it's my duty to send
the kids to Neverland...
...and protect them from this world.
What happens...
...in that room?
You know every
single person in my life...
...has left me at some point.
Well, not you.
Um.
(sniffles)
No, you're special.
Mm.
You're different from
the other women I've met.
Something greater than this world.
Oh, you'd never leave me.
So, why don't you
sit down and...
...have some more of your
magic pixie dust, hm?
(ominous music)
Good girl.
Tell me.
I think you know.
Why now?
What's gotten into you?
(phone buzzing)
(ominous music)
What the fuck is that?
(phone buzzes)
Who the fuck is in this house?
(Tinkerbell gasps)
What's going on here, Tinks?
Don't hurt the boys.
Hurt?
Hurt the boys?
What do you mean hurt them?
I'm saving them.
But who the fuck are
you to question me now?
After all I've done for you.
After all the care...
...I've given you
when no one else wanted you.
(Tinkerbell hums)
And society rejected you.
Where are they?
(Tinkerbell breathes shakily)
(Michael hyperventilating)
Michael, listen to me.
You have to trust me.
(door slams)
(ominous music)
He's coming.
You have to hide.
(sinister music)
(door thuds)
Where's Joey?
I heard someone in here.
Where are they?
Do you know...
...what happens to
little boys who lie...
...Michael?
They don't get to go to Neverland.
You know what happens instead?
They live the rest of
their lives...
...alone.
And in pain.
Now do you know how they
get to that place, Michael?
You see, I, I take my hands...
...and I put them around
their little throats...
...and like a snake
I squeeze as tight...
...as I possibly can till
their blood runs cold.
- Run!
- (object thuds)
Michael, run!
Go, go, go!
(door rattling)
(ominous music)
(Wendy shrieks)
No.
I can't let you go.
Tinkerbell, please.
Please.
Timmy?
(ominous music)
I know what happened to you.
(Tinkerbell gasps)
Your, your father misses you.
Huh.
Michael's family...
...misses him too.
You know...
...what's happening here.
It isn't right.
I, I just wanted to go home.
(ominous music)
(Tinkerbell shrieks)
(metal clinking)
(Wendy breathes heavily)
Hide.
- Go!
- Bitch!
(door thudding)
(Peter grunts)
(Tinkerbell whimpers)
Where is she?
(sinister music)
So, you're playing
with them now, huh?
(both breathing heavily)
Joey?
(Michael breathing shakily)
999, police
or ambulance, please?
You lied to me.
Lied?
The only ones who lied
to you are those outside.
For years...
...I begged and begged...
...to go home,
and you told me...
...they didn't want me.
Oh, Tinks.
(ominous music)
They don't see you for what you are.
See, you're meant for
more than this.
I told you one day you'd
fly with me to Neverland.
And you do this to me?
(Tinkerbell cries)
- You turn your back on me.
- Just stop!
It's time to stop.
(suspenseful music)
(metal clinking)
(Wendy whimpers)
(Wendy gasps)
Are you okay?
Come with me.
Come on.
Keep your phone on you.
We'll be tracking your location.
You know, I don't think you
deserve to go to Neverland.
You're just a failed Lost Boy.
Okay, come behind me.
I don't believe in Neverland.
Oh, well that's fine...
...because I never believed
in fairies anyway.
(both grunting)
(body thuds)
(glass shattering)
How dare you fucking betray me!
(bone crunches)
(Tinkerbell screams)
(body thuds)
Fuck with me once...
(foot thuds)
(Tinkerbell screams)
(bones crunching)
Well, you sure as hell
won't fuck with me again.
(knife thuds)
(Tinkerbell screams)
(bones crunching)
(blood splattering)
(Tinkerbell whimpers)
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay. Hold on.
(Wendy grunts)
Okay, it's okay.
Okay.
Okay, (indistinct).
Okay, okay.
(Wendy grunts)
Fuck.
(wood clacks)
(Wendy grunts)
(Wendy panting)
Listen...
...when you get out of here...
...you need to run as fast as
you can and do not look back...
...do you understand me?
- No matter what.
- Okay.
Okay, you need to send help here,
Joey.
- Yes, you understand?
- Okay.
Okay, I'm gonna get you out.
Quickly.
That's it.
Go!
Go! Go, go!
(ominous music)
(grass rustling)
(metal clattering)
(water dripping)
(ground rustling)
(Wendy gasps)
(suspenseful music)
(ominous music)
(metal clattering)
(Hook screams)
(Wendy screams)
Gotcha!
(knife thuds)
(Peter groans)
Where do you think you're going?
(foot thuds)
(sinister music)
(Wendy gasps)
(chain rattling)
(Wendy whimpers)
(ominous music)
Help me.
(Hook whimpers)
It's okay.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
(Hook whimpers)
(chain rattles)
I will get you!
I have to go.
(Wendy gasps)
(Hook whimpers)
I'm sorry!
I'll send help.
Help me!
(door squeaks)
(door thuds)
(dramatic music)
(Wendy screams)
(sinister music)
- Get back here!
- (Wendy screams)
(both groaning)
(mouth crunches)
(Wendy screams)
(sinister music)
(glass shattering)
(Wendy shrieks)
(knee thuds)
(glass shattering)
(body thuds)
Looks like you need
a plaster on that.
(Peter breathes heavily)
Don't give up.
(skull crunching)
(Tinkerbell screams)
(Wendy screams)
(Wendy cries)
(suspenseful music)
(Peter grunts)
(skull crunches)
Get on up!
(objects clattering)
(Wendy shrieks)
(needle thuds)
(sinister music)
You!
(muttering indistinctly)
I fucking know.
I know.
(Peter groans)
(Peter gasping)
(door thuds)
(glass crunches)
(Wendy shrieks)
(suspenseful music)
(Wendy gasps)
(door thuds)
(Peter grunts)
(Wendy whimpers)
(tape rustling)
(sinister music)
(wood cracking)
Girls don't get to go to Neverland.
(Peter grunts)
Marco.
(upbeat carnival music)
Polo.
(Wendy grunts)
(metal thuds)
Michael! Michael!
Wendy!
(ominous music)
I don't want to stop playing.
(door thuds)
Get away!
You!
It's time for you to
go to Neverland.
(Peter grunts)
(Peter groans)
(Wendy shrieks)
(dramatic music)
(Michael coughs)
(body thuds)
No!
(bat thuds)
(Wendy grunts)
(glass shattering)
(Wendy groans)
(objects clattering)
(Wendy panting)
(Wendy whimpers)
(blood spurting)
(sinister music)
(glass shattering)
(table thuds)
(Peter whimpers)
Don't hurt me.
(Peter crying)
Please, don't hurt me.
I'm just a little boy.
I'm just a little boy!
(Wendy yells)
(bat thuds)
(metal clattering)
(both groaning)
(eyes crunching)
(Wendy screams)
(object thuds)
(Wendy gasps)
(Michael screams)
Michael.
(object thuds)
(guts squishing)
Stop.
(Michael screams)
(Wendy breathes heavily)
(Peter grunts)
??
You ruined everything.
You can go to Neverland alone.
(Peter gurgling)
(ominous music)
(suspenseful music)
(Hook screams)
(guts squishing)
(Peter screams)
(sinister music)
(Wendy gasps)
(sirens wailing)
(light dramatic music)
Okay, make a wish!
Let's go!
Woo!
(everyone cheers)
Yay!
- Well done!
- Yes!
Happy birthday!
Right, onto the presents.
- I made you the icing-
- Yes!
- Did you make a wish?
- Oh, yeah.
- I've got that.
- Yeah, yeah.
You sure?
Did it come true?
(indistinct)
Ooh!
Drum roll for this one!
- It's a drone!
- Yay!
Is that the one you wanted?
- Yeah.
- How cool is that?
- Is that a camera there as well?
- Yeah, there's a camera.
We can go down to the beach
and we can fly it (indistinct).
??
Yeah.
That's sick.
- Birthday's a lot better this year?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Right.
I think it's time for my presents.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So, step aside.
Um, which one should we do next?
Let's do this one, which
is not even wrapped.
(laughing) Oh,
sorry, I was in a rush.
- Okay.
(phone ringing)
- Oh, uh...
- Do you wanna guess what it is?
I'll grab that, guys.
You go on and open it,
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Hello?
(upbeat carnival music)
(ominous music)
- Stop, ooh!
- Do you like'em?
Yeah.
(suspenseful music)
(indistinct talking)
(haunting music)
(suspenseful music)
(sinister music)
(sinister music continues)