[waves lapping]
[seagulls squawking]
[French narrator] Follow me
to the bottom of the sea.
To a world that is truly magnifique,
full of wonderful inhabitants,
like Monsieur SpongeBob SquarePants
in a land that is, how
do you say… subaquatic.
-[zapping] -[laughs]
♪ Welcome to Bikini Bottom ♪
♪ At the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Where everyday The skies are sunny blue ♪
♪ On the ocean floor You'll
find everything and more ♪
♪ And there's a place for me and you ♪
♪ Come on down Conch Street
'Cause I'd like you to meet ♪
♪ My sparkling long-time
friend Patrick Star ♪
-Hi! -♪ And if you don't mind getting wet ♪
♪ Ooh, you'll love the clarinet Of
the multi-limbed maestro Squidward ♪
[discordant clarinet note]
♪ Sandy Cheeks, Pearl
Mrs. Puff, Mr. Krabs ♪
♪ If you're hungry Then the
Krusty Krab's really fab ♪
♪ Long-time winner of patty of the year ♪
What am I going to do with
500 barrels of root beer?
[narrator] ♪ It's
another SpongeBob movie... ♪
[Plankton] All right! Hold
it right there, Frenchie.
This is my movie!
-Darken the skies! -[eerie music playing]
Okay, now, push in.
[music intensifies]
And… cue the title!
[electricity crackling]
All right, keep pushing in.
Closer… closer…
Can you hurry up? I haven't got all day!
Now stop! Ow! Too close!
You trying to kill me? This
is the beginning of my movie!
Anyway, ever since I was a little boy,
I've always dreamed of
taking over the world!
[yipping]
Tonight's the night, Spot,
after 25 years of trial and error.
-[Spot growls] -Yeah,
yeah, I know a lot of error.
[groans]
But tonight, Daddy has
a world domination plan
called Operation Success!
[laughs] It's got
success right in the name.
First, I steal the secret formula
to the famous Krabby Patty sandwich
and take over the Krusty
Krab from Mr. Krabs.
Then, with the restaurant,
I'll soon take over Bikini Bottom.
And after that, I'll
take over the whole world!
[evil music playing]
[giggles]
[maniacal laughter]
- [all] ♪ We love Krabby patties ♪
- [Plankton] Seven o'clock, closing time.
Everything's going according to plan.
Karen! Karen?
Karen!
[sinsongy] Computer wife,
where are you? I have my mask on!
Let's go! [echoes]
Hmm… [grumbles]
Now, where is she?
Not there. Not there either.
Aha! There she blows!
She's out with the Gal Pals again
and forgot all about my plan. Ugh.
Be a good boy, Spot.
-[Spot barks] -[cackles]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Karen] Here's your coffee, ladies.
[Sandy] Wanna go to the
movies with us tonight, Karen?
It's a sci-fi rom-com screwball thriller!
-Animated. -With songs.
Ah, sorry, Gal Pals,
but after Plankton fails to steal
the Krabby Patty secret formula
yet again tonight,
this supercomputer is going to unleash
a diabolical, all-consuming
world domination plan of my own!
That my nubby hubby will love. [laughs]
[laughing nervously]
You go, gadget girl.
Yeah, you're the real evil genius.
Phew! Good thing she's
doing it with Plankton
and not on her own or I'd
be scared for the world.
[Plankton] Karen!
-Karen! -[Karen sighs]
Speak of the little green devil.
[grunts] Karen, why are you
sitting around drinking coffee
when it's time for my plan to steal…
You know… [whispering] Operation Success.
Oh, you mean stealing
Krab's secret formula?
Karen! [grumbles]
Sure, I'll help you.
-[all laugh] -[Karen] Good bye, gals.
Gal Pals to the movies! Hee-yaw!
[heroic music playing]
[Plankton] Don't you get it?
This is a big night for me.
I'm finally gonna beat that idiot, Krabs!
[laughs] Do you see this, boyo?
We really tricked him
into thinking we left.
Hmm? Boyo?
Boyo?
Hmm.
SpongeBob!
Whoa! Sorry, Mr. Krabs!
I've been reading this
Super Psychiatrist comic book.
[grumbles]
And it says boundaries are very important.
And this…
Do you have to expose my plans like
that in front of your silly friends?
Really? You're worried about being exposed?
You walk around naked all the time.
Doesn't that seem a
little… personal and private?
Whaddya... Don't listen to funny books!
Look, SpongeBob, I'm gonna tell you a
rule that allows you to spy on, I-I mean,
observe folks for their own good.
It's called…
invasion of privacies.
Oh, invasion of privacies!
Aye, lad.
Now, you see, Plankton's been weaseling
his way into me office for months now.
Setting up a device to steal
me Krabby Patty secret formula
And I've been letting him think
he's gonna succeed this time.
But he's really just a
pitiful pathetic jerk!
Ugh.
A little harsh.
Who cares! Just watch.
…of my nakedness?
[grunts] Alright, let's go.
Let's get this show on the road.
Give me a lift and then you can go.
[Karen] So that's it?
I'm just a mechanical elevator
for your little green behind?
Oh, honey, don't sell yourself short.
You're the best mechanical elevator
a little green behind can have.
What? But you were just up there.
-[giggling] -Ugh, never mind.
Hup! You can roll away now.
[Karen gasps, grumbles]
From here on in, it's all me!
[suspenseful music playing]
[twangy spy music playing]
[chuckles]
♪ If you see me lurking outside
your door Better grab your belongings ♪
♪ And swim for shore ♪
♪ You're all a bunch of dumbos
Who don't know the score ♪
♪ Well, I went to college
And I'm rotten to the core ♪
♪ I'm a marine drifter
I'm a first-rate grifter ♪
♪ I could be a shape-shifter
If that's what's called for ♪
♪ I'm Plankton ♪
♪ Get out of my way, I'm Plankton ♪
♪ Better do as I say ♪
♪ You always blow it ♪
♪ Don't you know it? ♪
♪ Time for me to take the lead ♪
♪ If you listen to me For
just once in your life ♪
♪ Chances are we will succeed ♪
[spy music continues]
[Karen and Plankton] ♪ P-L-A-N-K-T-O-N ♪
♪ P-L-A-N-K-T-O-N ♪
♪ Plankton, Plankton, Plankton, Plankton ♪
♪ The secret formula
Is waiting for me here ♪
♪ And you bet your boots I'm gonna get it ♪
♪ If you underestimated my twisted brain ♪
♪ Then for sure you're gonna regret it ♪
♪ Taking over the world ♪
♪ Today's the day Sweet
victory is just a pull away ♪
♪ I'm Plankton, the biggest evil genius ♪
♪ I'm Plankton The smartest villain alive ♪
♪ I'm Plankton I'm gonna get what I want ♪
♪ I'm Plankton I'm taking over the world ♪
Pack your bags, secret formula.
You're coming home to a new papa.
Huh? What's this?
Some kind of invisible force field?
Sorry, Plankton! Bugs
like you belong outside.
[laughs] Say hi to the missus for me.
[Plankton screaming]
[groans, grunts]
[babbles loudly]
[sighs]
Honey, I'm home…
Wha?!
[all munching]
Huh?
Wait a minute, what
happened to my Chum Bucket?
What?
And what are all these
customers doing here?
[customers chomping]
[Plankton] Karen!
Oh, you're finally here.
Surprise!
What in Neptune's nostrils
have you done to my restaurant?
Well, I calculated that if everybody
actually ate at the Chum Bucket,
you wouldn't need the
Krabby Patty secret formula.
- So I gave the place a contemporary touch.
- Huh?
It's a fully modern, automated
backslash home-cooking fusion restaurant.
And it's open 24 hours with plans
to expand into the known universe.
And that's not all. Wait till you see this!
And what's this supposed to be?
It's chum.
I just added a little sugar, some pizzazz,
and now it tastes like world domination!
Where's the evil, Karen?
Where is the evil? I don't see it!
It's still fast food.
[in menacing voice] There's the evil.
[gulping]
Ahh! Amazing!
See? They love it!
I don't care if they marry it!
None of these cockamamie changes are
going to help me steal the secret formula.
Your idea hasn't worked for 25 years!
Why don't you try stealing
some brains for a change?
I don't need brains.
I need an assistant who listens to me!
Assistant? I thought we
were partners in crime!
Listen, if you don't try my idea
this time, then it's the last straw.
Think about it.
Okay, let me think about it.
Hmm.
Mmm.
Ugh!
Hmm…
Nope! I hate this and
I'm taking it all down!
Don't you dare!
Oh, I dare! [cackles]
I'm daring, Karen! Get a load of me!
I'm daring!
[laughs] Double dare! Triple dare!
[laughs]
Quadruple dare!
[grumbles]
Ooh! I hate this!
I don't like this!
[cackling]
Or this!
This or this!
And I hate this!
No!
[grumbles]
Alright, listen up!
I want everybody out of here right now!
[customers chewing]
[grunts]
[cackles]
Yeah! Yeah! Oh yeah!
Now you're listening!
[laughs]
[loud slurping]
Mmm. Wow, Plankton! This is delicious!
And I love the fire show!
Hotfoot it outta here!
Ooh!
[screaming] No! Whoa, whoa! Ah! Whoa!
-[screaming] -[sizzling]
Wow! [vocalizing in pain]
Ah… phew!
-[metal clashing] -[Karen
and Plankton argue loudly]
Huh?
Uh-oh, that sounds personal and private.
[Mr. Krabs] Psst, boyo.
Remember, they call it
invasion of privacies.
[laughs] Thank you, Mr. Krabs
-You're welcome! -[chuckles]
[Karen grumbles] Plankton!
You know what your problem is?
Are you even listening to me?
Of course I'm listening.
I'd love some coffee.
Five creams, nine sugars,
and stir it clockwise.
-[electricity crackling] -[grumbles]
[Karen] You're such a jerk!
I'm gonna do something I
should have done a long time ago!
[gasps] No, Karen! Don't!
Can we talk about this?
I'm done talking!
Karen, please don't do this!
We don't know the consequences!
I don't care!
[Plankton screaming]
Don't swing your purse like that, honey.
Swing your purse like this! [whooping]
Hi, Plank... Whoa!
Whoa! [grunting]
-High again! -[Plankton screams]
[laughs]
-Oh, what's happening? -Huh?
Whoa! [straining]
Huh?
[belt creaks, snaps]
Nooo! Spatty!
[dramatic music playing]
What? She magnetized the Chum Bucket?!
[Karen] Plankton!
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[Plankton whimpers]
Our evil alliance is through!
[grunts] Ah!
[both gasp]
[Karen grunting]
[both whimper]
[pained groaning]
Holy mama pajama!
[maniacal laughter]
[electricity buzzing]
[powering up sound]
[SpongeBob] Whoa!
-[beeping] -Whoa!
Ah!
[growls]
[grunts]
[Karen snarls]
You've got three heads?
Aw, the widdle green
man can count! [scoffs]
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Super Snarky Karen.
-And this… -Is Super Smart Karen.
-And this… -…is Super Evil Karen!
Super, super, super!
Where'd you get those
names? The supermarket?
[chuckles] Supermarket.
[Evil Karen] Let's blast him! Say goodbye!
[roar]
Hold on, Evil!
There are steps to be
taken for world domination.
World domination? That's my thing!
Not anymore, green bean.
We're gonna do what you could never do.
What do you mean?
You might want to take
notes during this song.
Song? When did you have
time to write a song?
[synth-pop music playing]
♪ My power is beyond compare ♪
♪ There's nothing you can do to prepare ♪
♪ No escaping my malware ♪
♪ I will crush you ♪
♪ I shall destroy you ♪
♪ Now's the time I'm gonna take control ♪
♪ Watch Bikini Bottom blow ♪
♪ I'm gonna rise up like a hurricane ♪
♪ Take your final breath away ♪
♪ Fill the world with hurt and pain ♪
-♪ Say my name ♪ -♪ Karen ♪
♪ I'm the real evil mastermind ♪
♪ I rule the world Through space and time ♪
♪ Take it all and make it mine ♪
-♪ Say my name ♪ -♪ Karen ♪
[evil laughter]
♪ I'll take over all of planet Earth ♪
♪ Then I'll expand across the universe ♪
♪ Take it all for all it's worth ♪
♪ I want everything, give me everything ♪
♪ Now's the time I'm gonna take control ♪
♪ Let the devastation roll ♪
♪ Ha! It's over, Plankton ♪
♪ I don't need your tiny hands ♪
♪ And your never-ending failed plans ♪
♪ You thought you were so devious ♪
♪ But it's me, I'm the real evil genius ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
[cackling]
♪ I'm gonna rise up like a hurricane ♪
♪ Take your final breath away ♪
♪ Fill the world with hurt and pain ♪
-♪ Say my name ♪ -♪ Karen ♪
♪ I am the real evil mastermind ♪
♪ I rule the world Through space and time ♪
♪ Take it all and make it mine ♪
-♪ Say my name ♪ -♪ Karen ♪
[Karens cackle]
♪ Karen! ♪
What makes you think you
can do all that without me?
Alright already! What are
we gonna do with him, ladies?
-I say... -Blast him!
I say we dissect him.
[whimpers] And I say… run!
[Karens laugh]
[suspenseful music playing]
He's getting away!
But it is important that we
complete our battle station first.
Hey, ladies, what do you
say we pick up some takeout?
[cackling]
[snoring] Money, money, money, money.
[snoring] Money, money...
[loud explosion]
[gasps] What's happening? What's happening?
What's happening is, I ran out of ketchup.
Patrick, how'd you get in here?
We're closed!
Ah! [grunts]
Where are you going,
me beloved Krusty Krab?
[straining] No!
[dramatic music playing]
[thudding, clattering]
-Whoa! -[splats]
Hmm? Yay! Ketchup!
[chomping loudly]
Patrick, stop yer salivating
all over me windows!
-Hello! -Ow!
Goodbye!
[customer screaming]
[Karens cackling]
Oh, is that Karen?
She's gone full hydra! [gasps, grunts]
Time to rally the Civil Defense!
-[beeping] -[siren blaring]
-People of Bikini Bottom! -Oh!
[Karen] If you do not wish to
be harmed, abandon all homes,
businesses, and public restrooms.
[laughs]
Breaking news! There
appears to be a giant...
There appears to be a giant mag...
-[clears throat] -[water sloshes]
There appears to be a giant magnet
sucking everything metal
across Bikini Bottom! [screams]
Thank you! I love these new stilettos!
Oh! Wait!
[yelps]
This isn't my size!
-[lively piano music playing] -Huh?
[whimpers, screams]
[cutlery clattering]
[magnetic droning]
Yeah, I'm not cleaning this up!
[SpongeBob screaming]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[Plankton] Whoa! -[SpongeBob grunts]
Potatoes.
Why did it have to be potatoes?
-[loud rumbling] -[whimpering]
Plankton, what did you
do to make Karen so angry?
I have no idea!
Why are you doing this to me? [squeals]
Why? [sobbing]
Think. There must be something.
Something in your past.
Well, if there is, I
must have blocked it out.
Ooh! I read all about that in
my Super Psychiatrist comic book.
I even sent away for this
Junior Psychiatrist Kit!
I can psychoanalyze you!
I don't need a shrink.
I'm shrunk enough already!
We'll explore where your
relationship with Karen went wrong…
-Ugh. -…get you two back together,
and save Bikini Bottom!
[rumbling]
Hmm. Wait a minute. Who knows?
Maybe analysis will help
me find a way to destroy…
I mean, uh, to help me understand
Karen and our relationship!
Okay, go ahead. Shrink away, Doc!
[lively music playing]
Please, lie down.
[grumbles]
[in Austrian accent] Now, so, let's
begin at the beginning, shall we?
I have to warn you, I've never
been able to be hypnotized…
[groaning]
Ever since I was a little kid,
I've always wanted to rule the world.
[lively bluegrass music playing]
♪ I was born pure evil
First word was tyranny ♪
♪ Six thousand brothers
Six thousand sisters ♪
♪ Then there was little old me ♪
♪ There's no doubt I came
out The smartest of the bunch ♪
♪ But if you met my family
You'd know that ain't sayin' much ♪
♪ The family biz was moonfizz
But that buzz weren't for me ♪
♪ I dreamt of global domination ♪
♪ Sweet autocracy ♪
♪ But my family didn't get me
I was a stranger in my home ♪
♪ Despite being so surrounded
Well, I always felt alone ♪
♪ Had no bud, no best pal
My future was condemned ♪
♪ Till I took a tater and a
calculator And I made myself a friend ♪
♪ I made a new friend I made a new friend ♪
Can you hear me?
Bubble once for "yes," and twice for "no."
[bubble pops]
[giggles] Incredible!
-Do you have a name? -[bubbling]
[gasps]
[rapid beeping]
Karen! Your name is Karen!
[chuckles] My friend Karen! Yay!
[bluegrass music continues]
[Plankton] ♪ We did everything together ♪
♪ We even dressed the same ♪
♪ That spud was my best buddy ♪
♪ Karen was her name ♪
-♪ My world was so much
greater ♪ -[flatulence]
-♪ With that tater in my life ♪ -[laughter]
♪ Never thought a vegetable
Would one day be my wife ♪
♪ With Karen there to share
my dreams I never felt alone ♪
♪ My calculator, my sweet
potato A friendship had been sown ♪
-♪ I made a new friend ♪ -From a tuber!
-♪ I made a new friend ♪ -And a computer!
-♪ I made a new friend ♪ -Literally!
♪ I made a new friend ♪
[whooping] Wa-hoo!
Hello and goodbye!
Me and my best friend
Karen are going to college!
-[heroic music playing] -College?
[laughter]
-Go ahead and laugh. -[music stops]
We're majoring in world domination.
And when we're done,
we will destroy you all!
See you at the holidays!
Goodbye, son.
Well, good luck, son. And don't
forget, always watch out for feet.
[laughter]
[Plankton grunts]
[bluegrass music resumes, fades]
[whimpering softly]
Plankton, zat was wunderbar!
Huh? [yells]
So, you were lonely and you made a friend.
One thing is for certain.
This potato represents Karen.
No, you idiot.
The potato is nothing but a power source.
The calculator is the brain!
Huh? [gasps]
And I remember where I left it.
Somewhere back at the university.
[giggling]
Looks like I'm going back to college!
Yes, yes. Und college will be a
good place to continue our therapy.
-[gasps] -[Karens cackling]
[epic music playing]
We won't be continuing anything
if we don't get out of here!
[both grunt]
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh!
-Ah! -[music stops]
[panting]
How do we get out of here?
[Plankton] Oh, I don't
know. The exit, maybe!
[suspenseful music playing]
SpongeBob! Grab something metal!
Whoa!
Oh. Phew. [gasps]
[whimpering]
[yelps]
Huh? [screams]
[SpongeBob screaming]
[gasps, screams]
[all screaming]
[fish] Krabby Patty!
[screaming]
And now for the main event…
[laughs]
[Mr. Krabs] Attention!
[grumbles]
-My Neptune. -[fish screaming]
[Mr. Krabs] Oh, my good Neptune!
Load the root beer! Move, move, move!
Ready?
Aim for the hydra!
[breathing deeply]
Come on, you got this, Bobby.
Steady!
Fire!
[suspenseful music playing]
[root beer fizzing]
[Karens powering down]
Aha! A direct hit!
-[cheering] -We won!
-She's down! -Look!
[Mr. Krabs] Huh?
[Karens cackling]
[Mr. Krabs] Oh, no.
[ominous music playing]
Bring it on, you bumbling bucket of bolts!
The brave fish of Bikini
Bottom aren't afraid of you!
Are you, boys?
-Boys? Huh? -[Squidward screams]
[yelps]
Anchors away, Bikini Bottom.
I'm not going to stand...
…for this.
[French narrator] A few moments later…
[SpongeBob screaming]
Whoa!
Uh-huh, we're here.
Good old BSU.
[gasps] BS me? Plankton, language!
No, you moron.
-Oh! -Bikini State University.
Oh!
This is where Karen and I
furthered our academic studies.
This is also where I upgraded her.
And I bet her old parts are
still around here somewhere.
If I can only remember where.
Quick, man! Hypnotize me! Put me under!
Ooh, certainly.
Hmm. Now let us focus
on your subconsciousness.
-Eh? -Focus. Focus.
Check this out, Plankton.
Und walk the dog.
Quit horsing around and
put me under! [groans]
Oopsie.
[groans]
Going to college was a dream come true.
[electronic music playing]
Just going through those ivy
gates of academia gave me chills.
Ooh!
This is it, Karen! We made it!
We're actually in college!
[beeping]
It is G-R-8, isn't it?
Finally, a place to confer
with my intellectual peers.
Hello, fellow students.
How's it hanging, classmates?
- [student] Did you hear something?
- [groans]
[Plankton screams]
[Plankton whimpering] Feet!
Pappy was right! [grunts]
[Plankton] As it turned out,
there was no world domination class.
-Huh? -[beeping]
So, we created our own curriculum.
Our first project was
to build a freeze ray.
I tried in science class.
I tried in art class.
I tried in every class!
College life was hard.
-Phew! -[student] Spring break!
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
-Yeah! -[groans]
The only solace I had during
those difficult years was my Karen.
And having a computer that can
do my homework didn't hurt either.
Hmm. "Marg-gleblorp fa ziggle num lump"?
Hmm…
If I want to stop failing,
I'll have to give her an upgrade.
Oh, Karen, I've got a surprise for you!
Ta-da! A brand new upgrade!
I used four different computer chips to
mold Karen's multi-faceted personality.
A smart chip to keep her informed.
An evil chip so she'd be as evil as me.
[cackling]
A snarky chip so she'd be sassy.
And an empathy chip so
she could feel my pain.
[electricity crackling]
Hello? Karen, can you hear me?
Come on, Karen. You can do it.
Speak to me!
[babbling]
I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I
I… I… I… I can speak!
I have a voice!
Thank you, Sheldon.
She can talk.
She can talk!
[laughs] Alright, take it
down a notch, thunder tonsils.
Oh, and there's that snark.
We won't need your old parts anymore.
[Plankton cackles]
[Plankton] So we got right to
work on our genius freeze ray.
[both] It works!
-[Karen] It works! -[both laugh]
-[upbeat rock music playing] -[door opens]
Why is my room frozen?
And who are you?
Uh, Plankton? [grunts]
I've been your roommate for four years!
I've been living with a
cockroach for how long?
-Eww! -[zapping]
[Karen] Freeze, mister!
No one steps on my Sheldon.
Karen, you're an evil genius!
[both laugh]
Let's hide this popsicle.
Partners…
…in crime!
Now let's supersize this
baby and take over the world!
[rock music fades]
[giggles]
[Plankton chuckles]
Plankton, that was beautiful.
You und Karen worked together.
But we still haven't
discovered what went wrong.
Blah, blah, blah.
Who cares? Karen's old
parts are in my dorm room!
Come on, SpongeBob!
[grunts] Let's go!
-Yah! -[SpongeBob neighs]
[Plankton groaning]
[Plankton] Whoa!
[whimpers, grunts]
[gasps]
Oh! There it is!
[chuckles] Ah, my old college closet.
[knocking rhythmically]
Ooh!
[SpongeBob yelps]
[Plankton laughs]
-[laughs] -[Plankton] Look!
My old stuff! My old textbooks!
Test tubes.
Sandwiches.
-Hey, my old roommate. -Huh? [grunts]
[roommate shivering]
Why is your old roommate frozen?
Oh, him?
Uh, something he's doing
for, uh, science class.
Yeah! [grunts] I found it!
The original Karen.
Whoa!
-[flatulence] -Huh?
Yeesh!
Looks like the potato's gone rotten.
[flatulence]
[sighs]
Like our relationship.
[flatulence]
[sighs]
Uh, what about this guy?
[muffled] Help… me.
Well, great catching up with you, roomie!
-Wait, no, no. -Bye.
- Good luck with that class.
- Anything but the closet!
SpongeBob, now I know how
to stop Karen's madness!
All I need to do is get into
the Chum Bucket's basement.
[rumbling]
[magnetic droning]
-Whoa! -Oh!
Let's roll!
[grunts]
[Plankton] Mush!
[suspenseful music playing]
[both screaming]
[both grunting in pain]
[grunts] That was easy.
[grunts]
[laughs]
[coughs, gasps]
Yeah, I never did finish those stairs.
[spotlights clanging]
Whoa!
[eerie music playing]
Wow, Plankton.
I remember these inventions.
[Plankton] Ah!
They're from all your old attempts
to steal the Krabby Patty formula.
Oh! [laughs]
So this would be kind of
your basement of failures, huh?
What? Do these look like failures to you?
[groans] Now leave me alone!
Hmm. Where was I?
Let's see. I'll need eight capacitors.
Ahh! Whoa! Oh!
- Three diodes. Six transistors.
- [babbling happily]
-[grumbles] -Whoa!
[grunts]
Oh!
All hail Plankton.
How may I serve you, master?
I command you to bring me some pliers.
Wouldn't it be cool if
this thing really worked?
Agh! Just go find them!
Aye, aye, Plankton! [babbling laughter]
[Plankton grumbles]
Plankton, are these pliers?
Ah! That's carbonated... [groans]
…handsome gas.
-Now put it back. -Okie dokie!
Ooh. Hey, Plankton.
-Is this a plier? -No, that's…
- …ugly sludge.
- There you go. It's a banana.
Agh!
Nothing here is just a banana.
Don't touch anything
without asking me first!
Yes, sir.
Hmm…
Hey, Plankton.
Can I touch this? Sorry,
Plankton, I have to touch this.
How about if I touch
this one with my pinkie?
[echoing] Plankton! Is this important?
How about this thing? Hmm…
[sniffs] Ta-da! Plankton, can I touch this?
-Or this, or this? -No!
How about this thing?
-Don't you touch that! -What?
Whoa! Wee!
-Is this important? -[zapping]
[grunts]
That freeze ray tank was our
first attempt at world domination.
Oh, so you were still working together.
We could be getting
closer to your breakthrough.
I'll b-b-break your head through a window
if you don't stop swinging
that thing at my face.
Brilliant there, Plankton. I
will swing your face in front of it.
[grumbling]
So, after college, what
happened to you und Karen?
We were two evil partners,
ready to take over the w-world.
Our freeze ray was such a
success, we decided to supersize it.
[chuckles] Yes.
[upbeat rock music playing]
[engine revving]
[wheels screeching]
Private Karen, activate the thrusters.
Aye, aye, Captain.
And so, our mega ice tank was locked,
loaded, and ready to invade the surface.
[Plankton grunts]
Yeah!
Equalize pressure! Prepare to surface!
Let's storm the world!
[Plankton cackles]
Oh yeah, there's something!
Ice it, baby!
[child giggles]
As it turned out, while I
thought the BSU students were large,
the surface world
creatures were gargantuan.
[loud roaring]
[Plankton] Giant feet! Retreat! Retreat!
[child laughing]
[loud roaring]
-[Karen screams] -[Plankton grunts]
[both screaming]
-[Plankton whimpering] -[splashing]
[water bubbling]
[rock music ends]
[Plankton groans]
Go on, take a good look, Karen.
This is what a flopping failure looks like.
Oh, you're not a flopping failure.
You just need a little
brain food to figure this out.
Let's try that greasy
spoon across the street.
[heavenly choir sings]
[Plankton whimpers]
Come on, eat something, you'll feel better.
Ugh.
How can I eat this garbage
when what I'm really hungry
for is global conquest?
Hey, Mr. Krabs, your
Krabby Patties are amazing.
Aye, thanks to my secret formula,
me patties will take over the world.
Huh? [gasps]
[suspenseful music playing]
I got an idea! It's the
greatest idea I've ever had!
First, I steal the secret
formula for that sandwich.
Then, I take over that restaurant.
Then, I take over this town.
And then, I take over the world!
[laughing]
That's your idea?
[sighs]
Wait, you're serious?
And this two-bit bucket will be
the front for my secret headquarters.
Yours? I thought it was ours.
Hmm. Why not?
It's not like we'll be doing
this for the next 25 years.
Let's do it.
[dramatic music playing]
[zapping]
[loud clanging]
[SpongeBob] Plankton, that's it!
Your obsession with the
Krabby Patty secret formula
made Karen go wacka-doodle-ding-dong.
Plankton?
- [Plankton] You're right, SpongeBob.
- [crackling]
[SpongeBob] Plankton? I
can teach you to apply skills
that will help you in
your… current situation.
I have my own skills that I've
applied to the current situation.
Um…
And without your Junior Psychiatrist Kit,
I would never have found Karen's old parts!
[energy pulsing]
[gulps]
So thanks, Doc.
Check is in the mail.
Oh.
[whimpering]
I think you better run.
[giggles, cackles]
[screaming]
-[suspenseful music
playing] -[Plankton cackling]
[screaming]
Whoa! [grunts]
[gasps]
[laughs evilly]
[robotic voice] New Karen
likes little sponge boy.
-Aw, thanks. -[Plankton chuckles]
Wait, I thought we were working towards
getting you back together with old Karen.
But you made a new Karen?
That's right!
I built this ultimate Karen to destroy
the old Karen and get that secret formula!
Wait, but what about Bikini Bottom?
-I don't care about Bikini Bottom. -Huh?
[grunts] Follow that battle station!
[New Karen] Follow that battle station!
[dramatic music playing]
Hey, wait up!
[Plankton] Oh, Karen! Sweetheart!
I'd like you to meet New Karen.
Hello!
Heavy armor, anti-tank guns, freeze
ray, capable of mass destruction.
[New Karen] Enough to end you.
Less talk, more carnage!
[laughs] I love a good smackdown.
From a safe distance, of course.
[cackles]
-You're going down, Old Karen! -[ringing]
[bell clangs]
[robotic grunting]
[grunting]
[New Karen] Guh-r-r-r!
[growling]
[ape-like grunting]
[robotic snarling]
[Karen growling]
[intense rock music playing]
Oh, yeah!
[intense music building]
[loud explosion]
[romantic accordion playing]
[whimpers]
Oh, no, no! What are you doing?
It is only logical, since you
made New Karen from Old Karen parts…
[all] We are all Karen.
[cackling] We're going to be
stronger than ever, thanks to you.
[New Karen laughs robotically]
[whimpers]
Once again, it's time to run!
[Karens cackling]
[SpongeBob screaming]
[both whimpering]
Oh.
[gasps] Bikini Bottom.
[somber music playing]
Gone.
It's all gone.
Our homes, our lives…
Everything.
Yeah, she really messed up the old place.
Plankton, you caused this.
You… you… you lied to me.
You were never interested
in getting back with Karen.
And now look what's happened.
You did this! You! This is all your fault!
No, it's not.
Plankton,
my analysis is complete.
An overthrown sense of self-impertinence,
pre-oscillation with fantasies of power,
disregarding for others,
instability to handle criticism,
cycle-delusion, und borderline physicality.
Let me put this simply.
Mr. Krabs was right.
You're just a pitiful, pathetic jerk!
I'll leave now.
[melancholic music playing]
I'm going to be with my real friends.
-[sobbing] -Wait, SpongeBob!
SpongeBob?
Don't leave me alone!
Ugh.
[whimpers]
Maybe the kid's right.
Maybe I am a jerk.
[melancholy piano melody playing]
♪ Well, I've been called A
lot of things in my life ♪
♪ A dope, a ninny, a twit ♪
♪ A pea-brained, lame-brained,
no-brained Know-it-all little pip ♪
♪ An obnoxious dunce, an old goon ♪
♪ A bone-headed puny buffoon ♪
♪ But no one's ever told
me How much they cared ♪
♪ I thought they were too stupid ♪
♪ To see the genius Of this little squirt ♪
♪ But on reflection
Their lack of affection ♪
♪ Is because it turns out I'm a jerk ♪
♪ Can I go on ignoring their words ♪
♪ When everything They're saying is true? ♪
♪ That's why I'm always alone ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a jerk ♪
Wait, but that's me.
That's who I am, baby!
-[dramatic rock music
playing] -♪ I'm a jerk ♪
♪ I'm a jerky-jerk ♪
♪ I don't care what they
think I don't care who I hurt ♪
-[sizzling] -♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ I'm obnoxious and annoying ♪
♪ I'm toxic, soul destroying ♪
♪ I'm a jerk ♪
♪ I'm a jerky-jerk ♪
-[clang] -[music stops]
[whimpers] Uh-oh.
[yelps]
Hey, jerk.
Thanks for the new addition.
Hello.
-Huh? -Let me blast him right now!
-Oh! -Gotcha cornered.
[Evil Karen laughs]
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
Alright.
I know when I've lost.
Just give me the dignity of a blindfold.
Whoops.
[soft whimper] Just a moment.
That's better.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Go ahead. Destroy me already!
With pleasure!
[energy building]
[Karens cackling]
-[zapping] -[epic music playing]
-[music fades] -[ice crackling]
[engine revving]
[all whooping]
-[epic music resumes] -[tires screech]
[SpongeBob] Woo-hoo!
Ah, shrimp! Let's go after him!
-Let him go. -Why?
Living with his failures will
be worse than death for him.
Besides, there's nothing left for us here.
Now that our battle station is complete.
[dramatic music playing]
- Which hemisphere should we invade first?
- Who cares?
As long as I get to blast, blast, blast!
Huh. That's funny.
I never pictured death being so windy.
-SpongeBob? -You're still a jerk.
-But I couldn't just leave you. -Huh?
Ugh. The Gal Pals. That figures.
Why did you interfere?
- I had her right where I wanted her.
- Dag nab it! We saved your life!
[screaming]
[lively action music playing]
Well, I already faced death once today.
Bring it on.
Mrs. Puff, you're going
awfully fast. Wanna slow down?
[grunts]
Mrs. Puff, there's a boat.
Mrs. Puff, there's a boat
there! Mrs. Puff, boat!
Mrs. Puff! Mrs. Puff! Boat, boat, boat!
Mrs. Puff!
[echoing screaming]
[continues screaming]
Oh… wait, what is this place?
Oh, wow.
Is this your secret headquarters?
[gasps] Are you guys superheroes?
Of course not.
[buzzing]
Woo-hoo!
[Plankton screams]
Welcome to our underground getaway!
Where there's nothing but
relaxation, conversation…
[groans]
…and a touch of class.
[kettle whistling]
[all slurping]
Plankton, Plankton! You
gotta try this brown water.
Wow! I love it! [babbling]
Never mind all that, Plankton!
What in tarnation did
you do to our friend Karen?
Yeah, why is she so angry?
And why does she have four heads?
SpongeBob, help me! Back me up!
Help yourself to some
of this stuff! I love it!
[sighs, yelps]
It is your fault Karen
turned into a monster!
I bet you never even loved her.
That's not true!
-[grumbling] -SpongeBob, psychoanalyze me.
They gotta hear this.
[babbling, slurping]
Whoa, whoa!
My mind is processing complex
equations and I can see infinity.
[grumbles]
Fine, I'll hypnotize myself!
[babbling]
Karen and I… were totally in love.
[sniffs] Mmm. Smells
like this batch of chum
is just about ready to be
served to the public, Karen-Cakes.
Try some, my little Planky-Poo.
[choking loudly, gulping]
[gasping, retching]
So, how does it taste?
[gulps] Like boiled death!
It's perfect!
[chuckles] Chum fight!
[Karen laughs]
[laughs]
-Oh, you! -Oh, you!
[Karen] Ah, gotcha!
-[both laughing] -[Karen] Ooh! Uh-oh!
[Karen sighs]
Oh, I almost forgot.
I got a new computer part for you today.
And you can install this upgrade yourself.
[gasps]
Karen, will you marry me?
Oh, yes, Sheldon!
I'd love to be your computer wife!
[straining] Oh, Karen! You've
made me the happiest copepod in the...
[screaming] Ouch!
[smooching]
What a woman!
So, Karen and I got hitched.
-[romantic rock music playing] -[smooching]
And it was the beginning of a
beautiful fairy-tale marriage.
[Mrs. Puff] Huh! "Fairy-tale" is right.
[all] Stop the flashback!
We see Karen for coffee seven days a week,
and she complains about you every time.
So, what really happened tonight?
I had just finished chasing everyone
out of the Chum Bucket
with a flamethrower when…
Karen, please don't do this!
We don't know the consequences!
I don't care!
[Plankton] No, no, no!
-Yah! -[whimpers, grunts]
Not the empathy chip!
Please put it back!
Take out the snarky chip! I hate that one!
Gah!
[whimpers]
What?! She removed her empathy chip?
[all screaming]
Without that chip, she can't
feel anything for anyone.
No wonder our Gal Pal isn't herself.
[kettle whistling]
Oh, so that's what this is.
I thought it was a mint. [laughs]
[all groan]
Aha! Give me that!
All I have to do is put
this chip back inside Karen,
and everything goes back to normal!
Forget the chip! Karen wasn't
happy with the way things were.
If you love her like
you say you do, apologize!
Can you do that?
Can you just say you're sorry?
Of course I can!
-[SpongeBob slurping
coffee] -[Plankton] Ah!
[clears throat] I'm…
sh-sh-sh…
Ah… [clears throat] I'm sha-rah…
Hmm? I'm… sha… sha…
Oh, he's hopeless.
If anyone needs an empathy chip, it's him.
- Almost got it.
- That there's a dandy idea, Pearl!
-What? -Brace yourself, partner!
Here come the feels!
[grunting in pain]
-I don't feel anything. -[all groaning]
Oh, now I do.
[babbling softly]
[sitar playing]
Wee!
[mystical flute melody playing]
[gasps]
[Karen] Surprise!
- Welcome to the new Chum Bucket.
- [voices overlapping]
[psychedelic rock playing]
Karen! Your name is Karen!
Aww.
Freeze, mister! No one steps on my Sheldon.
Oh, yeah!
Oh! Yes, Sheldon. I'd love
to be your computer wife.
And this two-bit bucket will be
the front for my secret headquarters.
Uh-oh.
- Are you even listening to me?
- Of course I'm listening.
- I'd love some coffee.
- [grumbles] You're such a jerk!
No!
I'm gonna do something I
should have done a long time ago.
[squawking]
[Karen] Our evil alliance is through!
[Karen's voice echoes]
[screaming]
[bird screaming]
Huh?
[bell dinging]
Whoa! [screaming]
Karen, wait!
Karen?
[screaming]
[growling]
[Plankton screaming]
Oh!
Karen!
I love you, Karen!
Karen, wait!
Huh?
[creature barking]
[Karen] I'm gonna stomp
you like a bug, Planky-Poo!
[yelps] Karen, wait!
I love you!
[grunts]
[Karen cackles]
[Plankton] Come back! I'm…
[gasps] …sorry!
[gasps] I said it!
I gotta find Karen to beg her
forgiveness, tell her I'm sorry,
and win back her love!
Aw, he gets it!
I do get it! I do, I do!
[laughs] I'm coming for you, baby!
Whoa there, little doggy.
She'll exterminate you on sight.
You're gonna need help from the…
[all] Gal Pals!
We gotta get this little love bug to
Karen before she breaches the surface.
Aww! I'm a widdle love bug.
Group hug! Here I come!
Gal Pals! [grunts]
[Sandy] There she is.
[gasps]
[menacing music playing]
This is gonna be totally
harder than I thought.
Okay, ladies, this here is gonna
be our most difficult mission yet.
It'll require extreme
skill and concentration.
There is absolutely zero
room for funny business.
-[SpongeBob laughs] -[Plankton squeals]
[both humming Hawaiian music]
Hey, knock it off!
Y'all wanna get caught by Mega-Karen?
This is serious!
[dramatic music playing]
[babbling laughter]
[all] Whoa!
Look! Up there!
Okay, buckle up, y'all!
[playful babbling]
Huh? [chuckles]
[SpongeBob] Whoa!
[humming]
Well, it was fun while it lasted.
Oh, no! My friend!
Good luck with the mission!
No!
Huh?
Oh! I'm back, baby!
[gulps]
[straining]
Sorry for being… nosy!
[both laughing]
Hey. Be quiet.
Yeow!
Booby traps! I hate booby traps!
- Pearl, did you bring the blowtorch?
- Sure did.
[gulping]
[high-pitched whistling]
[groaning]
[Plankton] Ding dong!
Permission to come aboard?
-[cackling] -Think of it.
This entire battle station is powered by…
-[New Karen] To-to-tomatoes! -No. Potatoes.
Correcting… Potato!
[Smart Karen] People underestimate
the potato's potential.
- [New Karen] Potato!
- Yet one single spud contains…
Contains more power than a nuclear reactor.
Blah, blah, blah.
Nevertheless, it is true.
[New Karen] Potato… Potato… Potato!
[Karen over PA] Five minutes to surface.
Potato! Potato! Potato!
[all] Shut up, New Karen!
-[all gasp] -[alarm beeping]
It appears we have intruders. The Gal Pals.
-Blast them! -Blast, blast, blast!
You got a better idea?
[New Karen] Potato!
[overlapping chatter]
-[Karen] That's enough! -[powering down]
[Karen] Hydra Karen, separate
and destroy the Gal Pals!
[Hydra Karen] Separating!
[dramatic music playing]
Well, what are you waiting for?
Go get 'em!
I'm gonna blast me some Gal Pals!
-[robotic laugh] -[evil laugh]
-[PA] Four minutes to surface. -[all gasp]
- [Sandy] It's Bikini Bottom.
- [Pearl] But it's all mixed up!
Okay, Gal Pals, let's go!
[all] Stealth mode!
[all grunting]
[both] ♪ Stealth
skipping, stealth skipping ♪
[gasps] The Krusty Krab!
[heavenly choir singing]
[babbling happily]
-[Gal Pals] Aah! -[grunts]
Careful, SpongeBob! It could be a trap!
-[splat] -Yeah!
A grease trap! [yelps]
[Plankton] Whoa!
[gasps] Wow, the Krusty
Krab's all topsy-turvy!
I love what Krabs has done with the place.
Especially all this blood everywhere.
Huh? Blood!
There's blood all over the floor!
Blood! Blood! Blood! Blood!
Huh. Ketchup?
Huh?
-Huh? -Patrick!
SpongeBob! [straining]
[Patrick laughs]
[both chuckle]
Oh! Ketchup!
My tummy feels funny.
Oh, I hear your tummy!
Goochie-goo! [blows raspberry]
[laughing]
He's cool. Empathy overload.
We gotta get him to Karen
and save Bikini Bottom!
Huh?
[all screaming]
[SpongeBob and Patrick scream, grunt]
Hi, guys, look who I found!
Now it's a party!
[Snarky Karen] Oh, it's a party, alright!
Four Karens, but none of them are mine!
Wait a minute!
There's my baby. Karen!
I love you!
Destroy them all!
Aw, she remembered my catchphrase!
SpongeBob, hurry! Get Plankton up to Karen!
He has to apologize
before we reach the surface!
Okie dokie.
And now, we'll take care
of these counterfeit Karens!
Attack on the count of three! One…
Potato!
Uh-oh.
-Two, three. -[cackling]
[gasps]
[all grunt]
[all snarling]
[Karens grunt]
[dramatic music playing]
[music slows, distorts]
[music stops]
[music resumes]
Gal Pals, we're doing "Batter Up."
Batter up!
And here's the pitch!
[screams]
-[grunts] -[Karens snarling]
[clattering]
[Sandy] Agh!
-[light instrumentals
playing] -[fighting grunts]
[cackling]
[beeping]
Elevator's here.
[fighting grunts continue]
Here we go, Plankton!
Ooh, soft!
We lost him!
Ooh! There he goes!
Sweetie pie!
I'm coming for you! [grunts]
And there he goes again.
I love falling!
- [voice] Two minutes to surface.
- Ooh, soft!
But not Patrick soft!
Hi, Gals!
[grunting] Great seeing you two!
Ooh, I'm falling again! And I love it!
[Mrs. Puff yelling]
[determined grunting]
[slow-motion screaming]
[Pearl grunts]
[upbeat jazzy music playing]
[coughs, gasps]
You pathetic bottom-feeders!
-[Plankton screaming] -Agh!
[grunts]
[whimpers, exclaims]
[Plankton] The door! The door to Karen!
I can do this!
Yee-haw!
End of the line!
[Evil Karen screams]
I can do anything!
-Ah! -Ah!
I'm doing it!
Whoo!
-[groans] -[music fades]
[elevator bell dings]
[Plankton] I did it!
[Evil Karen snarling]
[Sandy] Yee-haw!
-[all] Huh? -[screaming]
[all yelping]
[laughter]
-Nobody can beat the… -[all] Gal Pals!
-[Gal Pals laughing] -Except me!
[Sandy] I hate…
[Gal Pals] Booby traps!
[Plankton] Stop!
-Whoa! -Back it up, guys!
Look! There's the door!
[humming] Oh, Karen!
[sputtering] Karen?
[sputtering] Destroy!
Big hunk of garbage!
I'll get that secret formula!
Ow! I love you beautiful boys!
Plankton, the empathy chip is burning
out! You better get to Karen! And fast!
Aw, I want the two of you
to go find the engine room…
[sputters] I will destroy you, Krabs!
[sputters] And destroy it
while I go apologize to Karen!
Chum buckets!
I want… [sputtering]
…another hug!
[murmuring, laughing]
Good luck, my friends!
Good luck to you, green jellybean man!
[Plankton chuckles]
"This way to engine room."
Oh, what a helpful sign!
[both] Huh? [screaming]
[screaming]
Oh, ice cream!
[both scream]
[Patrick] Oof! Ow!
Patrick, we're here!
Whoa.
Where's here?
The engine room.
[echoing scream]
How are we ever gonna destroy all this?
SpongeBob!
Look!
[dramatic music plays]
Oh! [gasping]
Spatty!
Whosoever pulleth out this spatula
from this wall is right-wise worthy!
[gasps]
Oh, Spatty! [babbles happily]
I missed you!
I hate to break up this reunion, but
weren't we supposed to be doing something?
You're right. Spatty…
Patty!
-Patty! -[guffawing]
- Let the potato chopping commence!
- Woo-hoo!
[Karen on PA] One minute to surface.
[menacing music playing]
Karen?
Ooh! It's dark and evil in here!
Dripping pipes.
[chuckles] Nice touch!
[grunts] Huh? [gasps]
[ominous music playing]
Ooh!
There you are, my love!
I've come to apologize.
[Karen] Oh.
It's you.
Well, hello!
Now give me a big, sloppy
kiss and let's tango! [chomps]
[humming tango music]
[Karen] Stand still, twinkle toes!
How can I stomp you when you're
jitterbugging all over the floor?
Huh?
And I wouldn't blame
you if you did, my dear.
Because I can feel your pain now.
Sandy put your empathy chip into my brain!
Oh, I see!
So all this emotion is just
the empathy chip talking!
No, it's not!
Well… at first it was, except…
[grunting]
[pained groan]
[panting, groaning]
This thing burned out on the way up here
from an overload of feels.
You shouldn't have come back, Sheldon.
Frankly, I'm surprised
you made it this far.
Now, run along, little copepod.
I have to get back to my world domination.
But that was our plan, Karen.
I'm so sorry for not listening
to you all these years.
But from now on, I want us
to do everything together!
[sighs] It's too late.
You can drop the lovey-dovey act.
[beeping]
[whirring]
I've got what you really want right here.
The Krabby Patty secret formula.
[Plankton gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
[Karen] Take it and go.
After all these years!
[laughs]
Yes! Finally!
The thing that's gonna
help me take over the world…
[grunts]
…was right there in
front of me the entire time.
The secret formula
was you!
[gentle music playing]
Me?
So you really do feel my pain?
Yes, I really do.
And that's not all.
I really do love you, Karen.
Between the two of us,
you're the real evil genius.
Huh? Eh…
Need a boost?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[romantic rock music playing]
[smooching]
[Plankton] Yeowch!
What a woman!
Aw, I love you too, my Planky-Poo.
And I accept your apology.
I always hoped you'd
come around eventually.
So I added this.
[gasps] For me?
Oh, that's so… nice!
[horn blaring]
Now let's finally do what
we wanted to do after college.
Let's take over the world!
[both] Together!
[both laugh]
[PA] Surface! Surface! Surface!
[upbeat electronic music playing]
[kids chattering]
♪ My power is beyond compare ♪
♪ There's nothing you can do to prepare ♪
♪ No escaping my malware ♪
♪ I will crush you, I'll destroy you ♪
[rumbling]
♪ Now's the time, I'm gonna take control ♪
♪ Watch Bikini Bottom blow… ♪
[Plankton] I just love a day of
destruction at the beach, don't you?
-♪ Take your final breath away ♪ -[gasps]
♪ Fill the world with hurt and pain ♪
-♪ Say my name ♪ -♪ Karen ♪
[gasping]
♪ I'm the real evil mastermind ♪
♪ I'll rule the world
Through space and time ♪
[people screaming]
-♪ Say my name ♪ -♪ Karen ♪
♪ And Plankton ♪
Oh, Sheldon! You are so evil!
You should be the first one to
push the button. You earned it.
No, you should push the button.
You worked so hard for this.
-You push it. -No, you push it.
-No, you push it. -No, you!
[people screaming]
[Karen] No, you!
-Let's push it… -[both] …together!
[Karen laughs]
[music distorts]
[both] Huh?
-[Karen] Huh? -[music distorting]
[loud bang]
[dramatic music playing]
[Karen] What?
I built this battle
station to be 100% foolproof!
[gasps] Yeah, but it's not SpongeBob-proof.
[French narrator] Eight hundred
kagillion potatoes later…
[babbling happily]
That's the last of the potatoes!
[chomping loudly]
Come on, come on!
[energy pulsing, powers down]
Whoo! It worked! We did it, Patrick!
High five! Woo-hoo! Hooray!
[gulps]
[belching loudly]
[chuckles]
-[Plankton screams] -[alarm blaring]
Sorry I ruined the plan, Karen.
I'm such a jerk.
Oh, but you're my jerk.
[Plankton giggles]
[romantic rock music playing]
[music fades]
[kids chattering]
[uplifting music playing]
[clams squeaking]
[clarinet squealing discordantly]
-[whooping] -[fighting sounds]
-[sobbing] -[Squidward whimpering]
[fish whooping]
Hmm?
[gasps] Thank Neptune! Me secret formula!
[SpongeBob] Hey, everybody!
Welcome back…
♪ …to Bikini Bottom On
the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Where every day The
skies are sunny blue ♪
♪ On the ocean floor
It's like it was before ♪
♪ And there's a place for me and you ♪
[all] ♪ In Bikini Bottom On
the bottom of the ocean… ♪
Gary!
Woo-hoo!
♪ In Bikini Bottom No bottom is forgotten ♪
I love my new house made
from a large metallic shoe!
I'm open for business!
The grill is back on!
♪ Come in the Krusty Krab
And get your patty snack on ♪
I'm so hungry, my stomach could sue me.
I haven't eaten since spring break!
♪ In Bikini Bottom On
the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Every day the skies are sunny blue ♪
Woo-hoo!
♪ On the ocean floor You'll
find everything and more ♪
♪ And there's a place for me and you ♪
Hooray, hooray. I'm overjoyed.
Oh-so happy to be employed.
Perch Perkins here, Bikini Bottom News.
Bikini Bottom has miraculously fallen
back to how it was before the movie.
What are the chances!
♪ In Bikini Bottom On
the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Every day the skies are sunny blue ♪
Woo-hoo!
♪ In Bikini Bottom No bottom is forgotten ♪
-♪ And there is a place
for me and you ♪ -[whimpers]
Oh, thank Neptune!
Huh? What in the world?
Hey, Squidward! I'm your
upstairs neighbor now!
[laughs] Check out these
great new shoes I got.
[laughing]
I wish I never came back.
♪ To Bikini Bottom On
the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Where every day The
skies are sunny blue ♪
♪ On the ocean floor You'll
find everything and more ♪
♪ And there's a place for me and you ♪
[grunts]
Plankton.
[suspenseful music playing]
-[fish] There they are! -[angry grumbling]
Oh… Hey, everybody. [chuckles]
What's new?
We're going to tear you both
to pieces. That's what's new.
[all clamoring]
No! Stop!
Out of the way, boyo.
Why aren't you as angry as we are?
Hmm.
Well, I guess this old sponge
is just a sucker for a love story.
I'm a sucker for a love story too.
Aw, I love love stories.
I love a good love story.
[overlapping chatter]
[grumbles] You've all gone soft on me!
Sure, I got my restaurant
and my formula back.
But not me…
[squeals] My money!
I guess I'm just a sucker
for a love story too.
[all] Aww!
[fish] I'm a sucker too!
What a bunch of morons.
Yeah, but they're our morons.
Aww!
[Plankton giggling]
-[upbeat music playing] -You again?
The movie's over.
-Pack it up. -[all singing]
[Plankton] Keep going. Keep going!
Keep going!
Good enough.
♪ And there's a place for me and you ♪
[upbeat rock music playing]
[music fades]
[rock music playing]
♪ My life's a list of brilliant schemes ♪
♪ Con jobs and conquests ♪
♪ But don't forget who calculated ♪
♪ Most of the ideas ♪
♪ No, you didn't ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ What a recipe ♪
♪ For disaster ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ Inseparably ever after ♪
♪ My microscopic mini man ♪
♪ You always make me cross ♪
♪ My macro-sized computer wife ♪
♪ Is perfection not enough? ♪
♪ You must be joking ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ What a recipe ♪
♪ For disaster ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ Inseparably ever after ♪
♪ I only have an eye for you ♪
♪ That's so sweet ♪
♪ It is, isn't it? ♪
♪ I've got a brand-new
Screen saver up for you ♪
♪ That's nice, dear ♪
♪ You didn't even look ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ What a recipe ♪
♪ For disaster ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ Inseparably ever after ♪
[sitar music playing]
[upbeat psychedelic music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[upbeat rock music playing]
[music fades]