Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Morning.
What did the doctor say yesterday?
My blood pressure is a bit high.
That's all.
High blood pressure?
That's bad.
2016 HONG KONG BALLET COMPETITION
You might not carry to term.
You had better stay home.
I can't.
Why not?
Go back to work after the baby is born.
Good boy.
Honey.
Be careful.
You, be careful.
- You, be careful.
- You.
- Morning, sir.
Why are you all standing around?
Back to work!
Boy, snap out of it.
Something big is going down tonight.
Look alive.
Here.
What's this?
What else? It's for you.
Miscellaneous baby stuff from my children.
My wife told me to give it to your wife.
Thank you.
But I'm having a son.
I don't need the girl stuff.
Then have a daughter next.
I'm not taking it back.
- My wife will kill me.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Don't thank me yet.
You received another complaint.
What now?
Did you arrest Tall Ming
in Causeway Bay last week?
Yes.
Did you notify the division commander?
If I waited for his order,
it would have been too late.
Same excuse again.
You solved the case.
But Officer Kwan lost face.
You're good, but you're not a team player.
For once, try to get along with others.
So what happened? Did you settle it?
I took him out to dinner and fixed it.
- Great.
- Pay me back for the dinner.
I owe you. Let's go.
I am the field commander
of this joint operation.
Here is tonight's operation order.
Wong Kwun. We have tracked him for years.
Murder, arson, blackmail,
drugs, you name it.
CIB has a lead that at 9 p.m. tonight
Long Hair from the Vietnamese Gang
will do a major drug deal with Wong Kwun.
We will take them down
no matter how strong they are!
Our final briefing
will be at 8 p.m. tonight.
This operation is confidential.
The location will be released
before the operation starts.
We will arrest all those scumbags tonight!
- Yes, sir.
Dismissed.
- Yes, Beau?
- Bong.
I need your help.
Without you,
tonight's operation might get canceled.
- All right.
- Hurry.
I can't handle it. Okay?
I'm on my way.
Where the hell is he?
Beau!
You're late.
- The brass is waiting.
- Why will the operation be canceled?
You're lying again.
If I didn't say that, would you have come?
The brass is waiting for you.
It's urgent. Help me, okay?
Refuse this and I will be dead.
My future will be ruined, okay?
Considering I'm your boss,
classmate, and good buddy,
please help.
I'm not your buddy.
Sorry! The busy man has finally arrived.
Officer Cheung!
How are you, Officer Chow?
Not as fit as you.
Please sit. I will introduce everyone.
Officer Tai, our division commander.
You know Officer Lee.
This is Officer Ho.
- Senior Superintendent of CAPO.
- Hello, Officer Ho.
- Mr. Youli Chan.
- Hello.
And his son.
Mr. Chan has been our longtime supporter
and has asked to meet with you today.
Do you remember
the Hang Choi Bank robbery
in Tai Kok Tsui in 2013?
Officer Cheung cracked the case.
And, of course, in 2016,
the gunfight at Sai Kung Pier.
Officer Cheung singlehandedly captured
seven international criminals
with just two rounds.
- Gosh!
- They were former soldiers.
- Amazing.
To Officer Cheung,
who has solved many cases over the years!
- Cheers, Officer Cheung.
Gentlemen,
you asked me here today.
What can I do for you?
Officer Cheung, we know you are good,
but you just need
an opportunity.
Hello, Officer Cheung.
I am Mr. Chan's lawyer.
A few nights ago,
Mr. Chan Jr. had too much to drink
and accidentally injured this policeman.
He has forgiven Mr. Chan Jr.
- Therefore--
- I get it.
But I have already
turned in the report, so--
It's back on your desk.
Give it back to me next week.
That's right.
As you can see,
the victim is enjoying his lunch.
So even if it gets to court,
it may not hold water.
Beau, don't fuck around.
Don't you know me by now?
I want to help you
get promoted, that's all.
You set me up!
How? I'm not asking you to sell your ass.
This is worse.
Whether you agree or not,
the result will be the same.
The brass wants to impress the rich guy.
Just play along.
You're not young anymore
and will soon be a dad.
Please, I beg you.
I love you.
Sorry.
Officer Cheung, are you okay?
He's fine. He just drank too much water.
Have you made it clear?
Crystal clear.
This is good tea.
Waiter.
Is it expensive?
It's the best Iron Buddha Tea.
- It's 600,000 dollars per catty.
- 600,000 dollars?
It's good stuff.
I took two sips.
200 dollars should cover it.
Excuse me. I must go.
Officer Cheung.
Do you know what you're doing?
Of course I do. Do you?
Bong!
I'm warning you now.
Listen up.
If anybody screws up,
they will have hell to pay.
Chow.
Why are you taking so long
over some Kevlar vests?
What's wrong?
I don't have your UI.
What?
Any questions?
- No, sir.
Let's go!
Sorry, Bong.
I'm just following the procedure.
Your UI is not showing.
You're not a part of this operation.
Yes?
Location?
I can't tell you.
Are you fucking with me too?
Not me. I'm just following orders.
I told you to be a team player.
- Don't upset the higher-ups.
- They're boot-lickers!
CAPO and ICAC are investigating them.
But that takes time, right?
Yiu, you know I have waited four years!
I must capture
the bastard Wong Kwun tonight.
I know.
You just can't let it go. Neither can I.
Stay put.
They're looking to get rid of you.
I don't want you to lose your job.
Trust me. Wong Kwun is an easy job.
I will personally bring him back.
- You can take his statement, okay?
- Quit the bullshit! Location!
- Location!
- Goodbye.
Call your friend in CIB.
- I will get the car.
- Now!
OB calling Control Post.
I estimate over 20 lookouts onsite.
We believe the target will make the deal
at the third-floor skating rink.
Attention, all units.
The target is at the skating rink.
A-Team, surround the skating rink.
Back Stop, guard all entrances and exits.
Got it! Seaview Plaza, Tsuen Wan.
Officer Yiu, the Vietnamese Gang is here.
Take action?
Calm down. Wait until the goods
and money change hands.
All units, in position.
When the Vietnamese Gang arrives,
we will get them all at once.
What's wrong?
The monitors have gone blank!
Officer Yiu?
- Sir, we have interference.
- We're on it.
Hello, Vietnamese boys.
Are those party masks?
What the fuck?
That's some awesome shit, man!
Okay, straight to business.
Transfer the funds.
Fuck!
Are there cops outside?
Boss, there really are cops here.
Bastard, you dare mess with me?
Open fire at the scene!
Requesting urgent backup!
Officer Yiu, please respond! Officer Yiu!
All units, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
What the fuck?
Yes!
Hang in there!
You bastards.
Hello, sir.
You look ridiculous.
Who are you?
Show your faces.
Let me see.
I dare you.
Go one-on-one with me.
Mano a mano!
It has been a long time.
Over there!
We're at Seaview Plaza.
Over 20 injured. Get ambulances here.
What's wrong with you?
I said rob, not kill.
You killed so many cops.
Relax, anger is bad for you.
Here. Where's our pay?
The cops are too close.
Take your time selling the goods.
You're teaching me?
Ngo.
What's with you?
We suffered all those years in jail.
Make all the money you can.
But don't go too far.
Too late. Don't ask.
Hey!
Chu, burn that car.
Wah, listen for any news.
- Keep us far from the cops.
- Got it.
Chuen.
Keep the guns, ammo, and vests.
No one here should know
where you store them.
Chiu.
The walkie-talkies.
None worked! What's wrong with you?
Sorry, Ngo.
After this is over,
I will divide the money that is left.
Meanwhile, stay under the radar.
Take care of your daughter.
Go to work as usual.
Don't go out unless you must.
- Let's drink to Bill.
- To Bill.
License check! Lights on, music off!
ID cards.
- I don't have it.
- Do you not have an ID card?
Quit bullying me, damned woman!
Damn you!
- Come here!
- Sit down!
What are you doing?
Where is Wong Kwun's stuff?
- No idea!
- Bong, something has happened.
- You really don't know?
- No!
I will pretend you really don't know
and give you another chance.
Close this joint or be my informant.
Wrap it up.
- What are you doing?
- Out of the way!
What are you doing?
Attack!
- Victory!
- Flip the table over.
- Bad try!
- Want to play again?
- It's just luck.
- Lucky Bong.
Yes, sir?
Roger.
At 3:30 a.m. today,
business mogul S T Fok
was kidnapped at his home.
That is bad news.
What's worse is
he was with his female secretary.
The ransom is one billion dollars.
They warned Mrs. Fok
not to call the police.
So she called the Secretary of Security.
Could it be the mistress
who wants a billion dollars?
It's possible.
DCP has been cleared.
The operation is top-secret
for the safety
of the rescue mission and Mr. Fok himself.
These two thugs
have committed every crime.
One is called Coke,
the other is Wong Kwun.
These are their files.
Listen up.
The brass takes
Mr. Fok's kidnapping very seriously,
so we must rescue him
as quickly as possible.
- Yes, sir.
Ngo and Bong.
Save Mr. Fok by any means necessary.
- Yes, sir.
Goodbye, sir.
Shall we bet on his share price dropping?
INTERNATIONAL NIGHTCLUB
GOLDEN APPLE NIGHTCLUB
SHANGHAI HAIRSTYLE
- Congratulations.
- On what?
Another promotion next month.
You got your wish. Stay humble.
Envy me?
A little.
Congratulations, Star of Tomorrow.
- It's the same job.
- No, it's not.
We might only catch ten thieves now.
When I get promoted,
we can catch hundreds and thousands.
Then there will be peace.
That would be good.
When you get married, there will be peace.
- Set more tables at your wedding banquet.
- Exactly.
- There are a lot of us.
- Of course.
- He won't lose money with so many of us.
- Count me out.
Sir, we have eyes
on Coke going to his car.
Will the groom take him on?
I will take him.
Wong Kwun is all yours, Bong.
Then there will be peace.
- Stay sharp.
- Roger.
We have eyes on Wong Kwun
about to leave in his van.
I wait for you every time.
Next time, it's your turn.
How much are we betting on?
A mahjong game?
Make our move anyway.
Where is S T Fok?
Speak!
Where is the hostage? Speak!
I don't know what you are talking about.
What hostage? What are you talking about?
Get up!
No one is beating you up.
Sir?
What is the situation?
He won't say anything. Give me more time.
Your time is up.
I don't care how you do it.
Mr. Fok must be safe
before the stock market opens tomorrow.
This is a private operation.
Everything is off the record.
The commissioner will not know about it.
If things go bad,
I will have your back, okay?
But if you mess up,
the brass will crush us both.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
What's going on? You're crazy!
Where is the hostage? Speak!
Speak!
Bastard!
You will hear from my lawyer.
I don't know anything.
What are you doing?
- Come here!
- What are you doing?
I will count to three.
We'll see if you're really that tough.
I will make you swallow your own teeth!
One!
Two!
I will talk!
143 Wan Lee Street.
Bill, make the call.
143 Wan Lee Street, now!
He's here.
Mr. Fok, don't worry. We are the police.
You could have saved yourself a beating.
Do you like being beaten?
Did your mom teach you that?
You asked for it.
The bastard is biting me!
Let go!
Let him go!
Police! License check.
Take out your ID cards.
Stop playing now.
Stop. Show your ID card.
Behave.
Freeze!
- Out of the way!
- Freeze!
Open the door! Come out!
Stop fooling around! Do you hear me?
Come out!
Shall I blast the door open? Come out!
He's hiding something.
Come out!
Hi, Bong.
Hi, Jaws.
Moe, what have you done?
How bold.
You dare to take Wong Kwun's stuff?
Where did you get it from?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Guai!
It's from Guai.
CSU has determined that
the last lot of Wong Kwun's drugs
was the same as the stuff
from Au Man-guai,
also known as Guai.
A few years ago,
he was jailed for manslaughter.
He was released six months ago
and hid in Cha Kwo Ling
to recruit men.
A lot of fake refugees joined him.
He also groomed many knife fighters.
In other words, he's a nutcase.
That's a dangerous area.
My friend in DATS told me
a cop went there and was chopped up.
They got a South Asian boy to cop to it.
There was nothing DATS could do.
No luck. Boss says we need a warrant.
We won't get it tonight.
So? Let's go anyway!
We have neither a permit nor backup.
It will be dangerous.
So? Let's just go home and sleep, then.
We are policemen!
There's a criminal,
but we don't catch him?
How is that right?
You're not afraid, are you?
No, it's not that.
We must follow the rules.
You're telling me about rules?
If you're scared, just say so!
Hey.
You're funny.
Sometimes aggressive, sometimes sleepy.
Which side are you on?
I would like to sleep,
but we lost so many colleagues!
- I can't sleep!
- I can't sleep either!
- Stop it.
- Okay.
Okay.
Let's call it a day.
That's it, then.
We have been on duty
for over 20 hours straight.
Okay?
I know you're tired. Go home and rest.
Bong.
- We're just letting him go?
- Just go home.
- Listen to Bong. Call it a day.
- Bye!
ASIAN, YAU TSIM MONG DISTRICT,
PROCURING, GAMBLING, NARCOTICS
Gather around, everyone.
Things have changed.
Guai's goods are on the street.
Cheung Sung-bong found them.
Cops are everywhere. We could get caught.
So what should we do now?
You dare mess with me?
Do you have a death wish?
Damn you!
Stop it!
Bastard!
Stay out of trouble!
Don't call me unless it's urgent!
- What are you doing?
- What is he doing?
Who are you?
Who are you? Get down!
What? A cop is looking for me?
What the fuck?
What do you want? Who are you?
What do you want, sir?
There he is!
Let him go!
- Out of the way!
- There he is!
Go away!
- Sir, I'm not involved!
- Caught red-handed!
- Stop filming!
- This will get you 30 years.
Caught you!
Guai, congratulations!
You have been caught red-handed!
Hey!
- Guai.
- Sit down.
This damn cop insisted I bring him to you.
Sit down.
Shut up!
Well?
Quiet, downstairs.
It's just one handgun, not a machine gun.
Well, sir?
How can I help you?
Eight of my colleagues died
in last week's Tsuen Wan case.
A dozen are still in the ICU.
All for this stuff.
This is Wong Kwun's stuff,
and you have it now.
Explain yourself.
What if I said I found it?
Let's be frank, Au Man-guai.
You're in it for the money.
Tell me who did it,
and you will get a lighter sentence.
Here, take it.
You don't want it?
Give it to your men
to cover funeral expenses.
Being nice doesn't work with you.
You're coming to the station!
Don't you dare!
Calm down!
Don't try it.
What a mess. Let me clear this up first.
Boss, just tell him!
No way!
You bastard!
Freeze! All of you, drop your weapons!
- Come out!
- Come out if you dare!
I will kill you when you come out!
Stop!
Go back to the station with me.
Save it!
Let's go.
Back to the station.
Go to hell!
Tell me who did it!
No way in hell!
Tell me!
After long and detailed planning
by the police,
we successfully raided
a drug distribution facility
and found over 48 million dollars' worth
of pure crystal meth.
Our labs show
that it is from the same lot as
the drug-related robbery and murder
from last week.
The criminals involved in the case
were all shot dead by police
during our very successful operation.
The bastards love to brag.
They take all the credit
while we take all the risks.
That's life. What can we do?
Change careers.
What? I was joking.
I'm going home.
Are you really going home?
Yes.
We will get those bastards.
Damn, a whole tooth.
Let me clean you up.
You're all beat up.
This is the last time.
I'm sorry.
BILL CHEUNG
What did we do?
Please give us another chance.
We were loyal and dutiful.
We rescued people.
Why won't anyone rescue us?
Why?
My wife and kids are waiting for me!
Leave.
I told you to leave! Understand?
Hey!
Enough! That's enough.
No offense.
None taken.
Don't you have bad guys to catch?
I come every year
to pay my respects to Bill.
Just to visit him.
I heard you will be a dad soon.
Congratulations.
Yes, soon.
I will be a dad soon.
And you? Are you still seeing Ching?
No.
Not since I got out.
I was jailed for years.
We canceled the wedding banquet.
I couldn't expect my fiancée to wait.
Over the years,
I often went to see you.
But you didn't want to see me. I get it.
I was in jail. What was there to see?
Now you're out.
What are your plans?
Do you know that Wong Kwun is dead?
So I heard.
We planned for years.
We were going to take them down
during a drug deal last week.
But out of nowhere,
a group who knew
the police's plans ambushed us,
took the goods, and killed many people,
including eight of our colleagues.
Yiu was one of them.
How reckless of him.
Yiu was a cop for over 30 years.
He was a good cop and a good man.
You know he was my mentor.
Yes.
Without him, you wouldn't be a cop.
If not for you, I wouldn't have either.
But this society doesn't reward good men.
Bill was a good man. Now, he rests here.
I won't spare those bastards.
I will catch them all.
Good luck with that.
We got Wong Kwun.
He is lawyered up and not talking.
How are things on your end? Where are you?
Tsing Yi Dockyards.
Hey!
Stop!
Are you nuts? You guys are cops!
He's dead!
What now?
We were told to rescue Mr. Fok. We did.
Were we wrong?
Either the suspect dies
or Mr. Fok does.
Who would you choose?
I'm tired. I'm leaving.
Bong.
Bong!
Due to the sensitive nature of this case,
this trial will be conducted
behind closed doors.
Mr. S T Fok,
from what you remember,
besides the late Ho Wai-lok,
was the other suspect,
Wong Kwun, involved in the kidnapping?
I really am not sure.
There was no need
to kill anyone, was there?
What? If not for us, you would be dead!
We saved your life
and you said there was no need?
Please calm down.
Defendants, control your emotions.
Mr. Seto Kit,
according to my clients' statements,
you instructed them to lynch the victim
in order to solve the case.
Do you admit to that?
Yes, I repeatedly requested
that they solve the case
as soon as possible,
but I didn't tell them to lynch
or kill anyone.
Superiors often ask their subordinates
to complete their tasks quickly.
That is within reason.
But there are strict police guidelines
regarding force used in various operations
which officers must follow.
Thus, whether the six defendants
killed anyone
is unrelated to the fact that I asked them
to solve the case quickly.
What? You said you would have our backs!
Don't deny it now!
Please calm down.
Calm down.
I swear by Almighty God
to tell the whole truth
and nothing but the truth.
Senior Inspector Cheung Sung-bong,
according to the statements
of all six defendants,
you witnessed
the entire process on that day.
So I ask you.
Did you see the victim resist arrest
and fall to the ground to his death?
First, I must emphasize
that we received orders
from our superiors that night
to capture the two criminals,
Ho Wai-lok and Wong Kwun.
Your Honor, the witness
is avoiding the question.
I only asked
if he saw the victim resisting arrest.
Witness, please answer the question.
I had not yet arrived
at the scene when it happened.
So that is clearly a "no."
Did you see
the six defendants beating Ho Wai-lok?
Ho Wai-lok was
an extremely dangerous criminal.
I firmly believe that we as police
had to deal with him
with considerable force.
"Considerable force"?
What does that mean?
We cannot guess
how much force is "considerable."
Just answer me.
Did you see
the defendants beat Ho Wai-lok?
And, Inspector Cheung, let me remind you
that you are currently under oath.
Yes or no?
Witness, please answer the question.
Yes.
Thank you.
Drink!
You're late! Drink!
Drink it all!
Joseph is at the other club.
- Let's join him.
- Yes!
Sure, I'll get the bill.
Check, please.
I got it.
How nice of you.
- Thank you. You're so generous.
- It's nothing.
Look at that! That looks fancy.
It's nothing special.
Nothing? It costs over a million dollars.
I guess so.
Keep the change. Thank you.
Thank my babe. He treated you tonight.
Thank you, babe!
- Thank you!
- "Babe!" Gross!
You're really giving it to me?
Yes, whatever makes you happy.
Thank you, you're so sweet.
Babe.
You're taking more?
It's fine, I don't mind.
Wait here. I'm going to take a shower.
Hey! Don't snoop on my phone!
Who is this?
Just a friend.
Give me my phone back.
- No, you are mine!
- You're hurting me!
Bonnie, don't go.
Sorry, I--
Are you stupid?
Have you seen what you look like?
It's scary, dude.
And you're impotent, damned jailbird!
I hate being called "damned jailbird"!
If not for jail,
would my face look like this?
Bitch!
Bong, Marine Police
picked up a female corpse
at Chai Wan Pier an hour ago.
The victim's name is Kwan Mei-you.
This watch was found on her body.
CIB traced the serial number.
It was worn by Wong Kwun
on the day he was killed.
The victim was last seen in Wan Chai
renting a room with Chiu Chi-keung.
They were seen
on surveillance cameras entering a room.
But only Chiu came out,
dragging a suitcase.
What do you think?
Ngo did it.
He better not have.
Get to work.
Look into Chiu's phone records.
- Yes, sir.
- Roger.
Sit.
This is a huge job.
Do you have what it takes?
Don't mess with me.
It's a chance in a million.
Banks seldom switch security systems.
You're not the only interested party.
Don't waste our time.
Of course I'm interested.
Is your information correct?
Of course.
If you're in, we will give it to you now.
Bong, the target stopped
at the Mei Fai Building ahead.
Keep moving, sir.
Go.
Target is moving to three o'clock.
Chow, your team will follow Chiu.
Roger.
Jaws, let me off at Mei Fai Building.
- Stay on them.
- Yes, sir.
Cops.
Ngo, we're being followed by cops.
Throw out all your SIM cards.
Your location?
We're heading to Chai Wan.
What is going on?
Why are cops following us?
What have you done this time?
Sorry.
Bastard! Stay alert!
I will follow Wah. You stay with Chiu.
Roger.
Freeze!
Freeze. Hands up.
- Freeze!
- Don't move!
What? I can't go for a run?
You ran me down!
Cuff him.
- Into the car!
- Yes, sir.
Police. Do you have
comprehensive insurance?
All units,
don't let Chiu reach the highway.
Stop him at the next intersection.
Roger.
Police at work. Go back into your cars.
Close your doors.
- Do not come out. Hide.
- Stay in the car. Windows up.
Close the door.
Chiu is here.
Freeze! Hands up!
Damn it!
Went for a run?
You jumped out of a car!
So what?
There is no law that says I can't!
What's more,
you cops drove recklessly
and crashed into me.
- I will sue you.
- Don't mess with me!
Chiu is your buddy. You're part of this.
Admit it!
So much bullshit.
Don't you find it annoying?
Is this how cops do things nowadays?
Arresting people on a whim?
You need evidence to charge me.
Where is it?
How are you, Wah?
How is your family, Wah?
Your daughter must be six years old now.
She must be in primary school.
Shouldn't you stay out of trouble
and spend more time with her?
You have been caught red-handed.
After a few more years in jail,
she won't even recognize you.
You must think of her.
Last chance.
Okay.
You know what to do.
Get up!
No more!
I'm sorry.
I was greedy.
I stole Wong Kwun's watch.
There must be a way to rescue Wah.
He can keep secrets.
He won't rat us out.
We still have time.
Chiu has been caught.
But I know the police
don't have enough evidence to charge us.
Stay cool.
There is nothing we can do.
We're on the same team.
When someone makes a mistake,
the others have to make up for it.
It's the same with anyone.
The question now is
how we can rescue Wah
from Cheung Sung-bong.
There is only one way.
How many times have I said it?
If anybody screws up,
they will have hell to pay.
These are former policemen.
Four years ago,
they were jailed for manslaughter.
They were released six months ago.
We have reason to believe
they were involved
in several armed robberies and murders.
We have checked all border records.
Last week, they sent
all their families out of Hong Kong.
It looks like
something major will happen soon.
We only have evidence to charge Chiu.
We must catch them all.
- Yes, sir.
Okay, let's go.
Stop, all of you!
Who gave you permission to go?
I did.
Do you know
how many complaints we have had?
- Bong, we need to talk.
- Set out!
Bong!
Bong.
Please.
I know how you feel.
I don't like it either.
But you must realize this.
So many colleagues died
last time at the mall.
We must not make any more mistakes.
Moreover,
I have handed this case
back to Officer Tai.
- We will let it go now, okay?
- Not okay.
- It's not okay.
- This is an order.
- There's no way around it.
- Not okay.
You're a policeman!
So are you.
It's an order.
What can I do? Tell me.
Don't lord your title over me, okay?
- Beau.
- I can't--
Try to be human about this.
So many colleagues have died.
What else can I do?
You're putting me in a bad spot.
You can handle it, okay?
Okay. Let's go.
- Bong.
Ngo and his men are here.
They said they came to report a case.
What a big welcome!
We are just here to report a case.
Perfect.
You saved us a trip.
Make some coffee.
Yau Kong-ngo,
in these six months after your release,
there is no record
of your employment, residence,
travel, bank, or any other records.
You must have something planned.
Wong Kwun was killed two weeks ago,
and his goods were taken.
We lost eight colleagues. Did you do it?
You had a conflict with Wong Kwun.
That is reason and motive.
Admit it.
Wah confessed
for the sake of his wife and daughter.
He said you were involved
as the mastermind.
I don't believe that.
You must have come prepared.
Please explain.
What are you laughing about?
I was in that seat for over a decade.
I have said the same things you have said.
Take a guess whether I believe you.
I came today to report a case.
My friend is missing.
His name is Chiu Chi-keung.
You bastard cop-killer!
Fine.
Since you suspect us,
we're willing to cooperate.
We will stay here for 48 hours,
starting now.
Give me a coffee, please.
With milk, thank you.
Right away. Drink it if you dare.
He makes sense.
I will get you your coffee.
Less sugar and fresh milk.
Thank you.
Some things haven't changed.
I haven't smelled
the interrogation room in a long time.
I remember
the first time I took a statement.
You were next to me, right over there.
I remember. It was Hoklo Mun.
I was the bad cop. You were the good cop.
You were so scared
that you got a stomachache.
You love to remember my worst moments.
Well?
Chiu has vanished.
We are trying to find him.
I have told him many times
to stay away from shady guys
or he would get in trouble.
See?
Great, since you are here,
what can you tell us?
Bong, if not even you
can catch those bad guys
despite all the colleagues
who died along the way,
how can I hope to help you?
Of course you can. You're so clever.
I have a question for you.
Who is so bold,
has so little regard
for the law, so heartless,
and so cold-blooded?
Also, arresting them all
would bring peace.
What is your opinion on that?
I don't have an opinion.
Perhaps they have something against you.
In the end,
you need evidence to charge people.
Without it,
you can't do anything.
We will get evidence sooner or later.
Being so high-profile,
they are bound to make a mistake.
Once they do, we will catch them.
You are so confident.
I worry that more colleagues
will die when the time comes.
This time, the bad guys will die first.
As policemen,
we can't worry about those things
or we would have become postmen, right?
Postmen have it made,
just attending to mail all day.
You seem to be
attending funerals all day.
Let's see who will attend whose.
You're different from them.
If you wish to become
the prosecution's witness,
it is not too late.
I'm here to report a missing person.
Don't interrogate me like I'm a criminal.
I came to give you clues
to help you find Chiu faster.
The bad guys are all out there,
yet you're here talking to me.
Damn all this.
More coffee!
One, two, three, four.
Two, two, three, four.
Okay, from the top.
One, two, three, four.
Two, two, three, four.
Okay, stand still.
Watch me. Good job.
Chiu is dead. Police found his body.
They found a letter at the scene.
He took responsibility for everything.
With him dead, all the leads are gone.
It will be hard for us to charge them.
Everybody, out.
You need evidence to arrest people?
Evidence! Arrest!
That's brave.
What I am about to say
will not be a legitimate testimony.
You cannot use it in court.
You're killing your own buddies now?
You killed Chiu.
It was you at the Wong Kwun incident.
You also killed Yiu and all our men.
Why did you kill all those innocent men?
- Why?
- Innocent?
Who can be more innocent than us?
We gave our all to the police force.
We solved the case.
In court, you only needed to say one word,
and the five of us
wouldn't have gone to jail.
But you gave up on us and put us in jail!
Every night in jail,
the people we had arrested
would seek revenge on us.
Here. These.
Is that innocence?
You think you're so noble
because you spoke one truth in court.
You defended a crook
over your own brothers.
Coke was a criminal!
Don't confuse right and wrong.
You went too far and needed to pay for it.
You committed murder.
You had to go to jail.
Is that innocence?
What did you do?
You killed your colleagues and buddies.
And you killed Yiu!
You call that righteousness?
You were settling a private grudge.
If you wanted revenge,
why didn't you just come to me?
That was the original plan,
but you weren't at the mall that day.
Forty-eight hours have gone by so fast.
You have to let me go.
Bong!
Your wife is being
held hostage at the dance hall.
There's a bomb.
You bastard!
Open fire at the scene.
PNC has been shot and injured.
Bong, it's Seto Kit.
He has your wife and demands to see you.
He fired three shots.
Bong, in addition to your wife,
there are 10 children and 4 parents.
It's a very dangerous situation.
Also, Seto Kit has a bomb around his neck.
EOD checked and said that
there is a detector linked to his pulse.
The design is very complex.
The bomb squad has
no idea how to defuse it yet.
What can we do?
If we don't want the bomb to explode,
all we can do is
stop his pulse by shooting him dead.
One more problem.
Seto cuffed himself to your wife.
Stop!
Do you want more people to die?
Where is Cheung Sung-bong?
I'm here. Sir, let's talk it out.
Release my wife and the other hostages.
Come out. We will talk all you want.
Shut up!
Are you finally here?
I'm here.
What do you want me to do?
The men back there, get out.
I only want to see him.
Get out! Back out!
Okay.
Calm down.
Let the EOD
help you take off the bomb, okay?
If you want to help me, listen up
or my wife and daughter will die.
Calm down.
Let me finish first!
Four years ago,
my behavior was inexcusable.
I said you had to rescue him.
I forced Ngo to be more aggressive.
I also said
that if you fail to rescue Mr. Fok,
the whole team will be fired.
I forced them onto this path.
I was greedy for the credit.
I wanted to be on S T Fok's good side.
I should have taken responsibility,
but I didn't.
They were innocent.
I am the shame of the police force.
- I am the shame of the police force!
- I hear you, okay?
Bong.
You love to hear the truth, don't you?
That was the truth.
But we don't think he was sincere enough.
Let's give him 30 more seconds
and hope he can be more sincere.
Why did this happen?
EOD, withdraw.
Everyone has to leave immediately.
Bong!
Retreat now!
Stay away!
Give me wire cutters. Hurry!
Wire cutters, now!
I have already confessed.
Take the children and go! Quickly!
- Go!
- Run!
Help them, quickly! Go, evacuate!
Get the children out of here.
Everybody, out! It's going to blow! Run!
Bong, get out now!
Go. Leave me.
We will be fine.
The timer is connected to his pulse.
If his heart stops,
so will the timer.
Shoot him dead
if you want to save your wife.
Sir, there is no more time.
You can do this.
Okay.
Fire!
It's over.
You're okay.
I hope you understand
how little control we had back then.
Good luck.
Get everyone out, now!
Officer Cheung, we are
from Internal Investigations.
You are suspected of
intentionally shooting at the SDU,
disobeying multiple orders,
and violating police policies.
This is the warrant for your arrest.
Hey. What do you think you're doing?
Please cooperate with our investigation--
Doctor, how are my wife and baby?
Mrs. Cheung's blood pressure
and heart rate are high
due to the trauma.
Please don't worry. She is stabilized.
- Thank you.
- Please don't worry.
Officer Cheung,
as a fellow officer, don't make this hard.
Are you serious? His wife is unconscious.
Fine, I will go with you.
Wing.
Well?
Has everything been arranged?
Yes, long ago.
I have the most powerful guns
and bombs ready for you.
The bank vault
and security details are all here.
But...
You are not part of this.
What do you mean?
You dare ask me?
You have been exposed.
You are now fugitives.
I don't want to go to jail yet.
Don't give me that.
You would give up on
100 million USD?
I said you have no part in this,
but I never said I wouldn't do it.
To tell you the truth,
I have found another partner.
You may go.
What?
Why are you still here?
Get out!
You have no part
in this job either.
Officer Cheung.
That's it then. Wednesday night, 8 p.m.
What are you waiting for? Let's begin.
I have a meeting to get to.
Turn it off.
Senior Inspector Cheung Sung-bong,
this is an internal investigation hearing
presided over by SACP Lok Chi-fai.
The results will be submitted
to the Secretary of Justice.
You may be convicted. Do you understand?
You shot at the SDU team. Am I correct?
You are correct.
If you do not have
a reasonable explanation,
the Department of Justice will charge you.
You may be jailed.
Do you understand?
Yes.
- Excuse us, sirs.
- What are you doing here?
No auditors are allowed
at the hearing. Get out.
I know it is wrong of us to barge in.
But we hope
you will be merciful and not fire him.
Regardless of your relationship with him,
per regulations, you must leave now.
Sir, we are a team.
If he did anything wrong, so did we.
We must all bear the responsibility, sir!
The police force is
about responsibility and discipline,
not emotions.
If you don't leave now,
you will be disciplined.
Sirs,
the world really is
not just black and white.
There are a lot of grey areas.
In this incident, I really had no choice.
True,
I was wrong to shoot at policemen.
But I believe
that anyone else in my position
would not have made another choice
because...
I was saving my wife.
I think you
would have done the same thing.
I entered the Academy when I was 19.
I understand how to play this game.
Today, many people
who join the police force
think about making connections
rather than catching bad guys.
True, we learned a lot,
but all we do
is cover our asses and wait.
I get why I'm here.
Sir, it's just a job.
Must we risk our lives?
But at the right time,
we can be very persistent for one cause.
We can even sacrifice ourselves,
ignoring our own safety.
What are we thinking?
Not how to do less work,
but how to do better work.
Anything else?
Yes.
Regretfully, these criminals will escape.
I couldn't catch them.
It's decided.
Today's hearing
is adjourned
because I'm not feeling well.
We shall continue tomorrow
at the same time.
I cannot control
whether the DOJ will charge you.
But you are still a policeman
for the next 24 hours.
Don't disappoint me.
Hurry and catch those bastards.
Thank you, sir.
Bong, Central Crime Unit
has taken over the case.
They found a USB drive on Ma Gau-wing
containing all
the security data of BPA Bank.
They suspect a bank truck robbery.
All manpower is stationed there.
Got it. Thank you.
Bong, we just learned
that someone named David Wong
is among the dead.
He was the head of security
for Fok's HK Fortune Banking.
There is a shareholders meeting
at HK Fortune Banking today.
That means S T Fok
has returned from the US.
It is said that all merchants are evil.
Doing business is like warfare.
You can't win
without a bright and clear mind.
Who would want to be cannon fodder?
It's simple.
The lower class earns money with labor.
The middle class
earns money with knowledge.
Officer Hsia, the target isn't here.
- They already let you out?
- The target is not here.
The USB drive found on Ma Gau-wing
was planted to misdirect the police.
Look at me! The target is at Fok's bank.
HK Fortune Banking!
Prove it.
- Excuse me. Thank you.
- Thank you.
The evidence in this USB drive
is the bank truck routes
and security guard shift changes.
Everything points to the target being
this bank's cash-in-transit truck.
There is no harm
in sending some men there.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't try anything! What are you doing?
Don't mess with us.
Look, I won't transfer any manpower.
Why don't you go there yourselve
since you are used to breaking the rules?
Just stay out of my way.
Understand?
We are here
to give you leads, not get in your way.
What you are doing here is useless!
- Understand?
- You are in no position to speak!
Do you know you have
violated your superior's orders?
I have the right to report you!
Control Room, done.
Mr. Fok, we are ready.
Don't try anything stupid!
It's useless for me to come in here.
- This door is controlled by security--
- Come here.
Open it!
Don't shoot!
I beg you. I was wrong.
I did you wrong.
I am grateful you rescued me.
My statement in court wasn't aimed at you.
That's not what I meant.
But you did kill someone!
Please take all this money.
I can arrange your escape
anywhere you choose.
Call for backup!
Calling Control.
Suspects discovered
leaving HK Fortune Banking
and heading towards Tsim Sha Tsui.
They are believed to be heavily armed.
Requesting backup.
Bong, we have news.
S T Fok's body has been found
in HK Fortune Banking's vault.
Sit tight!
Get out of here!
It's dangerous!
Move! Out of the way!
Out of the way!
Get out of the way! It's dangerous!
Move!
Out of the way!
Ngo, drop your weapons!
You won't get away with this!
Fuck you!
Jaws, cover fire!
Forward!
Bong, they are crazy!
Can everyone get away?
Easy as pie!
Let's eat hot pot tonight!
Roger!
Mom!
Surrender.
- What do you mean?
- Listen to me, Wah.
Do you want everyone to die?
Drop your gun! I said, drop it!
It's not too late to surrender.
- Put down your gun!
- Okay!
I will. Please calm down.
You used to be a cop too.
Why are you taking a little girl hostage?
You have a daughter too!
Come here!
Ngo.
I can't go on.
Hang in there.
I need to rest.
Let's be buddies again in our next lives.
Run!
You have nowhere to run.
Surrender.
And go back to jail?
You say one thing and do something else.
Ching was that way too.
So as soon as I got out, I killed her.
Get up!
I have lost.
But I won't bow to my fate!
I had one thought when I was in jail.
If it had been you
who chased Coke that day,
would our destinies
have been reversed?