Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
Cherry Springs. The kind of
place that's frozen in time.
Friendly and familiar
faces on every corner.
I came back to find
comfort in that familiarity.
But beneath the facade of a
peaceful life, lies a darkness.
It seems even the quaintest
of towns hide big secrets.
And the truth?
Well, that's something I
just couldn't run away from.
Ok, come on.
Let's take a little walk.
Hey Uncle Joe. Need any help?
No, no, I think that's it.
I got the cake in the car.
We all set.
You still calling it "the cake"
after all these years?
What's wrong with that?
Well, it's your specialty.
Give it some pizazz.
Uncle Joe's Butter Bundt.
No. That's a mouthful.
People ask for the cake.
I give them the cake.
I'm a simple man.
And I love you for it,
Uncle Joe.
You know I didn't think you'd
stick around this long,
but I am glad that you did.
Well, Mom's house
isn't gonna sell itself.
Can you believe it's
coming up on a year
since she's been gone?
Yeah, I miss her
every single day.
You know I could've
handled this for you.
I know. I wanted to be here.
Anyway, all this talk of the
festival has got me nostalgic.
I couldn't miss it.
You want a ride?
Nah, I'm gonna stop by Rachel's.
See if she needs a help setting
up her pet adoption tent.
Look at you.
Been here for a
month and already
Cherry Springs,
citizen of the year.
C'mon, Bogie.
Let's go see some friends.
Come on buddy.
Come on, Bogey.
Bye. Have a good day.
Hey! Ready to head out?
Yep. Tony's out back
loading up the truck.
Hi!
Here's hoping we find
some little pups a home.
Sorry.
This guy's off the market.
This guy's taken, too.
They asked me to be a part of
the festival's eligible
bachelor auction,
but I turned 'em down.
Oh! That's a shame.
Could of used that twenty
dollars you would've earned.
Thanks, Honey.
I said he'd go for five.
Wow. Kid forgets who
signs his paychecks.
Good to see you Mel.
Hey.
Melanie, this is Ryan Monroe.
He works at the
auto body shop with me.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet ya.
And what brings you
out to this way?
Oh, I'm just visiting my
old stomping grounds.
Been friends with
these two forever.
I'm talking pre, Pre-K.
Rachel thought you'd be
back in Boston by now.
I told her you can't
get enough of us.
I guess I'm enjoying the R&R.
What did you do up in Boston?
I'm an investigative reporter
for the Boston Chronicle.
Exposes crooks.
Fights injustice.
Like Lois Lane
if she were Superman.
Always knew she
was going places.
Speaking of going places,
let's get a move on.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
Thank you all for coming
today to celebrate
the opening of the
Twila Birch Community Center.
Uh, ha ha, yeah!
A beautiful center like this
deserves a beautiful
celebration,
and our vendors and volunteers
have really brought
out their best
this year for our
inaugural festival.
Let's give it up for them.
That's right, that's right.
Now, I have volunteered
on the committee to make this
community center a reality
for the past three years.
And I can say that no one
has worked harder to bring
us here than one man.
It is my honor to introduce
to you a beloved member of
Cherry Springs, Mr. Dan Birch.
Thank you Diana for
that warm introduction.
It was my late wife,
Twila's,
dying wish, that we build
a place, where our entire
community can gather
and celebrate the spirit
of Cherry Springs.
So please sign up,
get your memberships:
because just in a few days
we're going to be offering
an assortment of classes
at the Twila center gym.
And after your workout,
after Pilates, you can
enjoy a run around the track
or even a swim
in the indoor pool.
Thank you all for coming.
And let's make this
a really special community.
Thank you.
Wow. Diana was really born
to be behind that microphone.
As a speaker? Yes.
As a singer? Not so much.
Oh, I still have PTSD from her
karaoke party
last year in Vegas.
Heads up. We've got a customer.
I-- can I...?
Yeah! Go ahead. Sure.
Sorry, he loses his
ability to form sentences
when he sees dogs.
Well, if you're
interested in adopting.
Uh no, I got enough to handle.
Come on. Please, Dad.
That's Bogie.
How old is he?
He's 8.
That's...
fifty-six in dog years.
Wow. That's some quick math!
Smart guy, like his old man.
Mention old man
and I shall appear.
I don't mind if I do.
I see you've met my niece.
So this is the hotshot reporter
you talk about all the time?
Sounds about right.
The part about Joe talking
too much, at least.
His baking makes up for it.
Well, you got that right.
I'm Melanie Abrams.
Jake Collins.
I'm just a sucker
who lost a bet.
A bet? You lose every one.
No, no, no, Jake and I,
we get together
from time to time
and watch the games.
Friendly wagers.
Well, it looks like he pays you
your winnings in baked goods.
I ain't complaining.
Dad! Can we play
that bottle toss game?
I bet I can beat you.
You're on.
It was nice meeting you.
Likewise.
We on tomorrow, Joe?
You know it. And I feel
like my luck is taking a turn.
You'll see.
Famous last words!
Quite the bromance you two have.
The way you described Jake,
I was expecting
someone, more mature.
Oh, hush up. You're not the
only one with cool friends.
Speaking of cool friends.
Hey Joe.
Hey.
I see you met Cherry
Springs' hottest bachelor.
What's his story?
Uh, moved here about a
year ago from New York.
Can't trust those
big city types.
He is a detective.
Don't know much
else other than he got
those new traffic cams
installed in town.
Bringing Cherry Springs
out of the Dark Ages.
Enjoy.
Mel! Hey!
Hey, Sarah.
Congrats on your big book deal.
Your uncle was telling
me all about it.
You got a book deal?
That Fall River factory piece
really made you a hot commodity.
More like a hot mess.
I haven't decided.
I'm not exactly in the right
headspace to write a book.
I should be congratulating you.
I heard you're gonna be parked
here full time at the center .
That's big business.
Thanks. I'm just working
on saving up money.
I'm trying to earn enough to
lease a space inside the center.
I am more than happy
to contribute to
that dream of yours.
Two lattes, please?
Coming right up.
Is that Detective Dominic?
Great speech up there.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, this is Melanie,
my childhood friend.
Mel, this is Dominic.
Or should I say
Detective Peters?
Heard about the promotion!
Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you, Melanie.
Likewise.
Here you go!
Oh, thank you!
Thank you!
Enjoy the day, ladies.
You, too!
Bye.
So cute.
Okay. Why are you
denying your fans a book?
Over a decade
of righting wrongs.
The spotlight suits you.
For every fan I've made,
I've made enemies, too.
Trust me.
Okay, well, if anyone tries
anything, I got your back.
Oh, I bet you do.
I've seen those biceps of yours.
Mom strength, it's no joke.
I'm the one taking care of her,
of course that's what she wants.
You asked her?
Yes.
What's that?
Tony, I'm exhausted.
I don't know what else to do.
Okay, It's our mother
we're talking about here!
The burden has been on me
so don't pretend like
you suddenly care!
C'mon.
I have customers,
I don't have time for this.
Hey Melanie!
I'm so glad you could
stick around for the event.
Oh, I couldn't miss it.
The center's such a beautiful
tribute to your wife.
Her journalism class
was an inspiration.
I owe her my career.
Twila taught a lot of
students over the years,
but you were always
her favorite.
Here I thought
I was her favorite.
No, you were a troublemaker.
Rachel, too.
A matter a fact,
the three of you together
were always up to no good.
Guilty as charged.
Only thing we're guilty
of is having a good time.
I requested our song!
Let's dance.
I will dance circles around you.
Wait. Who's watching my kids?
Ah no worries!
Uncle Joe's got 'em.
Bye!
Do you regret looking
into the Fall River factory?
What going to
happen to all those
workers who lost their jobs?
You got justice
but at what cost.
Knock, knock.
I got keys, remember?
Yes.
I brought you, uh, leftovers.
Oh! Thank you.
Come on.
Oh, you dancing up
a storm out there
with Diana and Rachel today.
You know, it was like
you never left at all.
Maybe I never should've,
I could've been
here with Mom more.
Making memories
instead of mistakes.
Your mom loved you
more than anybody.
She framed every one of
those articles you ever wrote.
I got no wall space
at the diner.
Well, not every
one of those stories
has a happy ending, Uncle Joe.
There's something you
wanna tell me about it?
It's nothing.
Look, I'm no fancy investigative
reporter but it doesn't take
Sherlock to figure that
something is not quite right.
One, you're in no rush
to sell this place.
Two, hardly packed any
your Mom's stuff
and three, every time I see you,
you're ignoring a phone call
from the publishing company.
The last thing I need is more
pressure and more deadlines.
I'm fine. I promise.
Just tired is all.
Okay, if you ever need
to talk about anything,
I'm right across the street.
Hey there, Boston!
Bogie!
Bogie, is that your buddy?
Game day at my uncle's,
I take it?
That's right.
Any excuse for grown men to eat
fried food and
take turns napping.
Sounds like my kinda Sunday.
Uncle Joe tells
me you're selling.
No bites yet.
I think Uncle Joe mowing
the lawn shirtless
across the street
scares folks off.
You know, if I could arrest
him for that, I would.
I think he's just trying
to make you stick around.
Well, he doesn't need me.
He's got his sports buddy now.
If Lucas had it his way
we'd still be in New York.
What brings you out here?
Not often a
high-ranking detective
relocates across four states.
Who said I was high-ranking.
You carry yourself
like someone who's a bit
above the average
inspector rank.
I'd say... sergeant?
Wow. I see those investigative
skills at work, huh.
Is that why they pay you
the big bucks in Boston?
Lucas, come on, man.
Game's about to start.
You didn't answer my question.
Why Cherry Springs?
Oh, I don't know.
It just seemed like a good
place to plant some roots,
when New York stopped
feeling like home.
You ready man.
Hello. Hello.
Guess who's here?
I come bearing gifts.
Is that Melanie Abrams I hear?
Andy! Long time no see.
Hey, come around here.
Way too long, if you ask me.
Haven't seen you
since our class reunion.
I'm surprised you
remember that night.
We actually had
to carry you out of there.
What can I say,
I drank Tony under the table.
Then wound up right under
that table with him.
Speaking of, Um, Tony around?
Oh, yeah, he's in the office.
How you been, huh?
I'm doing alright.
I was real sorry to hear
about your Ma passing.
Thank you. Yeah it's been
a hard year without her.
She was a great lady.
And those kitchen sink cookies
she used to make for us,
the best.
They were!
And I hear you're
selling the house, huh?
Working on it.
Gosh, a lot of great memories
growing up on that street.
We had some epic rounds
of flash light tag.
All those neighborhood
bike races.
You call those races?
I was just trying to keep
away from you and Rachel.
Well, you went from
running from the ladies
to running your own business.
It's a team effort. Couldn't do
it without my partner in crime.
What you got in the bag there?
Oh, just some food for Tony.
I owe him for
loaning me the car.
You're acting so weird.
Look at me.
And tell me that you're
not hiding something.
Is that Rachel?
Okay, you're lying.
You're lying.
Hey, everything okay?
Yeah, fine.
I gotta get some air.
I'll catch you later, Mel.
Rachel was really upset.
She said Tony's being evasive
about phone calls
he's been getting.
Anytime she asks,
they wind up in a fight.
Well, they have been bickering
since they were prom dates.
I wouldn't think
too much about it.
Yeah, I guess.
But Tony kinda seems on edge.
You saw him arguing
with his sister yesterday.
Yeah, well he's a hothead.
You know Tony.
To-go order is ready.
Thanks, Joe.
I had a hankering
for your onion rings
and I just couldn't shake it.
Well hey, I even threw
in a couple of milkshakes
for those two little
cutie-patooties of yours.
Oh, you think they're cute, huh?
One sip of this and they'll
be shrieking like banshees.
Easy, easy. It's me.
Sorry, I tried calling, but...
Yeah, I went for a jog,
left my cell at home.
Everything okay?
Tony never came home last night.
What?
After we fought,
I figured he was at a bar,
blowing off some steam.
But, then I woke up this
morning and he wasn't there.
I tried calling him,
but his phone is shut off.
So I called the police.
Is that unusual for him?
Well, he's been acting
strange lately, in general.
Closed off.
But disappearing on me?
It isn't like him.
I can feel it in my bones.
Something's wrong.
Okay.
C'mon. You gotta see this thing.
Slow down, dude.
There it is.
I don't think we
should go near it.
Whoever this belongs to
will probably come back.
Don't be chicken, bro.
Sick!
It's a roll of cash, dude.
Whoa. How much is that?
A whole lot.
since he left work yesterday.
Do you have the
Find-a-Friend app?
It can ping his location.
His phone must be dead.
It's not getting a response.
We can check in with Sarah Jane
at her coffee truck. Or his mom.
His mother.
She's been sick lately.
He could be with her.
This is why I needed you.
You help me think straight.
What do we got?
A jogger found the car abandoned
out here on a morning run.
Registered to one, Tony Patel.
He owns the auto repair
shop on Railroad Avenue.
Yeah. I know him.
He gave me a good
deal on a alternator.
Yeah, well, wherever he was
headed, he was in a hurry.
His tire is blown out and
there's skid marks on the road.
Huh, no sign of him?
No, no, just his cell phone,
found it in the woods.
It's a little water damaged
but should be okay.
Have your guys run
it for calls and texts.
And let's set up a perimeter.
Will do.
Yeah.
Did you find him?
Did you find Tony?
This is not a
good time for press.
There's no scoop if we
haven't started digging.
I'm not here on the job.
Rachel is Tony's wife.
He's missing.
I see.
We're going to get
to the bottom of this.
Any leads on his whereabouts?
Not as of yet.
But as soon as we know
anything, I'll let you know.
Ok, thanks.
Alright.
You know Tony
better than they do.
If he's out there somewhere,
you've gotta help me find him.
Please.
When's the last
time you saw Tony?
Eleven in the morning, I'd say.
Maybe eleven-thirty.
So Tony left the auto shop
and never came back.
That didn't raise any red flags?
No, not at all.
Tony opens the shop.
I shut it down.
That's how it goes.
Any idea where Tony was off to?
He didn't say. He was in a huff.
He and his wife had just
gotten into a little spat.
And Rachel?
She was at the shop?
Tony was being secretive lately.
Taking phone calls
in other rooms.
Giving two-word
responses anytime
I'd ask him what was going on.
I'd reached a breaking point,
I guess.
And he was having one of
those secret calls yesterday?
It was a text, actually.
Ryan Monroe,
Tony's employee at the shop.
Yeah, I was out towing a car
to bring back for repair.
It was the first time
Tony let me go out alone.
Kinda messed it up, though.
Couldn't get the cables
to work quite right.
So, you text Tony to help?
Yeah, he came out and
got the rig going again.
I towed the car back to
the shop and that was that.
That's right. Ryan got back to
the shop around 4PM or so,
towing a broken down car.
Alone?
Yeah. That's right.
He finished his work,
so I sent him home for the day,
and caught up on paperwork.
And Rachel?
Where was she?
I was home. All night.
Tony never came back.
I thought maybe he went
to get a drink, but,
I talked to Harry
at The Taproom.
Tony never showed up.
The last time I saw him
we had that stupid argument.
That's all for today,
Mrs. Patel.
We'll keep you up to date on
anything we find out, alright.
Okay.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
Alright.
Melanie Abrams, seems your
a tough person to chase down.
You're the one who's
been following me?
The van?
Not me.
I've only emailed
and called before now.
I'm Robin Carole,
from Pecanole Publishing.
Wanted to chat
about that book deal.
Right, right, sorry.
I'm just, a little on edge.
Come on in.
Lot of buzz about you.
You've proven to have
quite the keen eye
during your time
at the Chronicle.
Buzz isn't always a good thing.
Been a fan for years.
I appreciate your kind words,
but I'm not sure I have
any hot gossip for you.
I've taken a leave of
absence from the Chronicle
and it's company policy that
I never reveal my source.
Oh, I'm not asking you to.
I just want to hear
your version of what happened
at that factory
in Massachusetts.
I'm sorry,
I'm just not interested.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You have my info,
if you change your mind.
Something's been
weighing on me all day.
I should've told
you last night,
but I, I didn't think
it's any of my business.
But now, Tony's M.I.A.
And I...
It's okay. Talk to me.
I saw Tony with another woman.
Wait. What?
I was driving through
town square a few weeks ago.
This driver was too busy making
eyes with his passenger to
notice that the
light had turned red.
Just drove straight through it.
Almost hit me.
And then I saw, it was Tony.
And a woman in
his passenger seat
that was definitely not Rachel.
Are you sure it was him?
It was him.
Yeah I didn't tell Rachel yet.
But I know what I saw.
Okay, you should
go to the police.
Thought we could go together?
I don't know if I should be
getting wrapped up in this.
Okay, it's your call.
But, you in or out?
So, you recognized Tony,
but not the woman?
Yeah, I, I just know
is it wasn't Rachel.
And Rachel. Does she...
Haven't told her.
Figured we'd come to you first.
Hey, what if they faked
Tony's disappearance
and they ran off together?
You watch too much Crime TV.
Fair point.
I do do a lot of
late night binging.
Diana remembers seeing them
the week of the Fifteenth.
She also mentioned to me,
that you're responsible for
helping install
traffic cams in town.
That's right.
Well, I figured if we
can use traffic cam footage
to narrow down our
search window and find her.
I'm sorry. uh, we?
I'll take a look at
the traffic cam footage.
Thanks for the heads up.
So, that's it?
I'm sorry I thought
we were going to maybe,
check out the footage.
You know, crack the case.
Save the day.
Too much Crime TV. Copy that.
Look, I know you two are friends
with Rachel and you mean well,
but I have this covered.
Okay?
Uh, well, okay.
Okay.
Good night.
Come on.
Alright. You welcome.
Bye bye!
Hey, so I pulled the calendar
off Tony's phone like you asked.
We got lucky,
the S-D card was fine.
I made a list of his whereabouts
in the days leading
up to his disappearance.
And it looks like he trains
with a personal trainer
at Spring's boxing
every Thursday at 3.
I just need a
minute of your time.
Look, you're not a client here.
So, I can't help you out.
Please. This is important.
Your 10AM
just called in sick.
I'll take it.
You'll what?
You heard me.
I'm just a client in
need of some training.
Hey, Dom!
Come take a look at this.
Managed to track down that
traffic cam footage of Tony.
Well those two
certainly look cozy.
You don't recognize her?
No, but, uh, could be
she's not from around here.
I could look into it.
Wherever she's is,
Tony could be there
right there beside her.
And I aim to find out.
Seeing as I don't
require much training,
maybe you could use the time
to tell me about Tony Patel?
You don't quit!
Look, Tony boxed here.
He started showing up late,
and then he stopped
showing up about a month ago.
Any idea why?
Don't know,
he paid for all his sessions,
so I didn't ask any questions.
You gotta be kidding me.
Oh. Hi, there.
Why are you here?
Training sesh. Too fit to quit.
So you just happened
to be at this gym?
Small town.
Not exactly
gym-appropriate attire.
You know why I'm here.
Lats? Quads? Oh! Is it leg day?
By the way,
I was having a little
chat with my trainer, Jim.
It's Reuben.
Yeah, he was
telling me that Tony
stopped coming
about a month ago.
Okay, so where was he on
Thursdays from 3 to 4pm then?
Somewhere he felt
the need to lie about.
Would he happen to have
a locker here, by chance?
And who are you?
I don't see a...
Badge, okay. Never mind.
That's a badge.
Follow me.
Any luck with that
traffic cam footage?
Seeing as you
clearly have a habit
of eavesdropping
on police matters,
I'm gonna go with
"no comment."
Oh, come on.
You didn't even have
to break a sweat.
I saved you time here.
I find you mentally exhausting.
Does that count as a workout?
I get it.
All my brilliant
ideas blowing your mind.
Hard to keep up.
Something like that.
There you go, all yours.
Thank you.
Try the side pocket.
Preferably stuffing trash into,
particular random receipts.
Oh, okay.
Oh, here's one uh, for
Thursday, March 11th at 3PM.
Right around the time he's
usually here for
his weekly session.
Looks like he was at a place
called Smoothie Criminal.
That's a juice place in town.
Terrible name.
Great juice, though.
I could really use
one right about now.
I'm not gonna get
rid of you, am I?
Good afternoon,
I'm Detective Jake Collins
from the Cherry Springs
Police Department.
I'd like to ask you
a few questions.
Happy to help, detectives.
Oh, she's not a detective.
Right. Just a customer.
You know, my friend Tony
recommended this place to me.
Do you know him?
Oh, yeah. Tony? Sweet guy.
Great tipper.
Came here like clockwork.
Did he seem out of sorts?
You know,
he did seem kinda sad lately.
Sad.
Do you recognize this woman
here in the photo with Tony?
So you did get that
traffic cam footage.
I got that info for him.
We're kind of a team.
Yeah actually, She and Tony,
they'd come in at the same time.
And sometimes
they'd leave together.
So you have security cameras?
Yeah. The whole block,
so dentist office,
bookstore, coffee shop,
they're all on the same system.
Can you point us toward
the security office?
Yeah, absolutely.
What she means is can you
point ME to the security office.
Sure, it'll be on your right
at the end of the block.
End of the block?
Yup.
Thank you.
Hey, you don't
want to forget this.
Thanks.
You mentioned there was
a bookstore on the block?
Yup, it's right over there.
Thanks.
Bingo.
Thank you so much, officer.
That's right. Tony Patel.
Praying we can find him.
Okay. Bye.
Excuse me.
Sorry. Didn't mean to eavesdrop.
Did you say
Tony Patel is missing?
Do you know him?
We, uh, we're friends.
My name is Melanie.
I'm Emily.
I've been friends with
Tony and his wife Rachel
since we were kids.
Do you know Rachel?
Afraid I don't.
Oh, she's really worried.
We all are.
Do you have any idea
where he might be?
I'm sorry, detective.
But I can't give you
access to that footage
without a search warrant.
You gotta be kidding me.
When you two saw each other,
what did you chat about?
It's... kinda private actually.
Any information you have
could help me track him down.
Melanie, what do
you think you're doing?
Ah! Detective Collins.
Emily here is a
friend of Tony's.
Yeah, makes sense.
From the looks of things,
you two were, pretty close.
He wanted me to keep
things between us.
So, there was
something between you?
I just mean he wanted
me to keep things quiet.
About his diagnosis.
Tony, he has pancreatic cancer.
He didn't want anyone to know.
I feel bad saying anything.
Our support group urged
him to tell his family.
Especially his wife.
I see how that photo looks.
I get it.
But Tony was just
giving me a ride home.
I'd gotten some
bad news that day.
I was in remission and
found out my cancer was back.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I needed a friend. Nothing more.
Was there anything else weighing
on Tony, besides his diagnosis?
Financial security for Rachel,
in case anything happened.
But a few weeks ago
he seemed in a better mood.
Said he figured something out.
How did you know to find
her in that book store?
She could've been anywhere.
In the traffic cam photo there
was a book on the dashboard.
The only books Tony ever
reads is the sports section.
Smoothie gal mentioned a
bookstore in the building.
Took a shot.
Heck of a shot.
Kind of like the snapshot you
illegally took
of police evidence.
I found Emily
because I know Tony.
And because I'm good at this.
Admit it. You could use my help.
I certainly could use
your help at the next stop.
Yeah? Where's that?
To see your friend Rachel.
How could he not
tell me he was sick?
Well, you know Tony.
He could break a leg and
he'd try to walk it off.
He didn't want to worry you.
I wonder if Sarah Jane and his
mother know about his cancer.
Emily said he
didn't tell anyone.
So, that's it then?
He was sick and
decided to call it quits.
No goodbye letter. Just goodbye.
He could still be out there.
That's right.
You can't lose hope.
I'm gonna do everything in
my power to track Tony down.
And you got a good friend
here looking out for you.
I could use some company.
The house feels so
empty without Tony there.
How about I invite
Diana to stay over, too?
Like old times?
Sounds nice.
I know.
Okay, I'm going to make popcorn
and we can put on a movie and...
Sounds good.
Go outside. Both of you.
Call the police.
You sure?
Just go. Go.
Who's there?
None of my jewelry is missing
and all of our
electronics are still here.
What were they looking for?
Looks like the perp cut
themselves on the way in.
I'll have it tested.
And see if
they're in the system.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Sure.
Excuse us.
Yeah. Let's go.
Okay, this is
totally just a hunch.
Not the best way to start.
Just hear me out.
Tony told his friend Emily
that he'd figured out how to
take care of Rachel in
case the worst happened.
That's right.
Maybe whatever this perp
was looking for is the reason
Tony suddenly solved
his money problems.
So, what, you think Tony
had something valuable here?
And maybe someone was desperate
to get whatever it was back.
Hey Jake, someone called
the station asking for you.
Got a tip from a guy
who said his son found
something in Tony
Patel's abandoned car.
I was with my friend,
near the road by Spring Woods
and we saw a car
just like out there,
just left there, something.
Why didn't you report it?
I don't know.
Alright, go on.
Give him what you took.
Oh, Mm mm,
let's see what we got here.
Nine... Nineteen hundred.
Something weird about
that number to you?
What are you my math teacher?
Hey!
You play ball?
Starting guard for the
Cherry Springs Bulldogs.
Okay. Alright.
Bulldogs, you guys got
a game tonight, right?
Man, it'd be a shame
if you had to miss it,
I mean if I had to call
you back in for questioning.
Don't look at me.
I'm on his side.
Hey, two thousand.
Whelp, uh, thank you,
appreciate it.
Thank you, officer.
Alright, who am I looking at?
That would be William Dixon.
The man who robbed
Rachel's house.
Um, not bad, Dom.
Breaking records
with that speed.
How'd you manage that?
Gotta love vigilant neighbors
and those doorbell cameras.
I got a good shot
of this guy breaking in
and was able to match him
to a mugshot in our system.
Pretty hefty rap sheet, too.
Our boys are trying
to locate him now.
Hmm, well, good work.
What do you got there?
Those kids found
that in Tony's car.
Think it could be some of that
mystery money Tony
suddenly came into?
Not sure. Tony's got priors,
but from years ago.
Maybe worth a check in
with our friends in vice.
You know see if
there are any busts
with bills that are a match.
Can I tag along?
Sure thing.
Why? He's lawyered up
and isn't talking.
Yup.
But I got something.
Turns out this guy attended a
Reform school
for troubled youth.
You wanna know
who else attended?
Ryan Monroe.
Tony's employee
at the repair shop?
That's the one.
You want to know what else?
Ryan has a Juvenile record.
Then it's sealed.
Ryan doesn't know that.
You know the man in this photo?
Sorta. Billy went to my school,
but we weren't
friends or anything.
Any idea what he was
looking for at Rachel's?
How should I know?
We booked Mr. Dixon on
breaking and entering.
He's not the only one.
Yeah, I got a record. So what?
He stole some parts from
the shop a few years ago.
He was just a kid.
So, you took car parts
from your employers?
Yeah and Tony stole an
entire car when he was my age,
and he didn't end up a criminal!
He stole those parts before
he was ever working for us.
Why'd you hire him?
Cause they're good guys
who do nice things for people.
Tony arranged with
the court so that
Ryan could work here as
part of his probation.
So, you didn't want to be here?
Maybe not at first...
But I do now.
So Tony and Andy
don't press charges
and you end up working for them.
Is that right?
These guys saved my life.
These guys gave me a shot
when no one could care less.
He's come a long way.
So, you had nothing to do with
the break in at Rachel's
or Tony's disappearance?
I swear.
You swear?
Hey!
Look, I know you're
on this whole
"teamwork makes the
dream work" kick.
But we had an agreement
if I find something
I will come to you.
That's not why I'm here.
Okay, I think
someone's following me.
You see there.
These plates are false.
You said a van
was following you.
Are you into
some sort of trouble?
I've definitely made some
enemies over the years.
That's for sure.
The Fall River factory,
you mean?
I never said that.
I'm a detective.
You piqued my interest.
So, I did some digging.
Internet stalker, huh?
Curious as to why an
award-winning journalist
at the peak of her career
suddenly call it quits.
It was less of a peak and more
of a cliff. Went over the edge.
So Cherry Springs
is the bottom, then?
If being on the bottom
means being under the radar,
then so be it.
Look, if you're in some trouble
I can look into things further.
No, no. It's fine.
Don't go worrying about me.
The focus should
be on finding Tony.
Alright.
You let me know
if you change your mind,
you know where to find me.
I thought I was supposed
to let you come to me?
I can bend some rules.
It's the perks
of being in charge.
Alright.
Fish don't bite,
the birds do sing.
Vice just got back to me.
Found a match on
that roll of bills
those kids found in that car.
That right?
Yeah, could very well
be dirty money tied
to that drug bust
about a month ago.
What did Tony get himself into?
Hey Uncle Joe, I'm
actually making some chilli...
Sorry to cut you off,
sweetheart.
I've been with
the police all day.
I've got some bad news.
It's Tony. I found his body.
Cause of death,
gunshot wound to the back.
No sign of the murder weapon.
So, whoever did it tossed
him into the river.
And now that we know Tony's
official time of death
was between 7 and 9PM,
it clears William Dixon.
The guy who broke
into Rachel's house?
He have an alibi?
It's solid.
He was at the
River Rock Casino.
They sent over their time
stamped security footage.
Least we got him for the B&E.
Yeah, Dixon might
not have killed Tony,
but that break in and
Tony's murder are related,
we just got to figure out how.
I wish I there was something
better to say than, "I'm sorry""
There are no right words.
You being here is enough.
I have to get
back to the station.
But if you need anything,
please don't hesitate to call.
Thank you, Jake.
You guys take
care of each other.
Hi, Jake.
Hi.
Hi, sweetie.
Hey, I hope you don't mind.
I let myself in.
I made a lasagna.
Thirty pounds of
carbs just for you.
Oh, honey.
Hey.
You okay?
As okay as I can be.
I keep checking my phone,
thinking any second Tony'll
text me some silly meme.
Thank you for
taking care of Rachel.
She told me you've been putting
extra time at the
doggy day care, too.
Whatever we can do, right?
Hey, where's Sarah Jane?
I called to tell
her we'd all be here.
Tony and his sister had been
on the outs the past few months.
Yeah, I heard them
arguing at the festival.
About their mother?
Yeah.
They had their hands
full taking care of her
and trying to run businesses.
That's definitely stressful.
I think they took
it out on each other.
But I can't imagine
she'd ever hurt Tony.
No. I just wish she wasn't M-I-A
for Rachel during all of this.
No kidding.
Hey, Melanie.
What can I get you?
Well, we just missed you
at Rachel's earlier.
Just wanted to check on you.
I appreciate that.
I'm just trying to
focus on work because
if I dwell on it for
a second I'll break down.
I'm so sorry.
And Mom is a wreck.
She's already got enough
health issues as it is.
Tony had told me she
was making some progress.
Not enough.
We need to sell Mom's house
and move her
into a nursing home.
But, Tony thought differently.
I get it.
I'm in the process of having
to sell my childhood home.
It's not easy. Lots of memories.
True.
But you'll be amazed at what
real estate goes for these days.
You could sell for three times
what your parents paid for it.
So now when you go to sell
your mother's the house,
the profit's all yours?
I better get
back to my customers.
Hi!
So you said you were Tony
and Sarah Jane's cousin.
Yes.
I'm in for the funeral,
thought I'd just drop
in and say hello to Aunt V.
Thanks for the tea.
Oh, it's no trouble.
Mrs. Patel should be
up from her nap soon.
It's terrible what
happened to Tony.
He was so sweet to his mother.
He visited all the time.
Yeah, Sarah Jane
actually mentioned
wanting to move
her to a nursing home.
I think that's the plan.
Do you think she
needs to be moved?
In her current state, yes.
But it's a shame.
If you'd asked me
a couple of weeks ago,
I'd say she was fine.
How strange.
A rapid decline, huh?
Like somebody flipped a switch.
Forgetting things,
extreme anger.
I thought it could possibly be a
side effect of her medication.
Right.
Sarah Jane mentioned
a prescription
that was doing
wonders for Aunt V.
Oh what was it called,
something hard to pronounce.
Memantine.
That's it! And you've
been keeping up with it?
Sarah Jane administers
all her meds.
I'm just with Mrs. Patel
in the afternoons.
Hi. I need to pick up my
Mom's Memantine prescription.
Name is Vera Patel.
Date of birth is 4/23/50.
Please verify the address.
27 Fairdale Road.
We called you to pick up
this prescription weeks ago.
I'm sorry.
Things have been
unusually hectic lately.
It's very dangerous to stop
taking that medication abruptly.
Mom has been acting
differently lately.
Are violent outbursts and
memory loss side effects?
Yes. It's very common with
Alzheimer's patients
stopping Memantine.
I'll fill it for you now.
Thank you.
So you think Tony is
getting in the way
of Sarah Jane's
career aspirations?
She wants to open a coffee
shop inside the Twila center.
She told me herself.
Selling her mom's house gives
her the money to fund it.
I gotta say, this is good.
Never thought I'd
hear you say that.
No, I mean your Uncle's fries.
But yeah.
This is a solid lead.
How's Rachel doing?
She's keeping her head up.
I don't know how she does it.
It ain't easy. That's for sure.
I'm gathering you know
from personal experience?
Friend on the force
back in the Big Apple?
My wife.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have.
No, no. It's fine. I mean...
We were assigned partners.
Real competitive.
First I was hot on her heels,
then head over heels.
First came love,
then came Lucas.
New York is a city
that doesn't plays nice.
We knew what we were
doing was dangerous.
But we figured, you know, hey,
we'll move somewhere
safe for Lucas.
But before we could...
Liquor store shootout and
a stray bullet caught her.
I'm so sorry, Jake.
You know after she died,
everywhere I looked,
just reminded me of her.
So I figured you know, hey,
come to a new new place.
Well it doesn't get easier,
just different.
That's right. Look, I know
I've given you a hard time,
and I'm sorry.
I just don't want to
anyone else getting
hurt on my watch.
I appreciate it,
but I can take care of myself.
You sound like Shae.
Okay, uh, let's press reset.
So, Whoever trashed
Rachel's house
was looking for
something valuable.
Right. Something Tony
had to provide
for Rachel after he died.
So, we've searched the house,
doggy daycare and Tony's car.
we searched the auto shop,
What, what is it?
I talked to this kid.
He said he found
cash in Tony's car.
I need to take another
look at that GTO.
You can take that
to forensics, yeah.
There's gotta be some
secret compartment,
false bottom,
something we missed.
Man, I'd love to drive
a car like this someday.
Stick to the task at hand
and maybe you will,
young grasshopper.
Dom, come take a look at this.
Does the stitching on
the passenger seat look
a different color than
on the driver's side?
I mean, maybe slightly.
But it's an old car.
Sun might've faded it?
Or because it's
a different thread,
because one of these
seats has been opened
and stitched back up.
Whoa!
Would you look at that.
What's he doing with
this kind of cash?
My guess?
This is Tony's insurance plan
he had hidden away for his wife.
What is all that?
You tell me.
Found it in your brother's car.
Over a hundred K.
I have no idea.
I think you found
out about Tony's stash.
Got him out of the way,
then you hired someone to toss
his house looking for the cash.
I didn't kill my brother.
I loved Tony.
What about you Mom?
You love her?
Of course.
Withholding medication that
don't sound like love to me.
Should I get a
lawyer or something?
I don't know. Should you?
I've been putting in long
hours at the coffee truck
and forgot to pick it up, okay?
I don't buy it.
I think you sabotaged
your mother's health
to sell her house
for your own gain.
So, my question is what
would you willing to do
to your brother Tony to
get your hands on this cash?
I know nothing about that money.
And even if I had the money,
I wouldn't lease a space
from the Twila Center now.
Why's that?
Dan Birch said the center isn't
off to a hot start financially
so I'm holding off.
Well you know not
opening a coffee shop
doesn't exactly exonerate you.
Can I please go now?
You can go.
But don't make too
many plans, Ms. Patel.
Thank you everyone for coming.
And thank you to Dan Birch
for hosting us here.
Tony was my best friend
and he was the most generous
person that I've ever known.
You wanted the
shirt off his back?
You just ask him for it.
I didn't know the first thing
about cars til I met him.
But he had this
infectious enthusiasm
for everything that he loved.
His wife, Rachel,
knows what I'm talking about.
And I can tell you
without any doubt,
that he loved you more than
anything in this world.
I miss her, too.
It's like I can feel
her with me, in this house.
There's no rush to sell.
Would it be so
bad to stay a bit?
I admit,
it is tempting sometimes.
It wouldn't have to be here,
although of course that
would be my first choice.
I would just love to see
you settle somewhere
where you could be happy.
Call someplace home.
You know the dinner
rush is callin'.
Hey Diana! What's up?
You don't say?
This is the deed,
signed by Mrs. Patel.
Diana knows her realtor.
And this is Mrs. Patel's
signature on a tax document
from last year that
Rachel got for me.
The signatures don't match.
How can you be...
You see those tiny dots?
Often the forger will pause
to refer back to the original
signature and then
press down on the paper
when they begin
the stroke again,
causing these
ink blots there.
Where did you learn that?
Research for an article I wrote
about a forged
letter at a museum.
Huh. So Sarah Jane forges
her mother's signature
and takes ownership
of the house.
But she's not
opening a coffee shop,
so why the need for fast cash?
She's not?
She told me Dan Birch said
the center's in the red,
so it's not worth her while.
Really?
Because Dan told
Diana that he paid for
all of Tony's funeral costs.
Why would he
volunteer to do that
when the center is
financially trouble?
Very strange.
Especially for two
men who weren't close.
You make a big show
of your generosity
because you're feeling
guilty or redirecting focus.
If Dan and Tony
were into something,
that's probably why they wanted
Sarah Jane out of the center.
So she wouldn't get a whiff
of whatever they had going on.
I'm gonna track down Dan,
see what's what.
But I like where your head's at.
Like peanut butter and
chocolate, the two of us.
I wouldn't go that far.
Sarah Jane must be confused.
Like any new business
we've had our growing pains.
But we're doing fine.
Then why tell her
she couldn't move her
coffee shop into the center?
I don't mean to be rude,
but Sarah Jane is not
the most reliable person.
I think it best she stick
to operating her truck
outside in the warmer months.
She said you paid for
Tony's funeral expenses.
That's pretty generous
for a guy you barely knew.
Tony came to me a while back,
asking if the center made
charitable contributions
to individuals
for cancer treatment.
Unfortunately, we don't.
Anyone else know
about this visit?
No. Tony wanted to keep
his diagnosis private.
I felt horrible
about turning him away
so I paid for everything
out of my own pocket,
it was the least I could do.
Where were you on
April 17th, between 7 and 9PM?
That the night
Tony was murdered?
Let's see.
I was at dinner
with Maureen Silver,
she serves on the
board at the center.
Do you have receipt?
I'm sure my secretary filed it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Hello, Detective Collins,
this is Estelle Bradley.
I'm the Patel's real estate
agent, returning your call.
Yeah thanks for
getting back to me.
I was wondering,
uh could tell me
the day and time Sarah
Jane was in your office?
Sure. Give me a just a moment.
Actually, we signed at
the property. Ms. Patel asked
that we meet after work
on Sunday the seventeenth.
I arrived just before seven
and we finished up
around quarter to nine.
Nine, okay.
Um, and you were you
with them the whole time?
I did step away to take a call.
I was gone five,
maybe ten minutes.
So, Sarah Jane was
forging documents
during Tony's time of death.
Her alibi's clean.
I'll keep pressing Dan Birch.
Right now he's our only
person of interest.
I found some old photos
in the back of Tony's closet.
Look at you guys in
your football jerseys!
Rach, can I keep some of these?
I'd love to frame
them for the shop.
Yeah, of course.
Whatever you want.
We're all here for you,
you know that.
Look Uncle Joe,
don't worry I'm fine.
It's just a minor
concussion and some bruises.
I think it's
best you let Jake
take care of things from now on.
But what about Rachel?
She's my friend.
Exactly!
And she wants you to be alive.
With your mother gone,
you're the only family
that I have left.
I'm sorry to worry you.
I promise to be careful, okay.
Yeah, look,
it's been a long day.
I think I'm going to
go ahead and take a walk.
I'll be back.
Hey Joe.
Hi girls.
Hi! Oh, you two are
a sight for sore eyes.
I think I gave him a scare.
We were all so worried.
Thank goodness you're okay.
I'm very lucky.
What happened?
My brakes, they just...
gave out.
That doesn't make any sense.
I mean, Tony would never let
you borrow an unsafe car.
I had it towed to the shop,
Andy will get it sorted out.
I'm just waiting for
my discharge papers.
You think someone
tampered with your car?
We should tell the cops.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
I dunno, Mel.
She might be right.
Look, I appreciate you both
looking out for me, really.
But whatever it is,
I'll handle it.
What are you doing here?
Rachel told me
about the accident.
Why didn't you call me?
I just... I wanted to get
more information first.
It's nothing.
It's not nothing.
This is the exact thing
I was afraid might happen,
you get caught up
in Tony's investigation
and you put yourself
in harm's way.
Well, if I was
actually targeted,
all the more reason
to find Tony's killer fast.
Mel!
We just finished
inspecting your car
and it looks like someone
tampered with your brakes.
How can you be sure?
The car had a complete work-up
before Tony gave it to you.
Yeah, I changed the
brake pads myself.
But it looks like someone
cut through the brake lines.
But, not completely though,
cause you didn't notice
when you started the car.
Well, whoever did
this was smart, then.
They gambled the lines would
snap first time
you hit the brakes.
I'm gonna to need that paperwork
from the full work-up
before it was loaned to Melanie.
As well as what
you inspected today.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
I'm opening up a
full investigation.
No arguing.
Okay, you're clear on the plan?
I can not believe you
suckered me into this.
It's for Rachel.
Yup.
Dan! Fancy seeing you here!
Hi.
Hello, ladies!
I heard the fried clam
lunch special was amazing.
I had to try it for myself!
Yes it is! I come here once
a week for my cheat meal.
Okay.
You guys want to join me?
Oh, sure.
Love to.
Awesome.
Great.
Remember the Cherry Springs
production of West Side Story?
Oh, no.
What?
You were a great Officer Krupke.
My granddaughter though, she's
been bitten by the theater bug.
She starred as Annie last fall.
That is wonderful. Let me see.
Let me see a pictures?
It's about time you asked.
OK, let's see, let's see.
Okay, hang on one sec.
Sadie is so grown up.
I remember when she was born.
Do you know what goes
really well with fried clams?
Key lime pie!
Who wants to go halfsies?
No cheat meal's complete
without dessert!
Yeah.
None for me.
I've gone a little
overboard lately.
Alright, you and me. Let's go.
Come on, kiddo.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, no! Hey!
Okay, no problem, no problem,
I'll just get some napkins.
Hang on.
Almost there.
How long does it
take to clone a phone?
Okay, here we go.
Let's get this cleaned up.
Here you go.
I managed to save it
before the deluge.
Oh, thank you.
Alright, let's eat.
Oh, I love this.
Waiting on an important call?
Uh, something like that.
You promised me you would
let Jake handle things.
I know. I know. Okay I just...
I keep thinking that if
I can help find Tony's killer,
if I can give Rachel justice,
then maybe I can redeem myself,
in some small way.
Oh, honey.
Tell me what
happened in Fall River.
You mean what wasn't published?
That's right.
As far as I can see,
warning people about a factory
abusing it's workers
is a good thing.
I wanted the front page.
So my editor let
me hold the story.
That week,
a factory worker died.
That's exactly what
your article was about.
Negligence and poor
working conditions.
Yes, but had I published
the article sooner,
he might still be alive.
Your aim was to help people, you
gotta cut yourself some slack.
I thought that article would
actually force the owner
to improve conditions
but he just closed down the
factory and moved it abroad.
We all go through life,
doing the best we can
with the information
that we have, at the time.
All those poor people
in Fall River out of work.
Look at me.
Yes, they all need new jobs,
but at least they're alive
to do it. Thanks to you!
I hope someday I can
see it like you do.
Uncle Joe,
Can I borrow your car!
Yeah.
Be careful.
Thank you.
Alright.
Jake! Meet me at
Dan Birch's house right now.
I'll tell you when we
get there! Just hurry!
Oh, why is the
door open like that?
That's strange.
Stay here.
This is Collins.
I'm going to need backup.
For a unresponsive male with
a gunshot wound to the chest.
Confirming the victim
as homeowner, Dan Birch.
so we'll take it to the station,
We'll have cyber
crimes work on it.
Great. Um, run Dan's
personal financials, also.
Yeah, you got it.
Alright.
You okay?
I will be.
Guess it's just hitting me.
It's a lot.
Take all the time you need.
We found Dan Birch's cell.
Password is 2356.
I don't even want to
know how you know that.
I looked over his shoulder.
Kinda like you're doing now?
And I cloned his phone.
Cloning a phone is illegal.
Let's call it questionable.
I already know the rules,
I deleted the app.
There. I saw that text.
"Cops talked to me today.
You need to fix this ASAP."
Can you trace that number?
I don't know, I don't
recognize the area code.
It's probably from
a burner phone.
It's untraceable.
You still think
Ryan Monroe is innocent?
Look, I've been here
for almost two hours.
And I'm starving.
Could I at least
get water or something?
Later.
I'm gonna tell you something.
Dan sent a text saying
you were getting greedy
and they want to cut you out.
I'm not the only guy in town
with the last name Monroe.
Don't play games with me.
Cut you out of what?
What did y'all have going on?
I have no idea!
I barely knew the guy,
the first time I talked to him
was at Tony's memorial service!
So you don't know Dan Birch.
And you don't know
William Dixon,
who's awaiting trial for
breaking into Rachel's house.
Good. I'm glad you caught him.
Looks like sometimes
you can do your job well.
You are hiding
something from me.
No, I'm not.
What are you doing here?
Figured Jake
wouldn't have enough
to charge you with
and you'd be released.
Exactly.
Because I didn't do anything.
I think so, too.
The only way to clear your name
is to figure out who's trying
to throw you under the bus.
I know you don't
know me very well,
but would you be willing
to sit down and talk?
Dom. Come in here
and look at this?
Yeah.
Cyber was able to get
into Dan Birch's laptop.
Take a look.
A few months ago, Dan Birch was
close to declaring bankruptcy.
Had three personal credit cards,
maxed out.
Okay...
Now, last week,
right before Tony disappearance.
Dan Birch paid out all his debts
in giant, lump sum payments.
Not only that,
he's got a pretty hefty
sum in his checking.
Dan Birch was laundering money
through fake accounts
at the center.
Whoa. But why? And for who?
I don't know,
but the money
found in Tony's car
was scrubbed clean by
none other than Dan Birch.
And you're sure Dan
never came into the shop.
Tony never mentioned doing
any business with him?
No. Nothing.
I really miss Tony.
The garage isn't the
same without him around.
How's it been,
working with Andy?
He's a great, too.
You know, um,
they're both real generous.
Andy's been letting
me leave early,
but still gives me
a full days pay, so.
That's nice of him.
Yeah.
Shop would be swimming in
cash if it wasn't for all the
family and friends
discounts they give out.
I'm guessing those freebies
are left off the books?
Pretty sure.
Do you know any
of the other customers
that they loaned
cars up to recently?
No, no, that's Andy's thing.
Yeah, the cars are gone for
a week or two at a time.
The cars come back,
Andy services them.
If you were going to
hide something in a car,
where might you stash it?
Behind the AC vent or
inside the spare tire.
If you wanted to get
real clever with it
you could make a secret
compartment onto a car part,
like a muffler or something.
Not that I have any
personal experience in that.
Why?
Oh, just curious.
You know what,
you stay and finish.
Whatever meal that is.
There's something
I got to look into.
So I was going over the River
Rock Casino security footage.
Thought I'd spot
Ryan with William,
catch Ryan in a lie.
And did you?
No. But I found something
even more interesting.
That's Dan Birch!
And there's William Dixon,
who we know was involved
was involved in
a local drug gang.
The only reason why
an upstanding citizen
would get involved
in cleaning money
for a local drug gang
is greed and desperation.
Yeah, and based
on Dan's finances
we know it's the latter.
I'd bet the farm, our boy
Dan was a gambling addict.
That's where all his money went,
the River Rock Casino.
You know Dan never
did alibi out.
He could be Tony's killer.
But then, who killed Dan?
Yeah, okay,
we'll be right there.
That was the coroner.
He just finished Dan's autopsy.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Melanie.
Andy.
How'd you get in here?
What is that?
Looks to me like drugs.
Ah, Tony.
I knew he was
desperate for money
to leave behind for Rachel.
But do you think he...?
Dan Birch is dead.
What? How?
Someone shot him.
So he was involved with Tony?
Who... was Ryan involved?
The police seem to think so.
This is crazy.
Well, it certainly is.
You know, before Dan died,
he texted with
someone about Ryan.
Who?
The police don't know.
It was to a burner phone.
That's too bad.
Yeah.
Ryan mentioned you've been
letting him leave work early.
Made me wonder what was
going on here after he left.
TOD for Dan Birch is07PM.
07?
That's awfully exact.
Well he had a pacemaker.
The thing recorded
his very last heartbeat.
Dominic, the last text
that Dan Birch sent,
the one that incriminated Ryan,
was12.
Well that certainly
complicates things
since dead men don't text.
We got to run, Doc.
Thanks.
Why couldn't you just mind
your own business, Mel?
You were running
drugs through the shop.
You killed Dan Birch.
And you killed Tony.
I didn't kill them, okay.
I swear I didn't kill them.
Okay, then put the gun down.
Just, tell me what happened.
A couple guys approached me,
offering me a lot of money.
It's supposed to be easy.
Bring in cars with
these special mufflers.
I remove them,
I get the drugs out,
I reinstall the mufflers.
That's it.
Why would you get involved
with something illegal
when you have so much
going on for you at the shop?
Because I wanted
something of my own.
My name might be on
that sign out front,
but this place was Tony's.
I thought you were best friends.
I know.
And I loved that
guy like a brother.
But Tony called the
shots and I'd had enough.
So, I thought I could
make some quick cash
I could finally open
up a place of my own.
How did Dan get involved?
We needed somebody
to clean the cash.
So he ran it through
the Twila Center.
Why would he agree to do that?
Because Dan's a gambling addict
and he's up to his ears in debt,
It wasn't hard to convince him.
And everything
was working out fine,
and then Dan got greedy.
And he took bigger risks.
And we got way in
way over our heads.
So, what happened?
Tony happened.
He found a bunch of cash
and he wanted answers.
I tried to explain it to him.
When that didn't work
I tried to cut him in.
He told me I had
one week to stop
the operation or
he'd tell the cops.
But Tony kept the
money for Rachel.
How did you know that?
The police found it sewn
into the seat of his car.
Yeah, I looked
everywhere for it.
Cause I knew if I
couldn't up with that cash
I'd be on the hook.
So, you sent William Dixon to
break into Rachel's house?
And you cut my brakes because
you knew I was getting
close to the truth?
No, that wasn't me.
I swear, Mel,
I had nothing to do with that.
Okay, so, Dan killed Tony,
the drug dealers killed
Dan and you framed Ryan?
I found Dan's body after
the dealers killed him
and I sent that text.
Ryan's a good kid.
Okay.
But, I was desperate.
Okay, Andy look,
you made some bad choices.
But you don't have...
Listen you can turn this around.
Okay, just, just,
give me the gun.
I can help you.
You said it yourself.
I've made a mess.
And now I got to clean it up.
Talk to me Andy.
Okay, just, just...
It doesn't have to end
with one of us getting hurt.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Mel.
I thought I told you to
finish eating your pancakes.
I suspected the
same thing you did,
and I lost my appetite.
Police, show me your hands!
Thanks for coming.
Are you okay?
I will be.
Just a little shaky.
You have the right
to remain silent.
How'd you figure it out?
Oh, something Ryan told me
because I know how to get
people to open up to me.
What you did was
extremely dangerous.
You don't listen.
But you're a good investigator.
And a good friend.
Thank you.
Oh! Hi! Hello!
These are for you.
Aww, they're beautiful.
I picked them out.
That's so sweet.
There's something I want
to say and it can't wait.
On the list of things
that Tony loved most,
his shop was only second to me.
So, Ryan I want
you to take over.
Tony would be so
happy that it lives on.
What do you think?
Yes! Of course. Wow!
Thank you, Rachel.
I won't let you down.
Tony would be
really proud of you.
To Ryan!
To Tony.
To Tony!
Actually, I have my
own good news to share.
I called my publisher
this morning
and I've decided to write about
my experience in Fall River.
Yes.
And I figured what better
place to write a book
than surrounded by
all the people I love.
Oh, so you're staying!?
Yes. Yes. Yeah.
You see.
So, I looked into it and
the day your brakes were cut
Andy and Ryan were five hours
away picking up car parts.
So he was telling the truth.
Hey, we'll get to
the bottom of this.
But in the meantime,
just be careful.
I will. Thank you.
Alright.
Lucas, tell Bogie
you'll see him soon.
Bye, Bogie.
See ya.
Bye.
Tony's investigation
proved I can't just stand
on the sidelines when
there's injustice at play.
It's like my uncle always says.
Helping people is what I do.
I didn't want to tell my story,
but I realize I have to.
So here goes.