Downloaded from
YTS.MX
- * MTV *
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
- [whistling]
[humming]
[device beeps]
- Oh, shit. He's on it.
- Fuck it, it's gonna go.
[device beeps]
- Oh, shit. Whoa.
- Oh, shit, shit, shit!
Shit, shit!
Shit, shit, shit, shit!
Ah, shit! Ah!
Hey! Hey, somebody!
Call the fire department.
Get the car.
We're gonna have to call
air traffic control.
- [whimpering]
- I don't see him.
I don't see him.
Ah!
- He's right there.
He looks like Gonzo up there.
- There he is!
There he is!
- Hey!
- Jim!
It's Trudy!
Take one of these.
Jim, Jim, this is Trudy Wiegel
on the radio.
Over, 192.
- Hey, Trudy. Go for Jim.
- This is Raineesha.
She wants to say something
to you, Jim.
- Dangle, I see your nuts!
- That can't be the first
time, can it, Rai-Rai?
- Jim!
- So I'm still over Nevada
airspace, yes?
- You're confirmed
over Nevada airspace, Jim.
If you could just take
a little peeksy
inside my neighbor's backyard,
because I think she may
have stolen my weed whacker.
I would much appreciate it.
Over, 10-4, good buddy.
- Trudy, that's a confirmation
on the weed whacker.
It does look like it is
in your neighbor's yard.
Is there--not that you guys
aren't being helpful,
is there anyone on the ground
who could give me ground
support, do you think?
- Um...
- He's heading toward
the Bowling Hall of Fame, Clem.
You got to head him off.
- Yeah, I'm all over it.
I got eyes on him right now.
I'm chasing him at 90 miles
an hour down 395. Stand by.
I don't fucking care.
- He keeps going like this,
pretty soon he'll be out
of our jurisdiction.
- We'll see about that.
- Hey, guys, and good news.
I found my Go-Gurt.
[gunshots]
Shit.
What?
[gunshots]
They're shooting at me!
- But they're not hitting
anything.
[gunshots]
- Damn it!
- Oh, shit. Sorry, Jim.
- Whoo-hoo!
Norman Reedus's company
makes these.
[grunts]
Ah, shit.
Ah! Oh!
- [laughs]
- Don't worry, guys.
- [yelping]
[screams]
[all shouting]
[dog barking]
I'm actually okay.
[bicycle bell dings]
all: Oh!
- Except my spine!
I don't have a spine anymore!
- Go, go, go, go.
[heroic music]
* *
- These last few years have
been a nightmare to be a cop.
You're walking on eggshells,
and it's twice as bad
for someone like me.
Maybe, like,
a hundred times as bad,
because I hate everybody.
I literally
can't stand humanity.
So for me, I got to get over
hating everybody,
or my individual hatreds
come off like prejudice.
I'm a good guy.
I treat everybody the same.
I fucking hate them.
- It's been a bad year
for cops, man.
Between the Antifa/
Black Lives Matter guys
that have been trying
to defund us
and the Blue Lives Matter crowd
that actively tried to kill us,
I should have been a fucking
garbageman like Dad said.
- To be honest,
I thought I was gonna skate--
skate by, 'cause,
you know, I'm...
I'm the hip-hop cop,
you know?
People like me.
But it turns out they, uh...
they lumped me in.
They lumped me in,
and they hate me too.
- Good morning, gang.
- Mm.
- I hate it here.
- Good morning.
- [sighs]
[exhales]
I know it's been
a rough couple of years.
- Suck a dick, asshole.
- You're absolutely allowed
to vent like that.
Declan, the next time you feel
that rage, and I know--
Are you on the--
you're on your meds, yeah?
- Yeah.
- What are they giving you?
- LSD.
Everything's fuzzy
on the edges and drips.
- That's okay.
But you're not thinking
about hurting anybody, right?
- Oh, yeah. All the time.
Whatever Dr. Migifingers
has prescribed to you
to get through
this trying time,
stick with that.
- Why can't we all
just get along, guys?
Right?
- How come she's doing okay?
I don't get it.
She was the most fucked-up one
out of all of us,
and somehow she's doing okay.
[alarm chimes]
- [exhales]
- Sorry, that was
my medication alarm.
- Holy shit.
- That's quite a selection.
- White wakes me up,
blue calms me down.
Orange keeps the demons
from dancing all around.
And then this blue one
is so I don't get
bloating and gas,
and that I don't
shit my pants.
- What is going on?
- How do I get me
some of that?
- You just call the lady
and say,
"I'm thinking about
harming myself and others."
You have to say "and,"
not "or."
- Oh, you said "and others."
- And others. That's it.
It's the "and others."
Uh, in other news,
everybody knows Pizza Midget.
- Oh, yeah, they got them
little midget pizzas.
- Yeah, um, so apparently
this Q...
or QAnon,
whatever that is,
has been, uh, saying defamatory
things about them
on their message boards
and such.
- Pedophile ring
in the basement.
- That's what they said,
but to my knowledge,
there is not a pedophile ring
in the basement.
- No.
- Do they have a basement?
- They don't even
have a basement.
- No, they don't even
have a pinball machine.
- So that explains
this document.
So what's happening is
Pizza Midget
is suing Q
for libel.
And we need to--
- Like "QAnon" Q?
- Yes. The actual Q.
We need to put this in the hand
and serve Q.
- How are we supposed
to find Q?
The whole thing about Q
is that nobody knows where Q is.
- Does nobody know--
- That's the whole thing.
- Is Q even a person?
- We got to put it in the trunk
of Mr. "Snuffleufagus."
- All right, wait,
are you saying "Snuffleufagus"
or "-upagus"?
- "-Ufagus."
- Uh-uh.
- Is it "-upagus"?
- It's "-upagus."
- Oh, my God, dude,
don't get into this again.
- I got to get into it.
I have to get into it.
Om break!
all chanting: Om.
- It's "-upagus."
[guitar strums]
- Click on that article
about the Hollywood cabal...
- There it is.
- See if there's something like,
"If you want to contact Q,
click here."
- Contact Q.
- Look at all them people
they said is pedophiles.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- Tom Hanks?
- Yeah.
- I mean, those are some
ugly-looking white people.
- Steven Spielberg
has actual horns?
Oh, click on the pillow guy.
The pillow guy.
- [overlapped chatter]
- Oh, the pillow guy!
- There's so many
I could click on, guys.
- Hey, look at that.
- Okay.
- Q's Booze Cruise.
They're having a convention
on a boat.
- They're actually having--yes.
"Leaving from Panama, Florida,
to Nassau.
Fun events, lectures,
get together with QAnon..."
- I will volunteer.
- I'm dialing the number.
I'm dialing. I'm dialing.
- I'm in.
- I will volunteer to do this.
- I want to do this.
- Nobody sound like a cop!
- Uh, yeah, hi.
Um, I saw your--
the ad for, uh, the--
the Q's Booze Cruise.
- Hey, honey!
Are you on the phone?
- [in high-pitched voice]
Yes, Daddy.
- Sorry, I have many,
many children
who need my attention.
- Daddy, I'm hungry!
- [in Southern accent]
I'm here too, Daddy!
- I have a blended family,
and my children
are always pulling at me
in a million directions.
Ha, ha, ha.
I-I saw the posting
on our amazing--
our amazing Q site
for the Q's Booze Cruise.
Oh, that leaves on--
that leaves on Wednesday.
Uh, is the big guy
gonna be there?
Are there nine slots available?
There are?
Great, great, great.
And how much--
how much are those?
Do you have anything
cheaper than that?
You do?
Do you have anything
slightly cheaper than that?
That sounds amazing.
Great. Nine.
- Yes! Yes!
- Where we go one, we go all!
[all cheer]
- * Who let the dogs out? *
* Who, who, who, who? *
* Who let the dogs out? *
- Ah. Stop.
[coughs]
- [speaking foreign language]
- Junior Jr.,
please don't paint
the police car, Junior Jr.
- I want to paint
the police car,
and I'm gonna do it anyway!
- I don't mind getting out
of town for a couple of days.
* *
- * Who let the dogs out?
Who, who, who, who? *
- [screams]
- * Who let the dogs out? *
* Who, who, who, who? *
* Who let the dogs out?
Who, who, who? *
- It just goes to show you
that vision-boarding works.
And I am gonna land me
a bajillionaire,
because that is what I deserve.
[laughs]
Oh!
- Ah! Freedom!
* *
God, I hate this city.
- What's in the box,
you ask?
[chuckles]
No one asked that.
I just said it rhetorically.
I have some friends
in the box.
Some friends who are my ticket
out of this shithole.
- Sitting for paying
customer only.
- I am going to buy something!
- * Who let the dogs out? *
* Who, who, who, who? *
* Who let the dogs out? *
- My old friend, the sea.
Mic check. Mic check.
This is Johnny Tremain.
- * Who let the dogs out?
Who, who, who, who? *
* Who let the dogs out? *
* Who, who, who, who? *
- Welcome to Q's Booze Cruise.
Where we go one,
we go all...
to shuffleboard, on Deck 3.
- Thank you,
and have a patriotic day.
Don't forget
to own the libs.
- Oh, hi.
- Hello!
Welcome to Cruise--
Blue's Clues--
Welcome to Q's
Booze Cruise.
- [laughs]
Yeah. Nailed it.
- Thank you.
- Hi. I'm, uh, John Tremain.
- Oh.
- I'm a disgruntled, uh--
- Ooh, a double-platinum
elegance package.
- That's us. That's us.
- Love it.
- Just sign in here.
- Right.
John Tremain.
- Mm-hmm.
- And the job: laborer.
Disgruntled laborer.
- Yes.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you. Welcome.
- Great. I don't know--
- Thank you.
- Hello.
- Hello. Nice--hello.
- Morning.
- Hello, ma'am.
- Welcome to Clues Booze
Cruise--Q's Bees Cru--
Q's Booze Cruise.
- You know,
I'm here as an individual.
I'm not part of his, uh, part...
- It doesn't matter.
- Just a solo person.
Everybody's giving me
backstory today.
- I'm single.
- Uh-huh.
[light music]
- [laughs]
Mahalo.
"My hollow" stomach's
gonna be filled with buffet!
[laughter]
- I don't get that.
I don't get that at all.
- Oh, my God, I'm gonna play--
I'm playing so much of that.
- You can't.
It says you're not allowed.
- Oh, it's closed.
Oh, look at that.
Anybody got a 5
to give the lady--
Cute lady bellhops,
We give them a 5?
- I didn't bring any money.
- Hi, how are you? Hi.
- Stop.
- Oh! Oh, my God.
- Before you come on the boat...
- Uh-huh.
- We have to do health.
- Yeah.
- We have to do waiver, okay?
- Uh-huh.
Don't read. Just sign.
- Do not read.
- Initial. Initial. Sign.
- You have to sign a waiver
to eat at the buffet?
- Please be quiet.
I'm doing demonstration, okay?
- Please be quiet, guys.
- Ah. Ah. Ah.
- [screaming]
- We take temperature bottom.
- Okay.
- Oh, right there?
- From the back. Now bend over.
He's okay. He's okay.
- Is it okay? Oh, great.
See? Guys, this is so stupid,
it's easy.
- I have to check
your genital, okay?
- Yeah, yeah, of course.
You just got to check that?
- No, open more, okay?
I'm looking.
- Right after this, we get to go
on the stuff and everything?
Right up--
- No. Shh!
Next!
- Okay, I'm done.
- Maybe--excuse me,
if I could make a suggestion.
If the rest of the guys could
just all get your penises out,
then they're ready for her,
so then we can move it along...
- That's a great idea.
[applause]
- I don't want to take
my penis out.
- Hello, everyone!
- Oh, hello!
[applause]
- When I say, "hell,"
you say, "lo."
- Hell.
all: Lo!
- Hey!
- I am Captain Bonsoifisse.
And, yes, I am that
Captain Bonsoifisse.
- Oh!
- Hello. Before you wonder,
I have been acquitted.
All good.
Everything is good now.
- Great.
- Hola. Bienvenidos.
Hello. Primero Officer Memes
deporting for duty.
[laughter]
- That is a joke,
but by the way,
he actually has been deported.
- But we cannot talk about it,
okay?
But welcome. I am so happy
for you to be here.
I'm a fun guy, but, uh,
we do have some bad news.
all: Oh.
- Unfortunately.
We are dangerously low on beer.
- Oh.
- What?
- We currently have two types
of beer left.
- Okay.
- It is clam-nado hot beer.
- Ooh.
- Okay? It is very hot.
And we also have
a clam lite lime beer.
- What if you're allergic
to clams?
- Good question!
Let's move on!
- Oh, fun. Fun.
This is gonna be great.
- I have something very serious
to talk about now.
- Great.
- A lot of people say
the silent killer at sea
is diarrhea.
- Mm.
- Not true.
Diarrhea at sea can be loud.
- Very loud.
- Now, in the next three hours,
I am going to teach you
how to keep your diarrhea
down by the minutes using our
handy-dandy diarrhea app.
- Oh, okay, cool.
- With any luck,
we will be able
to keep your diarrhea
down to the first
five faces.
- Okay.
- Is there anything
we can specifically avoid
to keep from getting
in the bottom three?
- Yeah.
- I have never seen a cruise
without diarrhea.
- You're gonna get it.
- I don't want to get diarrhea.
- I didn't want to be born
with one leg
slightly shorter than the other,
but I was, and I lived with it,
and look at me now!
Bon!
- Listen, I didn't want to live
with my handsy uncle
when I was nine years old
either,
but I did it
and we got through it.
- Unbelievably depressing.
- [whistle blows]
- Okay, time to go to your room.
[excited chatter]
- Sorry. Excuse me.
Hey, Mr. Memes.
Mr. Memes, hey.
I just wanted to ask you,
what are you guys--
how are you guys set
for entertainment on the boat?
- Uh, you know,
we have the karaoke machine.
It's out of order,
but, you know...
- I would love to get
a couple minutes
just to pitch you something...
- Okay.
- That I think
could change your life
and save you a small fortune
with your entertainment dollar.
- Oh.
- It goes a very long way.
- We like to save money
around here.
- I can tell.
[smooth guitar music]
* *
[klaxon blaring]
[hull creaking]
So--
[electricity pops and crackles]
This--
I kind of like it, actually,
down here.
This is executive
double platinum?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
What's below executive
double platinum?
- Nothing.
- You are lowest.
- Right.
This is rustic.
[laughs]
Almost to a fault.
- It's nicer than that place
we had in Loughlin.
- By a lot.
And, uh, yes.
- You know the best part?
- Yeah.
- No windows.
- Mm.
- I have a hard time
getting to sleep sometimes,
but I feel like there's
so little oxygen in here
that it's gonna be pretty easy
to doze off.
- You want to work.
You want to work a little bit
when you sleep, you know?
- Earn your life.
- Earn the trip, you know?
- Is that a bat?
Those aren't bats up there?
- Oh, yes.
- Those are bats?
- Yes, they come with the room
complimentary.
- Oh, they're moving.
Look, they're moving.
They're wiggling around.
- That's beautiful.
- Aw, there's the baby.
- Oh, that's a baby!
- Aw!
- They're a family.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Johnny Tremain has landed.
- Hi.
- Hi!
- I'm gonna need you
to check your guns.
- I'm good, actually.
- Oh...
- No, last Q conference
in Dallas,
there was open carry.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah, 42 people
had catastrophic injuries
at bingo night.
- Oh, well, that makes sense.
- Yeah.
- He has a code he lives by.
Will you just pry it
from his hand?
- Just pry it.
- Okay!
- If you don't pry it,
he can't give it.
- Once you're off the boat,
Second Amendment.
- You're the--
You're the pink hat--
That's you!
- Yeah, that's me.
- You're the lady
from the peaceful protest.
- Yeah.
- Remind me?
- Yeah, she pooped
in Nancy Pelosi's desk
at the big peaceful protest.
- You did not!
- Yeah.
- You're that lady?
- Yeah. Remember?
- Look at that.
- Oh, my gosh! Whoa!
- You know Charlie Kirk.
- Color me starstruck.
- Wow.
- Holy cow.
- Would you like to buy
a copy of my book?
- You wrote a long book.
- Yes, please. How much is it?
Well, they're $9.99,
but $49.99 if I autograph it.
- Oh.
- Oh, wow.
- We'll just look at it.
- We're gonna look at it and
remember it was really great.
- Well, think about it.
- Thank you very much.
This was great.
I'm sure there's tons
of big stars
that we're gonna meet, so...
- I mean, I heard--
I heard Q was here.
- So where's his book table?
Or her book--
their book table?
- The Q.
- Do--do we--
do you recognize him?
Here?
- Okay, I don't know who he is.
- Mm-hmm.
- But I-I know he's handsome.
I know he's white,
but that's all I know.
- Well, we all assume.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- Are those the Black Lives
Don't Matter people
with the little tiny guns?
- I want a picture!
I got to get a picture!
- Got to go. Got to go.
- Have a good conference.
- It was nice meeting you!
- Thank you.
Oh. Oh, thank you.
- Hey.
[whispers]
Fan out. Reconnaissance.
Don't do anything to draw
extra attention to us, okay?
- No.
- Fan out. Recon mode.
Can you hear me?
Tremain to Chet.
Trudy.
- Yes?
- What's with the dress?
- It's part of our backstory.
- Oh, good.
- You and I...
we're a couple.
- Yeah.
- You...
are a 79-year-old Presbyterian
who owns an auto parts
dealership in Fresno
that you bought with your dead
grandma's money.
I am a 29-year-old trophy wife
who has a keen eye for fashion
and a masters degree
in birds and things.
I...
have one flaw,
and it's that sometimes
I'm a little too nice.
Our neighbor Rodrigo
has three dogs.
One of them is missing.
We think the nephew took him.
I think he may have
eaten him.
If you panic,
squeeze my hand 11 times
and we will start making out,
got it?
- Okay.
Trudy?
- Hmm?
You still didn't
explain the dress.
- Oh, I never got
to that part in the story.
I think I'm wearing
the wrong outfit.
- It's okay.
- Hello, um, strange...
people.
- And the deep state's really,
really...
doing--but--getting us hard.
- This is my husband.
Our neighbor's name
is Rodrigo.
- Don't do the whole thing.
- He has three dogs,
but one of them is missing.
- That's Raineesha.
It's Raineesha.
- It's a horrible story.
- You recognize Raineesha,
right?
- I didn't at first,
I got to be honest.
- I didn't think you did.
- Those are very distracting.
You should put them away.
- Nice meeting you, Coco.
- So nice to meet y'all too.
A beautiful QAnon couple.
- You should see him
with his pants off.
[all laugh]
- Hollywood's full of vampires.
Nothing but vampires.
[laughing]
- So nice to meet you,
Julian.
And thank you again
for getting me this free drink.
- Yeah, if I could have
bought it, I would.
[both laugh]
I couldn't buy it, though.
I couldn't buy it.
So good to be here.
- I'm surprised.
You know, 'cause I ain't think
they was gonna have
too many Blacks around here.
- Yeah, it's a lot
of white folk, ain't it?
Let me tell you
a little bit about myself.
- I'm listening.
- I'm an entrepreneur.
- Mm!
- I own a couple of businesses.
- Well?
- Yeah. I do real estate.
So, yeah...
- Married?
- No, I am not married.
- Wait a minute.
I'm gonna step a little closer.
- Okay, come on.
I'm single.
[laughter]
Look at you!
Oh, you got me blushing
up in here.
Golly. I also like to, um,
collect my poop,
so the government
does not clone me.
- M'kay.
- So you guys know
who, uh, Q is?
Q?
- What do you mean?
- That's a weird question.
Let me ask you something.
You guys cops?
- That's what I'm wondering.
That's like
a cop-like question.
- Yeah.
- "Do you know who Q is?"
- You know about
aliens and stuff.
Let's not get into
the grays, all right?
Aliens are real.
You got to be careful
of them too,
'cause they will abduct you.
It's happened.
And let's not talk
about the probing.
Did--did they get
whatever was in you?
I hope so.
[applause]
- Thank you. Thank you.
Uh, welcome, searchers,
pioneers, and patriots.
I-I hate to start off
with bad news,
but Sidney Powell will not
be giving our keynote address.
She is under house arrest
right now.
Uh, I apologize.
And, again, ever hopeful,
ever forward.
That is what we believe here.
Yes, thank you.
[cheers and applause]
So, um, you know,
Q is a question,
a query, and a quest.
And pretty soon,
it is going to be a quality,
much like the quality time
that many of us are being denied
spending with our kids
because of divorce court judges,
resentful ex-wives,
traitorous family members
who screenshot
our Instagram posts
to show family counselors who
are deciding visitation rights,
who are believing the lies
of the deep state.
Those masks will be lifted.
We are about to experience
much the same experience
that Rowdy Roddy Piper
experienced
in the movie "They Live,"
when the...
[applause]
- Yeah!
- When the big, uh,
deep state illusion beam
was finally destroyed.
That will soon happen for us.
That is what Q is doing.
And the masks will be lifted.
All of that will be lifted.
[applause]
Q has cracked the code,
and once you crack the code,
it is so easy to see
what is hidden out there.
What is keeping you from--
from real strength.
From real reality.
From real love.
That kind of code-cracking
is what we are here
on this ship doing.
You're the only ones
who can see it.
And thank you guys so much
for being on this cruise.
Full truth ahead.
And, um, everyone
enjoy the cruise.
Thank you, thank you.
[applause]
- Heil Hitler!
- No, Trudy, no.
Trudy, no, no, no, no.
I mean, kind of.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's right, yeah, yeah.
- Right?
- I mean, heil all kinds of--
- Heil everybody.
[PA system chimes]
- Check with staff
before you use
any restrooms on the second,
third,
fourth, and sixth floor.
- Morning, gang.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- [sighs]
Oh, God. Ooh.
- Hot, right?
- It feels like almost
dangerously so.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, creeps up on you.
- Johnny Tremain
has a thought over here.
The little bird, the, uh...
the speaker.
Little weirdy
with the short arms.
- Oh.
- Eyeballs all over you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Saw that.
- I thought he was looking
at me.
- Mm-mm.
- No, I think he's got a...
- He got a motor...
- He got a Marty Feldman?
- Yeah. Well...
- I thought he was
looking at my vag.
- He got a little bit.
- Nope.
- Here's what I'm thinking.
That horrible little
weird little midget man.
- Yeah.
- He feels like he's got
an itch he needs to scratch.
- Is this code too?
- Yes.
- Clemmie, code name: Roxy.
- Yeah.
- Could get next
to that little weirdo.
- Know what I mean?
- Easy.
- Honey trap.
- Seduction.
- I did it to become
Miss Teen Whiskey Pete's,
and I can do it now.
- I believe the after-party
is on the lido deck at 7:00.
Perhaps there
we should lay our trap.
- I have never felt
such a sense of purpose.
It's been a long time.
- On behalf of the Reno
Sheriff's Department,
I authorize you to go to third,
but not home.
- This might be kind of obvious,
but home is--
home run is vag.
What would butt stuff be?
- Grand slam.
Finishing in the butt?
- That's a walk-off.
- Wait a minute.
But what if you finish with
your peen between the teets?
What is that called?
- Sometimes it's just an error.
[solemn chanting]
* *
- Who is currently planning
a coup in Venezuela?
Is it Obama?
Hillary Clinton?
George Soros?
All of the above?
Which is the best chan?
4chan? 8chan?
69chan?
[chuckles]
German chancellor Angela Merkel
is, in fact,
a robot sent to the future
by Adolf Hitler...
- Ooh! Oh, I'm sorry.
[both laugh]
- [imitates robot beeping]
- I'm so clumsy.
- So close here. Um...
- I really liked what you were
doing onstage today.
- I noticed.
- Um...
You...
You know a lot about this--
this Q.
This mysterious Q.
- I mean...
do you have a couple hours?
Because--
- I do.
- Oh. Well, um...
Q is something I would like
to talk about with you.
That was a Q symbol
I just did on your shoulder.
- Listen, I, am...
waxed, chillaxed,
and unvaxxed.
So...
- [laughs]
[tinny fanfare music playing]
* *
- Mr. Memes.
Enchanting ladies
from...
the mysterious east,
prepare for little Mr. Jimmy
and friends,
available in your
floating showroom
in perpetuity
across the seven seas.
Now, sit back and enjoy
187 minutes
of world-class puppetry.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, got it.
[twangy guitar music]
* It's little tiny Jimmy
and friends *
* It's little friend Jimmy
and a box full of men *
* If you did a little sin,
gonna make amends *
* It's tiny little Jimmy
and puppet friends *
* *
[glass shatters]
[in high-pitched voice]
Hi, Mom!
Here we go!
Better get ready
to start the show.
- [chuckling]
Oh...
- Hey.
- Good to see you.
- [laughs]
- Beautiful night, huh?
- Yeah.
I guess you could
call it that.
- You know,
there used to be a saying
when I was in school.
Why think when you can drink?
My private stash.
Go ahead.
- I like that saying.
- Mai tai.
- Yeah. Now it's...
both: Our tai.
[both laugh]
- Cheers.
- Oh!
Have you ever played
"I Ain't Never"?
- "I Ain't Never."
I don't--
- It's the Black version of
"Never Have I Ever."
- Well, you know,
that game is probably
a lot more fun with women.
- I'll start.
- Okay.
- I ain't never...
run a ship aground
in Puerto Rico,
thinking that I saw someone
that I knew.
Yeah? Mm. Mm.
- That's so specific to you.
- Ah!
I need you to do me a favor.
- Hmm?
- Take these keys.
I am...
way too messed up to drive.
- I'm gonna walk away now.
- I'm going to watch you.
Bon!
- Voyage.
What the fuck?
- How was everybody's
intermission?
Act trois.
In which we travel...
south of the border.
Fuck it. I'm sorry.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Fuck it. Oh, fuck.
Hernan is about to learn
a little lesson
about amigo-ship.
And when you're on a ship,
friend--friendship is the--
Ah, fuck it. Sorry.
Hernan's gonna learn a lesson,
that when we're helping
other people...
[breathing heavily]
Hernan--fuck it, fuck it.
Fuck it!
We're gonna skip ahead.
Skip ahead, skip ahead.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
[boat horn blares]
[cell phone chimes]
- Oh!
Time to take my medication.
Oh, shit.
Meh, should be fine.
- [inhales and sighs]
Look at you.
Did you steal that gown
from a princess?
- Well, it's a Frozen
Halloween costume
that I bought at Rite Aid,
so, yeah, kind of.
- [laughs]
I'm Xavier Rothchild III.
I quit a successful career
in the cinema
to become a doctor for cats.
And now,
I go wherever I'm needed,
which is anywhere a cat
needs a doctor.
- Isn't that a...
a veterinarian,
technically?
- I don't think so.
- Okay.
Well, my name is Trudy.
I am an undercover cop,
which I'm not
supposed to say,
but I kind of feel like
you and I are getting along
really well,
and I can probably tell you
all my secrets, so...
- You can tell me anything.
- [titters]
- Trudy?
- Yeah?
- Would you like to join me
for a cocktail
and a walk around the ship?
- Well, I'm supposed to join
my friends on the lower deck
for a diarrhea test,
but I suppose I could.
- Oh, these are not for us.
Uh, I put out
a cigarette in this.
Sorry, let me get us
some fresh drinks.
- I'm not thirsty.
I'm not thirsty.
- It's okay,
come with me.
- Okay.
- Come with me.
- No, Caesar,
I will not renounce
the Christ.
[deeps voice]
This Christ seems to have
a power over mens' souls.
My name is James Ron Dangle.
That is the show.
I'm 66 years young.
I'm between apartments
right now.
I would love--
in fact, need--
to do this for you.
But it's not just me
you have to thank
for tonight's entertainment.
Let's meet all
of the 88 performers
who just brought you
this wonderful tale.
- Who eats baby hearts
to stay young-looking?
Kate Beckinsale?
Gwyneth Paltrow?
Ryan Seacrest?
- I'm in, um...
I'm in Cabin 1503.
- Okay.
- 1-5-0-3.
- 1503.
- Which is, um, you know,
March 15th backwards,
you know.
The Ides of March.
It kind of makes sense
they gave me that room.
- I'm gonna take your word
for that.
I liked this when I understood
what you were talking about,
and I feel like
where you were going
was you were going to
ask me to...
go bang in your room.
I felt like that's where
this was headed.
- Let me--really quick,
could I just, um...
[clears throat]
Would you come bang in my room?
- Let me tell you
what I'm looking for from you.
- Oh, okay.
- Okay.
We're gonna bone
and we're gonna talk about Q.
We're gonna listen
to some smooth jazz.
- Uh-huh.
- And we're gonna make this
the best two-day booze cruise
in all of history.
- Prepare to have your mind
and, uh, vagina blown apart.
- Ah.
[smooth jazz music]
- You got this.
You got this.
You give this guy
a blowner,
he might accidentally
tell the truth.
Happens to me.
- He's not gonna get
too far in my pants.
I've got an old-school Cotex
with a belt.
- That's my girl.
- Impenetrable.
- Well, well, well.
What do we have here?
- Oh, man!
Talking about the kraken.
- Why are you guys living
down here in the basement?
- It was a package deal.
- It was a package.
It seemed like--
they make it sound way nicer.
- Very affordable.
- Hey, man,
how about the great awakening?
- Yeah. The storm.
- Epstein didn't kill himself,
right?
Ha-ha!
- The storm's coming.
- Come on.
- So, uh...
word has it you guys...
know who Q is.
[clears throat]
- Why would we?
- I mean...
I'd give my body freely to Q,
just on principle.
- Fine.
FBI, guys.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
- Oh, my God.
- Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
- God damn it.
- Oh, my God.
- What a good badge.
- Okay...
Reno Sheriff's Department.
- You're kidding me?
- My name is not
Jonny Tremain.
- You're deep cover
looking for...
- No way.
- Oh, hey! Whoa, whoa!
- Oh!
- Oh, man!
So the deep state...
- Yes.
- Is gonna just do...
- Oh. You can cut the shit.
I'm CIA.
- You're CIA?
- I'm with Vice News.
Is anyone QAnon
on this whole boat?
- Hold on, I'm with
"Mother Jones" journal, man.
You think I would be here--
I wouldn't be wearing
all these flags and shit.
I'm a Black man.
- I thought you were a real Q.
- I thought you were real.
- Yeah, you were good!
[overlapping chatter]
- You look amazing.
- You look like that lady.
- Thank you. I know.
I really do look like her.
- Now that I see you,
I've seen you on Vice News
thousands of times.
- Yes.
- This is the lady
from Vice News-
- Oh!
You made that Nazi guy cry
in the thing
with the Proud Boys.
I've masturbated to you.
- Since we're all
law enforcement,
how about we, uh,
pool our resources?
- Why would we do that?
We got a beat on them.
I mean, we-we...
- [whispers]
- We don't have any...
- No, we're good.
What's in it for us?
- Look, we're the FBI.
We've got all
the high-tech shit.
Cameras, audio equipment.
You name it, we've got it.
How about a wire for her?
- Yeah.
- Yup.
- Yeah, let's wire her up.
- Working with the FBI! Whoo!
- Sweet.
And CIA. Hi.
[knock on door]
- Come in.
- Oh.
Hello, patriot.
- Hello, my cool ranch
Kate Winslet.
- [laughs]
- How are you? Mwah.
- Oh, I love that you
left your shoes on.
- Oh, well, you know,
you got to have
a couple of things
to throw off later.
I love a stakeout.
- [whispers] It's the best.
- It's the best.
Good just--
good coffee.
You get to smoke
in a tiny room.
I know it's a little
on the nose, but,
man, if we had, like,
old Chinese takeout,
wouldn't that be amazing?
- Oh! Takeout.
- Yeah, yeah, that's--
that's good.
- We're gonna get this guy.
Hope you don't mind
that I didn't make the bed.
I didn't want to try
to hide the lie
that I had been tossing
and turning
and thinking of you.
- [laughs]
- Because I have been.
- Well, great.
It smells so masculine
in here.
- Oh, well, that is the spicy
cheese puffs.
And if you're thirsty,
the clam lite lime.
- Oh.
- I would, uh, open one,
but I'm, um--
[stomach gurgling]
The clam lime kind of,
you know...
it's a kind of rush hour deal
right through me, so...
- Oh, as someone who has had
the clam lite lime
splatter shits before,
believe me, I shat my underwear
right off one time.
- Oh, um, sorry,
but vocalization leads to
visualization,
leads to realization.
Be right back in a second.
- Okay.
- I'm just gonna
leave the door open
and talk to you from here.
- Great, I have no problem
with that at all.
- So seriously,
thanks for coming...
[farting]
Uh, to just, you know,
I guess hang out and talk.
Most people--it's really rare
when a woman comes into my room.
- [laughing]
I don't believe that.
[toilet flushes]
You strike me as quite the lad--
Lady-killer. Oh.
- [stammers]
I wish I had some of those--
What are those matches
with the kind of--
Anyway, I just think
you're really pretty.
[stomach gurgles]
And...
- So do I.
And that's something
we have in common, Ron.
- It's like we were
talking about earlier.
Just, you know,
feeling so alone and, like,
there's no one you can...
[stomach gurgling]
- I hear it. I hear it. Go.
- Oh, okay, okay.
- It's fine. Yeah, I hear it.
- Wait, wait, wait.
This'll be--
this'll be a quick one.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, just a little quick jet.
A little quick jet! Oh!
- She should be getting
extra combat pay.
- Whoo!
That one had a bone in it.
[toilet flushes]
- Tell me some things, Ron.
You have such a way
about you.
I...
I bet you have a lot of...
secrets, maybe,
that people don't understand.
- Actually hitting the nail
on the head.
I...
I mean...
in a way,
I am a secret.
Forget--nothing, nothing.
Forget I said that.
I...
- Go on.
I'm listening.
I'm here for whatever
you want to say.
- And this will just stay
between us?
- Obviously.
- Because I don't think
I ever want to leave your side.
Right now...
You
are scratching the back...
Of Q.
I'm Q.
- He's Q.
- This guy's Q?
- This guy's Q. He's Q.
This is Q.
- Shit. Go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Oh, shit! I'm sorry.
[smooth jazz music playing]
- Here's to butt stuff.
- Always.
- Mm.
- Freeze! Freeze!
- Freeze! Police!
- [screams]
- Pizza Midget says hello!
- Fuck you, deep state!
- [screams]
- Oh, my--
- Get him!
No, after you.
- [stammering]
- Let me lick it!
- No, don't lick it!
Jesus Christ!
Get him off me!
[klaxon blaring]
- Freeze!
[guns cock]
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Don't you move--
[overlapped shouting]
- You're not canceling me!
- He's getting away!
[overlapped shouting continuous]
- Out of my way, lib-tards!
- Get one of the--
- Junior, Junior! Shit!
- What's happening?
- Uh, okay, uh,
what do you do?
- You push the red thing!
You push the red thing!
- Where's the red thing?
- Hold on, guys.
Hold on, I got it.
Slow and steady
wins the race.
Ow!
- Freeze, you little weirdo!
- [groaning]
It's okay, guys!
I'll just use
my getaway sticks.
Here she comes.
- The jig is up.
We know you're Q, guy.
- Q is bigger than me!
Q is bigger than all of this!
- I got a shot!
I got a shot!
[gunfire, screaming]
Sorry, undercover deputies
working on behalf
of Pizza Midget.
Sorry, we have badges, I swear.
[gunfire]
- Help me, Roger Stone!
- Don't shoot the food, Dangle!
[exciting music]
- Oh!
[screams]
* *
Hey! Hey!
- I got him!
Ha! Go, go, go, go!
- Freeze! Sheriff's Department!
- I'm coming for you, my love!
- Ron, over here!
- You'll never catch Q!
* *
[guns cock]
- [clears throat]
You've been served.
[camera shutters clicking]
- I'm gonna blog so hard
about this on my Reddit thread.
[solemn chanting]
[laughing and whooping]
- That is how you do it.
Clemmie, is your clam-nado lime
disagreeing with you?
- It's just not taking me
where I want to go.
- Oh, God, that's so hot.
You did great, kid.
Then why do I feel so shitty?
- Maybe part of you is sad
just because he's so gross.
- He's so gross,
and you've had a lot
of clam-nado lime now.
It's probably just that.
When I was feeling
mixed up and confused,
which I did a lot,
my Uncle Frederick
used to sing me
a little song that went
just like this.
[lively banjo music]
* *
* She dashed by me
in painted-on jeans *
* *
* And all heads turned
'cause she was a dream *
[clanging rhythmically]
- * In the blink of an eye *
* I knew her number
and her name *
* Yeah *
* She said I was the tiger *
* She wanted to tame *
all: * Caribbean Queen *
* Now we're sharing
the same dream *
* And our hearts,
they beat as one *
* No more love on the run *
* *
- * I lose my cool
when she steps in the room *
* *
* And I get so excited
just from her perfume *
* She smells good *
* *
both: * Electric eyes
that you can't ignore *
* *
- * Hey, ow! *
- * And passion burns you
like never before *
* *
[upbeat bluegrass music]
- * I was in search
of a good time *
* Just running my game *
* Yeah *
* Love was the furthest *
* Furthest from my mind, yeah *
all: * Caribbean Queen *
* Now we're sharing
the same dream *
* And our hearts,
they beat as one *
* No more love on the run *
- Whoo!
[saxophone solo]
* *
- * Yeah *
* Caribbean Queen *
* Now we're sharing
the same dream *
* And our hearts,
they beat as one *
* Yeah *
* No more love on the run *
* *
* Caribbean Queen *
* Now we're sharing
the same dream *
* And our hearts,
will beat as one *
* *
* No more love on the *
* Run *
[all whooping and laughing]
- Yeah!
- That's great.
I hate to break up
whatever this is,
but, uh, Ron is not Q.
He's a gym instructor
from Fresno.
- I guess Arby's has, like,
a restraining order against him.
- That's it.
- Sorry, guys.
- Sorry.
[solemn chanting]
- One more time from the top?
* *
- The ship has officially
run out of toilet paper.
Please use
your assigned towel.
- I can't believe I played
stinky pinkie
with someone who wasn't Q.
- Oh, okay.
[steel drum music playing]
- I hear steel drums.
I smell coconuts.
- Oh! We're in Nassau.
- Whoo!
- We're in Nassau!
[all chatter excitedly]
[upbeat calypso music]
* *
- Nassau! Nassau! Nassau!
Nassau! Nassau!
- Okay, everybody!
[blows whistle]
Please, attention.
Open your orejas, please.
I have some bad news.
I have just been told that we
have a super strain of diarrhea.
The worst diarrhea known to man.
No one can dock in Nassau.
We are officially quarantined
here.
- What?
- No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Mr. Memes.
- We've been bubbled
this whole time.
- You are not keeping us
on this ship!
We have already had
the worst diarrhea!
We're a pod. We're fine.
We're going. Good day.
[overlapping shouting]
[all screaming]
- Nobody,
absolutely zero people,
will be able
to leave this boat.
- All right, you guys,
enjoy your search for Q.
Bye, guys.
- Thank you!
- That's a sad look.
- Except for these guys.
They have to leave.
- Hey, Asians, Hispanic dude.
- Uh-oh. Oh, oh...
- As minorities...
- That's it, that's it.
We need to stick together,
all right?
You know what I'm saying?
Like, if my back
can wash yours,
then maybe you
can wash mine, right?
- Yeah, man,
me and my boy here,
we just like to party
up in the--
- No! No!
- No?
- No, no.
So how many days
are we gonna be quarantined?
- Just a short,
happy 30 days.
- What?
[overlapping shouting]
[tense music]
- [sobbing]
* *
- I got it. Let go!
- No!
No! No!
[panting]
* *
- I know you're watching me.
- I know you know
I'm watching you.
I knew it.
- [counting in native language]
Okay, bye-bye. Go.
That's all you get.
Use front, use back.
* *
[dispenser whirring]
- Hey, Travis...
- Huh?
- Why are you doing
all those so fast?
[sniffles]
- Toilet paper, Boss.
- Thank you very much.
- How long we been
quarantined?
- Almost a half-hour.
[mellow music]
* *
- Well, look at you.
- Nice to see you again,
Clemmie,
or should I say, "officer."
Well, it's not nice
to see you again,
you star-spangled turd.
- Oh, really?
The liar is offended
to see me again.
- I lied, but you should
expect that from a girl.
You said you were Q,
and that's a lot worse,
and I am so disappointed.
When a--
a goddess like you
shows any bit of interest,
of course I'm gonna lie.
I know you didn't ask to be
this gorgeous and this perfect,
but you have to be ready
for guys to do stuff like this
sometimes, okay?
- I am very interested
in the goddess part
of what you were saying.
- It doesn't matter.
I should have known
that you were a mirage.
I don't know if you can
understand this,
but my whole life
I felt like I am stuck
in this disgusting,
low-rent desert,
and I'm the only one
with any real inner beauty
and any actual dreams.
And I just want to rise up
like the burning eagle god
that I am.
Can you understand that
at all?
- Everything you just said
is everything
that I have written
in my own Akashic records.
[both moaning]
Oh!
[giggles]
[sultry music]
- Oh! Ah! Ah!
- Oh, yeah!
- [laughing]
- [groans loudly]
[sighs]
That was incredible.
- I'll bet it was.
- Yeah.
- I admire your efficiency.
- You know, only three men
have ever seen my labia before.
One was my ex-husband,
one was my pediatrician,
and the other
was an ambulance driver.
So consider yourself
very lucky.
- Proud to be number four.
- [giggles]
- I am tormented
by your beauty.
- Mm, can I take this
out of my mouth--
- Not yet.
- Okay.
- Just finishing the shading
around your beautiful face
and pubis.
- I'm gonna need a lot of
shading,
FYI, for the pubis area,
because one thing they don't
tell you in health class
is that your pubis does get
a lot bigger the older you get,
and I'm not bragging.
[laughs]
- Almost done with the shading.
- How does my butthole look?
- Let me take a look.
A little more pink.
- Hmm. You flatter me.
- Relax the face.
And relax the anus.
Yes. Perfect.
- [exhales]
- You know,
after being inside of you
for two seconds like that,
I just feel
so much closer to you.
I feel like I'm a part
of you now.
And I...
I would never ask this,
but I feel so comfortable
with you.
What's your real name?
- [sighs]
It's kind of embarrassing.
Clementine Anne Johnson.
- Clementine?
You mean like the sweet
nibbly cookie?
I'd say that's perfect
for you.
- Well, I never thought of it
like that.
- [laughs]
- But that makes sense.
- You know...
I'm not really Q.
I'm his right-hand man.
In a lot of ways,
I'm his mouthpiece.
I deliver his messages,
and sometimes...
[dramatic music]
I invent some of those messages.
Just the stuff like,
you know,
Britney Spears
is really Lee Harvey Oswald.
And, you know--
- That was you?
- Yeah, that was me. Yeah.
- [gasps]
- Yes, there's a bit
of a thrill of, you know,
being able to kind of control
the zeitgeist,
but the lifestyle
is fucking amazing.
We own Jeffrey Epstein's
old island.
It has a secret bunker
underneath it.
It has a food court with every
discontinued fast-food chain.
Kenny Rogers Roasters,
Burger Chef;
they're all in operation,
only at that one food court.
- Go fuck yourself.
- Yeah.
- You know what I find crazy,
Xavier?
You're a painter.
I make dolls
out of my old pantyhose,
so we're both artists.
And we randomly meet on a cruise
and fall in love
on the exact day
that I run out of
my anti-psychotic medication.
I mean, if that's not kismet,
I don't know what is.
- Perfect timing.
- Wiegel!
Wiegel, you're naked.
- I know that.
I'm being painted.
- What?
- Please leave us alone.
- Wiegel, Wiegel,
you are naked in the buffet.
- Can we please
have some privacy?
- Your friend cannot be naked
in the buffet.
- I know.
- We have a sign that says so.
You'd think we don't
need a sign that says,
"Please do not be naked
in the buffet," but we do.
- I see it.
- This is a diarrhea nightmare.
- I apologize.
Trudy, please.
- Don't listen to him, Trudy.
It's just you and I.
- Don't worry, sugar balls.
I only have ears for you.
- Trudy, that's a plant.
- God, you look so beautiful
right now.
- Come back, Trudy.
Come back!
- Your jealousy is gross.
- Trudy!
[smooth bass music]
* *
- Morning, gang.
all: Morning.
- Morning.
- I know it hasn't been ideal...
- [PA system chimes]
- If you haven't filled out
your diarrhea app,
do so immediately.
Failure to do so will result
in a very serious penalty.
Remember, message
and data rates may apply.
- Raise your hand if you forgot
to log your diarrhea today.
- I didn't forget,
but I tried and it crashed.
- Almost everyone!
- When I say, "hell,"
you say, "o."
Hello! Hello.
I just got off of the phone
with the doctors
from the ship
and the mainland,
and I am now
certifiably insane.
They actually used the word--
and I never heard a doctor say
this before--
cat shit crazy.
So I don't want to say
screw all of you,
so I will say
fuck all of you.
Fuck the ship life.
This jacket was
my grandfather's.
They took it off his cold body.
He wasn't dead yet.
You can have that.
Take that for you.
[exclaims]
Oh!
- Oh!
- [laughs]
Big son of a...
- I think this is cause
for concern.
all: Oh!
- How come he hasn't got
diarrhea?
- [whistle blowing]
Okay, everybody.
- Yes?
- Calm down.
All calm down.
- Why did you say "calm down"?
We were relatively calm.
[overlapping shouting]
- We were calm!
[whistle blowing]
- As you can see,
the captain has gone
a little bit crazy.
- Certifiably cat shit crazy.
- And since that is, you know,
he's a little cause for alarm,
I am taking over.
- I am not taking orders
from another guy in shorts!
- Pass. Hard pass.
- And you know what?
None of you updated
your MyDiarrhea app.
- I did, though!
Except for not them!
But I actually did.
You are not taking the ship.
Thank you, but no thank you.
[gunfire, screaming]
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Put them below deck.
- Okay, okay, we'll go.
[all shouting]
- No. No. No. No.
- Come on!
- Oh, my God.
No. No, oh, my God!
- Yes. Guns! Guns! Guns!
Guns! Guns!
When I say "guns,"
you say, "mm!"
- This is like that movie.
You know, the guy
with the glasses.
Come on, the one--
Come on.
When you--the thing?
- "Amistad"?
- Yes.
- How did you get that?
- I'm sorry, don't do that.
Don't compare a slave ship
to what we're in.
- How is this not
the exact same thing?
- Black people still have
high blood pressure today
because of what happened.
The salt was so...
- Was that the name of
that movie, by the way?
- Oh, don't make this
be like the whole thing
when he gives that
whole lecture about "Roots".
- I'll be honest, if I was--
[PA system chimes]
- Hello, everyone.
This is your captain.
I hope you are having
a wonderful day.
It's a good day to die.
Speaking of that, I'm about
to run this ship aground
and kill all of us.
- Go! Go!
[all scream]
Whoa! Whoa!
[klaxon blaring distantly]
- Everybody okay?
- Oh!
- Tell you right now, people--
Hands in.
Heroes are not made...
at a summer frolic,
at a picnic with a basket
of fruits, crudits,
cheeses, and meats.
- What the fuck?
- Maybe a sparkling white--
Hero--I'm getting
to this part.
Heroes are forged
in fire.
all: Yeah!
- [shouting angrily]
Let's do something about this!
- Yes! What do we do?
- Are we clowns, or are we the
Reno Sheriff's Department?
- We're the Reno Sheriff's
Department!
[shouting gibberish]
[exciting music]
* *
- Go, go, go, go.
- These decks is off-limits,
everybody.
Oh!
[laughs]
[all laughing]
- Hey, who did this?
[screams]
[water splashes]
[meaty thud]
[all gasp]
[mechanical whirring
and grinding]
- Oh, God.
Right into the propeller.
- He's all mixed up
in there.
- Circle of life.
Circle of life, right?
- In what way?
- Um, let's not get specific.
Let's--you know,
the circle of life.
- Oh, shit,
we got to stop the boat.
- Go.
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[speaking native language]
- Let's go.
- Captain!
[all shouting]
- Captain, we got to stop!
[overlapping shouting]
- All right, step back,
step back!
- Don't worry.
We do stuff like this
all the time.
[gunshot]
- [screams]
- Sorry!
Don't do it!
You got to let us in!
- How do we stop the ship?
- What if we drop the anchor?
- Yeah! Go, go, go!
Use your lower body.
On three.
[exhales sharply]
One, two...
[all straining]
I'm getting it!
I got a little bit!
I got something over here!
Son of a bitch,
I had something over here.
- Let's do it one more time,
'cause I have to admit,
I wasn't pulling at all.
I was just going, "Ah!"
- Fulcrum.
[all straining]
- Anything?
- Yeah, I felt it move!
I felt it move!
- I got something!
[overlapping shouting]
- One, two, three.
[all yell]
- Sometimes...
the best move
is to admit
when you need help.
- Help! Help!
- Don't scream.
Okay, no,
scream, scream.
- Help!
- We need help!
[all shouting]
all: Help!
- My brothers and sisters
of color,
Q weirdos who actually turned
out to be pretty nice folks,
America used to be great
'cause we did stuff together.
Let's do this together, guys.
And heave!
[all yelling]
Heave! Heave! Heave!
Heave! And ho!
Yes!
[all cheering]
[loud crash]
[water splashes]
Hey, guys...
we fucked up again.
- Yeah, it's supposed to be
attached, right?
- Yeah.
all: Captain!
- Capitn.
[all shouting]
- Hey, listen!
- I forgot, the crazy Black
captain "Bonofrise"
gave me the keys!
- Oh, my God!
- Let's do it.
- Go, go, go!
- So much better than violence.
Hey!
- Gentle. Gentle.
- Why don't you come on out?
Look what I got for you, huh?
- Oh. Shall we?
- Yes, we shall.
- Great, I'm gonna maybe
turn the ship off.
- I wish I'd known
you were here.
I would have let you in earlier.
- We did it.
- Man, you're batshit crazy.
Hey! We did it!
We saved the ship!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Don't have to thank us.
- [shouts angrily]
- Oh, shit!
- [gunfire]
[all scream]
- What? What?
- Are you out?
- No hard feelings, right?
- Mutiny in international law
is very bad.
I mean, we could kill you.
But we're not gonna do that,
because we nice.
And we want a good
Tripadvisor review.
Five star, please.
Thank you so much.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye, my love.
- Bye.
- Goodbye, my dear.
- I left one of my panty liners
under your pillow!
- [whispering]
Who is she talking to?
- I will wait for
you right here!
Fully engorged!
[boat horn blows]
- Bye, bye!
[speaking native language]
[dramatic music]
* *
[all gasp]
- Oh, my God!
- What the hell?
- Holy--
- Were you guys here
the whole time?
- Oh, yeah.
We--we turned this
into our little, um...
excuse me, but fuck nest.
[laughs]
- Ew!
- This succubus has me
up to, like, eight seconds.
Never lasted that long.
- Congratulations.
- Nobody asked.
- If I get into double digits,
this is the one.
[sighs]
- I'll buy you an ice cream.
- Oh!
- [both laugh]
all: No, no, no!
- Oh, come on!
- Just read the raft.
Read the raft, right?
- Does anybody know, like,
which way we're even drifting?
That's the drinking gourd
up there.
The handle points
to the North Star.
- I mean, if that really is
the drinking gourd, I mean...
I probably shouldn't
say this,
about a hundred miles
north of here...
[sighs]
[whispers]
Sorry, dude.
But, uh, Q's headquarters
are on my friend's island.
My friend had a really nice
island with a--
you know, a mansion
and a sex dungeon and--
- Jeff Epstein.
Who else has an island
with a sex dungeon?
- Okay, yeah, fine. Jeff
Epstein...
- Well, David Copperfield.
- David Copperfield.
- Okay, yeah.
- Well, how do we get there?
- Did you say 100 miles
north of here?
- Yeah. I mean,
I don't really know basic,
you know, boat craft or--
Whoa, what are you--
- There's a couple guys
in the world
that could get you
100 miles north of here
by the stars.
And one of them...
- Harriet Tubman.
- Is James Ron Dangle,
United States Coast Guard.
I mean, discharged.
Asked to leave.
- You know the story.
all: Yeah, yeah.
- For sure.
- Well, wait, I mean,
have you all heard it?
'Cause I haven't--
- You don't need to--
- My and another fellow were
asked to leave the Coast Guard
on the same day.
- Nah, we don't need to...
- Jim, what are you gonna do?
[heroic music]
* *
- [whimpers]
- Damn.
I am so over all of it.
Trudy, stop slobbing on me.
I'm tired of looking
at Dangle's ass,
I'm hungry,
and it's all your fault, Jones.
- My fault?
- You found the Booze Cruise!
- My fault because I can type?
- Actually, Dangle booked it.
- Dangle booked it.
- Clemmie, it's you!
You were the one who was
supposed to get information,
instead of having a fuck nest!
- Excuse me, excuse me!
- Don't you dare!
- This is a love fort!
- They're all just waiting to
turn on me!
They all know that it was--
[loud thud]
Travis? Travis?
- Hey.
- Hey, guys!
- Oh, my God.
[all gasp and cheer]
[all laugh]
- Whoo!
- Oh, wow.
- You did it, Jim.
You did it.
- Yeah!
Yeah, Dangle.
- Followed the drinking gourd.
[laughs]
- Welcome to, uh,
Jeffrey Epstein's island.
You are now all our prisoners,
and will be taken to trial
before Q!
- What?
[guns cock]
[all whimper]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa!
- Clemmie, you're gonna need
to decide.
Are you with me--
- I'm with you, yes!
- Okay, good.
- Yes.
- Do you want to yell
at the minions
and tell them--
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Hey, minions,
you with the colorful face.
Take these losers away.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
You're all losers.
Take them away!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Search their cavities.
Someone has something, I swear.
Sorry, not sorry!
[both laugh]
- Oh! I love our lives.
Oh.
[tense music]
* *
[indistinct radio chatter]
- Hello?
* *
[dramatic music]
- I love the open concept.
* *
- I'm impressed, Sheriff.
- I'm actually not the sheriff.
I'm Lieutenant James Ron Dangle,
Reno Sheriff's Department.
Also, uh, amateur puppeteer.
Almost went pro--
[yelps]
- So are you Q?
- [laughs]
Don't play stupid, Officer.
- She's not playing.
That was a legitimate question.
- She's really
not the bright.
- You should all be very happy
with yourselves.
No one else has ever gotten
this far.
So you came all this way
to find out who Q really is.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Well, I'll tell you.
Years ago, a ship wrecked
on this very island,
carrying a brilliant
and deranged professor.
That professor...
- Was Q.
- Died in the wreck.
- Okay.
- But we found this...
in the wreckage.
* *
- Uh, brother man, that--
that's a Speak & Spell.
- Yes, it is.
Or, it was.
Time and providence,
and probably
saltwater corrosion,
has altered its programming...
imbuing it...
and I'm not sure if I'm using
the word "imbuing" correctly.
But it infused it--
it infused it...
- Infused.
- With a dynamic,
divine wisdom...
- Oh. Yeah, okay.
- That Q imparts
and we disseminate.
- Oh, I get it.
So you guys are just
batshit crazy.
- Wait.
Listen.
- Hmm?
- And learn.
* *
[Speak & Spell chimes]
- Oprah has bears.
- [laughs]
Oprah has bears!
Let it be known
that Oprah has bears.
Go to your mobile devices,
get the word out on 8chan.
- This is a dumb,
dumb question.
This isn't how
the whole thing works, right?
[nervous laughter]
It is--
- It is, definitely.
- That's words, and then you...
put the words on an 8chan.
- It actually checks out
more than I would have thought.
- Yep.
[Speak & Spell chimes]
- The flu is from France.
- It's true, because sometimes
the flu is from France.
- But as often as not
it's not, actually.
- Well, sometimes it is.
[overlapping chatter]
- To the dungeon with them.
And go through the bunker.
It's faster.
And tell Ron to set off
that bomb.
The big one that will destroy
the island.
- Oh, my God!
We will not--
you do not have to kill us!
You do not have to kill us!
- Go, go, go, go.
- We won't remember!
- Come on.
- Blow them up.
- Can I just ask you
where you got that rag?
- Walmart.
- That's nice--
that's real nice.
- Clever, clever interlopers.
- We're not clever!
- Ow! Ow!
- Oh, hey, hey, ho!
- Sorry, I'm just a little
excited right now.
I've, uh-- [clears throat]
I've always wanted a monologue,
a secret fortress with
a smoking-hot vixen next to me.
- You do look hot, Clemmie.
- You look rad.
- Damn!
- The whole thing.
Show the whole thing.
- Look at that. Oh!
- Yes, queen!
- Work!
- Work.
- Marlene Dietrich in the front,
Stevie Nicks in the back.
- [laughs]
Oh.
- We've got the whole
nerve center here,
feeding all the greatest hits
into the algorithm.
You know,
the standard conspiracies.
Moon landing faked,
pumpkins aren't real,
Joe Rogan is a hologram.
The, uh, gluten-free diet,
um, causes levitation.
Um, that's a really good one.
Great work.
Now, of course,
that you've, uh...
seen all of this,
I have to blow it up.
- What?
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
[all shouting]
- Silence!
- I'm out!
- A bomb this exquisite
can only be set in motion
by somebody as exquisite.
- Clemmie, what about all those
great times that we had?
Remember all those
great times we had?
- Suck it, monkeys.
- [laughs]
- Hey, cut it out.
- Hey!
- Hey, now, Clemmie.
- Oh!
- Come on now.
Anyway, we would love
to stick around,
but we have to, um,
pack up a lot of money
and pills, right?
- Money and pills.
Glenn, to the dungeon.
[overlapping shouting]
- No, no, no, no, no!
No!
- Is this the first time you've
had hour friends blown up?
It's hard the first time,
but it gets easier.
- Does it?
- It really does.
Trust me, sweetie.
[both giggle]
- But, really, what were they
gonna live for?
Nothing.
- Sir?
- Is there gonna be, like,
snacks or anything?
- Appeal to his humanity.
Glenn, was it?
- Glenn?
- Hey, Glenn.
- Oh, I have an itch!
I have an itch!
- Is it bad that I feel like
I'm being threatened
with a good time?
Just to state the obvious here,
this is a really nice
sex dungeon.
- Yeah.
- I'm on the mailing list
of the company that makes
this domination gear.
They're an outfit out of Bruges
called Pamplemousse & Thunder.
I mean, this is some
of the nice stuff.
Some of this is actually
next year's stuff, by the way.
Literally, they advertise
that your submissives
will never escape.
So I don't want
to be a bummer,
but this is really well made.
[beeping]
- Warning.
Warning.
- Ron, thank you
for changing my life.
I deserve this.
- Thank you for being
the kind of person
whose life I wanted to change.
But all your friends,
I mean...
I am blowing them up.
- Yeah.
About that, um...
- Listen, hey, gang,
I gotta tell you--
I gotta tell you something.
I--I really think
this is it.
- Do you have to go
to the restroom?
- No, I think we're really
gonna die in here.
- Jones, don't say that!
- Don't say that.
- Don't you say that!
- Even though
it's probably true.
- It's kind of funny
if you think about it.
all: No, no.
- You just missed
the whole vibe right there.
- This is bad.
This is really, really bad,
and I feel--I feel--
I feel sorry
mostly for me and Rai-Rai,
'cause this--
this is really bad for us.
- Because of the optics?
Guys, can we not agree
this sucks equally
pretty much for all of us?
- No! No! No, we can't agree.
- Yes! Yes!
- No.
It looks worse for us, Jim.
- I think we should just
kind of go with it.
If we're dying, we're dying.
But can we do it
in silence?
- [sobbing]
I think this is it.
I think we're all gonna die!
- I'm gonna bust you guys
out of here.
[all cheer]
- Thank you!
- Shh! Shut up!
[dramatic music]
- Sheriff's Department...
take a knee.
* *
Ron Mackleberg thinks
he's about to blow us
to Q-dom come.
But I'll tell you right now,
I think his math was wrong.
I think he miscounted by nine.
- Nice.
- Here's the drill.
I am going to create
the perfect distraction.
Oh, fellas.
[whistles]
* Oh, it's little puppet Jimmy
and friends *
* Coming to your town,
coming 'round the bend *
* A place where... *
[necks crack]
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Hey, sweet thing.
* *
- [gasps]
- Hey!
- [grunts]
* *
[beeping]
- Cut it right about now.
[electricity crackles]
Oh!
[screams]
- [grunts]
* *
Let's get the hell
off this island.
* *
[both grunting]
- Hey, ladies!
You want a little piece of this?
* *
[grunting]
- Game over.
[grunts]
[whimpers]
[choking]
[both scream]
[crunching]
- Ah!
* *
- [screams]
[yelping]
* *
- [screams]
[yelling]
* *
- [panting]
[heroic music]
[chuckles]
And you...are...
served.
[beeps]
- You win.
- [laughs]
Any questions
about the plan?
- Actually, I have a question.
- Uh-huh?
- [whispering] I have a lot
of questions about the plan.
So you want me to kill
two girls with my bare hands?
- I'm just a guy
that had a plan and--
- You think I can
defuse a bomb?
And shouldn't I be wearing
safety glasses?
- I get--okay,
everybody hates the plan.
- I don't mean to piss all over
your really bitching plan...
- It's a pretty good plan.
- But...
I kind of already
roofied everybody.
I put it in everybody's
clam lite lime beer.
all: Oh!
- I'm sorry.
- A million times better.
Let's go stop that bomb!
- Does anybody remember
how to get out of here?
- I'm definitely turned around.
[alarm blaring]
- Ron!
- Ron! Come on!
- You got to tell us
how to stop the bomb!
- You can't.
The guys who killed
Khashoggi
traded it for an NFT.
It's un-defuseable.
- Ugh!
- What?
- He's talking gibberish!
- You know what that means.
Someone has to get this bomb
safely out to sea.
all: Not it.
- Obviously, I was gonna do it.
Why volunteer?
Why would I step in
and say that dramatically?
I'll do it.
- That was really unclear, Jim.
- Fuck it,
let's just get it out.
- You're acting like a martyr
and it's not a good look.
- Fuck it!
[dramatic music]
* *
I'll get it past
the breakwater
If anything happens,
do not help me.
- We won't.
- How could we?
- I want to tell you
one very short story.
The doctors told my mama
I would never dance.
Ever.
And I never did professionally.
[rapid beeping]
- Shit!
Goddamn it.
* *
[dings]
Wait.
I think I got it, actually.
[somber music]
* *
- Oh, no.
- Damn.
Do you see that bandanna
he had on?
That was mine.
You've been served.
- Now you guys
are real heroes.
I mean, nobody can know.
- Yeah, sadly,
this is all top secret.
From the FBI and the CIA,
we want to thank you.
- Yeah.
[triumphant music]
* *
- * Ave *
* Maria *
- [sobbing]
- * Gratia *
* Plena *
* Maria, gratia plena *
[boat horn blowing distantly]
Well, gang,
let's hit the bar.
[calypso music
playing faintly]
* *
- Jim?
Jim, is that you?
Jim?
- Dangle?
- Huh? Uh...
je ne parle pas anglais.
- What?
- I'm someone else.
Oh, fuck it!
Hey, guys.
Fuck! Goddamn it!
Fuck it.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
[guitar strums]
Good morning, gang.
- Morning.
- [humming]
[whistling]
The pig foot by the yard
place,
they've inverted--
it's called inverted
law enforcement discount.
- That mean we pay more?
- They're charging us more
for what they feel like
we've done to the community
in general.
Fair enough.
- [sighs]
- We deserve it.
[lively guitar music]
* *
- Uh, mixed feelings
about being back here
in the Silver State.
You know, in the perfect world
would I be living
the cruise lifestyle,
doing my puppetry,
making that--
making that puppetry money?
Which--it's not--
I've never--I've never, ever
done the puppetry
just for the money.
That said,
I've been doing it here
on the streets a bit.
You know, and in many ways
that's great,
'cause I'm also just outside,
you know?
Just to be outside at all.
- Hey, no smoke inside!
- I'm putting it out.
I'm already putting it out.
- I needed adventure,
and I got it,
and I have a renewed
sense of purpose.
And you're probably asking,
well, what about Ron?
What about him?
If you're asking me
as a deputy,
I have no idea about Ron.
If you're asking me as Clemmie
the woman, the goddess, um,
of course I know
exactly where he is.
I'm not stupid.
I know a good thing
when I see it.
Hey, handsome.
- Oh!
- [chuckles]
- I waive my rights.
- I got to be honest.
I took a lot of money from Q.
And I would do it again.
But don't worry,
I'm doing good things with it.
I brought all my friends
along with me.
[all laugh]
Hey, I'm sorry
I almost left you for dead.
- Forget it.
- It's all right.
- It's forgotten.
- The important thing is
you're here now.
- We are a family.
- Familia.
- I love you guys.
all: Cheers!
[all whoop]
- What a beautiful night
for an evening.
- Oh, it sure is.
To us.
- Stand behind me like this.
- Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Let's human centipede it.
We'll do a human centipede
Titanic.
all:
Human centipede Titanic!
- Ow! Ow! Ow!
- Guys,
we're crushing her uterus.
We're crushing her uterus.
- * Don't wanna stop *
- * And our hearts *
* They beat as one *
* Ooh, yeah *
* No more love on the run *
* Yeah *
* *
* Caribbean Queen *
* Now we're sharing
the same dream *
* And our hearts,
they beat as one *
* Oh, yeah *
* No more love on the run *
* Yeah *