Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[]
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING OVER TV]
SOPHIA [ON TV]: No, thanks.[WOMAN COUGHS]
If I want to look at pictures,
I go to Fotomat.
[WOMAN LAUGHS]Besides, Rose brought me.
She's waiting outside
with the dog.
Hey, you ever stick your head
out of a car window doing 50?
What a rush.
[]
[QUIET RUSTLING]
[FOOTSTEPS SCURRYING]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
[]
[RASPY BREATHING]
Friend?
Hello?
What do you want?
She's here again.
She was watching me.
Try and get back to sleep
before Dr. Birkin
finds you in my bed.
I saw her.
You didn't...
[SIGHS]
You didn't see anything.
Close your eyes.
[]
[RASPY BREATHING]
What are you, a pervert?[LAUGHING]
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]I was married for 45 years,
I never even saw
my husband's Gauguins.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
[]
[CREAKING NEARBY]
[MUSIC BOX PLAYING
GENTLE MELODY]
[HUMMING ALONG WITH MUSIC BOX]Hello?
[MUSIC BOX STOPS]
[]
What's your name?
[JOINTS CRACKING][RAPID, TREMBLING BREATHS]
Lisa Trevor?
[RASPY BREATHING]
Do you live here?
Where do you live?
[PAPER RUSTLING]
[RASPY, GASPING BREATHS]
Below?
[SCURRYING]
Hey.
[]
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
[SCREAMS]
What are you doing out of bed,
little girl?
Well?
She sleepwalks sometimes
since our parents died.
Oh.
Well, then.
Off to bed, both of you.
Wait.
Redfield, isn't it?
Chris and Claire Redfield?
You're a good boy for taking
such care of your sister.
Good night.
[]
[WHISPERS]:
Good night.
[CREAKING]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
[RASPY BREATHING]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[SCREAMS]
[GASPING]
That must have been
quite some dream.
["MORE AND MORE"
BY WEBB PIERCE PLAYING]
I almost shit my goddamn pants.[WHIMPERING]
If I knew you were gonna be
screaming in your sleep,
I would've left
you at the side of the road.
What are you doing out
hitchhiking
on a night like this anyway?
Oh, yeah.
Going to see your brother,
you said.
Right.
Used to live here,
you said.
[WHIMPERS]
Raccoon City.
Better you than me.
You know, one might
have nightmares
heading back
into that shithole town.
Nothing left 'cept the raccoons
since Umbrella
started to leave.
Do you mind?
[CHANGES RADIO STATION]They should tell your brother,
"Just get out of there."
["MY FAVOURITE GAME"
BY THE CARDIGANS PLAYING]
"Just pack up and leave."
[LAUGHS]:
Although, who you
gonna sell your house to?
Nobody. That's who.
[LAUGHS]
Live in Raccoon?
No, thanks. No way.
Maybe you want to stay on
till Gatlin,
tell him you had
a change of heart.
People put too much emphasis
on family anyway.
Sometimes you just
got to let it go.
Watch out!
Shit![TIRES SQUEALING]
[DOG BARKING]
[ENGINE IDLING]
[]
[DRIVER'S DOOR CLOSES]
Is she...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Fuck!
I di-- I didn't see her.
She came out of nowhere.
What's she doing out here
in the middle of the night?
We need something
to wrap the body in.
You saw it, right?
It wasn't my fault.
Jesus. Oh, fuck!
Fuck!Listen to me.
We need something
to wrap the body in,
and then we're gonna
take it into town.
It wasn't my fault!
Oh, Jesus! Fuck!
[RASPY BREATHING]
My brother's a cop.
He can help us.
Cop?
But it's not my fault.
It's not my fault!
I know. I know.
Fuck! Fuck!
[SNARLS]
[BARKING]
We can't just
leave her here, okay?
Fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
[DOG BARKS]
[PANTING, WHIMPERING]
Where the fuck
did she go?
Hello?
Hey!
You've been in an accident,
and you need help.
[DOG WHINING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
We need to go after her.
You can do whatever
the fuck you want.
I'm getting the fuck
out of here.
[]
[DISTANT SIREN WAILING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[GROANING]
[ALARM STOPS][GROANS] Fuck.
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
["I WANT TO SEE THE BRIGHT
LIGHTS TONIGHT" PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Fuck.
[SIGHS]:
Oh, fuck.
Hey, why don't you
just take a seat
and leave the poor kid alone,
huh, Wesker?
[SHUSHES QUIETLY]
Okay.
[SIGHS]
Ten bucks.
Ten bucks says you can't
shoot that off from here.
[WESKER CLEARS THROAT]
That's easy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.Hey, no, no.
Jesus fucking Christ.
With this, Valentine.
I mean, what the fuck?
20 says I can knock the bottle
without even looking.
I mean, yeah, sure,
I'll take your money.
[CHUCKLES]
[RICHARD LAUGHS]
[GASPS]
What the fuck?
[LAUGHTER][SIGHS]
[UNDER BREATH]:
Fuck.
[SIGHS]
Hey!You snooze, you lose.
Wait...
[SIGHS]It's Jill's sandwich now.
Hey. Oh, God.Mmm. Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm.
Come on.
Pay up.
Come on. Pay up.
[]
["IT'S A HEARTACHE"
BY BONNIE TYLER PLAYING]
[WHISPERS]:
Shit.
Fellas.
You back there,
Louise?
Hello, boys.
What can I get you?
Two coffees to go.
Long day?Uh-huh.
Hey, could I...Oh, you must be...
the rookie.
How you doing, rookie?
So, I heard
that you shot your partner
in the ass during training.
Is that true?
And that your, uh,
daddy, some big shot
on the force,
that he had to bail you out.
Now, is that why
they transferred you to this...
[LAUGHING]:
shithole town?
Yeah.Leon S. Kennedy.
What's the "S" stand for?
"Stupid"?
[LAUGHTER]Oh.
Come on, we're just playing
with you, kiddo.
Yeah, good.
[SIGHS]
Y'all working the graveyard?
Yep. Where you guys headed?
Well, someone found a body
up at the old Spencer Mansion--
it's all chewed up.
Didn't think there was
anything up there anymore.
Well, the sooner they shut this
whole town down, the better,
as far as I'm concerned.Hey, hey.
It's my hometown
you're talking about.
Well, you're welcome to it.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, come on.
We got to shake a leg.
And don't shoot.
I'm unarmed.
[CHUCKLES]
Fuck that guy.
Right, so, uh...
I guess I'm paying?Mm-hmm.
Come on, we should get
to the station.
Hey. Pay us no mind.
We're, uh, nice people
once you get to know us.
I'm Jill Valentine.
Leon... Kennedy.
Nice to meet you,
Leon Kennedy.
I wouldn't go there.
She's only got eyes
for the big fella,
and I don't fancy
your chances against him.
You really shoot
your own partner?
Y-Yeah.
Um, it's a long story.
You...
What's going on with your eye?
Oh.
I don't know, it's been doing
that the last couple of weeks.
You don't think you should
see someone about that?
Yeah.
It's probably nothing.
[LOUD THUD]
[]
Oh.
[BIRD WHINING]Well, look at that.
[PAINED SHRIEKING]
[LIGHTS CLICKING]
[]
[BRAKES HISS]
Hey, that, uh... that woman...[DOG WHINING]
That probably just wasn't
as bad as it seemed, right?
Yeah. Sure.
Thanks for the ride.
[]
Welcome home.
[WHINING]
What's going on with you?
[WHINES, GROWLS]
Don't go getting ill on me,
you son of a bitch.
I don't have insurance for you.
Aah! Fuck!
You fucking bit me,
you motherfucker!
[GROWLING]Fuck!
[]
[DOORKNOB RATTLING]
[CREAKING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING SOFTLY]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
[SNIFFS]
Still pining after Jill, I see.
Never gonna happen, bro.
[]
He's been like
a father to me.
I see you wax your chest now.[CHUCKLES]
Funny.
After you ran away,
William was the closest thing
I had to family.
How'd you get in?
Picked your lock.
You realize I'm a cop, right?Yeah.
You need better security.
It's a single-cylinder
dead bolt, Claire.
Most people knock.
Yeah, I tried.
No one answered.
So you broke in.
Why are you back here?
Missed Raccoon City so much
you had to come pay me a visit?
Yeah.
I fucking love Raccoon City.
"Go, you Bandits."
[SCOFFS]
You're an asshole.
No, you know what?
I owe this town... I owe Birkin
and Umbrella everything.
They raised me, put me
through school, the academy.
They were there for me.
Where were you?
I haven't even heard from you
in five years.
Nice seeing you.
Chris, wait.
I'm sorry.
I'm back now.
Look...
I think there's something
seriously wrong
with this place.
What do you mean?Okay, so I-I was
hitching a ride in a truck,
and...
Soliciting a ride--
also illegal.
Arrest me.
Look, we kind of hit
this person,
but-but they just got up
and they-they walked away.
You hit someone?
Holy shit, Claire.
Have you reported it?
I'm reporting it now.
You not listening to me?
They-they just got up
and-and walked off.
You could be party
to a hit-and-run.
Shush. Just...
No, Claire,
I don't have time for this.
No. Look, okay,
so I've been talking
to this guy in a chat room...
What the fuck's a chat room?
It's a place on the Internet
where people chat.
Just... just watch it.
His name's Ben Bertolucci.
BEN [ON VIDEO]:
It's in the water, Claire.
It's in the fucking water.
Um, this whole town's
been poisoned.
Slowly, over years and years,
and, uh,
people are getting sick.
Oh, come on, Claire.
Not again.Shh!
You "shh."See, uh,
Umbrella just thought
that they could, uh,
pack up shop
and let this town rot away
while they go off
and-and start afresh
somewhere else
all shiny and-and new, and...
they almost fucking did it,
but, uh,
a couple days ago,
they had a little incident.
And I'm not just talking about
waste poisoning the water.
No, I'm talking about
a real bad leak.
Like Chernobyl,
if you know what I mean.
And, uh, they've been trying
to contain that shit,
but the genie is
out of the bottle now,
and I... I don't think
it's going back in.
I'm afraid, Claire. I'm a...
I'm afraid of what they're
gonna do to this town...
and the people in it.
I've not been able
to make contact with him since.
Great.
He's crazy
and probably dangerous.
Look, your conspiracy theories
weren't true when we were kids.
They're not true now.
All right?
Why are you really here?
Did you lose your job?
Do you need cash?
You show up here,
you break into my house.
What-what kind of person
can pick a lock like that?
It-it's kind of impressive,
but also, what the fuck?
I'm sorry,
I got to get ready for work.
Chris.
[SIGHS][FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[SIGHS]
Fuck.
[SCREAMS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING][PANTING, WHIMPERING]
[WHIMPERING CONTINUES]
Honey, hey.
Mom and Dad are here.
I saw a monster.
Oh, honey,
you just had a bad dream.
Shh.But-but... but I did see him.
He was all green and slimy,
and he had big yellow eyes
and teeth, like this. [GROWLS]
I think I'd be frightened, too.
Right, honey?
Oh, my gosh,
I'd be petrified.
Terrified.
Come on. It's okay.
I'd never let
anything hurt you.
[PHONE RINGING]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
I'll be right back, okay?[WHISPERS]: Okay.
[HISSES]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
All right,
let's get you
back to sleep, okay?But-but wait.
What if the monster comes back?Hello?
Honey, there's no
such thing as monsters, okay?
- Do you promise?- I promise.
[]
[PHONE BEEPS]
...really good thoughts.
So let's do that, okay?
Remember last time
we went swimming.
Okay?
All right?
Think about that.
We need to go.
What are you talking about?
Who was on the telephone?Now!
[ALARM BLARING OUTSIDE]
What is happening, William?
Get Sherry dressed
and meet me at the car.
Uh, okay.
Uh, hey, look at me.
Look at me.
[ALARM CONTINUES BLARING][LIGHTS THUMPING]
MAN [OVER P.A.]:
This is
the Umbrella Corporation.
For your safety,
please stay in your homes
and await further instructions.
This is
the Umbrella Corporation.
For your safety,
please stay in your homes
and await further instructions.
[ALARM CONTINUES BLARING]
This is
the Umbrella Corporation.
What is that?
For your safety,
please stay in your homes
and await further instructions.
Nothing.
It's nothing.
I got to get to the station.
Here. It's not much.
Wha...?Just take it, okay?
Lock-pick the door behind you
when you leave.
Chris. Chris!
Just get out of here, okay?
[OVER P.A.]:
This is the
Umbrella Corporation.
For your safety...And don't touch the bike!
[OVER P.A.]:
...and await
further instructions.
This is
the Umbrella Corporation.
For your safety,
please stay in your homes
and await further instructions.
[ENGINE STARTS]
This is
the Umbrella Corporation.
Why aren't you sick,
big brother?
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES]
[SNIFFS]
[SIGHS]
[SQUEAKING]
[]
Can I help you?
[LOUD THUD][GASPS]
[DOOR CREAKING]
Hello?
[THUMPING]
[]
Hey. You need help?
[WHISPERS]:
You need help.
What?
[SHRIEKING]Oh, shit!
Itchy, tasty!
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
[]
[ENGINE STARTS, REVS]
[TIRE SQUEALS]
MAN [OVER P.A.]:
This is the
Umbrella Corporation.
For your safety,
please stay in your homes
and await further instructions.
[ALARM CONTINUES BLARING]
This is
the Umbrella Corporation.
For your safety,
please stay in your homes
and await further instructions.
What would the worst way
to die be?
What?
To be swallowed whole by a snake
or eaten alive
by a great white shark?
You're a freak, Valentine.
I plan on dying peacefully
in bed,
snuggled in Wesker's
big burly arms.
[LAUGHING]: Yeah.[WOLF WHISTLE]
Me, too, brother.
Funny.
Uh, what's Vickers doing here?
Thought we lost the chopper
with the rest
of the budget cuts.
Maybe he just missed us.Oh.
Fuck you.Ooh. [LAUGHS]
Is that right?
Guess not.[LAUGHTER]
Hey!
Okay, Chief,
what's this all about?
Yeah, what's with the alarm?
Power's out.Well, if you all
shut the hell up for a second
and listen,
maybe you'll find out.
Honestly, I don't know.You don't know?
That's right, Redfield.
I do not know.
What I do know is that
Marini and Dooley
are currently
not answering their radios.
They're investigating
a report of a body
up by the Spencer Mansion.
You think it's connected?
Um, what's
the Spencer Mansion?
Well, as I think
most of you know,
Oswald Spencer was the creator
of the Umbrella Corporation,
and the mansion was his home
until the year
of his death in...
What the fuck
are you doing here, Leon?!
VICKERS [LAUGHING]:
Holy shit.
You said, "Everyone
into the briefing room,"
so I... here I am.
I didn't mean you, you moron.
Not you, Leon. Everyone else.[LAUGHTER]
What if someone wanders in
and there's
no one behind the front desk?Sure. Okay.
An old lady's looking for
her cat or something.Okay.
Yeah, you're right.Jesus Christ.
Get back there, man.You're right. Okay.
And get a haircut,
you goddamn hippie.
[PAGER BEEPING]Geez.
It's not Woodstock.
[LAUGHTER]
Aw, take it easy
on the rook, Chief.
[SNIFFS]
I-I'm sorry, Wesker.
Is that important?
No, it's-it's... I'm-I'm good.A new girlfriend?
Huh?
[CHUCKLES]
Maybe you could take her
out to eat at Planet Hollywood.
They have a new one in Gatlin.
Oh, they got a great salad.
[CHUCKLES]Little wine.
Or maybe just take her back
to your apartment,
rent a movie at Blockbuster,
get cozy on the couch,
or put on some Journey.
Steve Perry's voice, what it
does to a woman's heart, huh?
Am I right?
[CHUCKLES]
How's that sound?
Sounds like
I might be getting laid.
[LAUGHTER]
But it ain't gonna
happen tonight,
because I want you dressed
in five, all of you,
and ready to fly,
because I want to know
where the hell Bravo team is
and what the fuck
all those alarms are about!
You got me?
Come on, get moving. Go.
Let's go.
Get a move on it!
[JILL CHUCKLES]Yeah. [GROANS]
Hey, I'll meet you guys
in the chopper.
What the fuck is this?
[]
Wesker, let's get going.
Slow down, William.
Y-You're gonna crash.
William, slow down!
Where are we going?
Why can't you tell me why
we're in such a hurry to leave?
Leaving--
that's what they want.
So they can destroy
my life's work.
Daddy, watch out!
[SCREAMS][TIRES SQUEAL]
You almost hit that girl.
You okay?
[]
NURSE [VOICE-OVER, ECHOES]:
Wake up.
We need you to get up
and come with us.
Where are we going?Shh.
It's okay, little girl.
Because we have found you
a new family.
They're waiting for you
just outside.
It's all so very exciting.
Oh, don't worry
about your brother.
He'll be coming along as well,
in due course.
We would never separate
the two of you.
We just need you
to come with us,
and someone will collect
all of your belongings.
William!
[]
[TRUCK'S HORN DRONING]
[WHINING]
[]
["CRUSH" BY JENNIFER PAIGE
PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES]
[SONG FADES]
[]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
["CRUSH" CONTINUES PLAYING
FAINTLY OVER HEADPHONES]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[OVER HEADPHONES]:
[FIRE RUMBLING][METAL CLATTERING]
[GUNSHOT][SONG STOPS]
[PANTING]
What the fuck?
You might want to get
a fire extinguisher.
And lock the gates.
There may be others.
Huh? Oth... Other what?
[]
[SIGHS]
Fuck this.
Hi. Uh, sir, um...
Uh, what's going on?
'Cause, um...
Should we...
should we call someone?
Who you gonna call?
You're the police.
An ambulance?
Look, I'm no medical expert,
but I think that guy might
just be beyond saving, hmm?
Besides, I think you'll find
that all the phone lines
in the city are dead.
Take care of yourself, Leon.
Fuck. Fuck.
Uh, sir? Hey, hey.
Sir!
Where-where are you going, sir?
Uh...
Shit.
Hey, hey, uh...
Hey, sir, um,
I know I'm new here
and I don't really know
what's going on, but, um...
so, where are you going?
Who's in charge now?
You are.Uh, no, no, no.
No, um,
I'm-I'm a rookie, right?
Yeah, well, congratulations,
rookie, on the promotion.
I'm sure your father
would be incredibly proud
that his pathetic specimen
of a son
is rising so quickly
through the ranks.
S-Sir, I-I really don't think
you should go.
I-I don't think
I'm prepared to handle...
I'm going. At ease.
Take care. Good luck.
I know you'll do a great job.[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Sir.
Sir!
[TIRES SCREECH]
Fuck.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[]
Right here.
Radio Irons. Tell him
we found Bravo team's Jeep.
Will do.
[BUTTONS BEEPING]
Holy shit.
Jesus Christ.
What the hell happened here?
Where are they?
[WINGS FLUTTERING][BIRD SCREECHING]
What the fuck?
[SCREECHING]
What the fuck is wrong with it?
[GUNSHOT]
Really?
What?
Someone should confiscate that.
Just...Uh, hey, guys?
They went this way.
[]
[BIRD SCREECHES]
[RATTLES, CREAKS]
[]
Marini and Dooley
are in here somewhere.
We should split up.
What?
The faster we find them,
the faster we can
get the fuck out of here.
All right, we go in pairs.
I'll go with you,
Wesker.
Keep your shit wired
at all times.
[]
IRONS [SINGING ALONG TO RADIO]:
["ANY WAY YOU WANT IT"
BY JOURNEY PLAYING]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is not good.
MAN [OVER P.A.]:
This is the
Umbrella Corporation.
Return to your vehicles,
and return to your homes
and businesses.
[ENGINE REVS, TIRES SQUEAL]
Hey![HORN HONKS]
Come on! Go back![INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Go back!
Move your truck back!
We're blocked in!
How much longer
is this gonna be?
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.[GUNSHOT]
Oh![RAPID GUNFIRE]
Oh! Oh!
Oh, goddamn it. Oh!
Oh, damn, damn, damn, damn.
Open up! Come on, please!
Get off!
Get the fuck away from my car!
Get off, Jack! Get off!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING][RAPID GUNFIRE]
Please don't shoot.
I'm unarmed.
Fuck! Oh, goddamn!
Oh, man!
Oh, that is close.
Oh, shit.
[ALARM BLARING IN DISTANCE]
[AIR HISSING THROUGH MASK]
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
Raccoon City,
locked down and secured.
[]
Please let me in.
Let me in.
[WOMAN GROANING]
Help, please!
[GROANING, SNARLING]
[CLANKING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[COUGHING]
[GASPING]
[HIGH-PITCHED MOAN NEARBY]
[SNARLING]
[SQUISHING, THUMPING][GRUNTING, MOANING]
[HIGH-PITCHED SQUEAL]
[]
[PANTING]
[WHIMPERS]
Come on, come on.
[SNIFFS, GRUNTS]
[LOW GROWLING]
Goddamn bullets.
[BARKING][IRONS SCREAMING]
[DOG SNARLS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DOG GROWLS]
[]
[DOG SNARLING]
[WHIMPERS]
[GROWLING]
[GUN CLICKING]
[SNARLING]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
Hey, hey! Drop your gun!
Show me your hands!
[GUN COCKS]
[PANTING]
Haven't got a gun.
[FIRE EXTINGUISHER
DROPS TO GROUND]
Who the fuck are you?
Come on.
Leon, put that gun down.
So, are you in charge again?
[FRANTIC MOANING AND GROANING]
Please let me in.
Let me in!
Let... me in.
Where's my brother,
Chris Redfield?
So you're Chris's
little sister, huh?
I didn't think
the two of you spoke.
[MOANING AND GROANING CONTINUE]
He's up in the Arklay Mountains
with the rest of Alpha team.Hey, um, sorry.
Does someone want to tell me
what the fuck is going on here?
I mean,
what's happening to them?
Let me in!Let me in.
[YELLING]
Clearly, some bad shit.
All the exits out of Raccoon
have been blocked by Umbrella.
We need more ammo and guns.
The armory's downstairs.Where are you going?
I'm gonna try and get ahold
of your brother.
There's no way
out of Raccoon by road,
but we might just be able
to take a helicopter.
[SHRIEKING]:
Let me in!
[]
What is that?
Uh, I'll explain in a minute.
[]
[QUIET, RASPY BREATHING]
[SQUISHING, MUNCHING]
Hey. RPD.
MAN [WEAKLY]:
Help me.
Hands. Show me your hands.
[DRIPPING]
What the fuck?
[WHIMPERING]
I need you to stay right there.
[SHRIEKS]
Oh, fuck.
Marini. Fuck.
Hey.
Okay, here, here,
here, here, here.
It's... Put pressure
right there, okay?
As much pressure as you can.
Find Dooley.[RASPY BREATHING IN DISTANCE]
You're gonna be okay,
all right?
You'll be fine.
It's just nothing.
Shit.
Oh, God. Shit. Shit.
Oh, man.
Oh, man, Marini.
[]
[FOOTSTEPS SCURRYING
IN DISTANCE]
Just hold on, man, all right?
It's...
[GURGLING, BREATHING WEAKLY]
[EXHALES SOFTLY]Fuck.
Shit. No, no, no, no.
[]
[FOOTSTEPS SCURRYING]
Dooley.
[GUN COCKS]
[SHRIEKS, SNARLS]
[LOUD BANG]Richard!
[SNARLING, SHRIEKING]
Redfield!
[GRUNTING, WHIMPERING]
Aiken!
Let's get the fuck out of here!
[GUN CLICKS][YELLS, GROANS]
[SCREAMING]
[SNARLING]
["WHAT'S UP?" BY 4 NON BLONDES
PLAYING FAINTLY OVER RADIO]
[GLASS SQUEAKING]
[SONG FADES]
[SHRIEKING]
[DOORS CREAKING]
[JILL EXHALES SHARPLY]
[]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
The fuck you doing, Wesker?Hold on.
[PLAYS SIMPLE MELODY]
Listen. Do you hear that?
[MELODY CONTINUES]
[CLANKING]
[MELODY STOPS]
What the hell is Vickers doing?
Run!
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[]
Okay.
Yeah, I've actually never
been in this room, so, um...
Oh.
That's good, right?
I think it's just, uh...
Think it's sort of jammed.Here. Uh...
Put this on.
So, how do you know
so much about guns?
My parents died in a
car accident when I was eight.
My brother and I grew up
in an orphanage here.
I ran away a long time ago.
I had to learn
to handle myself quickly.
Right. Yeah.
You're probably wondering
what a guy like me
is doing as a cop, right?
Kinda.
Yeah. Me, too.
MAN [MUFFLED]:
Hey! Someone get me out of here!
Hello?Your police station.
I'll see what else I can find.
Yeah.
I'm in the fucking basement.
They put me in
the fucking basement.
Get me out of here.
I know you're up there.
Oh, thank God.
Thank fucking God.
You got to get me
out of here, man.
Who the fuck are you?
How about I tell you once you
get me the fuck out of here?
[MAN COUGHING]
[COUGHING CONTINUES]
Jesus.
[GASPING]
Is he okay?
[COUGHING, GASPING CONTINUE]
Him?
Oh, yeah, no,
he's fucking fine. Yeah.
Yeah, who doesn't cough up
a little blood on the floor
when they're feeling sick?
Just a little cold.
Of course he's not
fucking okay, man.
Look at him.
Open the goddamn door.
Why-why are you locked up?
Why?
Because I found out the truth.
The truth? What-what truth?
[GRUNTS] Hey.
Listen to me,
you fucking boy band wannabe.
You think Umbrella
spend all their time
making aspirins
and little vitamin tablets?
No fucking way.Jesus Christ.
Hey, whoa, whoa! That's...
Open the goddamn door.That's my gun.
Do it.You don't have to do this.
Sure, I don't.
And you and all your
police buddies,
you're not sick
like the rest of the town
just 'cause you got
a good immune system, right?
Fuck, you probably had
a little injection,
a little vitamin pill
you didn't even realize.
Keeps you safe
at least for a while.
But the others,
ordinary people,
expendable ones...
Yeah, good fucking luck, right?
Open the goddamn door.
The keys are over there
in the desk.
Do it! Go!Okay. Okay. Okay.
Here I go. Okay.
Jesus...
[WHISPERS]:
fucking Christ.
[SIGHS][OPENS DRAWER]
Come on, man.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Hurry up.
[SIGHS]
Oh, fuck me.
Yeah, you ever heard of
the T-Virus and the G-Virus?
Uh, of course
you fucking haven't.
Well, it's a virus
that genetically modifies
the DNA of a living cell,
and it's turning these people
into fucking weapons, man.
You need to get me
the fuck out of here, okay?
[KEYS JINGLING][CLOSES DRAWER]
Be an asshole about it.
Yeah, well, I'm done
taking chances.
[WHISPERS]: Oh, fuck.[LOCK RATTLING]
Come on, man.
Jesus fucking Christ.
All right. You know what?
Just one second, please.
You're no Einstein,
are you, buddy?
[GRUNTS]
Thank fucking God.
[SHRIEKING]
[SNARLING][GRUNTING]
Fuck!
[GROANING]
Shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Wait, just slow down.
Uh, let's...
Uh, uh, uh...
Wait, wait, wait.
[GRUNTING]
[SHRIEKS][GUNSHOT]
[PANTING]
Hey.
[]
Ben.
Get your shit together,
or you're not gonna make it
through the night.
[SNARLING QUIETLY]
[SIGHS]:
Oh, fuck.
[YELLING]
[BODY THUDS]
[LEON BREATHING HEAVILY]
Are you done?
I just really want
to get out of this town.
[STATIC DRONING]
Vickers, can you read me? Over.
Vickers, this is Chief Irons.
Pick up your damn radio!
[STATIC DRONING]
IRONS [OVER RADIO]:
Vickers, can you read me?
Over.[JILL COUGHING]
Vickers, this is Irons.
Pick up your damn radio.
[JILL AND WESKER
COUGHING, GROANING]
[PANTING]
Hey.[GROANING]
[WHISPERING]:
Come on. Hey.
Holy shit.
[BOTH PANTING]
You saved my life.
[CREAKING]
Oh, shit.
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
Come on.
Come on, come on.
[]
Holy shit,
she was telling the truth.
Truth about what?
Wesker,
what's going on?
They contacted me
several months ago.
It was once
Umbrella started moving
their operations
out of Raccoon.
I don't know who they are.
I don't know, and I don't care.
They're just some people
with a vested interest
in getting hold
of whatever dirty secrets
Umbrella are keeping down there
and exposing them.
What are you talking about?
Come on, Jill.
Don't look at me like that.
It's just money.
All right?
And they have plenty of it.
It was just a way
of getting out of this...
this small-town, dead-end life.
So, uh...
...you were just
gonna leave us?
Come on.
We have to find
Chris and Richard
and tell them
that Vickers is dead.
Come on.
Come on,
these are your friends!
I can't.
What are you...
[SHRIEKS]
[JILL PANTING]
[SNARLS QUIETLY]
[SHRIEKS]
[GUNSHOT]
Oh, my God.
What the fuck
happened to him?
I don't know.
Wesker.
Wesker!
[MOANING AND GROANING]
[SHRIEKING]Let me in!
[SNARLS]
Did you get ahold
of my brother?
No.
[SNARLING]
We need that helicopter
to get out of here.
We need to get
to the Arklay Mountains.
How?
I think I know a way.
Come on.
[SQUEALING, SNARLING]
Oh, shit.
Come on!
[SNARLING]
The loading dock's this way.
[]
[DISTANT SQUEALING]Shit.
[GROWLING][GUNSHOT]
[SHRIEKS]
[GUNFIRE]
[SNARLING]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[SHRIEKING][GUNFIRE]
Let's go, let's go!
Go, go!
Come on, come on, come on!
[SNARLING, SHRIEKING]
[]
[DISTANT SCREAMING, SNARLING]
[CREAKING]
[DOOR OPENS]
What are we doing here?
[]
[DISTANT RUSTLING]
[LIGHTS CLICKING]
NURSE [VOICE-OVER]:
We need you to get up
and come with us.
YOUNG CLAIRE [VOICE-OVER]:
Where are we going?
[]
Hey.
Why are we here?
This place has
a secret passageway
that leads to
the Spencer Mansion.
How'd you know
about this place?
They bought you off,
didn't they?
They paid you to keep quiet
about all the shit
they were doing in here.[CREAKING]
And now they've left you
to rot here just like us.
[THUMPING, CREAKING]
Fuck.
[RASPY BREATHING]
[PANTING]
Uh, guys?
Shh.
Look.
And now they've left you to rot
in the gutter
like the rest of us.
Don't be so damn naive.Guys!
What the...
No, there was...
there was somebody...
There was someone there.
[IRONS GRUNTS]
[IRONS GROANING][CREATURE SQUEALING]
[IRONS GRUNTING][SQUISHING]
[SHRIEKS]
Run!Come on!
Go!
[YELPS]
Shit.
[SNARLS, SHRIEKS]
Uh, uh...
[SNARLING]
[CHITTERS, SHRIEKS]
[RASPY BREATHING]
[GRUNTING]
[SHRIEKING]
[PANTING]
[RASPY BREATHING]
Lisa Trevor.
We need to get
to the Spencer Mansion.
You know how, don't you?
[LISA MUTTERING QUIETLY]
Claire... Claire...
Friend?
Come on.
[]
YOUNG CLAIRE [VOICE-OVER]:
Why are we going in here?
I want my brother.
ORDERLY [GROANS]:
She bit my hand.
[GROANING]
Get her.
[LISA WHEEZING SOFTLY]
K-K-Key, key, k-key.
[KEYS JINGLING]
The second k-k-key.
Go to...
K-K-Key.
Key. Key.
[CLANKING, CREAKING]
[RASPY BREATHING]
Thank you.
Claire.[METALLIC CREAKING]
You got some weird friends.
[SIGHS]
[CREAKING]
[SNARLING]
[MOANING]
[GUNSHOT]
[PANTING]
[DISTANT SHRIEKING]
[SNARLS, SHRIEKS][GUNSHOTS]
[BODY THUDS]
[PANTING]
[]
[DISTANT GROWLING]
[SHRIEKING][CHRIS GRUNTING]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[HYPERVENTILATING]
[SHRIEKING][CHRIS GRUNTING]
[TEETH CLICKING]
[SHRIEKING STOPS, BODY THUDS]Fuck.
[PANTING]
[DISTANT GROWLING]
[DISTANT SNARLING, SQUEALING]
[SHRIEKING NEARBY]
[WHEEZING, GURGLING]
Dooley?[SQUEALS]
[LIGHTER FLICKING]
[SQUEALS]
[UNDER BREATH]: Fuck.[LIGHTER FLICKING]
[SHRIEKS]
[CHRIS PANTING RAPIDLY][FOOTSTEPS SCURRYING]
[SNARLING]
[SHRIEKS][CHRIS GASPING]
[RAPID GUNFIRE][SHRIEKING]
[BOTH PANTING]
[BOTH SIGHING]
We have to get
to the helicopter.
Where's Wesker?
The helicopter crashed.
Vickers is dead.
Wesker betrayed us, Chris.
What?
He was gonna
leave us here to die.
We have to follow him,
'cause I think
it's our only way out of here.
[CLANKING]
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[]
[PROJECTOR RATTLING]
What is this place?
What... what were Umbrella
doing here?
This is where they were bringing
the kids from the orphanage.
They were experimenting on 'em.
This is where
they tried to bring me.
Claire.
It's okay.No!
[GRUNTS, YELLS]
[PANTING]
It's okay. It's okay.
Let's go find my brother.
[PANTING]
[]
[DISTANT SHRIEKING]
Shh. It's okay.
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
[WHIMPERING SOFTLY]
William, what have you
been doing down here?
God's work.
[WHIMPERING CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
William.[SHERRY GASPING]
Hey.
How did you get d...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Listen,
I've just come for that.
[LAUGHING]
This is my life's work.
I'm not giving it to anybody.
I'm not really offering you
a choice here, pal.
Okay, wait, wait. J-Just...
just-just put the gun down.
Uh, just put it down.
Who do you work for?
Doesn't matter.
No, I don't suppose it does.
[ANNETTE AND SHERRY WHIMPERING]
[GROANING]
[ANNETTE AND SHERRY SOBBING,
SCREAMING]
[ANNETTE SCREAMS]
No, no, no, no.Daddy!
God. Oh, my God. Okay, okay.
[WEAKLY]:
Vials. Vials.
Vials.
Hey!
I need that.
Just hand me the vials.
Okay, don't do anything stupid,
lady, okay?
No!
[BODY THUDS]
Fuck.
Where'd the kid go? Kid?
Kid?
What the fuck?
You.
[WILLIAM GROANING]
You didn't have to
make it like this.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
[GURGLING]
This is so fucked.
[TWO GUNSHOTS][WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
[GLASS CRUNCHES]
[GUNSHOT][GROANS]
[BODY THUDS][BREATHING HEAVILY]
Hey. It's okay.
He killed them.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.[WESKER GROANING]
Jesus, Valentine,
you and that fucking gun.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, no, no, no. We're gonna
get you out of here.
No, no, no, Jill.
I fucked up.
Umbrella are gonna
destroy this place.
All of Raccoon, okay?
There's a train tunnel
beneath this facility.
It leads to the other side of
the mountains and into Gatlin.
You need to get to that train.
You need to go now.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
I'm sorry, man.
I'm sorry.
I wouldn't have pulled
the trigger, kid.
[LAUGHS]
[GROANS]No, no, no.
Wesker!
[SHUDDERING BREATHS]
[JILL SOBS]
[]
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING, GURGLING]
[SNARLS, ROARS]
[JILL GRUNTING, PANTING]
Come on, this over here.
[GRUNTS]
Okay, come on, come on.
[GRUNTING]
Oh, shit.
[CREAKING]
[GROANING]
[ROARING]
[BOTH GASPING]
Jesus.
[DISTANT ROARING]
Hide.
Come on. Go. Go.
[GROWLING]
[WILLIAM SNARLING]
[WILLIAM ROARS]
[GROWLING]
[SNARLS]
Chris, come out and play.
[WILLIAM GROANS]
[WILLIAM CHUCKLING]
Did you really believe
you could be part of my family?
Ooh, such a sweet
little soldier.
Such a loyal little drone.
Where are you, Chris?
[SNARLS]
[LAUGHING]
How could you be so dumb
when your sister's so smart?
[LAUGHING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLING][GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You know...
I almost feel sad
having to kill you.
[GROANING]
Almost.
You know,
I should have taken
you and your sister
down to the lab.
You would have made
excellent specimens.
[LAUGHS, GROANS][GUNSHOT]
Get...[SQUEALING]
the fuck...
away...
...from my brother.
[GURGLING]
Do it.
Chris, my boy.
[CHUCKLES]
Shut the fuck up.
[GUNSHOT][WILLIAM SHRIEKS]
[EXHALES SLOWLY]
[]
I'm so glad you're okay.
This is really nice,
but I think I broke some ribs.
Oh, my God.
Sorry. Are you hurt?No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
We got to get the fuck
out of here.
Umbrella is gonna
level this place.
Okay.
Hey, whoa. [CHUCKLES]Rookie?
Yeah. Trust me, I'm as
surprised as you are, buddy.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
[PANTING]:
Okay.
Come on!
[ALL PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[SQUISHING]
Sit down.
- We'll get it started.- Okay.
We only have five minutes left
until the place self-destructs.
How does it all work?
Um...
[SWITCHES CLICKING]
[LEON GRUNTS][ELECTRICAL WHIRRING]
Whoo, whoo. All right.
[CLANKS]
[LIGHTS CLINKING]
We're gonna
get out of here.
Whoo!
[METALLIC SCREECHING]
[]
I should've listened to you
a long time ago.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I may have scratched
the paint on your bike.
Oh, my... [CHUCKLES]
[GROANS]
Don't make me laugh.
Sorry.
[BEEPING]
Oh, f...
[RUMBLING, CRACKLING]
[EXPLOSIVE RUMBLING]
[]
[WHIMPERING]
[METALLIC SCREECHING]
Go get the others.
I'll find a way out.
You okay?Uh-huh.
[STEADY THUMPING, CREAKING]
[SNARLING]
Oh, my God.
Sherry, get behind me.
[ROARS][GROANS]
Sherry, run!
[WHIMPERS, GRUNTS]
Claire!
[CLAIRE WHIMPERS]
[SCREAMS]
[ROARING]
[CLAIRE YELLS]
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLS]
[HISSES]No!
[SHRIEKING][CLAIRE YELPS]
[GROWLS]
[GUN CLICKS]
[WHIMPERING]
[ROARS]Hey!
You ugly fuck!
[GROWLS, ROARS]
Oh, shit!
[SHERRY SCREAMS]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
A rocket launcher?
[CHUCKLES]
Found it in first class.
[ROCKET LAUNCHER
DROPS TO FLOOR]
[GRUNTS]
Holy shit.
What the fuck you guys do
to this train?
[MUFFLED EXPLOSIONS]
Shit.
[EXPLOSIONS, RUMBLING]
[COW BELLOWING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[THUDS]
[GROANING, GASPING]
You're awake at last.
[WESKER TAKING SHALLOW,
RAPID BREATHS]
Where am I?That doesn't matter.
Wait, I... I don't understand.
I thought I was dead.
You were.
My eyes.
What happened to my eyes?
I can't see.
It's a side effect.
One of the things we had to do
to bring you back.
There will be others.
[]
[PANTING]
You never told me your name.
Ada.
My name is Ada Wong.
What do you want from me?
[]
[MUSIC FADES]