Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
Why don't we, uh,
take a vacation, you know?
That's a break from everything.
And then...
we can try again,
when it feels right.
Is Emilia here?
Oh! Coffee shop.
Okay, okay.
Hey there.
Hi. I only have the half-hour.
I know.
I'm sorry, Emilia.
I got all the stuff
that you asked for.
Took a while to find
that blue scarf.
I know you would've walked
right toward it.
Thank you for bringing these.
How's the painting?
Did you find a place to work?
Uh, it's small,
but it has decent light,
-so it'll do for now.
-Only for now?
Um...
I, um, ordered you
a chocolate croissant.
Benedict... please.
It's been months.
Two months.
Are you really this...
okay with this?
We both need the time.
Yeah. Okay.
All right.
Let's take a vacation.
Right? You're a teacher,
you get the whole summer off.
I close the shop
for a couple of months,
I mean,
that's a real break.
Then we can
recharge our batteries,
come back here,
try again.
Um...
We don't even have to try.
You talked about
having a family
since the day we met.
Yeah, 'cause I thought
that's what we both wanted.
It was, and...
heaven knows we tried,
but I can't anymore.
I'm... I'm tired
of feeling like a failure
for it.
It...
I have-- I have to go
and open the shop.
Hey, hey, no. Adriana's there.
There's no need to rush. Just--
Look.
You're not a failure.
Why don't you come over
tonight, okay?
We'll talk.
Come to the house,
I'll make dinner.
It's not a break
if we don't take the space.
You should try that too, Ben.
Just take time, please.
Just find something
that makes you happy.
Here you go.
They're beautiful. Thanks.
Bye, Emilia!
Ciao.
Okay, I don't care
how busy you look.
Tell me--
how was breakfast?
Ah, it's the same, Adriana,
no matter what he claims.
Just the same.
Oh, he can change.
No. Benedict does not change.
The furniture in the living room
hasn't moved an inch
in 25 years.
Well, that never
bothered you before.
Maybe I should have
paid more attention
to what that meant.
One can be happy being single.
You are a beautiful proof
of that.
Oh, Pedro may be the reason
I came to Washington,
and why I opened this store,
but he wasn't a good husband.
Now, if the right man
were to come along tomorrow...
Only if he was
the right man for you.
Por supuesto.
Why settle?
Even if I can't have a baby,
I can still be happy.
You know,
happy with what I have,
with what I am,
'cause life is happening
right here, right now.
I can't wait.
If Benedict cannot see that,
if he can't get unstuck, then...
Hey, guys.
-Hey, Ben.
-Hey.
Anything biting today?
Ah, caught
a couple of rockfish.
I caught a sunburn.
-Oh.
-The usual?
Oh. Always.
Steve and Sean work here now?
Uh, yeah, if you want
to call it that.
It's more like work release
with these two.
Owen, the boys
are on probation?
Yeah.
They're doing time here
until they leave for school.
Their Ma needs the peace
and I need the help.
Hey, guys. Knock it off. Go.
So what's the occasion?
Huh?
All dressed up.
Oh. Uh, breakfast with Emilia.
Ah.
I saw your face
when you walked in.
Hmm.
Well, uh...
I don't know
what to say to her.
I don't...
We just always come back
to the same thing,
every time.
She's not ready
to try for a baby again.
I get it. You know?
All the doctors
and procedures
and hormones
and then it doesn't,
you know...
Ben, maybe
it's not meant to be.
No. She, I mean...
she just needs more time.
You know?
Yeah.
You need to finish
that necklace, Benedict.
The joints are messy.
You can clean that up.
The lines of it are beautiful.
It's a good design.
You're really talented.
Are you sure you can handle
Charlie while we're gone?
Yeah. I've got it, Mom.
Don't worry so much.
Ahh. Here it is.
Look at the veins
in that stone.
It's Madagascar agate.
It's a powerful healer.
Is that where
you and Mom are going?
-Madagascar, right?
-Mm-hmm.
Take me with you, please.
You have school, Charlie.
Come on!
I'm gonna run away.
-I'll help you pack.
-Stop.
Hey! I want to see both of you
right here when we get back.
All right,
can you give that to Dad?
-Here you go.
-Mom, can you pass me the bowl?
Yes.
Emilia, you can use your key.
Can I help you?
Are you Benedict Stone?
Yeah.
I'm Gemma.
Your niece.
Gemma?
Charlie's daughter.
Your brother?
He did tell you about me, right?
Uh, your mom sent
a birth announcement
to the store,
-but that was just--
16 years ago.
Can I come in?
Sorry. Yeah. Come in.
-You're...
Charlie's daughter.
You're his brother, right?
You're my uncle?
Uh, yeah, I guess I am.
So, what...
what are you doing here?
What-- how did you...
I wanted to meet you.
So I took a bus and a ferry.
From where?
New Mexico.
Is that where Charlie lives?
What--
How did you get here?
I just said.
I know, besides the bus.
Did Charlie tell you about me?
My mom did.
She said you and Dad
did not get along.
"Don't bring it up."
So I didn't.
-But then I found the bag.
-What bag?
Do you have any juice?
I haven't had anything to drink
since Seattle.
Sure.
That's expired coffee creamer.
Yeah.
I wasn't expecting anyone.
Yeah, I can see that.
Maybe just some water?
-Thanks.
-Mm-hmm.
I wanted to talk to you
about something.
-Um, yeah, sure.
You know what this is?
I found it
in my dad's study last month
and he told me
it was his inheritance
from his brother.
And at first, I thought,
"a bunch of rocks?"
But I started looking them up,
and they're all
gemstones of some kind.
Not tons-of-money jewels,
but...
you'd put them in jewelry.
But you knew that.
I knew Dad
grew up in Washington,
and I found your shop
and your name,
and then this address.
So...
what did Charlie say about me,
when you asked to come here?
He said
he hasn't spoken to you
in years
and you guys were never close,
and I should forget about you.
Does my brother
-know you're here?
-Sure.
All right,
we need to call him.
My purse got stolen
when we stopped in Seattle.
Oh. What's the number?
It's in my phone.
In my purse?
I don't know, like,
actual digits--
it's in my phone.
Oh.
Oh! Are you, um, cold?
Do you want me
to make you some tea?
You know,
something hot?
Oh, no. No, I'm beat.
Maybe just a towel,
and show me where I can sleep?
Yeah.
Okay, so there isn't really
a guest room.
There's, uh, an office
and then there's
this.
Wow.
This'll work.
Did you paint these?
No. My wife did.
She picked up the hobby
a few years ago.
I have an aunt? Awesome.
Can I meet her?
She's not home.
Look, you can stay tonight,
but, uh, tomorrow,
we've gotta contact your dad.
I texted him from Seattle,
but, yeah, okay, whatever.
Thanks, Uncle B.
That's not my name.
Okay.
Rest up.
Angel Aura Quartz.
Connection.
Positivity.
Joy.
Hey, Uncle B?
Your wife is beautiful.
Oh. I didn't even know
you were up.
Is this you and my dad?
Yup.
And who are these people?
That's Emilia and her family.
They live in Buenos Aires.
Yeah.
Ohh... these are Aunt Emilia.
Totally.
And all this...
is yours.
Well, this was my father's,
and, uh...
yeah, it's mine now.
All their stuff is here.
If Charlie wanted
any of it, okay,
he could have had anything.
He's good for furniture.
Thanks.
I've been looking it up.
and there are eight
"Charles Stones"
in the New Mexico area--
but none of them the right age.
Oh, well, we live
off the grid, actually.
-Where?
-It's a ranch.
Honestly, GPS doesn't even
get it right.
My dad knows where I am.
What's the problem?
Well, this isn't... normal.
Well, what did "normal"
ever get anyone?
It's an adventure!
Yeah, but you need--
I need food.
I need breakfast.
I didn't eat at all yesterday.
All right,
I can make you breakfast.
No, I've seen your fridge--
no offense.
Is there somewhere we can go?
My treat!
I'll pay you back,
or I can work at the shop.
Or both.
Uh, don't worry,
I-- I'll get you breakfast.
So, what about your mother?
-Uh, she's gone.
-Gone?
Hey, Ben!
This is my niece!
She's visiting.
-Hi!
-Hi.
Wait. Why aren't we stopping?
Am I embarrassing?
No. I've got to get
to the shop.
Wait. Wait, please?
Please, can
we go check out the pier?
I've never seen
the ocean before,
and it was too dark last night
to even see.
Ple-e-e-ease?
Sure.
Gemma, slow down.
What do you mean,
your mom's "gone"?
Whoo!
I'm the queen of the world!
Whoo-oo!
You make the jewelry?
You're an artist!
No. It's a... craft.
Hi, cutie.
Don't touch him, he's feral.
Oh! But he's so cu-u-ute.
Been here for days.
Anyways, I looked up
a bunch of the stones
from my bag,
and did you know every stone
has a meaning?
Well, of course, you do,
because you have to pick out
the right ones
for your jewelry,
but I thought it was amazing.
Hey, that woman looks
like your wife.
Good eyesight.
20/10 vision,
even at night.
So what's the deal?
-Excuse me?
-With your wife?
Why wasn't she
at your house last night?
She likes to hang out
with her cousin, you know.
She's an elementary school
teacher,
and helps at the flower shop
during the summer.
So I'll see her tonight?
We should go over
and introduce me--
No! We're...
We're on a break.
She left you.
How long
have you been married?
-Ten years next month.
-Then how'd you meet?
Gemma, I got
a lot of work to do today.
Do you have plans?
Stuff to do?
How'd you meet?
Can we just take a minute,
catch our breath--
Oh, come on, Uncle B.
It was a hike.
There was a club with an ad
in the back of the paper--
anyone who was interested
in hiking Green Falls Trail.
Wow. I can see it now.
A steep, dangerous climb...
with a great view--
it had to be!
And only the two of you
showed up.
No, there was
a bunch of people.
But you spotted her
and... what?
Oh, come on!
Was it "hi," "hi,"
"what do you do," blah, blah?
"Shoulder."
That's your big opening?
I was hiking
and I heard a voice behind me
say, "Shoulder."
So, I stopped, turned around,
and it was Emilia.
She had a rock in her shoe,
so she leaned on my shoulder
and took off her shoe,
and shook it out.
Then you looked in her eyes
and she looked in yours,
and that was it?
No, wait!
You definitely
put her slipper back on
for her, right?
It was a running shoe.
Okay, but you slipped it
back on,
you looked in her eyes,
and you said...?
I don't remember.
You were speechless.
Okay.
You had to be.
I mean,
the power of that moment.
So what're you gonna do?
Excuse me?
To win her back!
She left you,
but you want her back--
how're you gonna woo her?
"Woo"?
Oh! You are so lucky
that I am here.
This is a mission.
-Oh, no.
-Oh... yes.
"W.E.B."
"Win Emilia Back."
We're gonna get you in shape,
you're gonna be
a boyfriend again.
You need romance
and big gestures!
We're gonna remind Emilia
why she fell in love with you.
She will be back!
We should make notes.
Are you cold?
You're shivering.
Yeah. This is summer?
Welcome to Washington.
Here. Go buy yourself
some warm clothes.
You can't have much
in that little backpack.
You're gonna need some things.
Seriously? Thanks.
Um, before you go,
does Charlie have an email?
-Do you remember that?
-Um, yeah.
It's "CS...
@SW.Net."
It's our zip code.
I'll get us something low-fat
and healthy for lunch.
Tiger's Eye.
Protection.
Making Contact.
New Changes.
All the prices are marked,
except for
the consignment pieces.
Thanks.
They're from
the set of a movie.
They just arrived.
Can I put these here
while I look?
Yeah, sure.
That is for the town's
end-of-summer block party.
It's really fun,
if you're around.
I plan to be.
I'm Maggie, by the way.
Gemma.
-Hi.
Um, I'd love
to come by the house today
to pick up some canvases
from my studio.
Oh, yeah.
You want them for your show?
Yeah, I got the flyer.
Congratulations.
Yeah.
Um, I may need some of them.
I'm still making decisions.
A-About the show.
Right.
Okay.
Um, uh... uh...
That's very exciting--
first time out,
solo show.
I guess Lawrence
has big plans for me.
I don't know.
Um, when is it
a good time to come by?
Uh... those canvasses
are heavy.
I can manage.
No, no. I'll bring them
by Adriana's tonight.
Um, I'm not staying there.
I'm at Veronica's.
She's in the city,
so I'm staying at the apartment.
Oh, okay. Great.
I can bring them--
I can bring them there.
-Okay.
-Okay. See you.
Ciao.
Super-awkward!
Sorry.
It just wasn't the right time
to introduce you two.
Yeah, I got that by the look.
Well, I got pretty much
everything I need
at the secondhand store.
-Mm-hmm?
-There's your change.
Who's Lawrence?
He's the gallery owner.
What's this?
Lunch. For "W.E.B."
We might need you to recreate
your hike, when you met,
or something,
but we need you
in tip-top shape.
Never get the "sale" salad.
This one's turquoise, right?
Only it's raw?
Looks like it.
We have a lot of it back home.
Turquoise promotes healing
and communication
and...
Can I use your computer
and look it up?
I have a better idea.
Wait.
This is a treasure chest.
Are we rich?
Depends on what
you count as rich.
All right.
Let's see here.
-That's you and Dad?
-Yeah.
Why do you look like that?
Well, it was right after
your grandparents' funeral.
Dad said they drowned together.
Yeah, they were overseas,
uh, buying gemstones.
I was here,
babysitting your dad.
And there was a tsunami.
It took everyone by surprise.
When I didn't hear from my mom,
I just knew...
and the next morning,
I got the call.
Their stuff arrived
three weeks later.
Here. Go ahead.
Take it out.
What did your dad tell you
about his family?
Um...
that his parents were magical
and died tragically.
That was true.
He said he was an orphan.
We were.
You stayed here?
In this house?
Yeah, I was 18, so...
I raised Charlie.
Thank you.
I did the best I could.
I don't understand.
You raised my dad
and we couldn't ever visit you?
If, uh, you want what
we're looking for,
it's gonna be over here.
Did my grandmother make these?
Your grandmother?
Uh, no,
she was better than that.
Those are some practice pieces
that I was working on.
I don't even know
what they're doing in there.
Because they're awesome!
No! They're really flawed.
These are way more interesting
than all the stuff
in the shop now.
Gee, thanks.
There we go.
All right. Here.
My dad started
this gemstone book
when he was younger.
Wow.
There's a lot
of blank pages here.
If I stay longer,
I can fill them in for you.
Look up the stones,
like he did.
"Peridot--
rich green stone,
sometimes called Chrysolite.
It can lessen stress,
and help us find
what is lost..."
You so need some peridot,
Uncle B!
Maybe!
Oh...
What are the holes for?
Uh...
I told Emilia
I'd bring those paintings over.
You keep that.
I meant to ask
about the weapon earlier.
Deserted Dog
had props from some movie.
Whoa.
I got it cheap.
Don't worry.
Check it.
It's surprisingly solid, right?
You need to make
a statement to Emilia.
Yeah, I'm gonna bring
the canvases over to her.
That's like... an errand!
Like she sent you to the store.
And, okay,
that's a husband thing,
but you need to be
her boyfriend again.
I'm not really sure what the--
Her boyfriend!
The man who will fight for her,
if need be.
Yeah, well, I mean,
I can see where, you know,
some of that would be...
Okay, yeah,
but I'm not sure
this is the message!
Because it's silly?
Well, for starters, yeah!
Unpredictable?
A big gesture?
Why not?
I mean, look--
Emilia is a few pillows
and a couple throw rugs away
from out of here.
What have you got to lose,
Uncle B?
This apartment...
is there a balcony?
Uh... yeah.
Then it's perfect!
You're there to fight for her,
like Romeo!
Mm.
None of that ended well,
if I remember correctly.
It didn't?
You know,
we should go to Argentina.
What?
I want to see everything
that molded you.
All the influences.
Did you paint there?
-I actually started here.
-Mm.
It's a bit chilly.
Hmm.
-Uh, do you want to--?
-Yeah.
Hi.
Ahh.
Dinner tomorrow?
Oh, I'm sorry, I can't.
How about if I promise
it's only work?
Would that be true?
Eh...
I'll be sorting the art
in the gallery next week.
We can go over things then.
Sure.
-Great.
-Good day.
-Ben?
-As promised.
Hope I'm not too late.
I--
Is that a sword?
Yeah!
Were you expecting pirates
on the way?
Oh, you never know.
Uh, no, actually, uh,
Gemma gave it to me.
-Gemma?
-Yeah. The girl
who came in the shop earlier,
when you were there.
Um...
she's Charlie's daughter.
-That's incredible!
-Mm-hmm.
You heard from Charlie?
No. She just showed up
last night out of nowhere,
unexpectedly.
What did Charlie say?
I couldn't call--
she doesn't have his number,
and her phone and bag
were stolen on her trip.
Ben, this girl
could be anyone.
She looks exactly like him.
She's Charlie's kid.
Ben, this is huge.
Yeah, she is something.
I'd love to meet her.
-Yeah. Can we do that soon?
-Please.
The last of your summer roses.
Thank you.
[Gemma narrat.
Initiating.
Life force.
Self-confidence.
There were muffins
on this plate last night!
-No starchy carbs
until day eight.
This feels like day--
Five.
Three more days
and you can have a cheat day.
You're doing great.
Mm.
Hey, guys!
Hi, Harry. Hi, Owen.
Hey, hey.
Anything biting?
Mosquitoes.
How's your day, Gemma?
Going good.
Started
with a healthy breakfast,
followed by
a 15-minute cardio blast.
I blasted.
-Oh, it shows.
Yeah.
Oh, hi, Maggie.
Hey, Gemma.
This is Tony.
S'up?
We're here looking
for an engagement ring.
Congratulations!
Okay, well, we have
some, you know, old, standard--
"classic" rings...
...but my Uncle B can design
something just for you--
one of a kind,
with any stone you want.
Wow!
We just want
a little diamond.
That's cute.
Oh... yeah.
Tony proposed to me
at a party
and it was all we had.
It's actually gonna be hard
to let it go.
Well... I have an idea.
This... is aquamarine,
and you would love it
because it promotes openness
and communication
and imagination,
and my Uncle B can design
something like your ring,
but put that in--
Can we just be normal?
What about these?
Can you just look at this
before you decide?
You telling me you're not
gonna show them to me?
Um, honey, you know what?
Why don't we do this later?
I've got to get back.
Thank you so much, Gemma.
Come on.
Ugh! That wedding is doomed!
She needs
to ditch that guy.
Uh, we sell the client
what they want, all right?
Do you know how much I clear
on an engagement ring?
And they're already made.
But it wasn't right!
You didn't see her face.
She loved this idea.
But she didn't buy it,
did she?
Okay, but people browse!
I'm just trying to help.
But whatever!
I need air.
Wait!
Oh. Sorry. Oh...
-Hey.
-Emilia.
Okay, now I'm really sorry.
Gemma, I was just coming
to meet you.
Ben is so happy you're here.
Well, not today.
He can be so,
"This is how it is."
Yes, he can.
But, you know he's...
such a great guy,
when he's not...
you know.
I do.
Do you think you need
a little break this week?
That'd be great.
But, um, look,
it can be all three of us.
We're not speaking
till after lunch.
Be ready for the hike.
-See you soon?
-See you.
That's Gemma.
She just got so mad.
I don't know why.
She can turn on a dime.
-She's like...
-A teenager?
Yeah.
Have you heard from Charlie?
No answer.
She says her mom's "gone."
No explanation.
Something's not right here.
You know that.
I know, but I don't know
what to do about it yet.
Are you two free
on Thursday?
We can be.
Hey, what are you
doing in here?
Get off of there.
Come on. Get, get, get.
Little guy.
So...
Thursday,
what do you want to do?
Uh, the three of us?
I don't know.
Something different,
like...
I've never had lobster before.
Oh, good! Yeah. Lobster.
Hey, you know,
Charlie loved lobster.
When he was little,
he'd, uh...
eat it in a big bowl of butter.
Must be hard to find
out in the desert.
Uh, maybe in
a casino dining hall,
but that's definitely
not fresh.
Yeah.
So Charlie goes to casinos?
Around us,
they have the best restaurants.
Let's ride bikes, too.
Why not?
I'm really glad
you're here, Gemma.
So am I.
You're doing great.
That was easier
than yesterday, right?
Yeah.
The air here...
the water,
and all the birds!
I love it!
-What?
-Come on!
Let's see some moves...
or it's more jumping jacks.
Come on, Uncle B!
Come on.
I don't really...
Yeah-yeah-yeah! You got it!
Yeah-yeah-yeah!
You got it!
You got it! You got it!
-No, I'm gonna do this.
-No!
-Yeah.
-I'm gonna switch to this.
-What?
So, I was thinking,
for the show--
we get the same flower,
the same plant,
for as many paintings
as we can.
I love it.
What did Lawrence say?
If you love it,
he'll love it.
I see the looks he gives you.
Adriana--
I'm not blind.
If you threw a stick,
he would fetch it.
I'm still married
and you love Benedict.
I do, but I am your team--
whoever makes you happy.
I think these are ready
to go into a pot.
That's why you make
the best malfatti in the family.
You're patient.
You're gonna
teach Marcos for me.
That's your job.
Oh, you raised him
just as much as I did.
I was so busy opening the shop,
and Pedro was gone--
you were the one
taking care of him.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That didn't help.
You know, I'm...
I'm fine. Really. I am.
Sometimes, it just
sneaks up on me, that's all.
Come here.
That couch,
this shoulder...
yours,
whenever you need.
I want you know
how grateful I am
that you let me tag along
with you and Pedro moved here.
Tag along?
Are you kidding?
My husband was dragging me
to Washington
and I was gonna face winter
on my own?
No, thank you.
It was an adventure.
Well, whatever happens,
it still is an adventure.
It sure is.
Salud.
-Salud.
That's what I was saying.
We know each other, right?
Hey. Check the cooler.
We need more limes.
Sean, limes.
-You get 'em.
-No, you get 'em!
Knock it off.
-Steve. Limes.
-Yeah.
You're a brave man
for hiring your sons.
Oh! What was I thinking?
Cola with lime,
and we're getting more limes,
fresh.
Thanks.
All right, all right.
We're-- We're fresh enough.
-Thanks.
-Anyway, anyway.
back to what I was saying--
Diane, it's like she knows
what I'm gonna say--
-Before you say it.
-...Before I even say it.
Yeah, well, she can depend
on you--
that's what counts.
Yeah, well, I mean,
her birthday's coming up
and I want to get her
something special,
you know, something
she won't expect.
What, like a surprise?
Don't say it like that.
It's totally romantic.
And Uncle B
can design it for you!
-You can?
-I can?
You can.
Okay.
Yeah. Yeah, no problem.
Um, yeah, so, Diane--
I'm thinking, um... a bracelet?
Trust us to pick out the stone?
I can look it up.
You can do it?
Her birthday's in 10 days.
Yeah. We'll use her birthstone.
-Yeah.
-All right.
Hey, can we get the check?
We have a big day tomorrow.
That's right!
"W.E.B." in action.
Does that mean you'll be
wearing your good flannel?
You know it.
No! No, no, no, no.
"Good flannel"?
Those two words
don't go together.
-No, I can pull it off.
This one brings out his eyes.
Kunzite.
Love.
Mood lifting.
Frees emotions.
Okay, that's huge.
You guys'll help me, right?
I'll help you
with the leftovers.
Mom had a shellfish allergy,
so I could never even
try lobster.
Is your mom
from New Mexico?
She was.
Where is she now?
Who knows?
She and her Trevor travel a lot.
"Her Trevor"?
It's what Mom calls
her new husband.
"Her Trevor".
He does something with money.
That's exciting.
You can see new places.
-Mm!
-Like I'm invited?
They'd seriously
be no fun anyway.
Do you ever see her?
Once a year,
and that's plenty.
Did you see a ladies' room?
Yeah, right over there.
I'll be right back.
Please change the subject.
Thank you.
It's not a chore.
She's a sweet girl.
No, I know, but I can't get her
to open up like that.
She never wants
to talk about family.
It's so strange that Charlie
hasn't answered you.
What happened
between the two of you?
You said you had a fight
and he left,
but that cannot be all.
I never understood.
Neither did I.
I know you don't
like to talk about it.
It wasn't good,
and I can't be
the only one to fix it, so...
People gotta give you
a chance.
Can I help you find something?
No.
Spying.
Those two
are hopelessly in love.
Or just hopeless.
One of the two--
I can't tell yet.
Okay.
This is a good model.
No, that's too flawed.
No, it isn't.
Yeah, it is,
I made it as a kid.
Look, look at this line,
and these melds...
It could be straighter,
but not better.
Hey, Reggie can be kind of
argumentative, he's a lawyer.
-I'll take him.
-No, it's okay, I got it.
No, he can be really tough.
No, it's really okay.
Hi!
Can I help you?
Those earrings.
-For your wife?
-My daughter.
How old's your daughter?
-Excuse me?
-Hey, Reggie.
What can we do for you today?
Lisa's going away to college.
I want some nice earrings.
-Your best.
-Okay.
Right here.
Some of these are good.
The best ones aren't here.
Uncle B has to make them
just for your daughter.
A unique design.
Really?
That's what you do?
Uh, yeah.
That's what I do.
I want custom-made.
Okay.
Personally, I really love
how Uncle B combines
different stones.
I think
she'd really like those.
Well, these stones
in particular
bring peacefulness
and healing...
and calmness,
and soothe emotions...
Well, if those stones
can do all that,
I'll pay top dollar.
So, this is a rough sketch,
but...
It's good.
It's different.
Different's good.
I'll take 'em.
I'll write you up.
Lisa would never believe it,
but she means the world to me.
Then tell her!
Make her believe it.
She's your kid!
Gemma.
Excuse me.
Sorry about that.
Teen girls.
I have something for you.
Follow me.
What is that sound?
Seagulls.
Okay, you say seagulls--
there's no way
that sound is birds.
Just wait.
When our parents brought stones
back from their travels,
some were too flawed
to work with or sell,
but Mom loved flawed things.
You remind me of her.
And she believed everything
had its perfect place,
so this became ours.
After every trip,
we'd come out here
and hang all
the imperfect stones together.
This is
our real family tree, Gemma.
And you might be
the only Stone left
to carry on that tradition,
which makes you
the most important thing
in the world to us.
This is Kyanite.
It's for new beginnings.
Here. Find your spot.
Welcome home.
Poppy Jasper.
Enthusiasm.
Enjoyment.
Fresh energy.
It's only been two weeks,
but no sugar,
daily cardio,
and some hiking,
and look at you.
I feel...
Better?
"Thank you, Gemma.
You're a great coach."
Yes, and thank you.
-Oh, your dad emailed me back.
-Oh, yeah?
He didn't have much to say,
like when school starts or--
Oh, I still have
a few weeks, relax.
We'll figure it out,
but can't we just decide
to be happy for a while?
Yeah. We can.
We only have one week
until Emilia's big opening,
so what're you gonna wear?
Well, I don't know.
What, like a tuxedo?
I mean, that--
Mm. Not the vibe.
Hey, Harry!
Hey.
Hey, wait, what if I rode up
on a big white stallion
and swept Emilia off her feet?
-It's kinda old-school.
-Yeah, but it's a classic.
Hey! Hi, Gemma.
Hi, Harry.
Hey, can I rent this horse
for something next week?
Bingo?
Well, I don't see why not.
Ah! All right.
I'll call you with details.
-All right.
I didn't know
Uncle B could ride.
Yeah, I wasn't sure
that he could, either.
Hey, Uncle B?
Mm-hmm?
Can you ride a horse?
Well, I'm not gonna be,
like, jumping any fences
or anything.
You know?
I'll, like, watch a video.
Mm.
I got a better idea.
You sure
you know what you're doing?
How hard can it be?
Hey, it's your first ride,
in a long time,
so go slow.
It's better
for the horse's back anyway.
Hello! I grew up on a ranch.
Okay.
Let foot goes in that stirrup,
and your right leg,
swing it over,
but not too hard.
-Oh! Yeah.
-Okay. I got it.
Well, that would be
"too hard."
-Got it.
Okay, now remember--
separate the reins, thumbs up.
heels down--
like that.
When do I pull the reins?
Okay, your legs
are what move the horse
and then the reins
help steer the horse.
So squeeze your legs
against him,
-but not too hard--
-Oh, here we go.
I think I squeezed him
too hard.
He looks scared.
Don't worry.
Uncle B will be fine.
No, I meant Bingo.
-Oh!
It's good, right?
-Yeah--
-Where is he going?
-Yeah, you got it, Uncle B!
-Whoo!
-Hey! This is easy!
-Yeah!
Heels down!
There you go!
Way to go, Uncle B.
I think I need some chaps.
-No.
Hi.
Mind if I browse?
Sure.
Who's that?
A stray.
With a cat carrier and toys?
Well...
it-- it's now "Kimberly".
"Kimberly".
Uh, Gemma bonded with it.
I said "yes" to the store,
but a hard "no" to the house.
Oh, you pick your battles.
You got to.
Uh...
so, it's nice to see you.
I'm looking for a pin...
a brooch.
It's for Veronica,
'cause for letting me
stay in her apartment.
She collects them--
brooches.
Right. When is she back?
In two weeks.
Uh, I can
make a brooch for you--
uh, her.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Let's see...
I was just working on something.
I mean, this is just something
I've been noodling.
I think this could probably
work as a-- as a brooch.
That's very Veronica.
-Right?
-What are these?
Uh, those are...
uh-- oh, here we go.
Tourmaline quartz, so...
let's say like that.
She wears
a lot of black and white,
so this is perfect.
Oh, look.
The reflection on the stone...
deepens the design.
Yeah. Look at that.
You didn't notice
you had done that?
You know, sometimes,
you're just in it,
and-and, uh, things happen...
Yes.
Tourmaline quartz is, uh...
...it heals,
and it brings
inspiration and...
confidence.
-Where did you get that from?
-The journal.
My dad's journal.
I dug it out of the trunk.
Gemma reads it out loud to me.
She loves it.
You've been busy.
May I?
Sure.
It's a lot of commissions
and one-offs.
Uh...
Wow! I've never seen
you design like this.
I'm just giving it a try.
Gemma has been
a really good influence on you.
-Yeah.
Benedict.
-Are the earrings ready?
Yeah.
Ohh! Emilia,
it's nice to see you.
Hi, Reggie.
Uh...
these are--
Oh! Look at that.
Oh, wow.
They're for Lisa.
They're beautiful.
She's gonna love them.
Um, I'm late.
No, this is just
gonna take a minute.
But you're coming
to the opening, right?
On Thursday? With Gemma?
I'll see you there.
Don't let that one get away.
Though, from what I've heard,
if you do need a lawyer...
Let's take a look
at these together
and make sure
that we love them.
What?
I don't think
I can put this up for sale.
Oh, but it's one of your best.
It has to be in the show.
This should stay
in the family.
Let's mark it "sold"
and you can still show it
for everyone to see.
That's a good idea.
Is Ben coming?
Yes. You should see
the work he's doing.
Gemma has him designing--
really designing.
Very creative stuff.
Good for him!
Isn't it?
I'm just...
I don't know why didn't do that
when we were together.
Who knows?
I mean,
why did you start painting?
I was restless.
I wanted to express myself.
Be me,
apart from anyone else.
And you found this self,
and you made something good.
You got inspired.
I guess I did.
Benedict was stuck.
Now he makes something good
out of it, too.
He's finding himself,
and that's a good thing.
You're right.
Fire Opal.
Individuality.
Awakening.
Progress.
Hello?
Gemma!
Gemma? Hey, where are you?
Come on.
You gotta go to school tomorrow.
-What are you doing?
-Waiting.
They're just late.
But they can't come back,
Charlie.
Mom and Dad are gone.
You don't "know" know that.
Y-You didn't see them
in those boxes.
They can get lost sometimes.
It's gonna be okay.
Who are we listening to?
"Restore the Hope."
They're playing a concert
here next week.
Where have you been?
I was at work.
I got caught up.
You didn't even call!
Do you even know what kind
of sound this house makes?
Things were hitting the roof.
Uh, branches.
They didn't sound
like branches.
Sorry. You're right.
I should've called.
Washington must sound different
than New Mexico.
Do you miss home?
No.
I love adventures.
I want to see everything.
Yeah, you come by that
honestly.
But both things can be true.
Hi!
Hi.
Hi. Thank you so much
for coming.
-Hi!
-Hi.
Hi!
Everything looks great.
You okay?
I should've practiced riding
in these pants.
Oh, that's the least
of our worries.
Who's the guys with his hands
all over Aunt Emilia?
-Lawrence Donnington.
-That's no good.
Couldn't agree with you more.
Okay. Um, listen,
in a half an hour,
meet me outside with Harry
and the horse.
I'll bring Emilia out there,
and off we go.
And where are you going?
Into the sunset.
Romantic, right?
Totally.
Oh.
Go ahead.
-Hey.
-All right.
-How's it going?
There he is!
Benedict!
Thank you so much.
I love it.
It was all Owen's idea.
Yeah, I would've harvested
those pearls myself,
if I had to.
Uh, anyone seen the bar?
It's over there.
Fair warning--
white wine only.
Hi. I'd like to grab
this painting over here.
Purchase it.
Perfect.
The Powells want to meet you.
They have an art gallery
in San Francisco--
very high-end market.
Hey.
Remember that concert
that I was telling you about?
Guess who's going.
Um...
the goofballs?
Come on, you know their dad
and everything.
I'll think about it.
Remember, be outside
in 20 minutes.
-I won't forget.
-Okay, okay, okay.
Focus.
Okay.
You bought it?
Yeah, it was the first one.
I couldn't let that go.
I wanted to get the gem tree,
but it's already been sold.
No. It's just not for sale.
I couldn't let that one go.
Shoulder?
I'm not used to these heels.
Uh, if I could have
everybody's attention, please,
for a moment.
I have to go.
Hello, everyone.
I wanted to thank you all
for coming tonight,
to welcome
a bright new light
to the art world
on the West Coast.
Emilia brings her passion
and a sense of color
and light
from her Argentinean roots,
and gives our Washington flora
and countryside
a special glow.
Hard to believe
this is her first show.
I'm grateful to be
the art dealer who found her.
Emilia...
congratulations.
Thank you.
Well, this is a first
for me--
to be showing my art
and also to be talking to
what looks like
the whole population
of the island.
I didn't know
you were such art lovers.
When I started painting,
I did it for myself,
and I've never dreamt
that I would be showing
these paintings here tonight,
so I want to say thank you.
I am so grateful
for your support.
Only vintage
would be worthy of you tonight.
Oh, thank you.
Hey.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
I have a surprise for you.
Outside.
-Where?
-Just out front.
Okay.
Uh, Emilia, where are you--?
There's a surprise
for me outside.
A surprise?
What's this?
Maisy.
Where's Bingo?
He twisted his ankle
in the turnout.
He should be good
in a week or two.
I didn't want to leave you
high and dry,
so here's Maisy.
What in the blazes
am I supposed to do with Maisy?
Uh, who's your furry friend,
Benedict?
Uh, Maisy.
Everyone...
Everyone, Maisy.
Um...
Llamas...
represent strength...
and perseverance--
Beauty.
Beauty!
And grace in rocky places.
And that's what Emilia is...
beauty and grace, I mean.
Not rocky.
She's adorable.
Thank you.
An opening-night llama?
That's, uh, definitely a first.
Emilia, your husband's a hoot.
I love llamas.
Could you give us a minute?
This wasn't the plan.
Bingo twisted an ankle.
"Bingo"?
Uh, there was a white stallion
to ride
and, you know, sweep you away.
Who was gonna ride it?
You?
And you.
Uh, Emilia?
Some buyers
want to say hello.
I'll be right there.
I have to go.
Okay.
Uncle B?
You ready to call it a night?
Hey... what do you
want me to do with Maisy?
Bloodstone.
Courage.
Guidance.
Instinct.
Great job under pressure.
Bonus points!
No more big gestures.
Oh, no, no.
You just need the right one.
Honestly, it was 50-50
you would even
stay on the horse.
And where were you gonna
put Aunt Emilia?
Yeah, I just realized,
I didn't really work that out.
I think she was impressed.
Seriously.
Anybody can give out
a bottle of champagne.
Which one do you think
she's gonna remember?
Heh! There is that.
Also, you don't have to worry
about that Lawrence.
-Oh?
-I figured it out.
-Really?
-He may sell art--
-Uh-huh?
-...But you make art.
I saw two Benedict Stone
originals in there tonight,
and they look amazing.
You may not know it,
but you had a great night,
Uncle B.
You really want to go
to that concert, don't you?
Oh! So much!
But that's not why--
Oh, give me a break.
I raised a teenager.
I'll see you coming.
Okay, well, I'm glad
you've been trained.
I know I can be a handful.
Why would you say that?
"Handful."
Oh, it's just something
Dad always said.
Says.
Hey! The ice cream shop's
still open.
My treat.
I guess my tab with you's
getting pretty big now.
Okay, every single piece sold,
Emilia.
Now, that never happens.
These are friends
and neighbors.
They were just being supportive.
Nobody's polite
with their money.
Ah! Listen to your cousin.
Okay, I've got to run,
but this is just the beginning
for you and I, Ms. Ramirez.
Ciao.
Don't.
Everything's
still up in the air.
Thank you.
Gemma, I need to ask you--
we haven't heard from your dad
since that one email.
Why do you got
to "make it work"?
What?
"Everything is beyond ruined.
If you don't belong here,
then there's nowhere else."
I didn't write that.
What's ruined?
Why do you have
nowhere else to go?
You want me to go?
Fine! I'll leave.
Gemma, is Charlie still alive?
What?
Of course, he's still alive!
Then what's going on
with you two?
Tell me the truth.
The truth...
My dad's actually
just really happy
that I'm gone right now.
He's remarried--
Haley--
and they're having a lot of fun,
so I wanted to spend
the whole summer here.
Not just a few days,
that's why I had to...
"Make it work."
All right.
Is there anything else
I need to know?
No.
Well, there is one thing.
Mm?
This shop needs a makeover.
Okay, I see it.
A total...
extreme...
makeover!
Whoa. One coat of paint,
maybe,
but I pick the color.
We'll see.
Nice, right?
This is the gesture
Emilia needs.
Watch your step.
We're going through the door.
Careful.
-A few more steps...
-Okay.
Almost...
Okay.
Stay there,
stay there, stay there.
Open your eyes.
Ta-dah!
Wow.
Looks like
a completely different shop.
Right?
Oh... Benedict.
You didn't have to do that.
It's perfect there.
I mean...
you belong here.
Your work does.
Let me take you both
out to celebrate.
Oh. Well,
I have a headache
from all the fumes.
So does Kimberly,
so I should take us both
back home,
but you two go.
Ben?
-Alfie's Bistro.
-Yeah.
Hey, the cat stays
in the crate, all right?
Okay.
To your show.
-To your new shop.
-To us!
What?
Is it Lawrence?
Ben! We're still married.
And that's stopping him?
He's a gentleman,
and I keep things
professional.
Come home, Emilia.
It is different.
-How?
-I mean...
I know I wasn't very open
to adoption before,
but now I can see it.
Benedict.
You don't want to adopt?
It's not about kids anymore.
It's about us.
You and me.
Could you be happy
with just the two of us?
I mean, that's how it's been
for the past 10 years.
I'm-- I was...
-Happy?
-Yeah.
We were,
but waiting, always--
waiting on treatments
and test results.
It was as if
waiting for a child meant
we were waiting
for our own lives to start.
That has to stop.
You're right.
Just like that?
Why not?
Could you be happy
with just the two of us?
Yes.
I could.
It's a big change.
But...
There's no answer tonight.
Just dinner.
Azurite.
Memories.
Release.
Mysteries.
Hey, since when
do you wear makeup?
Aunt Emilia gave it to me.
Her cousin's hilarious,
by the way.
She gave me the eyeliner.
This is not a date.
With either Steve or Sean,
correct?
It's just a concert.
I think
their dad's even going.
Here, um...
a phone
and some emergency cash,
in case you get separated
in the crowd.
I don't need it.
Listen, um...
there's plenty of minutes
already prepaid on that thing.
Set up a meeting spot,
just in case
you get separated.
Relax!
You get the night off from me.
Have fun.
Not too much fun.
And there's a hit
up the third base line
into left field.
That's going
to bring in a run.
And Davis,
with a one-out single,
gets it,
and it's 3-2.
Something new.
You're supposed
to be in your crate, cat.
How did you even get out here?
Yes. You forget your key?
Well, don't go up there.
Hey.
I'm not kidding.
Just stay put.
I'm coming up to get you.
No, no, no, no, no!
Oh, my...
Hey, kitty-cat. Kimberly.
Get outta there.
I'll get some snacks
for your crate.
Hey. It's Charlie.
Leave a message.
Hey, Charlie. It's Ben.
Your brother... Benedict.
Uh, Gemma's here.
She's in Washington.
Um, she said you knew,
but I just found her phone
and saw your messages.
Uh, she gave me
an email for you,
but it's obviously
an address that she controls,
not yours.
Um...
anyway, she is safe,
and she is home--
uh, at the house.
So...
call me, Charlie.
It's the old number.
That drummer was amazing!
Unreal!
Shh! I think
Uncle B's probably asleep.
Whoa.
That tree is sick.
So big.
How old is it?
I don't know, but it's been
in the family for forever.
-Yo! Let's climb it.
-Race you to the top!
Guys.
No! Wait! Please!
Dude!
Whoa!
What is this?
No, please. Please.
It's private.
A private tree?
You hang rocks from a tree?
No, you don't understand.
Please just get out.
We're not gonna hurt it.
It's a tree.
It's not just "a tree."
-Steve, listen.
No, please. Please stop.
Gemma.
Look what you've done!
You don't even know!
You stomp in here,
out of nowhere,
and ruin everything!
Guys, I think
it's time to go home.
Sorry, we didn't mean to--
I'll handle it.
Just go.
Sorry.
Hey.
Let's go inside.
I'm sorry I lost it out there.
I just need sleep.
We'll talk in the morning.
Gemma?
Are you awake?
I made breakfast.
I can't.
I'm sick.
Should I call a doctor?
No.
I just need sleep.
I'll come back at lunch
and check on you.
Charlie didn't know
Gemma was here?
Doesn't look like it.
Which makes more sense,
rather than let her
take off on her own.
Yeah.
Did she stay in bed today?
Oh, yeah,
she doesn't want to talk.
She knows what's coming.
What is coming?
I gotta take her home.
At least now you're gonna
be able to see Charlie.
This is what
you always wanted, right?
-Ben, please.
Why can't you just tell me?
You ever do something
you were ashamed of,
but if you were in
the same place,
you'd do it all over again?
I'm not sure.
When our parents died,
there was life-insurance money.
It would've been split
between us,
and the lawyer told both of us,
so Charlie knew,
when he turned 18,
he'd get his share.
He wanted to travel,
he wanted to see the world,
like our parents.
He talked about it all the time
and it became his way out.
I was already 18,
so I took over the shop.
I didn't know
what I was doing,
but I needed
to keep us afloat,
so, I took
all the insurance money,
and I paid off the house,
and I paid off the shop.
I didn't even ask him.
I didn't even tell him
until the day he turned 18.
Oh...
We both said a lot of things
that we shouldn't have.
But the next day,
he took off,
and I haven't heard
from him since.
You were in
a desperate situation, Ben.
You were a kid yourself,
trying to take care of you both.
He thought I cheated him.
And maybe I did, you know?
I did what I wanted--
to keep everything the same,
no more surprises,
to keep Charlie here.
You don't like
to let go of what you love.
But you have to.
I do get that now.
To give them room...
to come back.
That's what I want, Emilia.
I'm ready to let go of anything.
Everything
that gets in the way.
I don't need
somebody else's idea of perfect.
I don't need that.
I need what's real.
And that's you.
What if I, um...
pick up some groceries,
come over,
cook some dinner,
and we can talk about
what that may look like.
What else do you need?
This.
You and me.
That's all.
Do you want me
to talk to Gemma?
And that. Yes.
Yeah, please.
I'll pick up some things
and come home.
I'll be there.
Ben.
Charlie.
Onyx.
Gives strength.
Old sorrows.
Letting go.
Where's my daughter?
She's in the house.
Why didn't you contact me?
I told you, I tried to.
I didn't know where you were.
Obviously,
Gemma didn't want me to know.
So you didn't think
it was strange that a teenager
would just take off
without talking to anyone?
She's your daughter, man.
I don't know.
Did you hear what you just said?
Do you want to play that back?
Hey! That's not the same, okay?
This is different.
She's only 16.
She just ran away.
Hey, man, she told me
she had permission.
I reached out to you--
Do you honestly think
I would let her
come anywhere near here?
I don't want anything
to do with you
or the Stone family "museum"
you're living in--
That's hilarious.
You named
your only daughter "Gemma".
That was for Mom and Dad,
not this.
Okay, I would never have--
-Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-...anything
they don't want to do.
I made sure
you had a home, Charlie.
A home that wouldn't blow away
with some storm, okay?
I didn't ask Gemma to come here,
but she likes it here.
She feels like she belongs.
Gemma has a home!
Oh, really?
Why'd she run away?
I don't know, okay?
Come on.
You must have some idea.
My wife's pregnant.
Twins.
Gemma's been
pretty quiet about it.
I knew she was upset,
I just didn't realize how much.
I'll just take her home.
And that's it?
See you in another 20 years?
Never?
I don't even
know you anymore.
And you know nothing about
what I had to do to survive,
let alone--
No. I'm not doing this with you.
-Okay?
-Mm-hmm.
-Where is she?
-She's in your old room.
Okay.
Gemma?
Gemma, come down here, please.
Charlie, wait.
She's gone.
What?
Yeah. And she took her phone.
I'll get my car.
She's on foot.
If she overheard us,
she can't have gone far.
We'll find her--
Hey, it's Gemma.
Leave a message.
Is that Charlie?
Yeah. Gemma ran away.
Gemma, it's Dad.
Where are you?
What happened?
We were arguing
and she heard us.
Ohh...
I'm not mad.
Please call me back.
No answer.
Hi. I'm Emilia.
I'm Ben's wife.
-Hi. Charlie.
-Hi.
Where could she be?
Where could she go?
Everywhere. She thinks
the whole place is an adventure.
Wait. No. She likes to hike
Green Falls Trail.
She loves the smell
of the trees and the ocean.
Okay. Let's go.
I'll put this here.
Gemma!
Gemma...
Gemma?
Gemma!
You hear that?
Yeah. This way.
-Gemma?
-I'm over here.
Oh... sweetie.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
What happened?
I heard you two yelling
and I had to get away,
but I fell off the path
and I got stuck.
Okay, okay. It's okay.
Uh, can you wiggle your toes?
-Yeah.
-Okay. That's good. That's good.
This is just gonna be
like that rockslide
on the West Mesa.
Remember that?
I'm gonna lose a boot?
But you get to keep your foot.
That's fair.
Okay, honey, listen,
look at me,
this is what
we're gonna do, okay?
On the count of three,
he's gonna lift,
and then I'm gonna pull
your leg out, okay?
Nice and easy, all right?
-Yeah.
-Okay. You ready?
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay. Let's go.
One...
two...
three!
Ow!
-Oh. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's not so bad.
-You hurt?
-Mm-hmm.
Okay, can you stand?
-Mm-hmm. Yeah.
-Yeah?
Okay, let's give it a go.
Nice and easy.
Ahh!
-Try not to stand on it.
-I got you.
Ow.
Okay, here we go.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Come here.
Don't scare me like that.
You're never in the way.
I don't fit anymore.
You're always gonna be
my little girl, okay?
Come here.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go. Let's go.
Nice and easy.
Look at them.
They look close.
It's a good thing.
Yeah.
Nice and easy.
Right this way.
I haven't heard.
Hey. You scared me.
I'm sorry.
So are you okay?
Yeah, I just need these
for a few days.
I booked a hotel,
so I'm gonna take Gemma
there tonight.
Grab her stuff tomorrow?
Yeah. I'll pack it up.
It looks like your old room's
gonna be an art studio again
real soon.
Mission accomplished!
Thank you.
For everything.
Hey, if you're up for it,
we're heading
to the block party.
Are you coming?
Oh, Dad, can we? Please?
I've been waiting all summer.
Just for a bit?
than the numbers
Gemma!
Hey! Come meet Jason!
Be right there!
Jason?
What happened to Tony?
Oh, that was
obviously doomed, Uncle B.
Hey, Charlie...
you don't have to rush off,
you know,
you could stay for awhile.
You could stay for lunch.
Look.
It doesn't matter
how Gemma feels about you,
"Uncle B."
It doesn't erase what happened.
I know it won't.
But it's lunch, Charlie.
It's a start.
Dad!
Come on.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Lunch.
Hey.
If she had to run,
I'm glad
she had somewhere to run to.
Dad, come on.
All right, I'm comin',
I'm comin', I'm comin'.
Ohh...
We should put that
in the living room,
then everyone can see it.
For now, this is for us.
Hey, I know
it's a few days early,
but, um...
happy anniversary.
Ben...
it's spectacular.
I love it.
There's 10 different stones.
One for each year?
Mm-hmm.
Rose quartz
for unconditional love,
forgiveness, trust...
where we started.
Aventurine--
harmony, prosperity.
And this year--
topaz.
Eternal romance.
You have a lot of those
on here.
I'm hopeful.
Me too.
Would you?
Mm-hmm.
Will you marry me again?
Today,
you have renewed
the promises and vows
you made to each other
on your wedding day.
So, it is with pleasure
that I conclude
the ceremony
that has joined you...
...and forever binds you
as husband and wife.
I totally called it.
They're made for each other.
Please celebrate this renewal
with a sign of affection
and ongoing love
for one another.
You may kiss!