Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Come on, everyone.
What did you steal?
-I got a sugar cube.
-I got a biscuit crumb.
-I got a toenail.
-Oops.
-Dad?
-Yes?
On the next sneak,
can we break into the house with the…
What's that?
Oh, it's a…
Inside! Now!
It's a… It's…
Funny-looking. Can we eat it?
No! It's a…
Well, it's a robin, I think.
Hi, Robin.
Can we keep her?
Well, maybe.
After all, she's only one little…
robin.
Wait.
Wait for it.
Okay, let's go slowly--
-Yes!
-Hey!
We're on our way to break into a house
Might be a bird
But I sneak just like a mouse
-So, what are you getting tonight?
-I might get a pie crumb?
-Something moldy, I think.
-Well, I'm gonna sneak a whole crust.
Well, I'm going to sneak
a whole sandwich. Yes.
-You can't sneak a whole sandwich.
-How do you sneak a sandwich?
Like this.
Race you to the fence!
That's in my eye!
Don't do that.
-Pip, you're up front.
-Yes, Dad.
-Dink, don't drag your tail.
-Okay.
-Flynn, Flin, no showing off.
-All right.
And, Robin…
Got it, Dad!
I didn't say anything.
Robin!
Robin?
The rules of the sneak are simple and thus
Follow them close
You could steal a crust
-Or a crumpet rind
-Or a pinch of pie
Or the grease from the tip
Of a soggy french fry
Crumbs and crusts and stale bread
Soggy flakes and bin dregs
Any old leftovers
We'll sneak home with us
First find a secret entrance
Keep your eyes open wide
-For a hole
-Or a crack
-Or a window with a gap
-Just enough to squeeze inside
Once we're in, we creep around
Tiptoe past without a sound
Keep to the shadows
Don't get heard
Whisper every single word
-What?
-Come on.
Last, the most important
Remember in the who-man place
They're choosy who's invited
So we must never leave a trace
Crumbs and crusts and stale bread
Soggy flakes and bin dregs
Any old leftovers
We'll sneak home with us
A whole sandwich!
When we're done, we disappear
Nobody knows that we were here
-With crumbs in our hands
-And warmth in our hearts
And the sludge from the tin
Of a moldy jam tart
-Don't make a sound
-Robin!
Don't leave a trace
Keep to the shadows
Take what we need
The rules of the sneak are these
Who-mans!
Robin!
Well, let's not go back there again.
They'll be setting out traps
or maybe even getting a kitten.
Kittens!
Don't listen to them.
-Nice one, Robin.
-What?
Well, the spoon, and the sandwich, and--
Pip, enough of that.
Come on. We've still got plenty to eat.
There's the bag of Earl Grey.
I'm sick of Earl Grey!
All right. Well, come on now. Off to bed.
It's okay, Robin.
We'll figure this out together.
Yeah. I mean, next time, I'll just…
Stay away from spoons. Yeah.
All that mold!
Sandwich…
"Hi, Robin. What's all this?"
"Crumbs? For the whole family?"
"Yeah. It was easy.
Just got them from a who-man house."
"Oh, wow, Robin!
You're the most amazing sneak ever!"
Can't wait to see the look on Pip's face
when I come back
with a crumb the size of his head.
No. No. No. No.
Oh, excuse me.
-Do you know where the--
-No.
Okay. Thanks anyway.
The who-man house.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize this was a…
cat house!
No. No.
Now, that's a yes!
Cat!
Oh dear.
Silly bird, fly!
What? Wait!
Why aren't you flying?
I can't fly.
-Well, I've got a broken wing!
-Oh no. How did that happen?
Magpie? Wait for me!
-Let's get you safe indoors, hey?
-Thanks. Is the cat still--
Poor little thing.
Oh, awful!
Out there all by yourself--
-Are we safe in here?
-Yes. We're safe.
The thorns keep unwanted visitors out.
Usually.
Oh, good.
Is this your house?
It's very…
Why, thank you. I suppose it is rather…
Perfect.
Well…
A who-man house.
Bet they've got loads of crumbs in there.
Them. Yes.
They've got loads of everything.
And all because of that
magic shiny wishing star, eh?
Yeah.
The magic shiny…
Wait. Sorry, what?
The star.
You don't…
Right!
Okay. It must be here somewhere.
Once a year, the who-mans
take the spikiest tree in the woods,
cover it in tin-soil and boo-bells,
until their tree
is all twinkling and beautiful.
Just like mine.
Then, they put a shiny magic star on top,
make a wish,
and in the morning,
they get anything they want.
Like crumbs.
Crumbs?
Don't be absurd.
Well, what could be better than crumbs?
"What could be better than…"
Things!
Things, they make you happy
Things won't fly away
Things will stick with you till the end
Oh yes, on things you can depend
See my bathtub? It's designer
Finest china! Well, kinda
Simply must have the latest bottle top
I love it so, I'll never stop
This chair? Hedgehog hair
Pamperclips? I've got the pair
This is a limited-edition piece of string
I was a bird who couldn't fly
Felt tiny while they flew up high
Surrounded myself with things so gorgeous
Felt enormous!
So afraid and alone
Things turn a hovel to a home
Got no personality?
I let my lampshade speak for me
Hollow inside? You're not enough?
Just stuff that hole with lovely stuff
Things are things that make you happy
Who needs friends? I've got a shoe chair
No one there for you to care for?
Polish up your silverware for?
There's no better company than one penny
Look, my point is,
wish for something far better than crumbs.
Right.
Better than crumbs?
Like a whole sandwich!
Never mind.
Okay, then.
I'll do it.
-Do what?
-I'll go get the star.
Impossible! It's inside the who-man house.
Maybe I forgot to mention?
I was raised by mice.
Explains the ears.
And if there's one thing
us mice are good at, it's sneaking.
Sorry, what?
Oh, like, into houses.
To get stuff. Like, stealing it.
Right.
Right!
Show me.
Okay. I'm in.
What are you doing?
You're supposed to wait outside.
-I thought that we were--
-Who-mans!
Okay.
We're going to have to be
the sneakiest mice we've ever been.
I'm not a mouse.
Just do exactly what I do.
What are you doing?
You'll wake the who-mans.
I'm being a sneaky mouse.
That's not sneaking.
The whole point of being a mouse
is that you don't draw attention
to yourself.
Careful.
Got it!
Who-mans!
Not bad for a couple
of flightless fools, eh?
Why is it you don't fly?
I just never learned.
I mean, mice don't fly.
Well, it's easy! You just flap!
No, thanks. I'll just…
All right!
Oh, you're a natural!
Oh dear.
The star!
Perfect.
Hello.
What's this?
An unexpected visitor.
Why…
it's the little bird
who sneaks about on the floor like a…
mouse?
And who are you trying to fool
with those…
funny things?
-My family are mice, so…
-Mice?
Oh, and the ears are…
Oh, I see.
So tragic. So sad.
Trying to fit in.
You know you'll never be a real mouse.
Oh, no, I…
You see,
you're a misfit.
You're an oddball.
You're a freak.
No, I'm not.
Micey ears atop a birdy beak
Well, yeah.
But I've never seen a bird
So peculiar, so absurd
How about we play a game
Of hide-and-seek, if you can?
As a mouse, to me
You seem to be just terrible
Fitting in is more
Than dress-up and pretend
If it's fitting in you're desperate for
Come down, search no more
I know the perfect place
For you, my friend
For you, I've the perfect place
Not picky, stick with me
What's in a name?
A robin or a mouse?
After all, under the skin
You're all the same
It's what's inside that counts
Fitting in could be a breeze
Just a squash and a squeeze
Brush out those ears
Come along with me
Quick as a glug
You could be sitting snug, perfectly
You don't fit in
But you'd fit into my belly
For you, I've the perfect place
You really are a terrible mouse
with nowhere left to sneak.
Robin! And the star!
And the…
This is bad.
Get back!
Oops.
That's made it worse.
We did it! Everlasting happiness awaits!
Told you us mice are good at sneaking.
Sneaking?
You know, I think we make very bad mice.
Yes. Quite terrible.
But who cares? We got the star!
Terrible?
I'm not a terrible mouse.
Am I?
This goes here.
There we go.
Isn't this wonderful?
Suppose so.
Well, I hope you thought
of something better to wish for
than a soggy old sandwich.
You know, like a hubcap.
Or a shiny fork. Or a pincil sharpener.
Or a thimble. Or how about a safety pin…
Yeah.
Well, I wish I wasn't a bird.
I wish I was a mouse.
A real one.
Magpie?
Robin?
It…
It didn't work, did it?
No.
Come now.
It was always a bit of a long shot, eh?
Stars and wishes.
A fool's dream
was what it was.
A mad…
fool's…
dream!
It works! Robin! The star!
It works!
A real one.
What's that? For me?
A lovely, shiny…
Wonderful!
What the…
-Robin!
Robin!
Dad?
We've been looking everywhere for you!
-Robin?
-Sorry, I…
I went to sneak us some crumbs, but…
it all went wrong.
Because, well,
I think I'm a…
terrible mouse.
Robin…
I couldn't have said it better myself.
In!
A kitten.
It's all right.
Don't worry.
There's no way she could fit through the…
door!
Oh, look.
It's the whole family.
What are you doing?
-Robin!
-What is she doing?
She's being a terrible mouse.
The rules of the sneak are these
And that!
And this! And that!
You really are
a terrible,
terrible, terrible mouse…
with nowhere left to sneak.
Wait.
I don't need to sneak.
I'm a bir…
d.
Robin!
-Robin!
-Dad!
Robin!
That was the most un-sneaky…
-And stupid…
-And brilliant…
Birdy-mousy thing we've ever seen!
Robin, you were marvelous.
Thanks, Dad.
Robin, you're not a mouse.
But, of course, you're a mouse.
-Sorry, is that confusing?
-Yeah, what? She's a bird.
Exactly. She is a bird,
and that's wonderful.
And what I mean is,
we're the mouse family. All of us.
-Is the cat one of the family?
-No, Dink. The cat tried to eat us.
-Because she loves us?
-No. Because she's a predator.
-So, you fly now?
-Well, yeah. I guess so.
But we're all still hungry,
and you've ruined Magpie's house.
That's okay. They're only things.
Yeah, and I'm bad at sneaking.
If anything,
I just draw attention to myself.
Hey! Over here!
A song for your ear
While we keep to the shadows
Don't get heard
Whisper every single word
Look at me fly
Catching your eye
-With crumbs in our arms
-And a raisin or two
And a coin from the middle
Of this sticky brown poo
Look at me
And you won't see my sneaky family
-Don't make a sound
-Do make a sound
-Don't leave a trace
-Do leave a trace
-Keep to the shadows
-And to the light
-Take what we need
-This is more than we need.
-Magpie!
-Thank you!
The rules of the sneak are these
Sorry!
Well.
It's a sandwich!