♪ Feel like
I've been hypnotized ♪
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
♪ When I look into your eyes ♪
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
♪ I get feelings ♪
♪ Crazy feelings deep inside ♪
Fred:
Well, here we are --
Warner Bros. Studios,
home of Hanna-Barbera.
Daphne: They've shot so many
great reunion specials here.
Now we get to have
our own reunion special.
Velma:
But how is it a reunion
if we haven't spent a day apart
in 52 years?
♪ I feel magic in the air ♪
♪ I feel magic everywhere ♪
♪ I feel magic,
crazy magic in the air ♪
♪♪
[ Sniffs ] Here we are.
Our soundstage
where it all began.
Stage 12.
Where we've been filming
ever since
our original series --
"Scooby Doo Where Are You!"
premiered on Saturday mornings
in 1969.
Dude! I used to love
watching that show.
Well, let's go inside.
Time to make the doughnuts.
Doughnuts!
Doughnuts?
♪♪
Shaggy: Oh-ho-ho.
Ohh.
Daphne:
It hasn't changed a bit.
Wow. So many memories,
so much history.
I wonder if that sandwich I was
in the middle of eating
is still here.
[ Slurp! ]
Not anymore.
[ Giggles ]
Hey, Velma, remember
when we shot the scene
where you lost
your glasses?
It was right over there.
And then that other scene
when you lost them again
over there
and over there?
[ Bonk! ]
Hey, my glasses.
I can't see without them.
[ Crash! ]
My glasses.
I lost them.
[ Roar! ]
[ Crash! ]
Oh, there you are, Shaggy.
Okay, I get it.
Velma's thing is she's always
losing her glasses.
I only wear them
because they make me look cool.
Welcome, Mystery Gang.
[ Gasps ]
A g-g-ghost!
Not quite. A host.
Although you're not too far off.
There are rumors
that this studio is haunted.
Geez. Does everywhere we go
have to be haunted?
You can relax, Shaggy.
I can assure you
it's just me,
Janel Parrish,
a real human being.
So the five of you --
Daphne, Fred, Velma,
Shaggy, and Scooby --
have been playing characters
who solve mysteries
for 52 years.
Um, yeah, we know.
We lived it.
So have any of you
ever experienced
a ghost in real life?
Whenever I try to get my agent
on the phone. Ha!
[ Laughter ]
[ Laughter continues ]
-Crack up.
-We have fun.
"Scooby" has persisted
because the characters
are really, really good,
and it's a wonderful formula.
Silverman: It's iconic.
It's been on the air
almost continuously since 1969
in one way or the other.
It has that alchemy
that works for people.
Green: The idea of a troupe
of sophisticated,
intelligent,
best-friend teenagers
is something that has
been pioneered
so flawlessly in "Scooby-Doo"
and then reflected through pop
culture for every year since.
The characters
really are archetypes,
you know, like Fred
is the muscle
and Daphne is the heart
and Velma is the brain
and -- and Scooby and Shaggy
are the stomach.
I think that's part
of their appeal
is that they're just sort of --
they're sort of universal.
A kid can enjoy that right now
like a kid could 50 years ago.
Every generation can find
something in them
to remind them of themselves.
So there is
a lot of excitement
in store
for you guys today.
Later on,
you'll each be competing
in a mixed-martial arts
tournament
with some of the world's
top fighters.
Plus, Scooby,
you'll be meeting the litter
that you never knew
you had.
Huh?
But first,
let's take a look back
at some of our favorite moments
from your very first adventures
in "Scooby Doo Where are you!"
♪♪
Even in the beginning,
everything that made you you
was there --
the heart, the bravery,
the teamwork.
You lifted each other up...
literally.
[ Chains jingling ]
When one of you lost yourself,
the rest of the gang
would find you...
again, literally.
[ Thunk! ]
[ Thud! ]
[ Patter! ]
No matter how haunted the house,
you could always rely
on each other,
your resourcefulness,
your teeth.
♪♪
It wasn't always easy,
but you had each other...
and nerves of steel
and also the van.
Show 'em, Scooby.
You soared to new heights
and inspired generations
of ghost hunters.
Yay!
Yay, Scooby!
No one will ever forget the name
Scooby-Doo.
[ Sighs ]
Wow, such powerful memories.
Third time I've called him
this week.
Why am I paying him 10%
if he can't even call me ba--
Shoot, I got to go.
[ Thunder crashing ]
[ Evil laughter ]
♪♪
Oh, wh-- wh-- what was that?
I don't know.
It's not part
of the reunion special.
It must be...
a mystery.
Hey, Scooby Gang.
It's us -- Marvin and Wendy
from the Super Friends.
We hang around
with some people
with pretty cool powers --
Wonder Woman,
Aquaman, Superman.
But you have
a superpower, too --
your friendship.
Plus,
you also have a van.
And what appears to be
an unlimited source of money.
And a talking dog.
But really,
your friendship.
Yeah, they should call you
the Super Friends.
But you can't
or the Super Friends
will drag you to court.
So we had arrived
that four teenagers
were gonna be involved
in mysteries.
And we threw in a dog
to kind of help it along
and give it touches of humor.
That was Scooby-Doo.
What happens, of course, is that
you went into the mysteries
and Scooby began
to steal the show.
[ Giggling ]
[ Growling ]
Also he had a way of talking
that our great talent
Don Messick did.
Welker: I would watch his face
and those jaws would go,
and I try to do the same thing
to emulate Don
as close as I can.
[ Imitating Scooby-Doo ]
[ Whimpering ]
Ruh-roh.
One of Joe Barbera's maxims was,
"If you ain't got a big, sloppy
dog, you ain't got comedy."
[ Laughing ]
[ Munch! Munch! ]
Scooby-Doo-o-o-o.
Bryn! Bryn, that thing
happened again.
Oh, sorry
about that, folks.
We've been having electrical
problems all over the studio.
This is Bryn, our producer.
Actually, I produce all
the reunion specials here.
Next week we're filming
the "Friends Reunion" reunion.
The fans really miss
those characters
from the original
"Friends Reunion."
Excuse me. If that was just
an electrical problem,
how do you explain
the scary, classic
"Scooby Doo"
villain laughter?
Great question, Velma,
but we're here to have fun.
Hey, did you know
that when Hanna and Barbera
and Joe Ruby and Ken Spears
first came up with the idea
for your show,
you were all gonna be
in a traveling rock band?
Shaggy: We could have had a song
in America's Top 40.
The hits from coast to coast,
hosted by Casey Kasem.
And Scooby started off
as a very different
kind of dog.
Scooby: Yikes!
There was
a brilliant illustrator
who worked for Hanna-Barbera
named Iwao Takamoto.
He turned Scooby
into a Great Dane
and developed
the way you all look.
Velma: Too bad he didn't develop
a turtleneck
that doesn't give me
a neck rash.
But the network
wasn't interested....yet.
Iwao put it all together
in this one drawing
and the concept
came to life.
The head of the network,
Fred Silverman,
was presented this image,
and he said yes
on the spot.
Daphne: We look so young.
Fred: Wow.
I can't believe
I used to wear
that weird ascot.
Was that ever
in style?
Beck: Hanna-Barbera had access
to some of the best talent.
They knew their animators,
their background painters,
the writers to help create
these characters.
They were practically supporting
the animation industry
on their backs.
When you have
a really great design,
that will help you have
a great longevity
with, you know,
with great characters
and all the characters
have very strong silhouettes.
Daphne is always like...
That's a very essential part
in the animation
is that their silhouettes
are completely recognizable.
Scooby-Doo is a Great Dane,
but the way Iwao designed him,
he's not a champion Great Dane.
Iwao actually went
and got a book on dog breeds
and read what a Great Dane
should look like,
and then he broke every rule.
Scooby has got a belly
that hangs down
and a back that sags
and a bump in his nose
and his ears are always crooked
and pointing
in two different directions,
and his eyes
could be different sizes.
And all of those things
are done on purpose
because it makes
Scooby charming,
and it makes Scooby relatable.
Like, what he lacks
in physical perfection,
he makes up for in personality.
Then came the casting.
Do you all remember
when you came in
to audition?
Well, in case you don't,
we dug up
your original audition reels,
and let's just say
you hadn't quite nailed
the characters just yet.
Ohh.
Yikes.
Well.
I'm Fred Jones,
and I'll be reading
for the part of Fred Jones.
Huh. What a coincidence.
Oh, Scooby, would you do it
for a Scooby snack?
[ Giggling ]
Uh, excuse me.
How do you pronounce...
"zo-inks"?
My name's Jabberjaw.
And today I'll be reading
to be Shaggy.
[ Clearing throat ]
I can already taste those
chocolate-covered hot dogs.
Let's see who this ghost
really is, dumb-dumb.
Guys, we have to check out
that abandoned carnival.
[ Laughter ]
That's terrible.
Oh, boy.
Then the real work began,
right, Bryn?
Huh?
I wonder where...
Anyway,
you all got straight to work,
preparing for your roles,
and for Scooby, that meant
working with a vocal coach.
Before he got that, uh, TV show,
he was classically trained,
doing Shakespeare everywhere,
all around the country.
And ironically, his first role
in the theater
was with another Great Dane --
Hamlet --
in which he played Hamlet's dog.
He got rave reviews
in "Julius Caesar,"
which he played the Dogs of War.
And he was understudying
Marlon Brando in "King Lear."
Scooby-Doo had to go on for him
and just knocked it
out of the park,
which, of course,
caught the eyes
of middle-aged Bill Hanna
and an equally middle-aged
Joe Barbera.
Alright.
Okay, let's try it.
Um...Okay.
5, 6, 7, 8.
Yikes.
Let's get out of here.
No, no, no.
Yi-ikes!
"Ret's" get out of here.
The problem was that
Scooby's diction was too good.
They were concerned
that the audience wasn't
gonna believe him as a dog,
and that's where I come in.
Yi-ikes!
See, my job was to help him
unlearn just enough English
that he could legitimately pass
for a Great Dane.
Look at me.
Look at me. Yi-ikes.
Yikes.
Let's get...
Yi-ikes.
Had to drill it line by line,
day by day.
Taking it very slowly
until he got it just right.
Yikes, yikes,
yikes, yikes.
We really found the essence
of this character.
Scooby Dooby-Doo.
Yes, Scooby-Dooby-Doo
indeed.
But I'd like to get serious
for a moment
and talk about...
Scrappy-Do.
-Ay yi yi.
-Really?
-Oh, boy.
-Yeah.
More like Scrappy-Don't.
You know, Scrappy wasn't
really part of the gang.
Yeah.
He started saying
these horrible things about
Scooby in these AOL chat rooms.
[ Thunder crashing ]
[ Evil laughter ]
♪♪
[ Clicking ]
What is that sound?
Is someone playing
the castanets?
[ Clicking ]
Hey, Scoob, I think
it's a good time for us
to have a reunion
with the exit.
Yeah.
Exit stage "reft."
Whoa, whoa, watch it.
Snagglepuss
is extremely litigious.
What's going on, Bryn?
Alright.
It's time I came clean.
This isn't
a normal reunion.
I'll say.
I used the TV special
as an excuse
to bring you all together here
because I need your help.
The ghost has been
running around all week,
scaring away
all of our productions.
Even the hit CW show
"All American"
wants to move their shoot
to Canada
and change the title
to "All Canadian."
Sounds like a mystery.
No way, man. We're not
getting mixed up in this.
Like, you guys,
let's get out of here.
Yeah, we only pretend
to be ghost hunters on TV.
I figured after 14 series,
a bunch
of straight-to-DVD movies
and the live-action films,
you'd be experts by now.
Look, the ghost
is just gonna
be a disgruntled employee
in a mask.
Probably even
one of you.
Unh-unh.
I saw it up close.
It was the Snow Ghost
from season one
of "Scooby Doo
Where are you!"
And it was totally real,
because I remember
that episode vividly.
[ Growling softly ]
[ Boing! ]
[ Roar! ]
Zoiks!
The Snow Ghost!
♪♪
[ Thud! Thud! ]
So we have
a copycat haunter.
Why would someone dress up
in a costume from our show?
It's not a costume.
It's real.
There have been sightings
of it all week.
Um, it looked a lot like
a Halloween costume.
Okay, Velma,
then it's a ghost
who's wearing
a Halloween costume.
Like, man, I don't know
what scares me more --
a real ghost or someone
who will wear a latex
costume for no reason
in 100-degree heat.
I'd take
the Snow Ghost.
Oh, my God, look!
♪♪
Someone ransacked
the snack table.
There's nothing left
to eat.
Not even Scooby snacks.
Like, I was thinking,
let's find this dude
and teach him some manners!
-Then you'll help?
-Yeah, sure. Whatever.
Anything to get out
of meeting Scooby's family.
Okay, everybody split up
and look for clues.
Ha. I've always wanted
to say that in real life.
Let's go catch this "ghost."
[ Bats squeaking ]
Good work, Scooby gang
Cleansing the world
of the scum that haunts
America's swamps,
abandoned carnivals,
and manor houses.
I know my good friend
Bruce Wayne appreciates it, too,
and you did it all without
the help of an elderly butler.
Thanks to you,
the only real monsters in Gotham
City are my personal demons.
You're an inspiration to us all.
From me to you, mazel tov.
[ Screaming ]
Hang on.
Be right with you.
Yankovic: Getting a chance
to hang out
with Scooby-Doo and the gang
was a million times better
than one of those Kennedy Center
Honor things.
It's just, you know, it's --
it's the top of the mountain.
It's as high as you can go
in the biz,
and those guys are really great.
Oh, Velma, she likes
to have fun, you know?
Well, well, they all did.
Um...
Sometimes a bit too much fun,
but I'll always treasure
the time
I spent with those crazy,
meddlesome kids.
Hi, I'm Olivia Liang.
And before I became the star
of the new "Kung Fu,"
I paid the bills
as a martial-arts instructor.
One of my favorite clients
was Norville "Shaggy" Rogers.
All his action scenes
in the show,
they may look clumsy and sloppy,
but they're actually extensively
choreographed and rehearsed.
He makes it look easy.
The training is grueling.
499, 500.
[ Panting ]
That's how Shaggy
is able to eat and eat
and still maintain
his slim figure.
You know, he may not look
like it with the slouching,
but Shaggy
is the fittest character
in animated television.
[ Boing! ]
[ Crash! ]
[ Clanging ]
The running alone.
[ Patter! ]
The guy runs
6 or 7 miles per episode,
and that's before his feet
even hit the ground.
Not to mention Scooby --
jumping into Shaggy's arms
at the drop of a hat.
Do you know how much
a Great Dane weighs?
No? I-I don't, either.
But I can look it up and...
♪♪
Hi, Carter.
Velma Dinkley.
What brings you
to the costume department?
The gang and I are here
solving a mystery.
It's about
the Snow Ghost
that's been
haunting the lot.
Know anything about it?
Oh, yeah, I've seen it
around everywhere.
Everyone is experiencing
post-haunting trauma.
We've even formed
an ad hoc support group
that meets on Thursdays.
I mean,
the coffee's not great,
but Alex does bring doughnuts
from that place on La Brea.
I'm a bagel person myself,
but good luck finding
a decent bagel in L.A.
Hah!
Yeah, well,
while I have you,
we haven't had a change
of clothes since 1969.
This sweater reeks.
Well, funny
you should say that.
Look, it's the costumes
for your next movie.
Wow,
these are so modern.
It's been over 50 years.
Your style
has to keep evolving.
Every incarnation
of Mystery Ink
has its own completely
different set of costumes.
Except for Scooby.
He's always naked.
Scooby is a nudist.
He was created in 1969.
Also, each of you have
your own distinct walk.
As a group,
even the silhouette,
the viewer can tell
who you are immediately,
and that's by design.
Is my haircut
by design, too?
I'd be happy
to give you a makeover.
You know
that's my kind of thing.
I'm sorry I couldn't
help you find any clues.
But a little more
than a week ago,
one of my costumes
went missing.
And where
the costume was hanging,
I found this.
Huh.
A matchbook.
And it says Bungalow 15.
Whoever made this
went to a lot of trouble.
Actually,
I think you found a clue.
At least
I think it's a clue.
Jinkies!
What?
Oh, uh, jinkies?
Well, it's kind of my thing.
It's what I say.
What does it mean?
Uh...
Okay, I'm gonna take off.
♪♪
Establishing a character's
personality by their walk
was a good way to infuse
personality into characters,
you know, when you have
a very tight budget
and they would animate
that fully.
Their movement is as iconic
as their characters.
Shaggy had a really cool
walk cycle.
Cervone: Swinging arms
and the way his feet flop
up and down as he walks.
That says a lot
about who Shaggy is.
Fred walks with his shoulders
back and his chin forward.
That's not a mistake.
Everything about how they move
says something
about who they are.
♪♪
That area is Stars Hollow
from the "Gilmore Girls."
You want
a mystery to solve,
it's a mystery to me
how a mother and daughter
can be
such good friends.
Hey, this ghost, you think
it could be that producer?
You know you can't trust
TV producers.
Captain Cavema-a-a-a-n!
Daphne Bla-a-a-ke!
We still on for Saturday?
You bet.
And thanks for the flowers.
Captain Caveman?
Really?
I like 'em hairy.
What's he even captain
of anyway?
Hey, look at that.
Huh.
Some sort of loudspeaker.
Wonder what that
could be doing here.
Probably a basic piece
of equipment
they use to make movies.
Or it could be
another clue.
Everything's a clue with you,
isn't it, Freddy?
So exhausting.
♪♪
They had very
distinctive villains.
They had a lot of them, and they
had an incredible imagination
in terms of the supernatural
designs they would come up with.
I mean, really inventive.
You know, I like the creeper.
I like the pirate.
But there's been so many
over the years.
[ Evil laughter ]
Watson: I think all kids
like to be scared,
and I think there's a way
of being scared with Scooby-Doo
where it's not like --
you're not gonna then
go in your bedroom,
just be terrified
to shut the lights off.
"Scooby" was my first show,
so I really didn't have
a lot of experience
and I wanted to do
some of these other voices.
I mean, it was fun doing Fred,
but, you know, gosh,
I-I see this monster.
And Joe Barbera,
he would go around the table
and ask the experienced actors,
and then he would never
get as far as me
because I was
just, like, this kid.
So I kept raising my hand
and raising my hand
and finally, Joe goes,
"Alright. Go ahead, Frank,
give it a try."
And I went...[growling]
"Alright, you're the monster."
Shh.
Shh. Huh?
[ Snarls ]
[ Patter! Boing! ]
♪♪
Hey, Scooby Gang,
could you use another member?
I've got to get away from my dad
and his bodyguard, Race Bannon.
They never let me out of
their sight. I'll do anything.
I'll wash the van,
I'll brush Scooby's fur.
My dad's gonna get me killed.
I just want to be a regular kid.
Shoot. Someone's coming.
Got to go.
Help me.
I got cast to play the sixth
member of Mystery Inc. --
Lazlo the Mechanic.
Yeah.
Whenever the van would
break down in some sketchy area,
my shtick was I had to fix it.
[ Clunking ]
Looks like we got
a busted radiator belt.
Sorry, can't fix it
till tomorrow.
I guess we'll have to stay
in that weird, old motel.
What did I tell you, Fred?
You got to stop
riding the clutch!
So I go to the big world
premiere of the show.
We get to my big scene...
and I ain't in it.
Yeah. See, turns out that they
cut me out of the episode.
In fact, they cut me
out of the entire series.
So I gave up acting and I got
a job as roadkill collector
and never looked back.
Best thing that ever happened
to me, I'll tell you that.
Scoob, we have had
some beautiful sandwiches
over the years.
Yeah, we should have,
"Raggy."
♪♪
Scooby and Shaggy,
most of the time,
are just comic relief
in their own show.
[ Gulp! ]
They just want to hang around
with each other.
They just want to eat.
They certainly don't want to go
into a haunted house
and solve a mystery.
Beck: They take the edge off
of what's scary.
If it's a ghost
or a perceived monster,
you know, having Scooby
and Shaggy around
and, you know,
struggling over snacks
or this or that makes us
feel more comfortable.
Welker: No matter what Scooby
eats, Shaggy eats.
No matter what Shaggy eats,
Scooby Eats.
But their story
is a story of friendship
and how friends
support each other
and how friends always
have each other's back.
That story of friendship never
gets boring and never gets old.
You mean thank Scooby
we're safe.
[ Slurp! ]
Man, does it
ever bother you
that we've been typecast
as cowards?
That's, like, some kind
of writer joke, isn't it?
I'm not even scared
of the Snow Ghost copycat.
Fred seems pretty sure
that it's the producer
trying to scare everyone.
Probably just to make the show
more exciting, you know?
And I trust Fred's gut.
Speaking of gut,
let's finally eat
these sandwiches, shall we?
Yes.
[ Roar! ]
Hey, Scoob. Keep it down
back there, would you?
Shh!
Keep it down back there.
Shh.
[ Growling ]
[ Screams ]
♪♪
Props department!
We can lose him in there!
[ Patter! ]
[ Owl screeches,
animals growling ]
[ Laughs evilly ]
Quick, find somewhere
hilarious to hide.
♪♪
[ Stammering ]
This way!
This way?!
♪♪
Watch out!
He's gaining on us!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
♪ Scooby ♪
♪♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Ghosts and goblins
better run for cover ♪
♪ Ain't a chance that
you could get away ♪
♪ Do do do do ♪
♪ Scooby and his friends
are gonna get ya ♪
♪ Do do do do do ♪
♪ It feels alright
and it feels okay, hey! ♪
♪ Scooby ♪
♪ Come on, Scooby ♪
♪♪
♪ Scooby ♪
♪ Come on, Scooby ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Ho! ♪
♪ Hey, hey, ho, ho ♪
This way!
♪♪
Grape Ape. Grape Ape.
Scooby. Scooby-Doo.
[ Gasping ]
Grape Ape. Grape Ape.
Yeah, Grape Ape.
My name is Arlo Davidsonman,
and I have the best job
in Hollywood.
In the early seasons,
Scooby would eat every Scooby
snack in the scene.
But most Scooby snacks
are very high in calories.
They're filled the palm oils.
By the end of season one,
Scooby had probably
put on 30 pounds.
And in this town,
sadly, that's code red.
And...that's where I come in.
I am Scooby's
personal spit-bucket handler.
Coming out of USC Film School,
everybody wanted this job.
Sometimes I take the bucket home
just to practice.
I always want to be at my best.
You know what I mean?
I want Scooby to not even have
to think about it.
Spit, boom, the bucket's there.
Half the time, I don't even
think he knows I exist.
I work at my craft...
Aah!
...every second, every day,
every chance I get.
I don't quit.
And I think it shows
in the product.
Scooby is a lean, mean,
hilarious machine.
Scooby's not just a Great Dane.
He's -- he's a great dog.
Oh, man.
Are we glad to see you guys.
What happened
to you two?
Eehh! [ Coughing ]
[ Speaking gibberish ]
Fred: Let me guess.
You were exercising
on a Stairmaster.
Your legs have cramped up.
You're being attacked
by invisible bees.
You're trying to reach
something off the shelf
in the grocery store.
Zumba?
You're Elvis Presley.
♪ Put your hands in the air
like you just don't care ♪
You're at a baseball game
and you're doing the wave.
You were there,
Shaggy.
Why are you guessing?
Ohh! The Snow Ghost.
He chased into
the props department.
Ugh. While you guys
were messing around,
I found a clue --
a matchbook
that says Bungalow 15.
Okay.
Let's split up and canvass
all the matchbook factories
in Los Angeles.
Or -- and this is just me
spitballing --
we could check out
Bungalow 15.
We could walk there
in 30 seconds.
Like, have you guys
even watched this show?
We catch some dude
and we go home.
We don't have to run around town
and investigate.
Great idea, Shaggy.
We'll set up a very complicated
and elaborate trap
at the iconic
Warner Bros. water tower
and lure him to it.
Shaggy, Scooby, we're gonna
need to use you as bait.
[ Sighs ]
I'll get the paperwork.
Thank you, Scooby gang.
You've shown us
that we never have to be
afraid of monsters.
We only have to be afraid
of the psychos
who dress up as monsters.
Shaggy:
Breaker, breaker, Fred.
This is Shaggy
and Scooby
on the walkie-talkie.
We've been waiting here
for three hours, man.
What makes you think
the Snow Ghost is gonna show?
Just a feeling.
I have a feeling, too.
I'm feeling hot and sweaty
from being in this Banana
Splits costume all day!
We have to get the suits
to wardrobe later,
so don't sweat too much
and don't pee in them either.
Scooby: Ruh-roh.
Where's my plan --
When the ghost shows up,
he'll see Scooby and Shaggy
dressed as two
of the Banana Splits.
If you've ever watched
their old shows,
then you know anyone
who lays eyes on them
can't help but chase them.
Shaggy and Scooby will lead them
under the water tower
and right into our trap.
Man, Fred.
You've had some pretty
amazing traps over the years.
Let's sit here
and think about them
while we wait
for the Snow Ghost to show up.
♪♪
We're ready down here.
Welker: Fred always has
these great contraptions.
But if the traps always work,
the mysteries
would be over too fast.
[ Spring! ]
[ Fishing rod clicking ]
[ Whee! ]
♪♪
I think when Fred
takes himself seriously,
that's kind of funny.
♪♪
Watson: When we first wrote
"Mystery Incorporated,"
we just gave Fred
his own obsession with traps.
So we thought, "Well,
let's just make it
a weird, like, obsession."
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
You know, it's an actual,
like, psychological obsession
with him.
We grounded it in the fact
that he'd lost his mother.
So anything that he cared about,
he was trying to trap
because he couldn't trap
his mother.
[ Roars ]
[ Evil laughter ]
Shaggy: Dude,
that must be him.
Come and get us!
[ Growls ]
♪ Tra la la, la la la la ♪
This way!
He's gaining on us!
♪ One banana, two banana,
three banana, four ♪
♪ Four bananas make a bunch
and so do many more ♪
♪ Over hill and highway
the banana buggies go ♪
♪ Makin' up a mess of fun ♪
♪ Lots of fun for everyone ♪
♪ Tra la la, la la la la ♪
This way.
Hello!
Hold it right there!
Now!
♪♪
[ Growling ]
We got him.
We got him, gang.
Now let's see who
this Snow Ghost really is.
Not quite yet.
First, let's get
everyone else together
so they can enjoy
the unmasking with us.
I'm really hot
in here, Fred.
I said wait.
♪♪
There's a certain format
to the show --
mystery and then unmasking
at the end.
It's that way
every single episode,
regardless of whose version
is up on the air.
The villains are gonna be
unmasked. They're not real.
I think kids
find that very reassuring.
I almost always get fooled.
You know, until we get
to the third act,
then I start
figuring things out.
But, yeah, I got to admit,
sometimes I'm not sure
who I'm taking the hat...
Yeah. Yeah, I've been fooled.
Daphne:
And now let's take a look
at some of our most memorable
unmasking from over the years.
♪♪
Yo, Fred, you ever get tired
of driving around
in that rusty old van,
you should trade out
the Mystery Machine
for a zippy
little speed buggy -- me.
Let the wind blow
through your hair
as you drive through the fog.
Can the Mystery Machine talk?
No, but I can.
In fact,
I'm talking to you right now.
This is Speed Buggy
peeling out.
Eat my spawn, suckers!
Okay, let's have a look
and find out who this really is.
But I have a feeling
it's our producer.
Fred, I'm right here.
Whatever.
-[ Gasps ]
-Jinkies!
Oh, my God.
I'm just kidding.
I have no idea
who you are.
It's someone that none of us
have ever seen before,
and now,
that's a true surprise.
Wait, I think I remember you
from season one.
Weren't you an extra
or something?
I was the mechanic.
My character's name was Lazlo.
Uh...
I played a major role.
Oh, right.
The test audiences hated you,
and you got cut out
of the show.
Yeah, that's right.
And you all went on
to become big stars
and you just left me behind
in the dirt.
Like -- like -- like some
kind of roadkill.
Well, I was finally
gonna get my revenge.
How exactly
was this getting revenge?
You know, by scaring you.
You've been planning this
for 52 years,
and that's all you had?
Well, if you're really
interested --
We're not, but..
You see, I've been creeping
around all week
haunting all the TV shows
and movies on the lot.
One by one, I was gonna scare
them all
into taking their business
away from Warner Bros.
Then the studio would go broke,
and they'd have to stop
making your TV show.
It was a foolproof plan.
Or so I thought.
At first everything
was working like gangbusters.
I mean, some people were super
easy to frighten.
Real suckers.
You know the type.
Others, not so much.
But I was all over the place.
Everywhere people went,
they were like,
"Hey, there's the Snow Ghost.
Aah!"
The problem is I became
so commonplace
that everyone got used to me.
Pretty soon, I was just
part of the scenery,
you know, like the iconic
"Friends" fountain.
Then I heard about your TV show
and I thought,
"This is my chance.
I may not be able to get
your TV show canceled,
but I sure as hell can ruin
your precious reunion show."
And that's exactly what I did.
Are you kidding?
This was the best thing
that could have happened to it.
All I had planned
was a lame blooper reel,
a Q&A with Conan O'Brien
and a surprise visit
from the actors
who do your voices.
Wait.
These aren't our voices?
Thanks to you,
I didn't have to produce
any of that stuff.
We didn't even need to do
an awkward trivia game
or fill the time
with clips and interviews.
Too bad. I was really
looking forward
to meeting Scooby's
illegitimate children.
Hold on.
How did she make it seem
like her voice was coming
from all around us?
With that loudspeaker
I found.
I told you
that was a clue.
Yeah, and I would have
gotten away with it, too,
if it weren't for you --
Wait, but how
did she make herself
appear and disappear
into thin air?
Huh. I think I can answer
that one --
movie magic.
-Ahh.
-That makes perfect sense.
Yeah, I would have gotten away
with it, too, if it weren't --
There's one thing
I don't understand.
What was the deal with all
those Bungalow 15 clues?
Bungalow 15
is the name
of a new
Warner Bros. movie.
They were giving away all
sorts of promotional swag --
hats, matchbooks.
Security, take her away.
I now pronounce
this mystery completely solved.
Well, I would have
gotten away with it, too,
if it weren't for you
meddling kids! I got it.
Goodbye, dumb-dumb.
Scooby-Dooby-Doo!
And no reunion special
would be complete
without a dance party.
[ All cheering ]
Alright!
Hit it,
Deejay Teen Titan.
[ Record scratches ]
♪ What's new, Scooby-Doo? ♪
♪ We're coming after you ♪
♪ We're gonna solve
that mystery ♪
♪ I see you, Scooby-Doo ♪
♪ The trail leads back to you ♪
♪ What's new, Scooby-Doo? ♪
♪♪
My name is Kate Micucci,
and I play Velma.
I've been playing her since
2014, and let me tell you,
it's a total -- total dream job.
When I get to be in the booth
and I just close my eyes
and I hear these characters
that I have known and loved
since I was a kid,
I can't believe that I get
to be a part of it.
♪ ...clue ♪
♪ The Scooby snacks will be
waiting here for you ♪
Hi, it's me, Matt Lillard.
It has been my absolute joy
to play Shaggy
for the last 19 years.
I love what he means
to generation
after generation of kids.
And one last thing --
Zoinks!
♪ Na-na na-na na ♪
♪ Na-na na na na-na-na ♪
I'm Grey Griffin.
I play Daphne Blake.
How I get into Daphne
is I do her catchphrase,
which is, "Jeepers.
It's a creepy mystery, Scoob."
And that would get me
right into it.
Well, really,
I just kind of make my voice
a little bit more nasally
and it sort of sits
a little bit deeper.
But for the most part,
it's kind of just me.
I found my glasses.
I can see with my glasses.
There is times when I have to
definitely talk to myself,
but, you know, it really isn't
that hard.
It's just like,
[ As Fred ] Hey, Scoob, would
you do it for a Scooby snack?
[ As Scooby ]
I don't think so.
[ As Fred ] Why not?
[ As Scooby ] Well,
I need three, maybe four.
♪ Scooby snacks will be waiting
here for you ♪
Scooby-Dooby...
Doo!
♪ ...that mystery ♪
♪ I see you, Scooby-Doo ♪
♪ The trail leads back to you ♪
♪ What's new, Scooby-Doo? ♪
♪ Na-na na-na na ♪
♪ Na-na na na na-na-na ♪
♪ What's new, Scooby-Doo? ♪