Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
♪♪♪
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
[SIGHS]
♪♪♪
What is that?
Mr. Lee.
[LAUGHS]
♪♪♪
Mr. Lee?
Christmas isn't for another
two and a half weeks.
♪♪♪
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
Amber.
[AMBER] I wanted to wish my
bestie insane amounts of luck
on her big presentation today.
Thank you.
Soon you'll be looking at
the new creative director
at Melanie Stone Advertising.
[AMBER] I'm so proud of you.
Gotta go. Scroll My Ad is my
task master, you know.
Lots of video bloggers to
watch and report on.
You know you love it.
[AMBER] Did I show you
my new favorite?
Rosie Gomez. She's like a
Hispanic female Simon Cowell.
[ROSIE] Guys, have you
seen the insane prices
at the Only At Christmas Store
on First Street?
Who do they think is going to
purchase an $85 stocking?
I hear a boycott
in our future.
[AMBER] I already feel sorry
for that store.
She has millions of followers.
Go get her, Amber.
[AMBER] You know I will.
I have Scroll My Ad dollars
with her name on them.
[SANTA] Can you give a little
something for children in need?
Oh! That's very generous.
My pleasure.
What's this?
A thank you ribbon. It makes
people feel good,
brings them luck.
Everybody could use a little
Christmas magic, hmm?
I wish that were true, but
the holidays are just good
for us advertisers to help our
clients sell more stuff.
Oh, but...
No, you see that building
over there?
That's my agency. That's where
the real magic happens.
There must have been a time
when you believed?
When I was a kid, I guess, but
everyone grows up, right?
Have a good one... Um...
Santa.
Suit yourself, Santa.
Everyone's waiting for you
in the conference room.
Let's hope it goes as planned.
Don't worry, Kendal. It will.
Come on, Tiffany,
kill the nice act.
We both know Curazon's campaign
should have been mine.
I've been here longer.
Kendal, I always give credit
where credit is due.
But this wasn't about seniority.
I got Curazon because you didn't
deliver for your last client
on their campaign.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Well, our client, Jeff Crane,
CEO of Curazon Enterprises,
obviously needs no introduction.
It's good to see you, Mr. Crane.
And you know our rising
star, Tiffany Baxter.
I had a great initial meeting
with Ms. Baxter.
I look forward to seeing what
she's got for me today.
Well, the room is
yours, Tiffany.
Thank you, Melanie.
Tomorrow, as you know, we launch
our new Curazon Toys
online Christmas ad, which
we will hard press
to go viral in the morning.
You asked for bold, Mr. Crane.
Melanie Stone Advertising
is giving you bold.
[MUSIC PLAYS FROM VIDEO]
[ANNOUNCER] When you have
Curazon Kid Picks
for the holidays, you don't
need anything else.
[TELEPHONE RINGING IN
THE BACKGROUND]
[APPLAUSE]
We've got a winner on our hands.
[MELANIE] Congratulations,
Tiffany. You did it.
Nice work, Ms. Baxter.
It is impressive.
And bold, as promised.
Thank you.
Alright, everyone, get to work.
We need to break the
internet tomorrow.
[LAUGHING]
Jeff, I do hope that
you'll be coming
to the agency Christmas party?
♪♪♪
[SIGHS]
Tiffany Baxter,
creative director.
♪♪♪
[AMBER] Congratulations.
[TIFFANY] Thank you.
You are my very best friend.
Very best.
But so clueless.
What?
[SQUEALS]
Oh my God!
[LAUGHING]
Duane proposed!
Oh. My holiday gift's
an old, crappy...
Don't be silly. Your gifts
are always awesome.
Besides, no one could be a
better best friend than you.
Always generous, and...
What? Can't I appreciate
my bestie?
[CHUCKLES]
Duane also got us tickets for
a two week cruise.
Two weeks?
I know I always help you
weather Christmas,
and you I always end up
somewhere fun,
like the wine country
cottage last year.
Yeah.
But I can't not go.
Of course, of course.
Don't be silly.
I... It's all good.
No, I'll be fine.
♪♪♪
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
[GROANS]
♪♪♪
I know, I know. Another amazing
ad that's already gone viral.
What can I...
What?
No.
[ROSIE] Have you all seen the
Curazon Christmas ad
this morning?
I am so mad. Basically
they're saying,
"Who needs Santa when you
have Curazon Kids Picks."
Oh!
[ROSIE] So, no one in
that little ad room
raised their hand to say that
this is a terrible idea?
What I want to know is whoever
came up with this nasty ad,
who hurt you?
I just created two
new hashtags,
#weneedSanta, and
#cancelCurazon.
Oh my God.
♪♪♪
Oh no!
[MELANIE] The second someone
has eyes on Tiffany Baxter,
send her to my office.
♪♪♪
She's here, Melanie.
She's coming.
Glad you could show up
this morning.
This agency is dead
without this client.
Curazon is our tent pole.
Do you understand?
I do.
[MELANIE] Good.
We need to come up with
a response fast,
and when I say we, I mean you.
Well, you always say that
there's no such thing
as bad publicity, and any
good campaign
always gets a little bit
of backlash, right?
A little backlash?
Curazon has already lost
millions, Tiffany.
Oh. God, um..
What can we do?
You're the creative genius.
Come up with something.
Take some time off, Tiffany.
Come back only when you
have the perfect idea.
Just make sure it's in time
for the Christmas party
so you can pitch it to Jeff.
Got it?
Got it.
Good.
Because if you don't,
not only can you kiss
that promotion good bye,
but I'm not sure
there'll be a place here
for you at all.
♪♪♪
I've... I got this.
Mm-hmm.
♪♪♪
[TIFFANY] I don't got this.
[MUSIC PLAYING IN
THE BACKGROUND]
I think my career is over.
[MUSIC PLAYING IN
THE BACKGROUND]
I literally don't
know what to do.
I know less than zero about
celebrating Christmas.
I always spend it with you.
Besides our trips, every year I
volunteer to do Secret Santa,
helping those that can't afford
it have a real Christmas.
What am I going to tell them?
Sorry, I'll be in the Bahamas?
How am I supposed to come
up with inspiration
for a time of year that
just makes me sad?
Like, where am I going to
learn what a heartfelt
holiday Christmas is?
To help me create
a new campaign.
♪♪♪
Wait.
What?
Oh.
No.
Not a good idea.
But I am your best friend,
and I need to help.
So, I can volunteer at your
Secret Santa event for you.
Are you sure?
I mean, you're kind of a...
Christmas Debbie Downer?
I know why.
I don't blame you at all.
Mm-hmm.
But these families really
count on this, Tiff.
It's the only Christmas
they have.
I won't let them or you
down, I promise.
[LAUGHING]
You just saved my
engagement cruise,
my almost marriage.
Mm-hmm.
And the holidays for
so many people.
You're the best.
Ah, just have a good trip.
[LAUGHS]
You know, I think you might have
just helped save my job.
I'm still going to hurt
that vlogger for you.
Hmm.
Okay?
Mm-hmm.
♪♪♪
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hello?
♪♪♪
Oh, can I help you?
Hi, I'm replacing Amber Thomas
for the Secret Santa
event this year. She
should have called.
Oh, my almighty God!
Yes, you must be Tiffany.
I am happy to meet you.
Are you Grey Johnson?
Oh, dear no. I see Amber has
told you oh so much about me.
I'm Phillip, Grey's assistant,
and your new best friend.
Mr. Johnson is in the gallery.
He's working on the tree.
So exciting! Here, follow me.
Oh, we're all happy for Amber.
I'm not sure how we'll
do without her.
Amber does everything
around here.
You've got big shoes
to fill, girl.
How hard can it be?
[LAUGHS]
Well, lets just say I hope
you love Christmas
as much as we all do.
Mr. Johnson?
Uh-huh?
[PHILLIP] Amber's friend
is here.
Hi, I'm... I'm Tiffany.
Okay, maybe you could start
with that big pile
of tangled lights over there.
Um...
Good luck.
I've heard a lot about
the good you do here
at Secret Santa from
Amber, of course.
Uh...
So much for the magic
of Christmas.
Girl, you did good.
But it's time for a break.
How are you holding up?
I'm okay.
Mm-hmm?
Thank you.
But I'm not sure how much
Mr. Santa wants me here.
I think I scared him off.
Yeah, don't worry about Grey.
He's just a bit upset that Amber
didn't give us any real notice.
Though he's happy
for her, of course.
He might seem tough, but
he's really a teddy bear.
He's just been through so much
in the last few years.
Like what?
Okay, uh...
When his wife got sick, Grey
left a job on Wall Street
to take care of her. And then
when Caroline couldn't do
the Secret Santa gig
anymore, he took over.
I think he thought it was all
temporary, but then it wasn't.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah. And I know that Grey
didn't think that he'd end up
raising Brandon all alone.
Brandon?
Oh, his son.
Hmm.
You'll meet him.
He's usually around,
but let's just say he's a
bit angry at the world.
It's been hard on them both.
Amber has been here through
it all with them though.
I can't believe she never
mentioned Brandon.
I also can't believe that
she let such a rookie
take her place.
[LAUGHS]
Thank you, Amber.
I'd better let you finish up,
and get out of here, yeah?
Phillip?
Mm-hmm.
Thanks for telling me.
Best friends, remember?
♪♪♪
Ugh! I've got some work to do.
But first, volunteer.
♪♪♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
Ms. Baxter.
Hi. And it's Tiffany, please.
How can I help you, Mr. Johnson?
I was wondering if you
could take on the task
of decorating the big Christmas
tree in the gallery today?
Decorating the tree.
I know, Amber told me
you're not much
of a Christmas person, but...
[SIGHS] Then why have me...?
Well, she didn't give me
much of a choice
with her last minute trip.
And also, I tend to think that
the foundation's holiday events
could change any Scrooge.
I'm not a...
Oh, no offense. You do know
what a Christmas tree
looks like, right?
Yes, of course. But you
don't want me to...
Actually I do.
Please, I haven't had a tree
since I was a kid. Just...
Anything but the tree.
Okay, tell you what.
You tell me the reason you are
so down on Christmas,
and I will give tree duty
to someone else.
I don't...
It's just...
Don't fight, but you
have been warned.
Decorations are in the supply
room down the back hall.
Got it.
♪♪♪
[MUMBLES]
What's that?
Yay! Yay me.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
[BRANDON] You need me
out there helping?
Um... Shouldn't you be
Not if I can help it.
You must be Brandon.
That would be me.
Who are you?
I'm... I'm Tiffany. I'm
taking over for Amber.
My dad told me she was getting
married. Perfect timing.
She gets to miss out on all this
fake celebration stuff.
Fake? You don't
believe in Santa?
Hello? I'm fourteen!
Right.
Christmas is just a publicity
stunt for companies
to sell more stuff.
You're a smart cookie,
aren't you.
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
I don't believe in Santa either.
Of course. You're an adult.
Usually all the people
around here drink
the Christmas Kool Aid anyway.
Your, your dad just put me in
charge of decorating the tree.
I definitely could
use some help.
Come on, it'll be fun.
I don't think so.
I'll pay you.
Bribery, huh?
Okay, that is not
how I meant it.
Please, please don't tell
your father that.
Price just went up.
You're joking, right?
Maybe.
Are you sure you're
only fourteen?
This way!
Hey, how's it goi-
[LAUGHING]
Sorry, would you mind taking
those down the hall
to the office?
I'll meet you there.
[CHATTER & LAUGHING]
♪♪♪
[TIFFANY] Okay, now it's fair.
Now you're taller than me.
You're only taller than me
'cause you're wearing
those heels anyway.
That is totally not true.
[LAUGHING]
[BRANDON] You've always got
something to say, don't you?
[TIFFANY] Watch it.
[BRANDON] You know, I
volunteered to help you.
[TIFFANY] Thank you very much.
You must be really proud of all
the work your dad's doing, huh?
I guess.
Well, lots of kids wouldn't
get presents for Christmas
if it wasn't for him.
Secret Santa's just
some rich old lady
who used to be friends
with my mom.
My dad has nothing
to do with it.
Well, he arranges the events.
You're here for that, right?
I am, but...
My dad is always too busy or too
tired during the holidays
to do anything else.
I think it makes him sad
to celebrate with me.
I remind him of my mom,
so he likes to celebrate
with the Secret Santa
families more.
Oh, Brandon, I'm sure
that's not true.
I'm sure he cares about
you very much.
♪♪♪
You know, I think it's
too quiet in here.
[CHRISTMAS CAROL PLAYS]
Come on, I know you've
got it in you.
[LAUGHING]
[CHRISTMAS CAROL PLAYS
IN BACKGROUND]
Hi, Dad.
We were just, um...
We were just finishing the tree.
[CHRISTMAS CAROL PLAYS
IN BACKGROUND]
Well, where's the star?
[CHRISTMAS CAROL PLAYS
IN BACKGROUND]
Let me.
I can, I can do it.
If you're sure.
Mm-hmm.
[CHRISTMAS CAROL PLAYS
IN BACKGROUND]
♪♪♪
Are you sure you're okay?
Yep. Absolutely.
♪♪♪
Oh!
[CRASHING]
[GREY] Tiffany!
♪♪♪
Are you hurt?
Um, no, no. I'm alright.
Are you sure?
Yeah, just a little embarrassed.
Okay.
And now I have a room full
of broken decorations,
and the opening event
is tomorrow.
I am so sorry.
Gotta admit, Dad, it was pretty
funny watching Tiffany
falling over, hugging a tree.
I just don't have time
for this right now.
I'm sorry again, Mr. Johnson.
If there's any way I can help.
♪♪♪
[BRANDON] He used to be fun.
Now all he thinks about is this
stupid Secret Santa.
Brandon, wait! I...
♪♪♪
[TIFFANY] Grey Johnson hates me.
[AMBER] I doubt that.
I ruined the celebration
for all these kids.
[AMBER] A few broken decorations
are not going to ruin anything.
I should have known better.
You know me and Christmas,
not a good combo.
[AMBER] I would have liked
to see you timber!
[LAUGHS]
It wasn't funny.
[AMBER] Wait a minute.
The elf Santa writing party
is tomorrow, right?
That should help.
Ooh, unless the tree is bare,
and it looks horrible.
Oh!
Had a rough day?
I, I ruined the holiday for all
these kids and their families.
Maybe Christmas is just
not what you think it is.
I find most of the time,
what we're looking for
is right under our nose.
What, you run out of
red ribbons today?
♪♪♪
Wait a minute, I know
what I can...
Can I keep this?
My pleasure.
Thank you! [CHUCKLES]
♪♪♪
[KENDAL] Give credit
when credit is due.
I helped you with your first
campaign when you were
a new hire, Tiffany. And this
is the thanks I receive?
You get Curazon, and I'm stuck
working on a dog food ad.
Hi, Phillip.
[PHILLIP] Hey, Tiffany.
I have an amazing idea,
but I can't do it alone.
Could you possibly meet me at
the gallery in like 20 minutes?
[PHILLIP] Yeah,
anything for you.
[TIFFANY] Great, thank you.
I owe you.
What kind of ad are
you making, Tiffany?
[TIFFANY] And Lyft.
Secret Santa.
♪♪♪
Tiffany.
What are you doing here?
I am here to save the tree.
How?
[TIFFANY] Well, I, I thought we
could do this fun activity
where people decorate
their own ornaments.
So, I could set up a
main area over here
with the majority of
the craft supplies,
and then maybe have some
starting materials on the table,
and then people could take
things, and share and trade,
and make what they want.
This actually could work.
Yeah. And then you could have
original decorations
from every year,
like a time capsule...
If you would want
to keep it going.
I'm impressed.
Well, if you knew me, you would
never underestimate me.
I'm starting to see that.
♪♪♪
Um... But I want to set up
everything before the morning,
but you should go home
and get some sleep.
Phillip said folks would
be here early.
I was planning to sleep
here, actually.
I should help you.
I know a kid who would be
really happy to see you
when he wakes up in the morning.
Besides, Phillip is
coming to assist,
and he will be here any minute.
That man needs a raise.
[TIFFANY] Yes, he does.
Go home.
Alright.
Good night.
Good night, Mr. Johnson.
Please, call me Grey.
♪♪♪
Good night, Grey.
[TIFFANY] Good morning.
[GREY] Good morning. I just
checked out the spread,
and everything looks
fantastic, Tiffany.
Thank you. I hope you
weren't here too late.
No worries. As an ad exec,
I've pulled many late nights,
and you're most welcome,
but I also had help.
I know. Phillip wouldn't take a
raise from me this morning
so I stuck a little extra in
his Christmas stocking.
[LAUGHS]
Smart.
Uh... Shall I go see if
he needs anything
before the doors open?
Sure.
Okay.
Oh, wait! Actually you can
do me one more favor.
These are racking up.
I know, I know.
Can you find Brandon for me?
I want him to participate
today,
and he's usually pretty
good at hiding.
I might have an idea
where he is.
Hey.
It's starting soon.
You, you ready to go.
Nah.
You can't possibly make me face
these Christmas lovers alone.
Somebody's got to keep me
away from that tree.
I am a walking hazard.
Come on.
If you make me talk to
any of those elves,
I'm out of there.
How about Santa?
Don't even.
Come on.
[CHATTER]
Hey.
Alright.
Everyone ready?
Mm-hmm.
This is it.
[CHATTER]
Let the holiday season begin!
Come on in!
Welcome, everybody.
Hey, welcome back.
Hi! Nice to see you, Tina.
Look at this one.
♪♪♪
Hi.
[GREY] Morning, everyone!
It is wonderful to see so many
familiar faces here today.
Hi!
As many of you know, Secret
Santa means the world to me.
This wonderful event would
not exist if it wasn't for
the dedicated work of my late
wife, Caroline Johnson.
And now for something
new this year!
As you can see already, you have
lots of crafts at your table.
Well, we need your help
decorating our tree!
So please, help us make
some ornaments.
Santa's helpers have
more crafts for you,
and don't forget to write your
letters and drop them
in our special mailbox over
there so that they go
directly to Santa.
And I promise that we will
personally deliver them
to the North Pole.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
[GREY] Thank you all for coming,
and we'll see you again
in a few days for gift giving.
Merry Christmas, everyone!
Merry Christmas.
[APPLAUSE]
Hey, Brandon, aren't
you writing?
My dad...
Said everyone should write
a letter to Santa, Brandon.
You too.
Yeah, yeah.
Come on, Brandon, let's
write letters to Santa.
What should I write?
Whatever's on your mind.
How about you?
It's complicated.
It's a waste of time. We both
know Santa's not real.
May I go?
Yeah.
Brandon.
Just wanted to see
if you're okay.
I'm fine.
You can toss that, Ellery.
Huh.
I was going to ask if you
wanted to come with me
to put it in the mailbox.
Oh! Uh... Sure.
Great.
Let's go.
What a great thing you're doing.
Well, it's my first year,
but I hope to come back.
We've been coming for six years.
If it wasn't for Caroline
Johnson are her Secret Santa
program, I'm not sure
what I'd have done.
I just couldn't afford
Christmas.
Do you know how embarrassing it
is for kids to go to school
and have to tell their friends
that they didn't get
any presents? Ellery used
to come home crying.
Kids can be very cruel.
Yes. And mine didn't understand
why Santa could bring
presents to all the other
kids but not her.
I never thought of that before.
That must have been
very difficult.
It was. And then all the
commercials come out,
these slick ads telling kids
what expensive new toy
they should be getting, which
of course I can't afford.
Yeah.
Speaking of, did you see that
new ad before they pulled it?
The one that said kids
don't need Santa?
Can you believe it?
The nerve of those people.
Yeah.
[NANCY] Hey!
Nancy! Excuse me.
I love this.
A videographer too?
Oh, but of course.
[LAUGHING]
Everyone signs overall releases
when they are put
on the guest list, and then
we can use the footage
for anything we need to.
That is really smart.
Thank you.
[LAUGHING]
We got some really
great footage today.
You are a man of
many talents, eh?
Oh! Honey, you have no idea.
[LAUGHING]
♪♪♪
Now let's see what's
really going on.
♪♪♪
Hey.
How's it going?
Today is very special.
Grey, thank you for letting
me be a part of it.
No, thank you for all your work.
[GREY] You made this happen.
[TIFFANY] It was...
It was just an idea.
[GREY] It was a good one.
All your work? What are you
doing here, Tiffany?
Mrs. Claus! Mrs. Claus!
Shh! No, no, no!
Give me... Let go!
Hey, everybody! It's Mrs. Claus!
Let go, you little brat!
[GRUNTS]
Ugh!
♪♪♪
[GIRL] Where are you going?
Don't go! Wait, come back!
♪♪♪
[CHUCKLES]
You've made the nice list
this year, my girl.
[TIFFANY] Hey, what are
you doing with Santa's letters,
you thief?
Tradition. I'm bringing them
home to read them
and make a master list.
Is Brandon doing it with you?
He prefers his video games.
Ooh, here we go.
Which he'll probably be playing
as soon as he's done
helping Phillip.
Can I give you a hand?
I don't know. Does this count
as another favor?
I haven't asked for
anything in return.
Yet.
Alright, trouble, yes. I would
love some help.
♪♪♪
He is out cold.
Brandon always refused
to participate,
but today he seemed to
have a great time.
He did.
[GREY] What happened?
Oh, I could tell you, but then
I'd have to kill you.
[LAUGHS]
So, how do we do this?
First we divide them into two
piles, things we can buy,
those we can't.
Such as?
Well, sometimes kids
ask for things
like getting their parents
back together,
or bringing back a loved one.
That's heartbreaking.
[SIGHS]
And I know it's weird, but it
feels funny reading these,
like I stole Santa's mail.
Ah, I thought you didn't
believe in Santa.
It's not that, it's...
It's personal.
I didn't mean to pry.
You didn't.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Dear Santa, I hope this year
you will come visit.
It's been hard for my mom.
Oh, and I'd like a Transformer.
Hey Santa, can you bring
my mom a new sweater?
It's really cold this
time of year.
Dear Santa, I know you're
not real but...
♪♪♪
Who is it?
Oh no, don't.
♪♪♪
[BRANDON] Can you please tell
my dad that I miss him?
I'd like him spend more
time with me,
and less time with you, Santa.
Oh, and please help him find
someone to love again
so he can stop being
so sad and stuff.
Brandon.
It's like you said, some
are heartbreaking.
♪♪♪
Um, I'm just going to grab us
some soda and munchies
to keep us going.
♪♪♪
[TIFFANY] Okay, so the next
store we need
is just a few blocks down.
Alright.
Well, I don't want to lose
this great parking spot.
Let's walk. It's a
beautiful day.
Sounds good.
I'm going to run ahead and
grab us some burgers
at that place next to the park.
Sure.
Thanks, Brandon.
I thought your dad was going
to starve us. [LAUGHS]
Funny.
In case you want
some money, here.
Shall we?
We shall.
Alright.
Next half.
Yeah. [LAUGHS]
Hands free.
[LAUGHING]
Uh...
♪♪♪
Tiffany?
[TIFFANY] I...
I haven't skated since
I was a little girl.
My... My dad used to take
me when I was little.
Why did he stop?
He... He left.
♪♪♪
I was about six, and one day
he left to go to the store,
and never came back.
♪♪♪
That's rough.
It was...
It was Christmas morning.
♪♪♪
Ah.
For years I asked Santa
to bring him back.
I wrote letters, and I waited,
and waited, but...
Of course, he never showed.
♪♪♪
The holidays are never easy when
you have to spend them
without the people
you care about.
♪♪♪
That's right.
[LAUGHING]
Are you done already?
You eat faster than a
fourteen year old boy.
Hey, I was hungry.
Good man.
Thank you.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, at least he
doesn't litter.
No, that's great. He's a very
respectable young boy.
Yeah.
[WHIMPERING]
Hey, buddy. Nobody took
you home? Oh!
Oh, this is so adorable.
Dad, look how cute he is!
Hello!
Can we take him home?
No! Brandon, you can't
be serious.
Someone just abandoned him.
Come here.
[BRANDON] Dad, please!
He needs a home.
Brandon, no. We are
not getting a puppy.
I don't have time to
look after a dog.
I'll look after him!
I'll do everything.
You won't even know he's there.
I could watch him sometimes.
You are not helping.
[BRANDON] Dad! Look at him!
Look at them.
[SIGHS] Thanks a lot.
We can get him?
[BRANDON] Yes!
Alright.
Yes!
Take him.
Thank you, Dad. You
won't regret this.
I already regret it.
So, what are you
going to call him?
I don't know yet. I need to
find the perfect name.
It'll come to me.
Let's get some supplies
for this menace.
[LAUGHS]
We got a dog.
I'm... I'm sorry. I...
I didn't mean to push but
Brandon looked so happy.
No, you were right.
To be honest, I haven't seen him
like this since Caroline...
He... He really is a great kid.
He's been so angry at me.
Sometimes I think he wishes she
was here instead of me.
Don't say that. You...
You know that's not true.
It all happened so quickly.
And it hit me so hard.
I just couldn't be
there for him.
And that's when you took
on Secret Santa.
Yeah.
All my life I was part of a
system where money
was all that mattered.
Suddenly I was making a
difference in people's lives.
It changed me.
But Brandon and I have
been growing further
and further apart every year.
♪♪♪
This week I've seen
that spark again.
He seems to be
excited about life.
Hmm.
Thanks to you.
He...
He really is special.
♪♪♪
So are you.
[TIFFANY] I should be
heading out.
[GREY] Alright. I'll walk
you to your car.
♪♪♪
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
I got the rest of the
stuff from storage,
but I missed my little
helper this morning.
He's off to school.
Hey, want a sneak peak
at some footage?
Oh, the infamous video.
[GREY] Yes.
I film every year
for our archives.
Also to show that the money is
going where it's supposed to go,
to people who need it.
[MUSIC PLAYS ON VIDEO]
They are so cute.
[WOMAN] I'm not sure what
I would have done
if it wasn't for Secret Santa.
That's what Secret Santa's
all about, you know.
That's the magic of
Christmas right there.
Yeah, I think I'm finally
starting to get it.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Hi, Irene.
Oh, hey Will. What a surprise,
I was expecting your mother.
Is everything okay?
Oh my God!
I... I just spoke to her last
week. I can't believe that.
Oh no!
I... I am so, so sorry, Will.
You know that I have always
appreciated your mother so much.
We can't do what we do
here without her.
What do you mean?
No, you can't be serious!
We had an agreement!
I understand that she's gone...
Okay, I get that she didn't
put it in the will
but you know that's what she
would have wanted.
♪♪♪
[GREY] Well, what are we
supposed...
Okay, I understand.
♪♪♪
What happened?
Our Secret Santa passed away.
Oh.
[GREY] I have two days to
come up with $50,000,
or I'll have no choice
but to cancel
this season's celebration.
Have you ever thought about
getting a corporate sponsor?
I... I... With the footage you
have, I know I could create
something compelling.
We have this client
that would...
No!
I have to find a real Secret
Santa, not some brand
who will use us to sell whatever
it is they're selling.
Look, I understand you
mean well, Tiff,
but bringing on a corporation
goes against everything
Caroline wanted.
Okay. Well, if there's anything
I can do to help...
Thank you.
If you wouldn't mind bringing
this back to Phillip,
I made a folder with
all the best clips.
Yes, of course.
We'll talk later, okay?
Tiffany.
Not a word to anyone, please.
Of course.
[PHILLIP] What's rumbling
in there?
Oh! Hi there.
Did you get into the Christmas
decorations?
Yes, you did. Yes, you did.
You got into the tinsel!
Tough work, huh?
Well, if they expected
me to work,
they shouldn't have
gotten a puppy.
Isn't that right, handsome?
Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
Brandon's been asking
for a dog for years.
I can't believe that
Grey said yes.
I'm afraid I might have had
something to do with that.
Oh. [LAUGHS]
Say hello.
Isn't he the cutest? Hi.
Say hello, mister.
What's his name?
Brandon's working on that one.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Um... Can I have a second?
It's my boss.
Yeah.
Melanie.
[MELANIE] Are you planning
on coming into work
at some point, Tiffany?
Of course. I...
[MELANIE] I told you
to take time off
until the Christmas party,
not disappear.
I... I was just about to leave.
Melanie?
[PHILLIP] Go, girl.
Don't worry about us.
Thanks.
[PHILLIP] Aren't you handsome?
Yes, you are.
[AMBER] What do you
mean cancelled?
That's what I'm trying
to tell you.
He needs to come up
with $50,000
or there will be
no Secret Santa.
[AMBER] Hey, where is he going
to find that kind of money?
I tried to talk to him about
getting a corporate sponsor...
[AMBER] Look, if you
knew him well,
you would know Grey would
never go for that.
But it's the perfect solution!
Curazon would love to help.
[AMBER] You're thinking about
saving your job right now.
That's totally unfair, Amber.
I... I care about Grey.
All I'm saying is that
I saw some footage
from the elves Santa
writing party, and...
The footage.
The footage. I still have
that hard drive.
♪♪♪
I gotta go, Amber.
[AMBER] Where are you going?
[TIFFANY] I'm sorry, Amber.
We'll talk soon.
I love you. Bye!
♪♪♪
I'm going to need some
more coffee for this.
♪♪♪
[CLEARS THROAT]
Good, you're finally here.
We've all been on the
hook waiting for you
to come up with some
genius idea
so Curazon doesn't take their
business to another agency,
and all our other clients
follow suit.
Well, I... I have something, but
I still have some convincing
to do to be able to use it.
No need to convince me,
I want to see it.
[TIFFANY] No, you don't
understand.
I have to talk to someone
else, it's not my...
Tiffany, my patience
is razor thin.
So, do you have something,
or don't you?
[SIGHS]
The footage. It was right here.
It was here. I know it was here.
What is happening?
Well, Tiffany was going to show
me her brilliant new idea
for Curazon, but apparently
it's disappeared.
[TIFFANY] I went to the lounge
to grab a cup of coffee,
and now it's gone.
What was it?
I had some footage
on a thumb drive,
maybe a new Christmas ad for
Curazon, something heartfelt.
I still have to get permission
to use it, but...
You said that before.
[MELANIE] Tiffany, are you okay?
You really don't seem
like yourself.
Are you sure you didn't leave
the drive somewhere else?
No.
So, the Christmas party is
tonight, and you don't have
anything to show Jeff?
I do, I have an amazing
idea, I just...
Jeff's been very
patient, Tiffany.
I know, and I will have
something to pitch him,
I promise.
You'd better. Come on.
I didn't realize how much this
situation was getting to her.
You don't think she made up the
thumb drive story, do you?
I hope not.
Otherwise this agency's
finished.
♪♪♪
What am I going to do with you?
[PHILLIP] Grey said that you
have my thumb drive.
It's my only copy.
Yeah, I don't like to have
it passed around.
I'm sure you have all the
footage on your camera, no?
[PHILLIP] No, I downloaded
everything,
and I was going to make a copy,
but then Grey took it
before I had a chance.
[TIFFANY] Gotcha. I do need to
speak to Grey if he's available.
I'm sure he is for you. Just a
moment, I'll transfer you.
Thank you.
[GREY] Hey, I was just
missing you.
I miss you too. It's... It's
weird being back at work
rather than detangling lights
and toppling trees.
[LAUGHS]
I was calling because there
is a Christmas party
at my agency tonight, and I
know it's last minute,
but would you care to join me?
You want me to come?
[TIFFANY] Yes.
[GREY] I've got a lot
of calls to make.
Well, there's going to be some
important people there,
pretty wealthy too, so I thought
maybe you would find
someone who can help you
with your problem.
♪♪♪
Hmm.
And I would very much like
for you to be my date.
♪♪♪
Then I'll be there.
[TIFFANY] Just a second.
♪♪♪
Wow.
You don't look so bad yourself.
♪♪♪
Shall we?
Hold on one sec.
♪♪♪
I like it.
I thought you might.
[LAUGHING]
♪♪♪
[CHATTER]
[MUSIC PLAYING IN THE
BACKGROUND]
There you go.
Thank you.
Cheers.
You must be Grey Johnson.
Tiffany has told us so
much about you.
Oh?
I have, have I?
Those poor kids. How does it
feel to make a difference
in so many lives?
Well, we don't call them poor,
they're just going through
some rougher times than others.
Kendal is an account
executive like me.
Tiffany. Please introduce
us to your guest.
Grey Johnson,
Melanie Stone,
CEO of Melanie Stone
Advertising, and my boss.
Pleasure meeting you.
The pleasure's mine.
And may I introduce Jeff Crane,
CEO of Curazon Enterprises.
Nice meeting you, Grey.
So, how do you connect to
Tiffany? Are you a client?
Actually Tiffany has been
volunteering for us
at Secret Santa in
her spare time.
Has she?
Impressive.
Yes, wonderful.
I've heard many good things
about Secret Santa.
Congratulations on
the great work.
[KENDAL] I didn't know
you volunteered.
That's Tiffany for you, a woman
of many secrets.
[MUSIC PLAYING IN THE
BACKGROUND]
Can I please invite you all
to the conference room
for a few minutes? I've prepared
a small surprise this evening.
Have you?
Oh, with Tiffany's
help, of course.
Oh, but I...
[JEFF] Come, Grey.
There is never a dull
moment in this place.
These ladies are...
Kendal.
Hmm?
What's going on?
You'll see.
[MUSIC PLAYING IN THE
BACKGROUND]
[KENDAL] Mr. Johnson, in case
you're unaware,
Tiffany is something of a genius
in the world of advertising.
She's exaggerating.
Uh, what are you doing, Kendal?
Giving credit where credit
is due, of course.
[GREY] I'm excited
to see her work.
[MUSIC PLAYING FROM VIDEO]
No.
I didn't...
[WOMAN] I'm not sure what
I would have done
if it wasn't for Secret Santa.
We love each other.
But sometimes it's not enough.
[ANNOUNCER] All you need
is love,
but when that's just not
enough, there's Curazon.
I love it.
It's genius.
You did this.
No, I would never.
[JEFF] Curazon, sponsor of
Secret Santa. It's brilliant.
I don't... I don't know
what this is,
but I already told Tiffany that
we are not interested
in having a corporate sponsor.
Who really cares where
the money comes from
as long as you get to give it
to the less fortunate?
I do.
I care.
And we don't need
Curazon's money.
[KENDAL] But aren't you
short of $50,000?
I... I didn't tell
her that. Grey.
We are done here.
[JEFF] Mr. Johnson, please
consider this.
Curazon can offer you a lot
more than $50,000.
It would be a shame for you to
have your event cancelled
because you're... Well, because
you're too proud.
Grey, Grey, wait.
♪♪♪
What have you done?
Kendal, not you, saved our
most important client.
So, you'd better go close
the Secret Santa deal,
or you're fired.
No need. I quit.
♪♪♪
Grey!
[GREY] Go back inside.
It's cold.
[TIFFANY] I don't care.
Go away, Tiffany. I can't
look at you right now.
♪♪♪
I...
[TIFFANY] I know you must
hate me right now
but you, you have to know
that was not the way
it was supposed to happen. I was
going to talk to you first.
[GREY] Stop.
Just stop.
I know your type. I used
to work with them.
Actually I used to be
one of them.
All that matters to you people
is money, and getting results.
It doesn't matter how
you get there.
I...
I thought you were different.
I am.
At first I was doing it for me,
but then I, I met you.
And Brandon.
♪♪♪
[TIFFANY] Spending time at
Secret Santa has opened my eyes.
♪♪♪
Please, please, I, I didn't know
about any of that, I swear.
I lost the drive, and then
suddenly Kendal was...
You lost the drive?
Yes, but I...
No, I've heard enough.
♪♪♪
Unlike you, I'm not willing to
sell out Secret Santa,
or the memory of my wife,
for $50,000.
Grey, I...
[GREY] And I never want to see
you anywhere near me
or Brandon ever again.
♪♪♪
[SANTA] It's a cold night to be
out, and you don't look
so good, my dear.
You don't want to know.
May I sit?
I screwed everything up.
I doubt that.
Though it probably
feels like it.
It does.
How do you know when
someone is good?
[CHUCKLES]
What if you do something
that's maybe bad
but you do it to help
someone you care about?
Can that be good?
Let's start over.
Here.
Now, what is it you're
trying to say?
♪♪♪
I think I belong on the
naughty list, Santa.
You may ask yourself, did it
come from the heart?
I... I think so.
Yes.
Yes, it did.
Then that's all that matters.
That doesn't fix anything.
Unfortunately not. That's
something you'll have to do
all on your own.
How?
You're a smart young woman.
I bet you'll come up
with something.
Something to fix this mess that
I've made of everything.
I don't think so.
I do.
And it will probably be
something that will help
a lot of people too.
♪♪♪
You are the best Santa I know.
I wish you were there
when I was a kid.
♪♪♪
Oh no, I...
[SIGHS]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[TIFFANY] Grey, I'm so sorry.
You've been crying.
Gossip mill in your office is
going crazy over the events
of last night.
I'm glad they called me
so I could fly back stat.
I am so glad you're here, but...
But what about Duane?
He's not thrilled, but he knew
that I would have been
miserable the rest of the time
knowing you needed me.
Don't worry.
Now, tell me the plan.
There is no plan.
Grey Johnson wants nothing
to do with me,
and the Christmas event
is probably cancelled.
Who are you, and what did you
do with my friend, Tiffany?
Tiffany's left the building.
Funny. I didn't leave my killer
cruise for a pity party.
Come on, Tiff. You've never
given up on anything
in your whole life.
You're one of the most creative
people I've ever met,
and one of the most talented
marketing people in this city.
There has to be a plan.
I got fired.
Or well, technically I quit, but
that... That wasn't the plan.
First, thank God you
left that woman.
You could do better.
Second, you're going to come
up with an amazing idea,
and we are going to
save Secret Santa.
Yes.
♪♪♪
I think that there's something
we might be able to do.
There she is.
But I'm going to need your help.
Of course. I'm not missing
my afternoon piña colada
for nothing.
Great, okay. Then first I
need you to make a call.
To?
♪♪♪
Rosie, thank you so much.
You have five minutes,
Amber, and that's it.
And only because your
company, Scroll My Ad,
now sponsors my video blogs.
Then I'll... I'll talk fast.
I'm the idiot that created the
you don't need Santa
Curazon ad.
Thank you.
What?
[ROSIE] That set got me a batch
of new followers,
and more sponsorship for
my internet eyeballs.
Awesome.
[ROSIE] That was an
epic screw up.
Yes, we know but...
Look Rosie, you were
absolutely right.
I can't even believe how wrong
I was about that ad.
But, well, things have
changed. I've changed.
And now I need your help.
And I can make it
worth your while.
How?
♪♪♪
Okay, I got the whole
Rosie thing,
but why are we doing this?
And don't say you're looking
for Santa again
or I may have to commit you.
Oh, there he is!
♪♪♪
Lord have mercy.
Will you do it?
For you, anything.
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks and all that.
But we need to get you
a new suit, Santa.
[GREY] I just want you to know
that I really, really appreciate
all of the work that you've
put into Secret Santa,
and I'm just sorry that
it's ending like this.
It's been a privilege
working for you.
Privilege was all mine, Phillip.
Just as I started to
like this thing.
And where's Tiffany?
Why didn't she come by today?
Um...
We're not going to be seeing
her anymore, bud.
Tiffany wasn't who I...
Who we thought she was.
Not everyone has to
love Christmas, Dad.
Why does everything have
to be about Secret Santa?
You're wrong about her.
It's complicated, Brandon.
When you're older...
I'll understand.
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry.
You still going to help me take
the decorations off the tree?
[SIGHS]
Making these were really fun.
I'm going to miss Tiffany.
Me too, bud.
[BANGING]
What's going on?
I don't know. I'll find out.
[CROWD CHATTERING]
I'm so sorry, but Secret Santa's
been cancelled this year.
Didn't you all get the messages
I sent this morning?
We did, but we also got this.
Sorry, I'm so sorry.
[PHILLIP] Sorry, excuse me,
pardon me.
Who sent this?
Apparently Santa did.
I'm already on it.
[ROSIE] This is where we really
need your help.
Go to the Fun and Done page
and donate anything.
Let's show the amazing people at
Secret Santa what we can do!
In the meantime, here's a few
more videos to show
what a great cause this is.
This is crazy.
Crazy good!
There's over $100,000 already on
the Fun and Done page, Grey.
That's more than we need.
You can help so many
more people now.
Oh my God.
[SANTA] Ho-ho-ho!
Santa is here! Ho-ho-ho!
Santa? Amber!
It's so good to see you.
And congratulations on
your engagement.
What is all of this?
Apparently you have
a new Secret Santa.
Who?
Well, if we told you that it
wouldn't be a secret now,
would it?
Trust me, this one's a keeper.
[SANTA] It's gift giving time!
[CHEERING]
[PHILLIP] Okay, go over
to Santa's chair.
Did you know about this?
And line up single file.
Hi!
♪♪♪
I knew you'd come.
I wouldn't have missed
it for anything.
♪♪♪
[BRANDON] I'm...
I'm going to go see Ellery.
♪♪♪
Did you do all this?
I... I didn't do it alone.
I had a lot of help.
Grey, I am so sorry.
No.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
But... But the video.
[GREY] Your heart was
in the right place.
I was just too angry to see it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Grey, I...
I promise I never would do
anything behind your back
I just really wanted to help
these people and their families.
I... I know how much this
all means to you.
Just to me?
No. I...
This place means
everything to me.
I...
♪♪♪
[TIFFANY] I've fallen in love
with this place,
and with... With you. I...
I don't know when it
happened, but it did.
♪♪♪
I feel the same way.
I think that's why I pushed
you away so hard.
I just couldn't admit
it to myself.
♪♪♪
You've changed everything.
What am I supposed to do
now, Tiffany Baxter?
Kiss me.
♪♪♪
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Secret Santa Advertising Agency.
Yeah, yeah, that's correct.
We only represent businesses
that focus on positive things
that make the world
a better place.
Oh, absolutely, Secret Santa
would love to talk to you
about that. No problem, hold on.
Very professional, Mrs. Johnson.
Well, I am a big, important ad
executive, Mr. Johnson.
♪♪♪
Mom, Dad!
Oh sorry!
We're ready to buy the presents
for this year's families.
Isn't that right, Santa?
Well, if Santa's ready,
then we should go.
We'll meet you and Santa
out front, Brandon.
I have one more thing
I need to do.
Okay. Come on, boy.
♪♪♪
What's up?
This.
♪♪♪
Merry Christmas, Tiffany.
Merry Christmas.
♪♪♪