Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
♪ Hey
Woo!
Hello!
Where have you been?
People are already
heading to the next stop!
- Merry Christmas.
- Did you use your app on me?
- All me.
- Okay.
Miranda!
How did you know? I love
this scarf and this company.
Well, I know you like
sustainable fair trade.
And you're always freezing so...
I wish my ex paid as
much attention as you.
The best gifts
make you feel seen.
How is the app going?
Well, if only I could get my
gift-giving mojo
into it, you know?
I'm so sorry I'm late--
No! Fine. Forget it.
Why are we here today?
- We are-- -Mingling! Yes!
Woo!
Ohh!
Santa Claus! Santa Claus!
Yeah. I really needed this.
Woo hoo!
- What?
- Sheryl's here.
Who?
My head investor!
I have a progress
meeting with her tomorrow!
I can't look foolish.
Okay. Easy fix, compadre.
Just hold on, okay?
Mm hm.
Here we go.
- Okay...
- Voilà!
Now I really don't
look foolish at all!
Okay. I have to go and
pretend to be interesting now.
Just give me one minute.
You're gonna leave me
like this?
Yes.
Okay.
Cute!
I look like Movember Claus!
No you fit right in here.
Wait 'til you meet
Santa's wife, Mrs. Claus.
Oh. Well, Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Paul... Paul.
Are you gonna put that away?
Yeah, I'm ordering a drink.
And, you know,
our app isn't gonna fix itself.
Oh no, what going
on with the... Oh no!
Did you get shut down?
Mrs. Claus plays for your team.
Okay, I'll make you a bet --
if I get her number I get
my phone back.
Fine, whatever.
But you're going to have
to use your personality only.
- You're so annoying.
- That's what family's for, bro.
All right, time me.
Okay.
Come on, guys,
let's go. Let's go!
Hey! I, uh...
I didn't know
Mrs. Claus had a moustache.
Oh these are lip mittens.
It's cold in the North Pole?
Come on, Mr. Claus, you don't
recognize your own wife?
Nah. No, I mistook you for the
angel that fell from the tree.
Oh,
wow. Not on the Nice List.
- Uh, I ordered--
- That's mine! Sorry.
- It's yours.
- No, I insist.
- I can't.
- Why not?
- Take it.
- You take it.
Please will you take the drink?
Oh, I'm sorry,
that's... that's our drink.
- Uh, I ordered this.
- Oh, so did we.
You all did. I'll be back.
Hey, listen,
we really need that drink.
I'm thirsty.
You're thirsty but
we're... celebrating!
- Oh, really?
- Mm hm.
Yeah, we're...
we're celebrating that...
we're going out... on a date.
We are?
She seems uncertain.
Well, maybe after
a credit check or showing me--
A lovely evening out.
Gentlemanly acts of
character, kindness and wit.
But we're mourning your attempt.
May your flirting rest in peace.
Good luck, pal.
You know I'm
genuinely intrigued.
That was easy.
The night is young and
my flirting ain't dead yet.
No, it's not.
♪ It's Christmas
time again! It's Christmas! ♪
Merry Christmas!
Do you know her?
That's my best friend.
Wow.
- She's awesome.
I'm smiling
underneath the beard.
So am I.
We could just take
the facial hair off.
Oh, why ruin the mystery
just yet?
We could be ugly
under here.
I uh...
I doubt that.
Where did
you learn moves like that?
Dirty Dancing was
the only DVD at summer camp.
Cute.
Please head to
the next Santa Crawl stop.
The last shuttle leaves in five.
Ooh! Where's the next one?
Let's catch
some air before we go.
- Merry Christmas!
Oh, excuse me.
Oh, our turn.
So do you believe
in destiny, Mr. Claus?
Ah, it's probability.
- Set patterns over time.
So romantic!
What about coincidences?
It's perspective.
You suddenly realize
what's been
in front of you the entire time.
What about you?
What's meant to be will be.
Oh!
Oh. Whoa! Careful.
Right? It's icy out.
Oh, candy canes.
Oh.
Thank you. You're not so bad.
How do you know?
So, tell me something personal.
Single father.
Seven-year-old.
Greatest thing
that's ever happened to me.
Keeps me humble every day.
So cute.
I've always wanted kids, too,
but I always pretend like
I don't.
Greatest fear?
Letting my parents down.
- You?
- Regret.
I've had enough of that already.
What do you want for Christmas?
This.
You?
More of this.
You better make
that Christmas wish.
I don't even know your name.
Yes, you do.
It's Mrs. Claus, silly.
- Oh, we're gonna miss
the shuttle! -Okay, let's go.
Oh my glove!
Oh, um, I'll be right back.
Oh, wait!
Wait!
No, wait!
No...
There you go. Thanks again.
Hey. Gift
recommendations are still off.
Yeah, it just needs
more data, lots more.
Well, we are running
out of Christmas, Paul.
And fields tests have already
started, you've got to go.
What do you think?
I'm posting on the Santa Crawl
page to find her.
"Looking for Mrs. Claus.
"We met on the crawl,
talked destiny and danced.
"I have your glove."
Okay, don't use
your own profile.
Why not?
Uh, people know your name,
anyone could mess with you?
Scammers, corporate espionage?
What if she's a con artist?
I mean who dresses
like a mustached Mrs. Claus?
Right 'cause, you know,
that's a political statement,
isn't it? Yeah.
Uh, all I'm saying
is just be cautious.
Okay, so... what,
make a fake profile?
Um... yeah, like, Mr. Claus?
Why do I have to hold
your hand through everything?
Because you're five minutes
older and you're so wise.
Hmm, it's true, isn't it?
Okay, you gotta go.
Call me after.
Yeah.
♪ Christmas, Christmas is here
Hey.
Hey! Would you like to try my--
Hey! Would you like to try
the gift recommendation app,
Giftverse?
How does it work?
Giftverse analyzes
a person's social media account
along with other info
to suggest
the perfect gift.
Like that app,
the Present Ninja.
Oh, no, we don't
push mass-produced junk.
We actually link to local
businesses
and independent
artists.
High-quality gifts.
You just want to enter your name
and the recipient's name
right there.
I never know
what to get my sister.
Well, with
machine-learning algorithms
I might be able
to help you with that.
Oakwood exercise bike?
We still have
some bugs to fix...
- Uh hm.
I'm sorry.
You're not following the script.
Do... do you need a T-shirt?
I worked a summer in
college selling phones.
I usually start with,
"Hey, can I ask you a question-"
Can I have my phone back?!
This isn't our, uh...
Do you usually go around
plucking strangers' phones?
- Who are you?
- Who are you?!
Paul Dennis, Present Ninja CEO.
Oh, "Christmas
brought to you by..."
"Present Ninja,
the gift-giving app."
Let me ask you a question.
You ever get someone a gift
they didn't like?
No.
Okay, well, our app
is going
to disrupt bad gift-giving
using technology.
Sounds fancy.
It's actually
really complicated.
I won't bore
you with the details.
So thoughtful of you.
It recommends
the perfect Christmas gift.
No more returns, no more
stress shopping, just hot deals.
You get more for
less. You follow me?
Huh. Well, aren't
you a dumpster fire of tact.
Sample?
- Take it.
- No, I insist.
- It's yours.
- You take it!
- I can't.
- Why not?
- Take it.
- You take it.
Oh, thank you.
Mm!
Mmm...
Your voice
sounds really familiar.
Well, maybe
you saw an interview of me.
I'm Miranda McCauley.
Giftverse founder?
Your app rival.
I'm sorry. I thought you were--
One of your corporate
lemmings?
Wow, I'm getting
the you-don't-like-me vibe.
It's not personal,
you represent everything
I'm against.
What's that?
Pushing meaningless chain
store junk
instead of promoting
independent artists
and local businesses?
I sell affordable.
You don't know me.
I knew you the second you
slapped your ad on Christmas.
It's business.
- Gift-giving is more than that.
- I agree.
It's gonna be a hot day
in December
before you and I agree,
Paul Dennis.
Well, good thing it's
cold. Would you like a T-shirt?
Actually, you know
what? I'll take a T-shirt.
Mm!
- Merry Christmas!
- Happy Holidays.
See ya.
I know we all work remotely
other than these holistic
team-building exercises,
but I like to think
of Giftverse as a family.
So know that I am here 24/7,
even if you just need an ear
to talk to.
I'm here both as
your leader and spiritual ally.
- Thank you, Miranda.
- You're welcome.
Sheryl, hi!
Hi! Sorry I'm late.
I just got off the phone
with the other investors.
Boutique Thrive has
made an offer to acquire us.
You're not actually seriously
thinking of selling to them?
No, no, no.
We're making progress!
Yes! The app no longer suggests
"Grandma, I get you lingerie."
No, but people are
using the app, Sheryl.
People are deleting the app
once they see that the gift
recommendations are off.
It's been months since launch
and the accuracy
has barely improved.
Okay, but we're so close.
Please. You know me.
I need the algorithms
to understand people
a little better.
Listen, it's not
personal, it's business.
I brought these over
from the house for you.
Oh, cute!
Agh!
What's wrong, Dad?
I can't get my holiday
kombucha anywhere else now
but that soulless e-commerce
juggernaut Boutique Thrive.
They're not so bad.
I mean, they're
committing to sustainable energy
and shipping, so...
Any dates?
No one? Nothing?
Well, I actually met
someone the other day.
You did? What does he look like?
Uh, he's tall with a beard,
likes red, always wears a hat.
Maybe he's balding.
Mm, I don't think so,
but his hair
is completely white.
How old is this gentleman?
Oh, elderly, in a timeless way.
Listen, Mira, we always said
that you could fall in love
with whomever you like but--
It was a Santa Crawl, Dad.
Very funny, ha ha!
Maybe a Santa Crawl isn't
the best place to meet someone.
There's more to life than work.
Yeah, so...
My app was
acquired by Boutique Thrive.
It wasn't my choice.
Well, what...
what does this mean for you?
I work for a soulless
juggernaut now,
I guess...
Or I could quit.
Hey, McCauleys don't quit!
All I wanted was to recreate
the same care and insight
that the local shopkeeper
would have like you guys did.
You know, promote the same
artists that we worked with.
But now Boutique Thrive
just swooped in.
Well, 'cause it's a great
idea, that's what they do.
They stomp on acquisitions
like a mindless child.
Times change and
our shop wasn't going to last.
Hey, maybe...
maybe you could, uh...
push for change on the inside.
You know, like a Trojan Horse
with good intentions.
- Yeah, we could help, too!
Yeah!
We could protest anything.
- Yeah, um...
- Your mom and I, we could...
we could chain
ourselves to whatever you want!
Like those trees!
Okay, yeah.
So I'm just
going to see how it goes first
and then I'll give you guys
a call... if I need you.
- Okay?
Okay.
All right. Rum and eggnog.
Okay, let's get
the party started!
- Woo!
- Yeah!
Thank you so much.
Ah.
What are you doing here?
Apparently you know as much as I do.
Good morning.
Hi. What are you doing here?
Good to see you too, Miranda.
Grant Boyd.
Boutique Thrive hired
me to oversee the process.
- Hey, how are you?
- Hi.
Hey.
- I'm really good.
Do you guys...
know each other?
Yeah, well, we...
well, we used to...
a long time ago, but it was--
Yeah, we worked at
a start-up together.
Ah, right.
Hey, sorry... what process?
Well, as you know,
your two companies
have been
acquired by Boutique Thrive.
But what you do not know
is that they have now merged.
That makes no sense.
Why would
Boutique Thrive want two apps?
They want to corner
all the gift recommendation
apps on the market.
But that's
combining apples with oranges.
- Mainstream and a bargain bin.
- Water and a gas fire.
Charm and you.
Okay, uh...
You know what?
You two are going to be working
together as partners.
That's a good one.
Yeah.
Improve the gift
recommendation accuracy
so that we can release
an update
to target last-minute shoppers.
We're fine, we don't need to--
Yeah, my app works fine.
No, no, your apps don't work.
Otherwise, I would not be
standing here in front of you.
Boutique Thrive wants
an increase by 20% in buys
for last-minute shoppers
and you two are going
to help us reach that target.
So can you double
the gift recommendation
accuracy in five days?
- Uh...
- Phew...
Okay, well, that is
why we are here, team.
You two work together, use
your expertise and your data.
Which data platform are
we using? Uh, both, for now.
Do that and you'll
retain your positions.
Oh, and we're gonna
be unveiling both versions
at Boutique Thrive's Christmas
party on the 23rd.
- Uh, okay.
- Any questions?
- Yeah, yeah-- -Okay, great!
I'm pumped.
You pumped?
Go get 'em! All right.
See you.
So, where did that adorable
name come from, Present Ninja?
Oh...
Wow, you're the gift that keeps
on giving,
aren't you?
I'm a giver.
What can I say?
So, you ready to
collaborate... partner?
Gonna be so much fun.
It's
a lack of data problem.
It's not just about shoppers'
trends --
it's understanding people.
Trust me, okay?
I have five start-ups under
my belt,
three e-commerce sites
and an Entrepreneur
of the Year Award.
Wow. So where's the trophy?
That's
not what I'm saying.
Hmm. Do you bring it with
you everywhere, show your mom?
I'm simply saying
that I have recognized
experience in this field.
Okay. Well, I actually
grew up in my family's shop.
So knowing customers and
suggesting the perfect gift
is in my blood.
Okay, so you're going to
personally figure out
each gift recommendation?
Mm hm. Oh, wow! It's...
beautiful.
And the Entrepreneur
of the Year goes to... Paul!
Yeah! Woo!
That's exactly how it went down.
Yeah. I'm sure. I'm sure it did.
Also know
his merger isn't my idea.
Well, we both
have that in common.
- Where's the data reports?
- Right there.
Hey.
Oh, have we met before?
I don't think so.
- I'm Miranda.
- Jackie.
Product manager
here. Wiser sister.
Hmm.
Okay, you said before
that finding the perfect gift
wasn't just
about business to you.
So what did you mean by that?
Everyone in tech talks about
disrupting,
but what about mending?
Hmm.
Elevating the quality of how
people
give and receive gifts.
That would
bring the world closer,
certainly the people I love closer.
So what now? Do
we start sharing?
Oh, do you... do
you want a T-shirt?
Huh? It's blue.
It's definitely your color.
This is going to
be a long December.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
- Here!
- Thank you.
Oh, so they hired Grant as
a consultant
to oversee the merger.
Grant. Uh huh.
Do they know that you two...?
Okay, but you're over him
so just make sure you look
fabulous, okay,
and leave this guy in your dust!
Yeah.
- You are over him, right?
- Yep.
Miranda, no!
It was just easier when
he wasn't around, you know?
I thought he was the one, Erika.
It's not just something
you toss away!
We were perfect...
until we were
a complete disaster.
Thank you! Thank you.
You haven't been able
to trust another guy since.
What about Mr. Claus
from the Crawl?
Oh, it was magical.
We talked about
Christmas, destiny...
female mustaches...
So how did you not
see his face...
or get his name?
We were being so cute
keeping the Mr. and Mrs. Claus
thing going, you know?
Hold on. Hold
this. Uh huh, continue.
I've just never felt
a connection so quickly before.
It was perfect, like everything
was supposed to happen.
Did you check
the Crawl's social media page?
Hm?
Okay! Okay, okay, okay.
"Looking for
Mrs. Claus. We met on the Crawl.
"Talked destiny and
danced. I have your glove!"
Do you think it's him?
I don't think it's a ransom
note for a glove, Miranda.
What's his profile pic?
Okay. Oh, it's empty!
- Fake.
- What does that mean?
It means he has
something to hide.
Okay, well, maybe
he's just being cautious.
Or maybe he's a criminal.
But you should
totally respond.
You literally just
called him a criminal.
Yeah, but what if he's
a really hot, charming criminal?
Make a fake profile,
too, if you're worried.
But this is a fun mystery.
You know, I didn't know I needed
this in my life.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad that my life is
entertaining you.
Really wonderful.
"Mr. Claus, thanks
for finding my glove.
"Sorry I left. Had to...
unexpectedly dash to
the North Pole for a friend.
"I had a magical evening..."
That was too
desperate. "I had a good time...
"Fun time."
Don't overthink this, Miranda.
So why
the fake profile?
Don't know yet if
you're on Santa's nice list.
How do I know you're not
really some 70-year-old man?
'Cause I'm the angel
that fell from the tree.
All right, buddy.
Play it safe.
"Why ruin the mystery just yet?"
So now what?
Let's pretend
that that night never ended.
So what do
you do for work, Santa?
What do you think I do?
I imagine
a clean-shaven predator
in a glass jungle fantasizing
of conquering the world
with an empty in-box.
Suppose so. I work in tech like
half the people in this city.
I imagine
you're the type of person
who organizes their books by
color and cries during movies.
I actually cry
during savvy commercials, too.
Also work in tech.
This is a very
important question.
Is it cheating if you watch
a TV show
without your significant other?
Definitely.
Mm hm...
If there was an Olympic
sport everyday activity,
what would you win?
Misplacing things.
I have a label maker.
Nerd.
What about you?
Accidentally killing indoor plants.
Well, I can help.
I've got lots of plants.
Plant dork?
is a hotdog a sandwich?
No.
Glad you have principles.
You have no principles.
Look, I had a single
mother and she could not afford
extravagant Christmas gifts, so
I want the gift recommendations
to be in reach of
single mothers like mine.
Accountability is my
principle, which you get
at scalability
with chain stores.
Okay, but
affordable junk is still junk!
We can do better
and support local businesses
at the same time!
Wait, why are we here?
I need a tree.
So you double-booked
our meeting.
I'm busy.
This is the only
free time that I had.
- You're incredible.
- Thank you!
- Dad!
- Hey!
Thanks for
dropping him off. Hey, buddy.
Hey, this is Miranda. She works
with your dad.
Miranda, this is my son Ryan.
- Hello, sir.
- Hi. You can call me Ryan.
Oh! Hi, Ryan.
I bet these trees
aren't even sustainably grown.
But we're gonna find
a perfect tree, aren't we?
Yes, we are! You know what?
I'm going to find
you the perfect gift.
Come with me.
Let's see... Ooh!
- What about this guy?
- Perfect!
- Thank you, Miranda.
- You're very welcome.
Dad, I want to pick a tree!
Yeah, go check.
We need boots on
the ground to figure out why
the algorithms are off.
What does that even mean?
What about this one? Whoa!
Well, it's
a little crooked, bud.
Yeah.
Okay, listen.
I found the perfect candidate.
Veronica S. Prolific,
online reviewer, shops local.
We understand her gift-buying
habits for her family,
we understand
half of our demographic.
Okay, so what?
We follow her like a safari.
You're finally catching
on, Entrepreneur of the Year.
This makes no sense.
Okay, well, it's time
that we try something different.
What about this one?
Wow! Yeah, it's a good
shape. This could be a winner!
Yeah. Color's off, not fresh.
Okay.
You want me to
help you pick a tree?
Yeah.
Okay, choose any one here,
show me which one you like.
This one.
Good choice.
Let's check the trunk,
see if it's sticky.
No, Ryan, don't...
Ew!
That means it's fresh! Okay,
now let's check the needles.
They shouldn't
snap. Hold the branch.
See how it doesn't come off?
- Fresh!
- You got it.
You're a tree-picking
expert now!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Veronica. Indulge me.
Okay. Got the tree, let's go.
Come on, Ry.
Uh, I'll just...
Don't worry about
me. I got it. Yeah.
- Hey.
- Hi!
Oh...
I just wanted to apologize
for the professional distance.
I didn't want to
show any favoritism.
- Wouldn't want to do that.
- Uh uh.
How's everything?
Good! Great, yeah.
You look really, really happy.
You're glowing.
Thank you.
So how are you? What's going on?
Oh, you know, saving the world
one start-up at a time.
No, no. In all
seriousness, I am phenomenal.
I love consulting,
coming in, helping businesses
with their acquisition
transitions.
Uh huh.
Look, I wanted to apologize
for the way
things ended between us.
You know, I really
hope things won't be weird!
Oh, no. That's like
years ago. I'm so over it, yeah.
Great! Whew! Yeah!
Okay.
Hello. Thank you, Mr. Claus!
I wanted to set aside
some time for update meetings.
Is this for me?
Yes, for you...
update meetings on the progress.
Just you and
I. What do you think?
- I-- -No, no, no.
I'm doing
the same thing with Paul.
Also, uh...
Truffle or pumpkin spice?
Look you don't
have to do all this.
You know, you deserve better,
plus they're from
your favorite spot.
You know my weakness. Oh!
And they're also
a work expense write-off.
So, how's working with Paul?
Um... we're going on a safari.
Yeah. I'm
excited. It's gonna be fun.
- Mm.
Okay.
So, Veronica,
how do you get inspired
for your Christmas Day shopping?
Okay, listen, are you guys
okay? You just seem tense.
Like you don't like each other.
What?!
I'm sorry.
I just don't want you
ruining my Christmas shopping vibe.
- No, we're cool.
- Yeah.
I so look forward
to hanging with Miranda.
Yeah, we're blessed. So fun!
Fine. Prove it.
Hm?
Excuse me, excuse
me. Comin' through.
♪ Jingle bells, jingle
bells Jingle all the way ♪
What are we doing?
Research!
♪ Jingle bells
Jingle all the way ♪
♪ Dashing through the snow
In a one-horse open sleigh ♪
Come on.
♪ O'er the fields
we go Laughing all the way ♪
♪ Bell on bobtails
ring Making spirits bright ♪
♪ What fun it is
to ride and sing ♪
♪ A sleighing song tonight
Christmas shopping!
You gotta feel the holiday
spirit to be inspired!
If you don't have
fun, your gift won't be fun.
♪ Jingle bells, jingle
bells Jingle all the way ♪
♪ Jingle all the way
Okay, let's do it!
I really hope you know what
you're doing
because we have
three days.
Veronica, wait up!
Veronica!
These are all yours?
Yes!
How do you pick Christmas
presents for your family?
Well, I walk as if I'm
in the receiver's shoes.
Like my cousins are into fashion
so I check which influencer's
they're following.
Knowing that,
I see what speaks to me here.
Got it.
Also makes me
feel closer to them.
Okay, my aunt loves sweets
so we'll hit up a chocolatier
and my uncle's into vintage
books and I know this guy who...
What... is that?
- What did we learn so far?
- A lot, actually.
Really?
Well, if you were observing
instead of grinching
maybe you would have noticed.
Is that a smile I see?
- Ooh...
- What are you doing?
Looking for the fun.
You're worse than Jackie.
Fine. You want
a full Christmas spirit?
Uh hm.
Let's go. The wild
life's getting away.
Oh!
Wow! One, two, three...
Why are you so
far apart? Closer.
Okay.
Ah! It's so cute. Aww.
- Hey!
- Hi!
So I'm double-booked
for a snowball fight meetup
0but I will try and
catch up for curling later?
Mm hm.
- Sounds good.
Let's see this on you.
Okay.
Hey, you look...
- Never mind!
- Yeah.
Curling?
Yeah.
Hey, listen, this has been
a lot of fun,
but what are
we doing here?
Veronica confirmed what I thought.
Which is...?
Okay, let me ask you a question.
What was the best
Christmas gift
you've ever received?
- A basketball.
- Why?
Because I knew money was
tight and I wanted something
that Jackie and
I could both play with.
- Okay, it brought
you closer together. -Yeah.
Mine was hockey skates.
I wanted to be a figure
skater
like Kristi Yamaguchi.
But playing hockey
with my dad was everything.
It brought us closer.
And I'm thankful for that.
The basketball is
your story, not demographics.
To fix the apps
we need to understand
our customer story better,
their values.
We need to really see them
just like how Veronica
steps into her loved ones' shoes
to be inspired.
So it's a data problem,
like I said days ago.
No, you're not listening to me.
It's how we interpret the data.
It's an intimacy
problem but with our users.
Okay, so I'll just book some
therapy sessions
for our apps then.
Listen,
I should be at the office
instead of
indulging in this field trip.
- I'm trying to save our apps.
- So am I!
Oh!
- Great, come here! -You're
really something tonight!
- Come here.
All right?
Ow!
Leave me alone, you grinch!
So, how's working
together?
Productive!
Paul?
We... we actually
learned a lot from Veronica so--
Sorry, did we?
What are you talking about?
I'm really wasting my valuable
time
listening to her pontificate
about hippy-dippy feelings
instead of getting it done.
- Okay--
- Hippy-dippy?
Well, if the app
doesn't work right
in the next two days Boutique
Thrive will shut you down
and re-appropriate
your intellectual property.
So get it done or go
home for Christmas with nothing.
Okay!
That went well.
I thought so.
How's the merger going?
Oh, the app is still off.
Then listen better.
We taught that at the shop.
Mom, it's getting the app
to understand users' values
through photos and posts.
No, it's about letting them
do the talking, Miranda. Listen.
Well, the app needs to
intuitively ask without asking.
Ah! You're the psychology major.
Oh, and I also have to work with
this arrogant CEO, Paul Dennis.
Comes with the territory.
What?! I'm a CEO, Dad.
But you're
kind of a new-age CEO.
- Is he... single?
- Mum.
Just curious. Love is love.
Is he... handsome?
Never give in to
the establishment.
- Taking it to 'em, Dad.
- That's my girl.
How did you find
out about this place?
This pudding!
A friend recommended it.
- I'm hungry...
- Uh uh.
Mm...
Come on.
"Dear Mr. Claus,
thank you for the tip.
"My parents loved the pudding.
"Your homework now is to send
me your favorite movie list.
"I'll send mine.
"I'm having trouble at work.
"Wondering if you have
any advice
"A difficult
co-worker won't compromise.
"What should I do?"
"Dear Mrs. Claus,
"managing people is, in fact,
my specialty.
"Get to know this person bette,
find out what they're after.
"See where you both
align and convince them
"of what you'll
bring to the table.
"I'm sure they'll soften."
Hey! What's
going on. Where's Ryan?
I got a babysitter.
So we can concentrate.
That's too bad.
I actually like spending
time with Ryan
more than you.
Do you want to grab food?
Absolutely.
I do need
your help on something else.
Okay, so you have no inkling
on what gift to get them?
Just recently met.
All right, well, what do
you love about this person?
She's a firecracker.
She'd run circles around you.
What makes her happy?
She's a dreamer.
Thank you.
A romantic. An idealist.
Hmm.
Mm, she likes gardening.
Should I get her a shovel?
What's her style?
I... I don't know.
I respect her privacy.
That's okay.
I don't need to know.
It's... it's a little
more complicated than that.
See, if you offered me
more details
I could probably
recommend an actual item.
But from the way
you smile about her
I think you need to get
her a romantically clever gift.
You're right.
Anyone else
you need to get gifts for?
Relatives, anyone?
See, you just need to
turn me into the algorithm
then we're gonna be fine.
How big are you?
'Cause could
you fit into this phone?
♪ We wish
you a Merry Christmas ♪
You know, I think
Santa is calling us.
Should we?
Hmm.
♪ And a Happy New Year
♪ ...Merry Christmas
♪ We wish
you a Merry Christmas ♪
♪ And a Happy New Year
♪ We wish
you a Merry Christmas ♪
♪ And a Happy New Year
So why'd
you start Giftverse?
Well, my parents
ran a shop for years --
stationery, gifts,
art supplies, all locally made
until chain stores
put them out of business.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
He's really good.
[Miranda[ I know that era's
over, but why can't my app
connect people
to those same artists
just like my parents did?
You know, if
small sellers united
they'd be bigger than chain
stores
and drive down costs too.
Passion doesn't come
from an assembly line.
And it's not just
knowing what customers want,
it's knowing how to
find those unique suggestions.
You know, quality and cheap
shouldn't be mutually exclusive.
That's all, just saying.
I'm just trying
to be the equalizer.
What about you, though?
How did you come up
with that name, Present Ninja?
Ryan.
Him sneaking around like a Ninja
trying to find
his Christmas presents.
Oh, I feel so bad.
I'm so sorry that I said that.
Yeah!
You should feel terrible,
judging before you know.
So where's his mom?
Yeah, she, uh...
lives across the country.
I got custody.
We got married
when we were too young.
A couple of years ago
she got him
a hockey stick for Christmas
and he doesn't even play hockey.
And he was really confused
why she would get him a gift
like that.
So after that I thought
I should create an app
that would improve gift giving.
You know, elevate
the quality of gifts,
you know, to match the level
of love we feel for each other.
I think everyone could use that.
That's really sweet.
Hey, you should look
at our algorithm parameters.
Maybe you could give your gift
insight to help rematch them.
You have access to our data.
Sounds good. Thank you.
No problem. Hey,
do you recognize that one?
Frosty? Yes.
Okay, that's who I thought it
was. It looked familiar, right?
It's Frosty. Frosty the Snowman.
Oh.
Sorry.
- What's going on?
Oh, nothing.
You wanna get out of here?
And go where?
We can walk and work.
Grant!
Come on. You're always
go, go, go.
So, let's go.
I'll grant you some Grant time.
You're still
using that line, hm?
It worked on you, didn't it?
Yeah, unfortunately it did.
So, I need
your help buying a gift.
Oh! For who?
For my girlfriend, Kelly.
Hm.
Can you do
your gift genius thing?
Yeah! What do
you love about her?
Her energy! I mean,
we feed off of each other.
She's a personal trainer.
Hm.
Why are you giving me that look?
I'm not giving you a look.
- Uh...
No look here.
No? I don't know.
I mean, she's not
into tech or fine dining,
but, you know, she's trying.
There's not a lot of
three-star vegan restaurants.
But we do a lot of
outdoor stuff, skiing.
She calms me,
she laughs at my jokes.
Well, what does
she love about you?
- All of me.
Yeah, nothing in there.
So what is
it that makes her happy?
Challenging herself.
Hm.
And what's
your favorite memory of her?
Uh...
Snowed in at
the chalet on New Years'.
You took her to the chalet?
No I'm...
The day she said, "I'm yours."
- Grant, I don't...
- You know? Forget it.
I already have
something in mind.
Why don't we hit up Sombrillo's
for a bite?
You always liked
it there.
- Yeah.
- Let's do it.
So Grant
has a girlfriend.
She's a personal trainer.
She is... vegan.
Sorry.
Oh my gawd, he's such a foodie.
What do they do together?
I don't know. He seems happy.
See? This is great news.
He's moved on and so should you.
Yeah.
So we're really
gonna go meet Mr. Claus?
Yes! Come on,
Miranda, this is so exciting!
This is like
a game show prize reveal.
Behind door
number one is Mr. Claus!
Or... like in a movie where
a spy just rips off his mask.
What if he doesn't
live up to my expectations.
- What if he does?
- What if I don't?
Look, we have a lot
of fun just chatting.
You don't need a pen pal.
That's true...
and he has my glove.
Okay, so we're
really going to do this.
We're gonna go meet him.
Okay, so if she's... she's
crazy or weird,
I need you to intervene.
Okay, what's the signal?
Uh... oh,
I'll scratch my head.
Okay, yeah,
that doesn't look weird at all.
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me.
Ugh!
Grab it, grab it, grab it.
But it's wet!
Hey!
- Hi.
Why are you here?
Ahh...
We... we were here first.
Why are you here?
We always come here.
How come I've
never seen you here?
How come I've never seen you?
Do you always answer
a question with a question?
- Do I?
- Okay. Hi, I'm Erika.
Hi... Jackie.
This is Present Ninja Paul,
the one I was telling you about?
Oh, yeah. Right!
So what are you two up to?
Um, uh...
Oh, well, he is
looking for--
Looking for what?
- Well, um... women.
- What?
Just... women.
- Women.
Plural.
Women.
Well, you found them.
Okay, this has been fun.
So fun.
We're gonna go,
though.
Erika? Let's go.
Yeah, Jackie.
Bye.
This is gonna be so
awkward with her here.
Watch, he's probably gonna
ruin my night... just watch.
No guy with
a glove. She's cute, right?
So did you know that Christmas
pudding
was originally a meat soup?
I don't see
anyone here with a glove.
Okay, hold on, all right?
No guy with a glove.
Maybe he's running late?
Yeah, yeah, it's only
been a... couple of hours.
Yeah, he stood
me up. Yeah, mm hm.
She stood you up, dude.
I'm gonna go talk to her friend.
You're gonna ditch me?
Yeah!
Hi.
Hi!
- Hey!
- Hi!
Mm hm. Okay...
Itchy?
Uh uh.
So after
the app works, then what?
- Oohh!
- Yes!
- Sorry.
- What do you mean?
What, you don't have
like side hobbies or a passion?
Giftverse is my passion.
What's yours?
- I want to find a house.
- Then buy one.
Nah, it's... like the challenge
of a start-up is addictive.
But most of those businesses,
they don't do anything
meaningful.
And I get bored and I jump ship.
I wanna find something that...
that lasts.
I want to
create non-profit apps.
Like what?
Like an app that connects woman
programmers
to female mentors.
Or even an app that shows you
where the best Christmas
lights are in the neighborhood.
You know,
Ryan... Ryan would love that.
Have you started any?
Oh! Honestly,
I haven't had the time.
Ahh, just do it!
Like that... see that?
That.
I jump ship all
the time, you just gotta jump.
I'll help you.
See where you wanna throw?
- I got this.
- Visualize it.
I haven't got one in yet.
Feel it?
Mm hm.
Fire.
Woo!
Got it!
I wasn't expecting that.
Come on,
we're gonna go
look at the Christmas lights.
Wanna go... see the lights?
Your head still
itchy or you good to go?
Really? You're
gonna bring that up again?
Unbelievable. Unbelievable!
Too funny.
So what do
you want for Christmas?
Just for Ryan to be happy.
- Oh!
Her!
- I dare you!
- No, I dare you!
One, two, three...
Gotcha!
Okay, well, I better go.
We've got that presentation
tomorrow so...
- Yeah, yeah.
- We gotta get to it, right?
Erika? We gotta go.
- What?
- Come on.
Oh, okay. Uh, I'll call you.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye!
- Yeah, I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye!
All right!
Come on, Jackie.
Jackie and
Camilla have finished
merging your data with ours.
Great.
I think it's pinpointing
a person's style and hobbies
much better.
Thanks to you.
Whoa. Okay, I'm
gonna write that one down.
That was what...
sorry, December 19th.
Miranda actually thanks me?
Stop.
I'll just stick
that right there.
I'm just gonna
stick that right there.
Why isn't this working?
Let me see.
There's one last trick
that I know. Just gotta...
No! Don't do that!
Just needed
a little manly touch.
Caveman touch.
Well, I think Grant will
be pleased with the progress.
You guys have a thing...?
Had a thing?
Oh, I'm sure he'll be impartial.
Um?
I have a system!
Uh huh. What's
that, utter chaos?
This looks... a little
wasteful.
I thought you were
a tree-hugger.
I recycle.
Mm... okay.
I'm helping you.
- You've got to live
a little, Paul. -No, no.
Here, have a cookie.
Oh, thanks.
Ah!
Thank you.
How good are they?
These are horrible.
Just horrible.
Okay. I gotta
head back to the office.
What are you drawing there?
We're picking
a Christmas tree in the forest.
I'm an expert.
Oh, yeah?
Does your dad wear
a suit
to the forest?
He always wears a suit.
Hmm, maybe he works too much.
You were leaving?
Yes, um...
So, you know, if
the presentation goes well
they're gonna have to name
someone in charge eventually.
Yeah.
I've been coordinating
with Boutique Thrive's
tech department
and they've
been hinting for us
to nudge the gift
recommendations
towards their merchant partners.
Favor their products?
In an un-biased,
uh, very biased way, yes.
So they're seeing if
we're team players over Miranda?
I like her.
She's cool, little man.
Go and do it.
Yes.
Bam, bam,
bam! Slam, slam, slam!
Boom!
What, it's my thing?
See ya later.
- Bye!
- Bye.
Don't start this.
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
Okay, okay!
Surrender, surrender.
I have to go to work. You have
to go to the babysitter.
Come on, come on. Come on, oh!
Sheryl, I know
you care about vegan leather,
ethical treatment of animals...
Yes!
What does it say?
Oh!
That accuracy
rate is not acceptable.
We've seen enough.
Grant, wait. Just
give us some more time.
I've been working
on Giftverse for years.
Just to be shut
down over one test?
You guys didn't
double the accuracy.
This debacle could hurt
sales more than help them.
Give us the weekend.
Please. Sheryl, you owe me.
Let's give hem the weekend.
Monday morning...
but build off of
Present Ninja's version.
What? Why?
It uses the data better.
Pillage whatever
you need from Giftverse.
You're in charge.
Miranda, I'm sorry.
- We'll talk.
- Yeah.
Let's talk!
What's the plan?
I'm shut down.
This is our app, together.
You don't need me.
Boutique Thrive doesn't care
about the right gift,
just percentages and sales.
I care!
Look, I'm naive to think
that I could change anything
from the inside.
I'm just going to be
a part of the problem.
We determine the app, not them.
A working app is too valuable
for them to tinker with.
We'll promote the artists
and sellers you want,
alongside affordable, mixed in.
Mixed in?
Calm your righteousness,
okay? This is a victory.
Why would you do that?
You know, I would
hate to see the world
miss out on
another pair of ice skates.
I'm doing this for Ryan.
I need to do this right.
I need you.
Can I trust you?
That we're not just going
to be helping the same type of
business practices
that shut down my family's shop?
I know how much
this app means to you.
Okay, let's, uh...
let's go do something fun.
Yeah. I have an idea.
Yes! Perfect.
Cool! Up you go!
Yay! Woo!
This was a really good idea.
Okay, one final little touch.
- Nice!
- Yay!
Dad, I wanna play.
Yeah, go play, go play!
So what's your favorite
Christmas tradition?
When my brother and I were
little, my parents used to hide
our Christmas gifts.
But like really,
really hide our Christmas gifts.
One year my present was
in the back of the freezer.
My mom and uncle
did the same thing.
Really?
Yeah, they made it special
even though
we didn't have a lot.
Aww...
Looks amazing.
Keep going.
Jackie was super competitive.
They would hide scrap pieces of
paper
with little riddles
as clues.
We got a gift treasure map.
How far did they make you go?
Up a tree.
A park,
a mile away. No joke.
Okay, more hair?
Hair!
One little final touch.
He looks like shocked!
Oh, it's a he?
Yeah.
Are you just
gonna leave your scarf?
Oh, he seems cold.
He... is a snowman.
Well, I knitted it so
I could just make another one.
May be we tilt gift
recommendations
towards family activities.
- Home.
Maybe we need to
go back to my roots.
Yeah. How good are
you with defending yourself
from people with
strong opinions, hm?
I can charm anyone.
Yeah, we'll see.
Look what I made!
Okay, Ry, woo!
Ry! Ryan, yes.
Weee!
- You're fun, Miranda.
Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay!
Hey, buddy! Hey, hey, hey.
Miranda's family might be
a little strange,
so just be polite, okay?
I'm always polite, Dad.
Are you polite?
Yes, you are.
Okay, come on.
Hello?
Well... hello there!
You must be the oppressor.
- Hi.
- Hello, how are you?
Good, how are you?
I'm very well, thank you.
Well, hello!
Hello!
Paul Dennis.
Miranda's told me all
about you guys
and your shop.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Judy, this is
Michael, come in.
We're so glad to have you.
Come on in, guys.
We've got lots of food.
I hope you're hungry.
Miranda!
Hi!
This is for you.
What is this?
I didn't use the app,
if that's what you're asking.
It's an organizer!
You're not supposed to tell.
Sorry.
It's a padfolio for your bag.
Thank you. It's very sweet.
Trying to buy her off?
Park the crusade, Michael.
So, Paul, how many
people have you laid off today?
Okay, why don't we eat?
- Good idea.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm starving.
Yum, yum, yum.
This looks good.
Uh huh! Dig in.
Wow! This
looks really amazing.
Well, Christmas
dinner is our specialty
and we expect
it all to be eaten.
Oh!
Good.
So, you guys,
you do this every week?
Uh huh.
It's like a chef's challenge.
We pick produce from
the local farmer's market
and then we have to
come up with dishes.
And I eat.
You poor thing, how do you cope?
Well, they get to eat
whatever and look great
and then I have to
bike it off the next day.
I bike too!
No way!
That's so cool, where do you go?
My mainstay is the loop
down by the marina.
I used to do that.
You bike?
Yeah, yeah.
You been up to Baldwin Hill?
Of course!
They finally repaved
it so the asphalt's grippy.
- No way.
- Yeah.
Well, you're
not what I expected.
Neither are you.
So, um... gift-giving?
Yes, as you know,
it's all about knowing
the recipient,
their story.
Well, the relationship
with the giver.
I mean, you guys are
basically matchmakers.
You're essentially
doing a dating app, in a way.
You guys are doing a dating app.
Yeah, gift giving is love.
It's giving a love of someone,
of a hobby, of a memory--
Lots of lovin', Dad. We get it.
You have to pay attention.
People want to feel heard.
Feel seen by
the gifts they receive.
Well, sure.
We used to ask people questions
when they came in the shop
and we got to know them.
Won't be fully automated.
Maybe you can't automate
what has to come from the heart.
Like a questionnaire,
the answers are the story.
Mm hm.
For example, what do
you love about the person
or what do they love about you?
Yeah. Favorite memory of them.
Listen to your heart speak.
Instead of sizing someone up.
Hm.
So who wants
s'mores for dessert?
Yes!
Ryan and I got this.
- Oh ho!
High five! Let's go.
Okay.
Oh, I'm stuffed.
So, Judy, what would
you like for Christmas?
Oh, I don't need anything.
Ahh, okay.
You're that family member
who nobody knows what to get.
What if you had
to choose a gift?
Well, I have
everything I need...
but I guess it would have
be something that fed that need.
Something that brought you together more?
Uh huh.
They're having so
much fun over there.
I'm missing all
the fun with Ryan.
- Go, go, go.
- Okay.
My parents love
doting over Ryan.
Yeah, well, do not let
him trick you. He is demanding.
Okay, I'll be on guard.
This is perfect.
Yeah, it is.
Do you have a charger?
Yeah, in my
office. Just over there.
I got you! And you too!
Hey, I'm gonna
join the festivities!
Let's go!
Oh!
I'm so sorry!
Who's team are you on?
We traditions here.
We have our marshmallow
fight before s'mores
and Ryan here seems deadly.
- You're on our team.
- Yes!
- Let's go!
- Wha...?
He's the family!
Hey! You're my son!
- Yeah!
Um...
Ah, that was fun. Thank you.
What do you say?
Thank you.
Aw, it was my pleasure.
So we'll implement
those questions into the app?
Yeah, the five --
What do you love
about this person?
What do they love about you?
Favorite memory of them?
Uh, what makes them
happy? And their style.
Exactly.
Merry Christmas.
Will you come back and visit us?
Oh, yeah.
- Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
You too?
Bye, Ry.
Bye.
See ya!
- Well, he's not the worst.
It was a great night.
"Dear Ms. Claus,
"I don't know why
you didn't show up that night.
"Hoping you weren't
just a fairy tale.
"Hope to hear from you."
He was there.
What's Grant doing here?
Hey.
Hey. Sorry to drop in like this.
Oh, okay. We're sitting.
Yes. I wanted to apologize.
I had to put Paul in charge.
Yeah, I understand.
No. Boutique Thrive wanted me to
push the Present Ninja
platform, too.
It was already decided.
Why?
Paul is a... team player.
Oh.
But if you can get
the app to work
that's a big cash-out.
Grant, I'm not
doing this for the money.
You could start
another app with that payout.
Or you could join me.
Really, work for you?
Yeah, come work for me.
It'll be fun.
You've got to start
thinking about your next gig.
- Engine slows for no one.
- Hmm...
It's an open offer.
I thought
the engine slows for no one.
For you I'd wait.
That doesn't sound like you.
Look, uh, I want you back.
You have a girlfriend.
I want you.
I made the biggest mistake of my
life messing things up with you.
Well, what about Kelly?
You and I, we really
suit each other. You know that.
Yeah, I don't know
how I'm supposed to feel
about this right now.
You don't have to say anything.
Just know
that I am here for you.
Yeah.
Well... you know what I think?
I think that...
you should go
home to your girlfriend.
Okay.
So...
We can forget
this ever happened.
Okay. I'll see you Monday?
- Yeah.
- Good luck!
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Hello?
I've got to talk to you.
I messaged Mrs. Claus again.
What, why?
Well, there has to be a good
reason why she disappeared.
What about Miranda?
What about?
Um... you seem to really
enjoy spending time together?
We're working.
Oh, yeah, you're
just working. Okay.
I can't have
her getting attached to Ryan.
And if I never meet Mrs. Claus
again I'll never know.
She didn't show up. Miranda has.
But... hey,
she's too good for you.
Listen,
I don't think we're gonna get
this new app build
done in time
with all these
new questions added.
It's a complete
overhaul, okay, in two days.
How do we solve this?
Well, we could full-on
push Boutique Thrive's products.
They've hinted that the accuracy
won't matter then.
And plus it buys us a little
more time
until after the holidays.
But I know
that you promised Miranda.
So I don't think we should--
Do it.
Just for now.
Alright, we'll
change it back later.
I'm not going to wase
two years over sentimentality.
Okay.
Thanks, Jacks.
So Grant wants me back.
Hmm.
I thought he had
a vegan girlfriend.
Maybe he finally
wants to settle down.
Maybe he's changed.
Oh!
That sounds really
bad out loud. Really bad.
Okay. Well, have
we heard back from Mr. Claus?
Yeah, he messaged me
saying he was there that night.
There was no guy with a glove.
I checked everywhere, Miranda.
Okay, well,
maybe he's lying too.
Maybe he's a hot criminal
like you said.
I don't know.
I just actually
don't know anything anymore.
What about Paul?
Are we just going
down a list of names?
No! He seems cool!
And you guys had
a lot of fun that night
and why have you been
acting so cheery lately?
You're just saying this
because now you're dating Jackie
and you want to do
a double-date wine tasting.
- No!
- Oh, yeah.
Okay, maybe once in a while.
I don't trust him.
You haven't trusted
any guy since Grant, Miranda.
I think it's time to
take a leap of faith, you know?
Maybe you're right... again.
Okay, you got the chocolates?
- Uh huh.
- Let's go.
You guys actually did it!
Woo!
- 86% accuracy.
- Woo!
Well, Miranda did it.
Their team did all the legwork.
Uh, yeah we did.
Bam, bam, bam! Slam, slam, slam!
Jacks, no.
You're awesome.
Ah, I love this energy.
I will let Boutique Thrive
know the great news.
Get this live immediately
and I will see
you all at the Christmas party.
Alright? Huh?
Ah, we'll party.
For you, Mom and Dad.
Hey!
- Hi!
We did it.
Yeah, we did.
Paul, where'd you go?
Come on.
See you tonight?
Uh huh.
Storm's coming
in. It'll be cold.
It's a short walk.
Hang tight.
"Dear Mr. Claus,
I was at the bar that night.
"I waited for
you. Where were you?"
Hey. That's better.
Thank you.
I'll see you tonight.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Okay.
- Bye.
- Good...
Miranda!
Ah!
Larry Sosa.
Boutique Thrive CEO.
Wow, it's so nice to
finally meet you, sir.
Now do you have, um... a moment?
Yes, of course.
Paul said that you solved
the algorithm issue.
An expertise
from our background.
You know, Paul changed the
algorithm to push our product
so he would get
into my good graces.
He did what?
But he didn't have to
because you figured it out.
I need people
who know what they're doing
to take this
app into the future.
Not a 'yes' man.
I want you to be in
charge of the app going forward.
What about
favoring your products?
Oh come on,
come on, come on, come on!
Gotta be a team player, too.
Shouldn't we be
pushing the best gift possible?
We have the opportunity here
to promote independent
businesses and artists.
Boutique Thrive is still
gonna get a cut from the app.
I know this is personal to you.
Can I keep
the app unbiased, Larry?
No.
Think it over
and, um... we'll talk.
Miranda? Kelly!
Grant's girlfriend.
Hi.
Listen, I want to thank you.
Oh. Thank me?
I was freaking out
when I heard
Grant was working with you.
But he's
suddenly been opening up,
showing me this
sensitive, caring side.
He's been a changed
man the last two weeks.
Has he?
I don't know what
you said to him,
but thank you.
Well, I...
Nothing.
I guess Grant realized
how much he's truly yours.
I'm really happy for you guys.
Hey,
what are you two chatting about?
Just how silly you are.
I'm funny?
He's so funny!
I'm going to get vegan
eggnog. You guys want anything?
I'm fine, thank you.
You owe me like
a bajillion cupcakes.
- Miranda!
- Don't worry about it.
I made a mistake.
Seeing you again,
all these
emotions came rushing back.
Me too.
But then I realized
that they're just
memories.
Like a photo album
that just
keeps all the good stuff.
Well, I'm sorry, again.
She's head over heels for you.
I know.
Be worthy of that.
I will.
- Okay, good.
- Okay,
Merry Christmas, Grant.
Merry Christmas, Miranda.
You look stunning!
You promised me.
You said you wouldn't
push Boutique Thrive's products
over the right gift.
I was making sure
that we didn't get shut down.
You used me.
We can change it back.
That's not the point.
Here I am helping
the same profiteers
that shut down my family's shop.
It's business.
Get off your high horse.
You're ruthless.
I am not some corrupt person
that you have in your mind.
No, you're worse.
You've tainted my dream
and now I've let my family down
because of you.
Listen to me, okay?
It was just the backup plan,
and we will change it back.
Not according to Larry.
You need to start trusting your
feelings and not your doubts.
You're right. I should
have trusted my instincts.
You've lived up to
my expectations, Paul.
So have you.
Oh, they offered
me your position.
Well, you deserve it.
I'm quitting anyways.
I don't want it.
I'm not willing to
betray everything I stand for.
Then make it what you stand for.
Your jacket's in coat check.
You know, you can step down
and act all high and mighty
about this
or you can fight for it.
Like I said, it's business.
Merry Christmas, Miranda.
I accept.
Well, I'm happy to hear that.
Let me introduce you.
Welcome, everyone, to Boutique
Thrive's Annual Holiday Party!
We have much to
celebrate and be thankful for.
Including the integration
of Present Ninja and Giftverse
into Boutique Thrive Family!
Now before I get
into my little speech here,
I want to introduce the person
who's going to be leading
the gift recommendation apps
into the future.
Miranda McCauley!
Thank you, Larry.
- Merry Christmas, everyone.
Merry Christmas!
I'm humbled by this opportunity.
But, most importantly,
I'm humbled by Boutique Thrive's
commitment
to the Christmas spirit.
I am pleased to announce
the Best Gift Initiative...
Boutique Thrive's commitment
to suggesting the perfect gift,
no matter the seller...
and to provide
users balanced options
that promote local businesses
and independent artists
alongside Boutique Thrive's
always affordable
merchandise!
Woo!
What are you doing?
All thanks to
the vision of Larry here!
Those are my terms.
We all know
that gift giving is about love.
But I've learned
that it's more than just that.
It's about trusting and opening
up our lives to one another.
Thank you. Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Wow, what a speech!
Thank you, Miranda.
Wow!
Hey! Here's
an article in Italian!
Look at that!
Your dad's been
saving all the online articles
on your initiative speech.
He keeps finding
new ones for his archive.
Yeah, well... she did what
we could never do with our shop.
You won.
Thank you.
And we're still
available if you need to boycott
or protest in the buff.
Oh, yeah.
I got it, Dad.
How about Paul?
What about him?
He's got a good arm
for marshmallow fights.
Ow!
Well, he... he let me down.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Anyway. Stuff
your face for me, Dad!
If I must.
Come on.
So how are things with Jackie?
Well, if you must know,
we're going on a Christmas Eve
Santa Crawl
tonight if you want to join?
Definitely not.
Okay.
- Milk?
- Yes.
Don't ask.
I wasn't.
- Sugar?
- Yes.
But really, come on, Miranda!
He lied to me, Erika.
He promised me.
He was fighting for you,
just not in the way you wanted.
People surprise you, Miranda.
You just need to let them.
And you had feelings
for the guy, too --twice!
Right?
Hey, Mom.
Did you send me a gift
or something,
or did Aunt Kathy?
Well, I got a present
in the mail
but there's no tag.
The return address
says "The North Pole."
Yeah, okay, I'll see you at 7.
"The app suggested a cake
tester to use with your mom."
What?
"The app suggested bolt
cutters to use with your dad."
What?
Okay, that's
a nine. What's this one?
Ten.
A ten? That can't be a ten.
What about this one?
Ten!
- Ten.
- That's also a ten?
This one?
Ten.
Another ten.
Wow! Okay,
this is a good street.
Merry Christmas, Dad.
Merry Christmas.
Did you tell Santa
what you wanted for Christmas?
I did. But I already got you.
I'm not a present.
Miranda!
Hi!
Part of me
always knew it was you.
You did?
What's meant to be will be.
I thought
you didn't believe in destiny.
I don't.
I believe in you.
Well, I found this
in your jacket pocket.
And I got your gift.
Did you use the app on me?
Nah, the skates were all me.
Romantically clever.
I realized that it's
best to listen to the heart.
Can I make snow angels, Dad?
Yeah, sure, bud.
Hey, look, I'm sorry
that I changed the app
without asking you.
You were right.
I should have stepped up
instead of stepping out.
And my publicity
stunt forced their hand.
I got full control,
at least for awhile.
Well, it's enough time
to prove to them your ideas.
I'm sorry I didn't trust you.
I just... I was so
worried about what might happen
I didn't even
consider what could be.
Hey, I need help
finding a Christmas gift.
Five questions, that's all I need.
What do you love
about this person?
She's witty, she's charming...
she always pushes me.
What does she love about you?
My stubbornness.
Are sure?
It's mutual.
What makes her happy?
Making others happy.
What's her style?
What I'm missing.
Favorite memory of her?
The next one.
What does she want?
To jump.
Me too.
♪ It had to be you
♪ It had to be me
♪ There had to be
Christmas lights on the tree ♪
That was my Christmas wish.
Let's go make snow angels!
- Come on, Ry!
- Woo!
♪ It had to be you