(dramatic orchestral music)
(fireworks exploding)
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
(whooshing)
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
(soft tinkling)
(wind whistling)
(whooshing)
(dramatic music)
(typing)
(flag fluttering)
(quirky dramatic music)
- Ooh!
- Oh!
(grunting)
(clowns laughing)
- All right, this is a stick up.
Stick 'em up!
Hands up, hands up.
Everyone, everyone, all of you.
Now...
Where's the stash?
- Uh...
- Gooey Chewies.
The Gooey Chewy bars!
(cashier grunts)
Thanks.
How do you do? (laughs)
(quirky, dramatic music)
(shoes honking)
(Wing Nut chuckling)
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, shh, shh, shh. It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
(door bell chimes)
(grunts)
(toy gun cocks)
Don't make me use this.
- Don't make me laugh.
- Funny you should mention that.
Feelin' lucky?
Punk!
(whooshing)
(bubbling)
(man laughs)
Huh?
(Wing Nut grunts)
(toy gun cocks)
Ah!
(whooshing)
(upbeat, percussive music)
(man laughing)
Who's next?
(cashier laughs)
(woman laughs)
(upbeat, percussive music)
(laughing)
(tires squeal)
(birds chirping)
(soft, tense music)
- Wherever evil lurks,
wherever it may hide,
it is time to unmask it and
reveal truth to the world.
It is time to right the world's wrongs
and fight injustice wherever it may lie.
To help the...
- Cut!
Cut.
- Adding Super Leaf to the shot.
Gotta get the leaf in the shot.
Sweet.
- IQ.
- This is not a film
on the supernatural properties of a leaf.
It has no business
being in my masterpiece.
- Hang in there, captain!
Super leaf comes in for the rescue.
(Bernie blows)
Now evil will rule the world.
(frenzied, upbeat percussive music)
(clown laughs)
- Hey!
Hey!
(whooshing)
(man laughs)
Ah, he took your candy bar. (laughs)
- Cool.
(laughing)
Woo hoo hoo hoo.
(clowns grunting)
Oh, watch the road, will ya?
- Watch the road, right.
(tense music)
- Hey losers.
- Here we go again.
- What are you scrubs up to no?
- We're making a cool movie
and Bernie plays as Gonzo superhero-
- Stop talking, what are you-
- Who's gonna save the world
as we know it, and the
bad guys, the bad guys...
Hey, you want to be the bad guys?
- Do I wanna-
- Anyway, these bad guys,
they try to destroy everything-
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Shut your trap.
- Shutting trap now.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Oh hey, a movie with a girl director.
What is this thing?
- Russell.
(Russell laughs)
- A viewfinder.
- Wow.
- That's enough.
- Yeah?
What are you going to
do about it, Super uh...
Wimp.
Yeah. (chuckles)
Super Wimp. (laughs)
Check it out, man.
I'm Steven spell, um, no it's stall...
Stool.
Spatula.
Gah!
Who am I?
- [Girl] Hang on.
- Give it back to her.
- And what are you going to do if I don't?
(tense music)
- Sick him, Splat! Get him boy!
(Bernie grunts)
(viewfinder shatters)
(Russell laughs)
- And cut.
Now that is what I call entertainment.
Oh.
- [Lens Cap] My viewfinder.
- Aww, now look what you made me do.
- [Lens Cap] Aww.
- Oh, well. That's showbiz.
(Splat barks)
(Russell laughs)
Oh! Hey, hey, hey!
(laughing)
Little mutt!
You're all lame-os.
(Splat growls)
Stay away. (clears throat)
We're out of here.
So...
- Spielberg.
It's Steven Spielberg.
- I should have stopped him.
- It's not your fault.
Your eye. What happened to your eye?
- Some super hero.
Can't even protect my friends.
(tires squealing)
(horn honks)
(tires skidding)
- Hey, mister! You dropped your...
Mister!
- Splat, no.
Splat, no boy.
You know how gassy you get.
- Ooh, Gooey Chewy bars.
- There's only three left.
- Cheers.
- To the lame-os.
- Yeah.
Lame-os.
(Splat farts)
- Oh!
- Ah!
- [Bernie] How many of
those did you eat? Geez.
(shoes honking)
(tense music)
(Wing Nut grunts)
- Let me get this straight.
You let the factory ship my special batch
of Gooey Chewies to the wrong addresses?
- We got 'em back, sir.
About one box.
- One box?
One bar will make a person
immune to my laughter generator.
Who's responsible?
(quirky music)
Well?
Well, who was driving?
(clown whistling)
(phone buzzing)
- For whom doth the bell toll?
- Yell-oh?
- It's tolls for thee.
(laughing)
(tense, dramatic music)
- Oh?
(gasping)
(funky music)
(honking)
(sighs)
(grand orchestral music)
He died doing what he loved.
- Wing Nut.
- Sir?
- We had trackers on each
of these boxes, did we not?
- Yes we did, sir.
- Then find it.
- What if someone's already eaten one?
- Then find him and bring him here.
- Okay.
- But do it quietly,
so we don't attract the attention
of The World Intelligence Team.
- Right.
- Oh, and Wing Nut?
- Hm?
- Do it now!
- On my way. (chuckles)
- Excitement continues to rise.
Every country around the
world will be watching
in eager expectation regarding
this unprecedented event where
the queen and the president
and other top world leaders
will soon be in Paris,
signing a treaty to once and
for all usher in world peace.
- The United Kingdom looks upon
this auspicious event with
the greatest anticipation.
Nowhere in the history of mankind
has such a possibility...
(Splat grunts)
Presented itself and it is in both honor
and humility that I shall...
- So, um, how do you like the meatloaf?
- Meatloaf...
I was wondering.
- It's not as good as what mom made.
(soft, melancholy music)
You still miss her?
(Bernie sighs)
Yeah, me too.
Hey, I heard a good joke at work today.
What did the sea monsters eat for lunch?
- Not tonight, dad.
- Come on, you like my jokes.
I mean they're a little corny, but-
- Yeah.
(soft, melancholy music)
- All right. What's up kiddo?
- Don't you ever, you know,
get tired of being a nobody?
- Um...
- No, no, I don't mean you.
Look, I know we need the extra money
and I get that schools
need custodial engineers.
- You mean janitors.
(Bernie sighs)
It's okay, we all have value.
- Yeah, right.
Like being some jerk's punching bag.
- Okay. So that's what
this is all about, right?
- I tried helping someone and messed up.
Just like always.
Talk about a loser.
- Hey, you're not a loser for messing up.
You have one of the biggest
hearts of anyone I've ever met.
- Right.
- You do.
And you...
You got that from your mother.
Come on, I see how you
look out for your friends.
- The lame-os.
Yeah. I'm real good at that.
- Lens Cap and IQ, they're
not lame-os, they're...
Okay, they're little
weird, but they have value.
We all do.
I know what'll cheer you up.
I have a surprise.
I want you to close your
eyes and don't peek.
All right?
(Bernie sighs)
And...
Voila.
- What is this?
- It's your dessert.
That is angel food cake.
Bam.
(laughs)
Okay, it's a little, it's
a little over cooked.
(pinging)
Okay. You know what?
You made your point.
(grumbles)
- Why don't you go upstairs,
start your homework
and I'll, uh, and I'll
bring some ice cream.
- Eh, you know, I think I'm good.
- I can't burn the ice cream.
- Hmm.
Go.
Fish and ships.
- What?
- What the sea monsters
ate, fish and ships.
(snorts)
You know...
Bern?
(Bernie sighs)
Everyone has value, son.
God, he doesn't make junk.
(soft music)
(sighs)
(water running)
(brushing)
(upbeat rock music)
- Give it back to her.
Give it back to her.
Am I speaking clearly?
You talkin' to me?
Boom.
Want another kick? Boom.
You talkin' to me?
There is no one behind me,
so you're talking to me
and that is a bad idea.
(grunting)
You go, leave.
You go, leave. I don't wanna
see you around her anymore.
Pick up the viewfinder or
else this will happen again.
Boom. But a thousand times.
Boom boom boom boom boom boom boom.
Thunder.
Lightening.
(grunting)
(hits)
(glass shatters)
(Bernie sighs)
- [Paul] Bern, you all right?
- Uh...
Yeah. I...
Yeah, I'm fine.
- [Paul] Hey, wrap things
up, sport. Time for bed.
- Yeah.
- [Paul] You're grounded.
You are grounded, mister.
And for a very long time.
- [Mom] Paul.
- [Paul] He left the gate open
and we could have lost Splat.
Sometimes I wonder if he
even has a brain in that-
- [Mom] Paul David Dingledorf.
God does not make junk.
- [Paul] I, I never said that.
- [Mom] You didn't have
to. That's what he thinks.
- I-
- Talk to him, Paul.
Tell him.
- But I didn't mean-
- [Mom] I know, just do it.
(knocking)
- [Paul] Bernie?
Bernie, son?
Can I come in?
Bernie?
- And so what am I supposed to do?
Just let him have his way?
I mean a guy's gotta stand
up for his rights, you know?
So I'm just gonna continue
to be a wimpy looser and that's it?
I miss you, mom.
Really bad.
(melancholy music)
(sign buzzing)
- Are you sure this place is okay?
This place being all secret and all?
Ooh!
(sighs)
Goodness.
- Here you go.
Only the select are given access
to such classified locations.
Rest assured men of great
power such as myself...
(grunts)
(bottle pops)
Can always make exceptions.
- Oh, oh.
(beeping)
(staticky buzzing)
- Hello?
- Madam Secretary.
- Where is everyone?
- Um, well, I'm only one
at this station, ma'am.
We are in the middle of nowhere.
- Which explains why we've traced
the secret warehouse
and weapons headquarters
of the notorious. Dr.
Chuckles to your district.
Who would expect world
peace to be destroyed
from such a no nothing location?
Is someone with you?
- Someone with, someone with me?
No, no.
No unauthorized personnel here, ma'am.
I'm all alone.
Agent 001/2 at your
service, Madam Secretary.
You were mentioning Dr.
Chuckles and world peace.
- High level security indicates
that he plans to destroy the
upcoming World Peace Conference
tomorrow in Paris.
- Well uh, how's that, Madam Secretary?
- He has developed a giant laugh generator
that will send the world,
starting from top leaders
and working its way
down to the common man,
into uncontrollable fits of laughter.
He plans to reduce conference into nothing
but laughing mayhem.
- Oh, that's terrible.
- And you.
You must shut that
machine down at all costs.
- I'll get right on it, Madam Secretary.
- There is one thing
you should know first.
His agents have stolen something
called Gooey Chewy bars
from all across your town.
- Uh, Gooey Chewy bars.
Why is that important, Madam Secretary?
- Our best guess is that he has created
a special batch of bars
with a unique ingredient
protecting Chuckles and his workers
from the effects of the laugh generator.
These bars could give you and our agents
protection against that laugh generator,
but Chuckles has retrieved
all of the boxes but one,
which our satellites reveal
was thrown into this garbage
can by this individual,
one Bernard Dingledorf.
- He looks dangerous.
- You must bring him in
and find out what he knows,
but quietly to not attract Dr. Chuckles.
Now we've sent agents to assist,
but time is of the essence.
- I will personally attend to
it myself, Madam Secretary.
- There's no one there to help you?
- Agent-
(grunts)
Thank you.
Agent 001/2 at your
service, Madam Secretary.
- Lord, help us all.
- Thank you, ma'am.
(alarm beeping)
(water spraying)
Thank you very much.
- Bernie, let's go. Time for school.
Hey. Seven o'clock kiddo, rise and shine.
Let's go.
Come on. 20 minutes.
Cereal's on the table. See you at school.
(toy squeaks)
(Bernie groans)
(upbeat, quirky music)
(quirky, mysterious music)
(car starts up)
(Agent 001/2 grunts)
(quirky, mysterious music)
- Hm?
(Wing Nut grunts)
(chuckles)
(quirky, mysterious music)
(grunting)
(thudding)
(grunts)
- Oh.
(quirky, mysterious music)
Oh!
(thudding)
(shoe honks)
(clattering)
(quirky, mysterious music)
(kettle whistling)
Hm.
(bowl clatters)
(Agent 001/2 grunting)
(grunting)
Ah!
(plates shattering)
(quirky, mysterious music)
(sighs)
- Oh!
(Wing Nut whimpering)
- Dad?
(thudding)
Splat? Wake up, boy.
(Splat grunts)
(cracks)
(grunts)
(nose squeaks)
(sighs)
(Agent 001/2 grumbles)
(sizzling)
(gasps)
- [Virtual Assistant] I'm
sorry. Will you repeat that?
- Shh.
- [Virtual Assistant] Shh
is not on your playlist.
Did you mean Strauss?
- Shh.
- [Virtual Assistant] Playing Strauss now.
(Wing Nut gasps)
(soft orchestral music)
- Mm.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- Splat.
(Splat panting)
(farts)
(soft orchestral music)
(sniffs)
- Hm.
(soft orchestral music)
Hm.
(soft, bright orchestral music)
- Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah-
(Agent 001/2 sighs)
- Thank you.
- Oh, sure.
- Ah!
(hits)
(grunts)
(squelching)
(Wing Nut yells)
(clattering)
(grunts)
(bright, upbeat orchestral music)
(grumbling)
(Agent 001/2 grunts)
(clattering)
(bright, upbeat orchestral music)
(Agent 001/2 chuckles)
(grunting)
(Wing Nut laughs)
- Ooh.
(Wing Nut grunts)
(grunts)
(weapons ping)
(weapons pinging)
(grunting)
(clattering)
(hits)
(grunts)
(Wing Nut laughs)
Yes!
(electric buzzing)
(Wing Nut blubbering)
Eh?
(thuds)
(bright, upbeat orchestral music)
(grunting)
(Wing Nut laughs)
(shoes honking)
Ah!
(Wing Nut and Bernie yell)
(hits)
(thudding)
(grunts)
(Wing Nut grumbles)
(thuds)
- You're gonna need those.
- Who are you?
What's going on?
- [Agent 001/2] Don't make me use this.
- A TV remote?
I don't think some
stupid TV remote's gonna-
(whooshing)
(eyes pinging)
(water dripping)
A motion freezer?
- Oh, it does much more
than that, my little friend.
We have many other even
cooler items packaged in here.
- Who are you?
Why am I here?
- Your government needs you.
- Manly Man Hair Restorers?
- Sorry. That was for a friend.
- You're a T.W.I.T?
Never heard of it.
- And you never will.
We're so secret, we don't even exist.
- But you're here.
- Where?
- Here.
- There's no here here.
- You're not here?
- Where?
- You're not here, I'm not here,
so you've kidnapped me and taken me
to some place that's not here.
- Very good.
Do you have a Gooey Chewy bar?
- And now he's hungry.
You picked up a Gooey Chewy
bar off the street last night.
- Yeah. It fell off the back
of a truck and I ate it.
(Agent 001/2 grunts)
- You ate it?
In its entirety?
Oh, this is not good.
- Actually, it was great.
What's going on?
- [Agent 001/2] Meet Dr. Chuckles.
- A clown?
- Yes, a clown.
A clown who plans to destroy the upcoming
World Peace Conference using
this dastardly war machine here.
Nope, not it. Sorry.
Here.
Nope.
Not it. Here.
No, I thought I shaved that. Ew.
Here.
Ah. The Laugh Generator.
He's going to broadcast
its special frequency
to every cell phone in the world
causing each and every citizen to break
into uncontrollable fits of laughter.
(sighs)
- What's wrong with laughter?
- Depends on the type.
There's laughter that's
innocent fun. (laughs)
Or laughter that's mean and insulting.
(laughs deviously)
Hm.
- And he's chosen the mean laughter?
- Yes.
And he's found a place
to unleash its power
in his diabolical plan
to destroy world peace.
Sorry.
- Excitement continues to build
as national leaders from around the globe
head for Paris and the
World Peace Conference,
where they plan to sign a special treaty
to finally end all wars
and initiate lasting worldwide peace.
All eyes around the world...
- But if everybody's laughing
by playing mean jokes on each other...
- Welcome to World War III.
- And anticipation upon
this momentous occasion.
- Ah, mm, thank you.
- We join the President now as he prepares
to depart from his pre-meeting in Germany.
- In preparation for this meeting,
the German chancellor
and I have just completed
a long and fruitful discussion.
(tense, dramatic music)
(quirky, dramatic music)
- Where is Wing Nut?
(quirky, tense music)
Spit it out.
Cat got your tongue?
(whimpers)
(burps)
- Oh, ah!
- Speak man!
- He's out searching
for the boy.
He's out searching for the boy.
(slaps)
Sorry, sir.
- We can wait no longer.
Our destiny awaits.
(cat meows)
Stand by for world domination. (laughs)
(machines whirring)
- Never in human history has
such a grand opportunity...
- It's possible the bar
you ate came from a batch
especially created to protect Dr. Chuckles
and his goons from the frequency.
- To proceed with utmost
sobriety, and I dare say...
- If that's correct,
you may be the only one
in the entire planet who can stop him.
- Yeah, right.
Well, I mean even if it's
true, how could I stop him?
- By infiltrating his headquarters
and destroying the generator.
(alarm blaring)
- What's that?
- Sensors indicate Dr.
Chuckles is preparing
to fire the generator.
- As I prepare to leave for
this monumentous meeting...
- Three, two...
(laughs)
One.
(blasting)
(Dr. Chuckles laughs)
(all laughing)
- I just wanna say...
(laughing)
What is that?
Tuck in, tuck in.
Tuck in.
(laughing)
(thudding)
(laughs)
- That's terrible.
- Mm-hm.
(Agent 001/2 laughs)
(clears throat)
(laughing)
It's um, it's beginning to
affect me, too. (laughs)
- But...
How are you going to stop
him? What are you going to do?
- I mean, you're the only one
who can stop the generator.
- But I'm just a kid. I can't-
- Hurry.
Save our world. (laughs)
- You've got the wrong guy.
(Agent 001/2 laughing)
Dad.
I gotta find my dad.
He'll know what to do.
I gotta go to the school
and I gotta find my dad.
(Agent 001/2 laughing)
- Agent Dingledorf.
You're our only hope! (laughs)
(alarm blaring)
(laughing)
Dingledorf.
(cars honking)
(officer laughs)
- Come on, come on.
No, no, just kidding.
Okay, okay.
Oh, stop!
No, you, you come over.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on! Come on, come on, come on.
Whoa!
(laughing)
Okay, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Whoa!
(laughs)
Come on, what is this?
Is this a car? Get out of here.
- So this is happening all over the world?
People are playing mean
jokes on each other?
- And breaking into
uncontrollable laughter.
- And you're the only one who can stop it?
(tires skid)
(crashing)
(officer laughing)
- Yes. That is so awesome.
(laughing)
- You wrecked my car.
- You were, and I was like no, no, no.
(laughing)
- I mean, that's what the guy
said, but how can I buy it?
I mean the whole place,
it doesn't even exist.
(Wing Nut grunts)
- Uh oh.
- All because he ate one of
those stupid Gooey Chewy bars.
(quirky, mysterious music)
- Wait. We ate them, too.
- That's right.
(Wing Nut grunts)
- Ugh.
Ew, ew, ew, ew, ew, ew.
(sighs)
- Cool. So we can all save the world.
- Why am I not encouraged?
- No, it'll be great.
I'll have to get my own light saber.
- IQ...
- Wear my Tarantula Man PJs.
- IQ, I don't think...
- And I'll need, uh, my
Captain Universe shield.
- IQ.
- Then I'll thrust
and aerial and jibber jab!
(Wing Nut yells)
- IQ.
- What?
I'll get better with practice.
(Wing Nut yelling)
- Nice kitty.
Oh, oh?
(Wing Nut yelling)
(cat squealing)
- You don't think we can do it?
- Save the world?
- An uncontrollable laughter (laughs)
seems to be sweeping the world.
Laughter that is not just for fun,
but that appears to be just plain mean.
Reports indicate that it is...
- Hey.
I like what you've done to the place.
- [News Reporter] And
filters its way down.
That said, in the strange...
(IQ gasps)
- Save the world?
We can't even make a movie.
- [IQ] What's this?
- Well hello there.
- Me?
- [Man] And welcome to secret agent
backpack orientation 2.4.
Among the various items
you'll learn to use
are our slow-mo explosive device.
- [IQ] What?
No way.
- [Man] Our banana peel launcher.
(IQ laughs)
- [IQ] I love bananas.
- [Man] Our compulsory dancing disco ball.
- [IQ] Nice.
Yeah.
- [Man] Our latest and
greatest gizmo, the Invisobeam.
(IQ gasps)
- [IQ] Invisobeam?
But I still see him.
(man clears throat)
- [Man] Uh, still in development.
- [IQ] Ah, gotcha.
Hm.
- [Man] And of course our standard issue
video cell phones socks.
- [IQ] Cell phone socks?
- [Man] This video will self-destruct
in five, four, three, two, one.
(man clears throat)
Uh one.
(exploding)
- Bernard Dingledorf.
This is no movie.
It's the real thing and
we could see real heroes!
- World leaders continue playing
their mean-spirited prank as they prepare
for the peace conference
in Paris. (laughs)
(laughing)
(alarm blaring)
(rocket whooshing)
(people screaming)
(man laughs)
(laughing)
(phone ringing)
- Oh, oh, oh.
Oh.
(news reporter laughs)
- No one is sure where to
turn let alone seek help.
Somewhere out there, there has to be...
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Agent 001/2] Agent Dinkledorf.
- Hey Bernie! It's for you.
- Hello?
(distorted laughter)
Oh. Hello?
- Help us, Agent Dinkledorf.
- The conference begins in 90 minutes.
- I'm not an agent. I'm
just, I'm just a kid.
- 89 minutes!
It's all up to you. (laughs)
- The world as we know it is over.
- Unless we really could stop him.
- Stop him?
- Right.
Stop him.
- We just need to have a plan.
- Great.
A plan.
(phone dialing)
Do we have a plan?
- Maybe.
Rule number one, know your enemy.
Leonard Sebastian Horkelsnorken.
- Dr. Chuckles?
- Child prodigy.
- Check this out.
At age eight, he invented
the big screen TV.
- In middle school, the first cell phone.
- That was him? I thought it was-
- That's what they want you to think.
(bullies laughing)
The kids always made fun,
calling him geek-o-matic.
(bullies laughing)
- [Bernie] Voted most likely
to wear braces until age 73.
- Later he earned 11 degrees at...
I can't tell, is that
MIT, Harvard or Yale?
- Yes.
(quirky, dramatic music)
(shoes honking)
- 18 months later he presented
his greatest invention
to the National Academy of Sciences.
Solar power nose picker.
Unfortunately it had a little design flaw.
- It slipped into reverse and became-
- A solar powered snot flicker.
- Gross.
- Yeah.
- Making him the laughing
stock of the entire world.
(quirky, dramatic music)
- So with everyone laughing,
he changed careers to become a clown.
- If you can't beat 'em, you join 'em.
- At first he was the hit at
the children's birthday parties.
(children chattering)
- It looks just like Fluffy.
(popping)
After she got ran over.
I love you, Dr. Chuckles.
- Aww.
- Oh, oh, oh?
- But then when he tried to
move up to the big league,
to the circus, no one would take him.
(Wing Nut yells)
(crashing)
(grunts)
(cat screeches)
- Oh, come on.
Nice kitty.
(cat screeches)
- He just wasn't funny enough.
- And that's when he finally cracked.
Went insane and vowed revenge,
determined to humiliate the world.
- With mean humor.
- So how's this all help us?
- Maybe if you tried to reason with him.
Remind him what his good
type of humor could do.
- Got to find him first.
(doorbell ringing)
(knocking)
(nose squeaks)
- Congratulations.
You've just won a year's supply
of lactose-free, sugar-free,
not to mention taste free...
(drum rolls)
(coins pinging)
Ice cream bars.
- Are you okay?
No offense, but you look terrible.
- Allergies.
May I come in?
- Hm.
Mm.
- Mm-mm.
(cat meows)
(Wing Nut gasps)
(Wing Nut chuckles)
- Do you have a cat?
- Yeah, what's wrong?
- A cat allergy.
I always break out in a
real bad case of claw marks.
But maybe you could come
outside, to my truck.
Make your selection there.
- Okay.
- Uh, Bernie?
- I'll be right back.
- Right this way.
- He looks a little pale.
- [Wing Nut] Can't believe that worked.
- Wait, what?
- Hm?
Nothing.
- Needs more sun.
(Splat barks)
(Bernie yelling)
Bernie!
- [Wing Nut] Away we go!
- Come on, come on!
(upbeat, dramatic music)
- Oh, look.
Look at the children.
Would you like some ice cream?
No!
(laughs)
(honking)
- I need to borrow this.
- That's mine! Hey!
- I gotta take this.
- Hey.
- So sorry.
- Our parents are gonna be mad!
- Come on, IQ!
We have to catch up!
Bernie!
(splattering)
- Get your ice cream.
- Ugh.
- [Wing Nut] Knock yourself out.
- Bernie!
(Splat panting)
(splattering)
- [Lens Cap] Bernie!
- Hey, trouble over here.
(laughing)
(machines beeping)
- [Wing Nut] Our city's finest.
- [Bernie] Help! Help me!
Please, please!
- He's fine.
(officers laughing)
- [Lens Cap] Wait up!
We gotta go faster!
(Wing Nut laughs)
- [Wing Nut] Come on, slowpokes.
- [Lens Cap] Get back here!
- [Bernie] Where are you taking me?
- [Lens Cap] We're gaining on him!
You go left, I'll close in on the right.
- Right!
- No, left!
- What?
- Go left!
- Mine or yours?
- It's the same thing!
- Same thing?
(upbeat pop rock music)
- Right here.
- [Bernie] Lens Cap!
(Wing Nut laughing)
IQ!
- [Wing Nut] Brace yourselves.
- You sure this is gonna work?
- Of course not.
- Great.
(Wing Nut laughing)
- [Bernie] Please don't, please don't.
- Ready?
Steady.
(Wing Nut laughing)
If we die, you'll live to regret this!
(golf cart puttering)
- What?
What?
Oh.
(Lens Cap laughs)
(Wing Nut grumbling)
(hitting)
(whooshing)
(Wing Nut chuckles)
(mumbles)
(thuds)
(Splat pants)
(Wing Nut mumbling)
(soft lullaby music)
I think, I think...
I think I'll just...
I'm just gonna sit down.
- [Bernie] Untie me.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm good.
IQ, what are you doing?
- It was under the seat.
- Come on.
- Come on. Go, go, go.
I'm driving. Move over.
- [Bernie] You guys, come on.
(upbeat music)
- [Lens Cap] Nice and easy.
(soft, upbeat music)
- Where are we going?
- GPS.
- I know what we are,
but where are we going?
- GPS.
- He was our only clue.
- Great.
- GPS!
Home. GPS.
- I know where home is, I just...
Oh.
His home.
- Mm-hm.
- IQ, you're a genius.
- All right.
Here we go.
- Now what?
- [Bernie] Maybe they got
a key hidden somewhere?
- Or we could try calling a locksmith.
(doorbell rings)
Or that.
- [Man] Good afternoon, jokesters.
Today's security question is
what's the last thing to go through
a grasshopper's mind when
he hits the windshield?
You have 60 seconds.
- Um, uh...
- The last thing to go
through a grasshopper's mind-
- Right, right.
Um.
- I know, I know.
I bet this is going to leave a mark?
- Really?
(spraying)
(quirky music)
- [Man] Your answer is incorrect.
You now have 41 seconds.
- Uh, uh-
- Think of something!
- Well, I don't know, I
should've bought life insurance?
- Oh, that's a lot better.
(spraying)
(quirky music)
- [Man] Incorrect. You have 32 seconds.
- Uh...
So you wanna play chicken do you?
(buzzing)
- Clear the runway,
I'm coming in hot?
(buzzing)
- Call the society for Prevention
of Cruelty to Insects?
(buzzing)
- Guys!
- [Man] You have 12 seconds.
- I know, I know, I know!
Butt!
- [Man] Nine seconds.
- Can't you be any funnier?
- Can't you?
- Butt.
- But what?
- The last thing that goes through
a grasshopper's mind after hitting
the windshield is his butt.
Like your tushy.
(man laughs)
- [Man] That's correct. (laughs)
What a crack up. (laughs)
Please, enter.
And don't forget to wipe your feet.
I said don't forget
to wipe your feet.
- Oh!
- [Man] Thank you.
- [Lens Cap] Okay?
- I need to find that generator.
(Splat barks)
(creepy carnival music)
Which door?
(growling)
- Not that one.
(feet thudding)
(upbeat marching music)
(Splat sniffing)
- [IQ] What'd you find, boy?
(train horn blares)
(gasps)
(creatures growling)
(Bernie whimpering)
- Honestly, that is so fake-
(elephant trumpets)
(splashing)
(woman screams)
- Sorry!
(creepy carnival music)
(machine whirring)
- Guys, I found something.
Whoa.
- [Announcer] Welcome to
the coaster experience.
- [Lens Cap] What did you do?
- Cool!
- [Announcer] Please
keep your hands and arms
inside the vehicle at all times.
- A roller coaster.
IQ, don't.
- Come on!
(announcer speaks in foreign language)
(Splat barks)
Come on, Splat, let's go.
(Splat panting)
This'll be awesome.
- [Announcer] Coaster departing in five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
(whooshing)
(yelling)
- What the?
- [Announcer] I told you,
keep your hands and arms
inside the vehicle at all times.
- [Bernie] Splat, you okay, buddy?
(Splat grunts)
(yelling)
(roaring)
(guns firing)
(yelling)
(dinosaurs roar)
(grunting)
- [IQ] Come on, Splat.
- [Alarm Announcer]
Warning, warning, warning.
There are numerous humans.
(IQ chuckles)
- Hello?
Hello?
Anyone there?
(clowns laughing)
- [Clown 1] Look out!
- [Clown 2] Road hog!
- Bernie?
- [Clown 3] Use your signal!
(clowns chattering)
(laughing)
- [Bernie] What are you doing?
- [IQ] Checking.
(clowns chattering)
- Hurry.
- [Clown 4] Let's get 'em!
- Cool!
- Guys, we gotta go, we gotta go!
Come on!
- [Man] Wrong way to Dr. Chuckles.
Why would I lie?
- Aw, nice kitty kitty ki-
(lion roars)
- Come on!
(upbeat, quirky music)
(alarm blaring)
- What is this place?
- [Dr. Chuckles] Well, hi there.
(Len Cap gasps)
- Dr. Chuckles.
- Present.
- Where are you?
- Where are we?
- In a very special room. (laughs)
You'll find out soon enough.
I must say I was very impressed with you
getting through my living
defenses and finding me.
- Thanks. It wasn't that big of a-
- I could really use you on my team.
- Team?
- You know, to help
with the little details, like,
you know, ruling the world.
- We would never work for you.
- Is there any pay?
- There's nothing wrong with laughter.
- Not if you're laughing with someone.
But if you're laughing at
them, that's just plain-
- Mean?
- Right.
And my dad said that we should
honor and respect people-
- Blah blah blah blah.
Yes, your poor father, oh, oh.
Speaking of which, let's
check in on him, shall we?
(Paul laughing)
(people screaming)
And by the way your entire
school is under my powers.
The teachers have all gone crazy.
- You free my dad, you jerk!
(electric buzzing)
- [Dr. Chuckles] Excellent.
- [Lens Cap] What was that?
- [Dr. Chuckles] You tell me. (laughs)
- I'm not sure what
makes you such a creep,
but it really seems to be working.
- What's going on?
- Now who's being mean?
Your meanness is creating
your own special prison.
- What?
- Your rudeness is no different
from my own comic genius.
- You're not a comic genius.
You're a comic goofus.
- Um guys...
- If laughter was the best medicine,
your face would cure the world. (laughs)
(Dr. Chuckles laughing)
- Welcome to my insult room.
(buzzing)
You can cry all you want.
There's no escaping...
Until, of course, you choose to join me.
(pinging)
- Look at me, Doc.
Beat up, depressed, under
appreciated by Chuckles.
I just feel like my life
isn't going anywhere.
What should I do?
Oh.
What's bothering me?
(Wing Nut sighs)
It's the boss.
Oh sure. He, he acts
bad, but on the inside?
I worry he's too good to be bad.
What do you think?
Do you really think he's evil enough
to take over the whole world?
(squelching)
(pinging)
Exactly.
Do you know he once tried
to use his humor for good?
Mm-hm.
And that cat he's always doting on?
(cat screeches)
Anyone who loves animals can't be all bad.
Perhaps...
We need a new leader.
Someone more focused on being bad.
Someone intelligent.
Good-looking.
A real clown among clowns.
Now, who might that be?
Who could that be?
Me!
It's me, you clown!
(sighs)
(chuckles)
Yes.
Oh, I'm so glad you agree. (chuckles)
Well I really feel a lot better, Doc.
Thank you so much.
(soft, quirky music)
Oh.
(Wing Nut grunting)
Excuse me.
(grunting)
- [Dr. Chuckles] Wing Nut?
Get back and guard the insult room.
(Wing Nut sighs)
Now!
(staticky buzzing)
Keep an eye on them.
- Yes, sir.
(staticky buzzing)
- What have we done?
- We're no better than he is.
- Just not as ugly.
(staticky buzzing)
- IQ!
- [Lens Cap] Guess we won't
be needing this anymore.
(staticky buzzing)
(phone ringing)
- Your feet are ringing.
- Hello?
(Agent 001/2 laughing)
It's for you.
Let me put it on sneaker phone.
(Agent 001/2 laughing)
- [Agent 001/2] Secret Agent Dingledorf.
- I told you, I'm not a...
- The leaders have
arrived in Paris. (laughs)
(soft, upbeat French music)
(laughing)
- Woo-woo. (laughs)
(blowtorch buzzing)
(laughing)
(tower creaks)
- The conference begins within the hour.
(laughs)
(silly string spraying)
- I told you from the start,
you've got the wrong person.
- Oh, and your dad called.
He wanted me to give you a message.
Something about... (laughs)
Junk.
(laughs)
- Like we're ever gonna break out of here.
(staticky buzzing)
- And what are you gonna do...
(Bernie grunts)
(thudding)
If I don't?
(Russell laughs)
- [Bernie] Don't you ever
get tired of being a nobody?
- Everyone has value, son.
God, he doesn't make junk.
(staticky buzzing)
- Dad.
Junk.
God doesn't make junk.
- You're getting pretty
good with all that stuff.
(staticky buzzing)
Did you see that?
- Yeah.
Hey, IQ.
You know, you're one smart guy.
(staticky buzzing)
- And you're a great judge of character.
- Hey Lens Cap, did I ever tell you
what a great filmmaker you are?
- Stop that.
- No, but I trust your opinion of me
since you're so smart and highly informed.
- Highly informed?
- I know what you're doing.
- Sure.
He's intelligent...
And a great friend.
- Stop that!
- Thanks.
You're a good friend, too.
- We're all good friends.
And we're smart, too.
(staticky buzzing)
(Lens Cap gasps)
- Come on, let's go.
- Clown code red.
Clown code red.
- [Bernie] Hurry, they're gaining.
- [IQ] I'm trying!
- [Bernie] The backpack,
anything else you got in there?
- Uh, laser nail Clippers,
rocket powered shoe laces.
Ooh, x-ray glasses.
(chuckles)
- [Bernie] Come on, any time.
(clowns laughing)
(whooshing)
- [IQ] I love bananas.
- [Bernie] Come on.
You guys, come on.
- Come on!
(clowns chattering)
- I thought it'd be a little more roomy.
- Breath mints?
Anyone?
(pounding on door)
- No thanks.
What?
- Guys, ideas?
Anyone?
(pounding on door)
- You said I was a great filmmaker.
Right?
- Yeah.
- Play along with me here.
(pounding on door)
(clowns exclaim)
Cut!
Congratulations. You've
all passed the audition.
- [Clown] What?
- For the new reality show.
They didn't tell you?
Ugh.
Figures.
Clowns Gone Wild on Nerdflix this fall.
You're all gonna be stars.
Love that look, sweetheart.
Don't change a thing.
Okay everybody, gather
in for a group photo.
Come on, let's go.
The camera loves you, kid. Uh-huh.
Yeah, keep it goin'.
Yep, come on, there we go.
Nice and close. Okay.
All set?
And action.
(door slams)
(clowns exclaim)
Come on!
- [Clown 2] Aww.
(clowns chattering)
- Go, go, go.
- IQ!
The backpack.
Make it melt!
- Right.
- Hurry.
That'll work.
- [Bernie] Come on!
(clowns shouting)
(machine whirring)
(staticky buzzing)
Whoa.
(Splat sniffing)
(clowns chattering)
(bright, upbeat music)
How do we shut it down?
- [Lens Cap] It's a bunch
of those giggle guns
wired and parallel.
- Making one giant super charged one.
- If we can disconnect enough of them,
I bet we can disable it and...
- [Bernie] Chuckles.
(booming)
IQ!
- I'm on it.
- [Bernie] Hurry!
(clowns shouting)
(whooshing)
IQ, come on.
- He's trying to get ahead.
- [IQ] Coming through!
(thudding)
Bernie, go!
(Bernie gasps)
- [Clown 1] Where'd they go?
- [Bernie] IQ.
(clowns shouting)
Can they see me?
- Eh?
(clowns chattering)
(tense, upbeat music)
- IQ, come on, I'm ahead of ya.
- [IQ] He's right behind you! Look out!
- IQ!
(whooshing)
(Bernie grunts)
A little help here.
Nice job, IQ.
(pinging)
(clowns chattering)
- Hey! Get down from there.
- IQ!
Help!
(pinging)
(clowns chattering)
- Bernie, catch!
(cat meows)
- You're too late, Dingledork. (laughs)
(exploding)
(laughing)
(spraying)
(President laughing)
- No.
They'll never sign the treaty now
and there's nothing you can do about it.
(world leaders laughing)
- Really?
- Wait. What are you doing?
You don't know what that can do.
(gun cocks)
- I have a pretty good idea.
- No, wait.
Listen, let's...
Let's talk.
- I think a good laugh
would be better, don't you?
- Wait, wait, please.
No, no, listen.
- I hate laughter.
I even tried to be funny
once, at the circus.
- We saw the pictures.
- People made fun of me,
told me I was worthless.
- No.
Nobody's worthless.
(quirky music)
- It was terrible.
It was humiliating.
I was good for nothing.
- No.
God doesn't make junk.
Maybe you were just
trying at the wrong place.
- Hm.
Yeah, dingleberry.
Well I'm in the right place now.
- No, please, please.
The world needs your ge-
(laughing)
Is this how you want the
world to remember you?
- They must suffer they
way they made me suffer.
(Bernie laughs)
What are you doing?
What is that?
(Bernie laughing)
Hey.
Let's see if we can make a big one.
- [Children] Whoa!
(laughing)
- Look what you could do.
Look what you could do.
- No, they're just kids.
- Look at their joy.
(Bernie laughs)
Look at the happiness you brought.
This is who you are. (laughs)
- I love you, Dr. Chuckles.
- [Dr. Chuckles] I love you too, Princess.
(clowns shouting)
(quirky, upbeat music)
- Uh oh.
(clowns shouting)
(IQ grumbles)
- [IQ] This thing...
(clowns shouting)
(upbeat, quirky music)
(Bernie laughs)
- That makes it look like so
and make it look just like this right here
and all of a sudden then we have
a Dr. Chuckles clown pizza.
Yeah.
- Don't listen to him, boss.
It's a trick.
(cat meows)
(Wing Nut gasps)
It's a trick.
He will humiliate you like all the others.
- You've got a gift.
- I was a loser.
- Look.
(Bernie laughs)
- [Wing Nut] Boss.
- Go.
Now!
(cat growls)
(clowns shouting)
(upbeat, quirky music)
(IQ grunts)
- Maybe it's the batteries.
Uh oh.
- Everyone laughed at me.
- No.
The children were laughing with you.
(Bernie laughs)
You should make a
generator that does that.
People laughing with each other
instead of at each other. (laughs)
You could save the world. (laughs)
(clowns shouting)
(tense, quirky music)
- [Clown 1] That little brat.
Is he under there?
- I don't see him.
(clowns shouting)
(quirky, tense music)
(whooshing)
(upbeat, funky music)
(clowns chattering)
(Wing Nut grunting)
- [Wing Nut] Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
(machine beeping)
- [Machine] Warning, maximum
laughter overdrive engaged.
- Oh?
(beeping)
(upbeat, funky music)
- Oh! That thing's gonna blow!
Go!
- [Clown 1] Clownin' around!
Oh no!
- [Clown 2] We've got to get out of here!
(buzzing)
- No!
(machine beeping)
(clowns shouting)
- Wait.
- Huh?
- [Clown 3] I thought it was done.
(electric buzzing)
(booming)
(laughing)
- Shut it down.
- I can't, I can't..
(laughing)
I can't stop.
- I can't.
(laughing)
- Shut it down!
- I can't!
(laughing)
- Give it to me!
(squelching)
- [Wing Nut] Huh?
(laughing)
- [Russian President] I had
sense of humor for a moment.
(laughing)
(dramatic music)
- [Wing Nut] Huh?
(splashing)
(sparking)
(Splat panting)
(Wing Nut grumbles)
- You did it, boy.
Good boy, good boy, you did it.
Good boy, you saved us all.
Good boy.
(buzzing)
(Splat farts)
- [World Leader 1] Nice to meet you.
- [World Leader 2] Thank you.
- [World Leader 3] Other side, here.
- Wow.
I had no idea.
- Imagine what could happen
if you used it for good.
- No.
- But-
- Juggleheads, take away these children
and let's begin our repairs.
It's never too late to end
human civilization as we know it
and to begin domin-
- How does a farmer count cows?
- Wait, what?
With a cow-culator.
(clowns laugh)
Or uh, how about this one,
what do ghosts have for dessert?
I-scream!
(laughing)
And...
Oh, this is a great one.
What do you sea monsters have for lunch?
- I don't know, Bernie.
What do sea monsters eat?
- Fish and ships.
(laughing)
- I-scream, I get it now. (laughs)
- See?
See how good people feel with
the right type of laughter?
With your genius and the right
kind of humor, you could...
- I could change the world.
- For the good.
(phone ringing)
- What?
- I ain't got one.
No, I got no phone.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
They've got the pace surrounded.
(clowns gasp)
They want you to give yourself up.
- It could be a new
beginning for all of us.
- Don't listen to him. (laughs)
He's been tricked.
(cat growling)
Follow me.
I will be your new leader. (laughs)
I will...
(cat growls)
Together, we will finish the revolution.
Together, we will-
(cat screeches)
Ah, ah, get him off!
(clowns laughs)
- My fellow jokesters,
a new day is dawning, a
day where we no longer
need to hide our true identity,
a day where we can make
the world a better place
by being who we were created to be.
(clowns gasp)
- [Clown 5] Oh, god, that's my nose.
(sirens wailing)
- [Officer] All right,
come on, keep goin'.
(clowns chattering)
(police radio chatter)
Move it. Move it along.
- [Female Clown] See you later, Bernie.
Be sure to write. (laughs)
- Well done, Agent Dingledorf.
- I told you I'm not an agent.
- Exactly, which is why
you're such a great secret.
You and your team.
- Team?
- For you.
And for you, Lens Cap.
Pretending to be an artist.
- Pretending?
(Agent 001/2 chuckles)
- And you, Splat, are disguised as
the poster dog for Overeater's Anonymous.
Who's a good agent?
(Splat grunts)
And last but not least, for you, IQ,
the brains behind the whole operation.
- Cool clouds.
- All of you pretending to
be boring, everyday people.
- Which we are.
- Exactly.
- [EMT] The victim has multiple
hats stretches to the face.
Yes, the clown.
Seriously, the clown.
- Allergies.
(thudding)
(Wing Nut grunts)
(grunting)
- Hordikins!
(Splat farts)
My hero.
- My muffin.
(kissing)
- I wanted to let you know
that one of those nice men
in those nice suits asked
me to give you this.
(Anna gasps)
Oh.
(gasps)
- The president wants to give me a medal.
- A medal?
- For?
- For planning this
whole operation, silly.
He's just the smartest
secret agent now, isn't he?
(Agent 001/2 chuckles)
- Well, duty calls.
(upbeat marching music)
Yep.
- Um, we're-
- Nope.
- I, uh...
Yeah.
- [Paul] Bern.
- Dad!
(Splat barks)
- Hey, are you all right?
Is everything okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, you?
- I couldn't be better.
(police siren beeps)
So guess what?
The Secretary liked your idea.
- Idea?
- Yeah, about Chuckles using his gift
to make the world a better place.
And if he does so, he
might only get probation.
Boom.
Let's go see the kids.
Hey, come on, Splat.
Let's go.
(Splat barks)
- The world can rest assured
that I have saved the day
and as usual the agency that I work for
does not respect my abilities
and I should be promoted
but they won't do it
because of politics...
(soft, upbeat music)
(birds chirping)
- Come on.
Stupid English.
(tense, quirky music)
- Pick it up.
I'll break you.
Boom, boom, boom.
You talkin' to me?
See these right here?
(Russell grunts)
- What are you doing here?
- Uh, I uh, I always take the shortcut.
What are you doing?
- Working on a stupid
paper for stupid English.
Doesn't sound so bad.
- Well not for you.
You're smart.
(Russell grunts)
(sighs)
I get another F, my dad's gonna kill me.
I'm such a loser.
- Well, maybe I could,
you know, help you out.
- What?
- Well like you said, this
stuff comes easy for me.
What's it on?
- Um, heroes.
- Heroes?
- Yeah.
Like those guys that saved the
World Peace Conference thing.
- Uh, yeah. I could
give you some pointers.
- You know, it doesn't
have to be hot shots.
It can be a normal, everyday people, too.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- Even um, know-nothing twerps that help
other guys out with schoolwork and stuff.
- Thanks.
- But never mention it.
- Right.
- To no one.
- Okay.
- Ever.
- Got it.
(soft music)
(whistling)
(bag thuds)
(quirky, mysterious music)
- No.
Nope. I'm not doing it anymore.
I'm done.
(phone ringing)
(Bernie sighs)
Hello?
(distorted chattering)
Oh.
Hello?
- [Agent 001/2] Agent Dingledorf, hurry.
Get in the car.
- What car? I don't see a car.
- [Agent 001/2] Oh. (laughs)
Sorry.
Hang on, hang on.
Whoa.
Get back, back, back, back, back, back.
Get back.
And forward.
(tires squeal)
Okay, here we go.
And, nope.
(Agent 001/2 grunts)
There we go.
No.
Yeah. There we go.
Hold on, hold on.
Just, and...
Okay, stand still.
No, no me. You stand...
Okay.
(Agent 001/2 mumbling)
There we go.
Hurry Agent Dingledorf.
- Shh!
- Oh, sorry.
Hurry.
(upbeat, mysterious music)
- Who's driving?
- [Agent 001/2] Not me.
- Agent 001/2, is that you?
- [Agent 001/2] Yes, it isn't me.
- You mean no it isn't you?
- I mean, yes, it's no that it's not yes.
- Who am I talking to?
- [Agent 001/2] Nobody.
- So I'm talking to
nobody who isn't driving?
- [Agent 001/2] You're getting very good
at this secret agent thing.
- Says who?
- [Agent 001/2] Not me.
Agent Dingledorf, your
country desperately needs you.
- I have school, a spelling test.
- [Agent 001/2] If we don't hurry,
there'll be no words left to spell.
Well?
- All right.
But seriously, this has
to be the very last-
(tires skid)
Time!
Wherever evil lurks, wherever it may hide,
it is time to unmask it and
reveal truth to the world.
It's time to right the world's wrongs
and fight injustice wherever it may lie.
To help the downtrodden and depressed,
using all our abilities to
make the world a better place.
Of honor and respect for all.
- Cut, cut!
Cut!
(upbeat, funky music)
(people clapping)
(cheering)
- Let's dance.
(upbeat, funky music)
Come on, everybody. Let's celebrate.
- [Bernie] Nice. Let's do it.
My milkshake boys are
coming to the yard
(clapping)
(cheering)
(sighs)
(laughing)
- Stop being funny, this is serious.
Ah!
- My hiccups are gone.
- Brace for it.
(laughing)
- That was the thing.
Didn't work.
- [Director] Cut.
- [Man] Lead camera only, marker.
- I feel accomplished.
All right, let's try and get this perfect.
- We're making this super cool movie
and Bernie plays a Bonzo
superhero and we're...
Sorry, can I go from the top.
I don't know what I did there.
- [Man] Adam, if you
could just do the shot.
(sneezes)
- Hurry!
(thuds)
(laughs)
(upbeat, funky music)
- It's possible the bar you ate
was especially crafted to
get the dialogue wrong.
- It's a bunch of those Google guns.
Sorry.
Did I say Google guns?
- Just remember I'm the
actor and you follow me.
- I follow no one.
- You follow no one.
Actually, that's a good answer.
- It's bunch of those Google
guns wired and parallel.
- Making one super...
Making one giant, supercharged one.
Yeah.
(chuckles)
You said Google gun again.
- I did?
- Sensors are indicating that Dr. Chuckles
is preparing to destroy the gener-
Not destroy it, to fire it.
I feel like we've done
this dialogue before.
- Yeah. Deja vu.
(upbeat, funky music)
- It's a bunch of those Goog-
Now I think about it.
- A clown who plans to destroy
the World Peace Conference using this
diabolical military
dialogue written for me
which I don't remember!
- [IQ] Hey, mister.
Mister.
(soft, upbeat music)
- [Director] Cut.
- Yeah, you're-
- Oh.
- Hey mister!
Mister! You dropped your...
(upbeat, funky music)
- To reach every cell phone in the world
so each and every citizen-
(farting)
Farts!
You wanna go back a little bit?
- [Man] Yeah, that was good.
(laughing)
Let's go back to the, uh, top.
- The secret warehouse
and weapons headquarters
of the notorious-
Sorry. One more time.
The secret warehouse and weapons...
Headquarters.
I don't know why I can't remember that.
Okay.
- Sorry, can I start over again?
Ah, sorry.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Sebastian Horkelsnorken.
Can we go again?
Hey, is your nose okay?
- You like punched it.
- I'm sorry.
I'll grab it from the side.
(laughing)
- [IQ] I slipped.
- Are you okay?
(yelling)
(hits)
- Oh gosh.
Sorry.
I accidentally, I tapped him...
(cheering)
(clapping)
- [Man] Z marker.
- Um, I think it's his uh,
initials, so it's weird.
- Wait, what?
- See?
- Ber-
- I'm dumb.
- Nie.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- This is the best your
career will ever be
right here in this moment.
Look at me.
You're probably gonna be the
biggest star in the world
and you're gonna remind me I said that.
- Yeah, I will.
- Oh, I already hate you.
- I'm gonna go back, I'm
gonna find your address
and I'm gonna say remember
when you said this?
- Remember when-
Find my address?
That's already the creepiest
thing you've said today.
(laughs)
- A solar powered snot flicker.
That's funny.
A solar powered snot flicker.
That's weird.
(clapping)
Ooh.
X-ray glasses.
Can we do it again?
Rocket powered shoe laces.
Ooh.
X-ray glasses.
(laughing)
Why are they, like, so weird?
They're, oh, I felt the wrong one.
(clapping)
(upbeat music)
Really? Another mission?
Cool.
(clapping)
(upbeat music)
- Yeah, dingleberry, I'm in the right...
(laughing)
- Sorry about that.
- [Man] We're rolling. Still rolling.
- Still rolling!
(clapping)
(upbeat music)
(laughs)
- [Director] You okay?
Got something in your eye?
- Nope.
Just bad acting.
(laughing)
(soft, upbeat music)
- Muffin.
- My hero.
- I stepped on your line.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Oh.
- [Director] My hero, rolling.
- I was just, I was ripping.
(cheering)
(clapping)
- He's just the smartest
secret agent now, isn't he?
Oh.
(soft, upbeat music)
(laughing)
- Where are we going from?
Are we good to keep going?
- Cut!
Cut!
Cut, cut, cut!
(cheering)
- It's a wrap!
(clapping)
- They'll be showing this movie
in film schools, you know that, right?