Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[vocalization]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[Tiffanie]
Tomorrow is my wedding day,
and I'm about to make the biggest mistake of my life,
because this man
isn't my future husband.
This man is my weakness.
I know it's wrong,
but I can't stop.
My desire for this man
consumes me.
It overrides reason,
morals, everything.
This is lust.
[vocalization]
But I'm getting ahead
of myself.
Let's go back to the beginning,
before Trey Taylor
shook up my life.
Damon King.
You want my arm to fall off?
-Billy Dee Williams...
-Lady Sings The Blues.
I know. You need to work
on your game, Mr. King.
Why are you so much trouble?
Because I'm your fiancee.
It's my job.
Damon, Damon.
Can I get a couple of minutes
for my viewers?
Sasha, of course you can.
How you doing?
I'm doing good.
You excited about the wedding,
Tiffanie?
I am. Very.
-I'm ecstatic.
-So when's the big day?
That's one week.
You know this is my masterpiece.
Talking about a masterpiece,
King Enterprises
is one of the biggest companies
on the sea.
What would you say
to aspiring entrepreneurs?
You know, you gotta wake up
every day and grind, 24/7.
Rumor has it
that you're opening a spa.
-Oh, yeah, that's right. Yes.
-Yes.
Urban Utopia's the name.
You know, we wanted to create
an oasis for the people.
You know, the average person
that can afford a nice getaway.
You come by the office tomorrow,
I'll have a letter of intent
for you.
Look, at the end of the day,
publicity alone is gonna garner
thousands of streams, Justus.
Listen, I know Damon
got the game on lock.
-Absolutely.
-But I'mma be honest with you.
[Justus] I need to meet
more people.
[Eric] Justus.
[Justus] Make it happen.
[Eric] I'll make it happen.
-Hey.
-Hey, babe.
-Mm.
-Thank you.
You want some
before I put it all up?
Oh, totally.
You ain't talking about food,
are you?
Mm-mm.
[both moaning]
On the counter.
Baby, it's unsanitary.
[moaning]
Take it out.
Hey. You can't talk like that.
[instrumental music]
Can we go upstairs now?
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
[moaning]
Well, that was so hot.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
-[cell phone beeps]
-Oh.
Eric says that
we are at the top of the list
for Justus' album release party.
You know, if we get that, it's
gonna take us to the next level.
-Right?
-Mm-hmm.
We're gonna be the king
and queen of Atlanta.
I must have missed
the coronation.
[chuckles]
What's up with you tonight?
[exhales sharply]
It's Urban Utopia.
Baby, we're just a few days
behind the opening.
-Uh, uh...
-I got you.
I took care of it already.
You agreed to be
a silent partner.
Making decisions about my spa
is so not silent.
All right, I might not be
college-educated,
but I think I've opened up
a few businesses.
And I've had some failures.
Tiff, I'm just trying
to shield you, that's all.
Hot shower's calling my name.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey...
We good?
King and queen of Atlanta,
right?
[shower running]
[Tiffanie] Something was off
with me and Damon's sex life.
I remember the cheesy romance
novels I'd sneak around with.
The passion! The orgasms!
Why wasn't I experiencing that?
Something was missing between
us, but I didn't know what.
He says the treatment tables
are in Idaho.
Oh, uh, we open
in less than two weeks.
[sighs] That would be
a saving grace.
Actually, I'm the signer
on the account, not Mr. King.
Yeah. Oh, is that right?
Y-you can just change that back.
Under my name, yes.
Okay. Thank you, Marjorie.
[sighs]
-[Damon] I mean, and timing is--
-[Phyllis] I got you.
I can go bigger
if you want me to.
Just say the word, I got you.
If you need anything,
you just call me.
Okay. All right.
[instrumental music]
Oh.
-[chuckles]
-Oh.
I cannot wait for you
to walk down those stairs
on our wedding day.
How on Earth do you look
so chic? I mean, look at me.
-You look comfortable.
-Child, stop.
That's a nice way of saying
sloppy.
-Pick one?
-Uh-uh.
This is Damon's taco stand.
I was told
to just show up on the day.
Geometrics, please. Thank you.
-[cell phone beeps]
-Let me take care of this.
-I'll see you in a second.
-All right.
-[chuckles]
-Mm...
-This wedding keeps expanding.
-You're not happy?
I always thought I'd get married
in my grandfather's church.
You know,
something small, simple.
You should have seen the look
on Damon's face
when I suggested it, you would
have thought I asked the man
to marry me in a barn
or something.
[laughs] Well, he does love
this house, doesn't he?
-Mm.
-Okay.
-It's ostentatious.
-Yeah.
I mean, how many great rooms
does one need?
-I'm sorry, I don't...
-No! No, no, no.
You're my bride.
I'm here for it all.
-Even the complaints.
-Yeah.
-Now, how's Urban Utopia?
-Oh, it keeps evolving.
-[gasps] Okay, well?
-[chuckles] Yes.
Well, I want Urban Utopia
to be more than a spa.
I want women to come, like,
even if they just wanna
visit the sauna
or the quiet room
or have some tea and journal.
I want it to feel
like a sanctuary.
-I like that.
-Oh.
And we hired a hairstylist,
'cause you know what our hair
does with the steam.
Child, you have single-handedly
figured out the problem
for every black woman
using the spa.
I mean, seriously,
that's exactly what we need.
Always think about
everybody else.
-Mm. That sounds great.
-Babe.
Uh, we gotta go.
-Phyllis, tall one.
-Okay.
-All right, we're all good.
-You got me, huh?
Uh, we're in the final stretch
now. You guys ready?
-Yes, we are.
-All right.
[chuckles] Okay.
[Tiffanie] Hi, grandpa.
[Damon] We're ready.
-Uh, we finished the exercise.
-What did you discover?
Well, we discovered
that we pretty much
problem-solve the same.
-Mm-hmm.
-[Tiffanie] We're lists people.
We pretty much jot down
the areas of concern
and compare notes.
Well, good luck with that.
-[chuckles]
-Grandpa...
It takes years for couples
to learn how to argue
in a healthy manner.
How long have y'all
been together?
A year and a half.
Tiffanie, your grandmother and I
have been married over 55 years
and we're still
trying to figure it out.
-Well, maybe we're an anomaly.
-Maybe.
But I'm concerned that you all
are being completely honest
with each other.
Trying to please each other
is very temporary.
And the truth,
as ugly as it can be,
is the key
to a very successful marriage.
You understand?
We agree.
-Don't we, babe?
-Yes.
Now, I want you all
to read and discuss
Ephesians chapter five,
verse 25 through 30, okay?
Ooh! Sweet! Hm!
Boy, nice!
[indistinct commentary on TV]
Hm.
Babe, your shirt's unbuttoned.
Oh.
Oh, this game...
Man, I knew I should've went.
I'm here for my interview,
Mr. King.
[chuckles] Interview?
My name is Angela,
and I'm here for our interview.
But, oh, I,
I don't have any experience.
Is there anything I can do...
Baby, you're so beautiful.
But all this kinky stuff,
you know,
I kinda, I did that stuff
in the past life.
I wanna leave it there.
Now, what we have is, is pure
and I love it.
I need you to do me a favor,
though.
I need you to pick up Trey
for me.
Can't Magic do it?
Yeah, he can do it, but you know
I have the meeting with Jaleesa
and her record label,
and he just came home,
and I want you to do it for me.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
-It is Magic's job.
-Mm.
Trey's leaving right after
the wedding, right, baby?
I'm sorry, but the man just got
out of jail five seconds ago.
I know, but he's changed.
Give him a chance, okay?
What time does he land?
You know you're my angel, right?
[chuckles]
Come on! Damn!
[Tiffanie] I know Shelly doesn't
have a ton of experience,
but she's a single mom.
Mm, you know, she did give me
that bomb deep tissue,
but she's not coming in
with any existing clientele.
We're a new business, Tiff.
It's risky.
-We're hiring her.
-[scoffs]
-All right, boss-lady.
-[chuckles] What's next?
You gotta pick up El Chapo.
-Yeah.
-You want me to go with you?
No.
It's not getting
any better, Sonia.
I warned you, do not give it up
before marriage.
Are you really saying that if I
stayed a virgin until marriage,
the sex would have been better?
Look, it was for me.
So God is punishing me?
No, but there are consequences
to your actions.
But I can't re-virginize myself.
-And that is not a word.
-It is now.
[both laughing]
I feel like I should get points
for waiting as long as I did.
I was practically
the 30-year-old virgin
when I met Damon.
You're right, exactly.
I mean, you waited this long,
so you could have just waited
a couple of years longer, 'cause
y'all are getting married,
what, after only
a year and a half?
-Yeah.
-In the grand scheme of things--
-I was just so ready.
-Yeah, to lose 'em draws.
[chuckles] Shut up!
[sighs] Okay.
How bad is it?
It's not, it's not terrible.
It's just vanilla yogurt.
But you, you look like
you like
that vanilla yogurt. Hm.
-Mm-hmm.
-Mm.
I was reading online...
Yeah, that's the problem
right there.
Do not ever go to the web
to self-diagnose yourself.
Uh-uh. Don't do that.
[doorbell rings]
Uh...
Ah, hm...
[instrumental music]
Oh.
Baby.
[sighs]
That is a good man right there.
Talk you later.
Love you.
[Damon] The story of our lives
is just beginning.
And I can't wait to fill all
of these pages with you.
-[doorbell rings]
-[glass shatters]
Damnit! Ah...
Ah! Just a minute!
[groans]
[wincing]
Uh, can I help you?
Um, you're bleeding.
I'm Trey.
You're Tiffanie, right?
Oh. I was supposed
to pick you up. I'm sorry.
It's all good.
I got an earlier flight.
[chuckles]
-Vanilla yogurt.
-Hm.
What's wrong
with vanilla yogurt?
It's boring.
[sighs] You're not gonna
cause trouble here, are you?
I can go.
Trey?
I'm sorry. Come in.
[Tiffanie] I realized later that
Trey never answered my
question.
[exhales sharply] Does it hurt?
[sighs] I can do this.
No, you can't be trusted at all.
This one here for you.
[wincing]
Minute ago you were just trying
to kick me to the curb.
Now I'm your hero.
I wouldn't say all that.
Look, I'm sorry about what
I said earlier. It's just...
Damon has worked really hard
changing his image...
So you think I'm bad for him?
I don't know. Are you?
There you go.
Let's get you all healed up.
[mumbling]
-Thank you.
-You're good. You're welcome.
You ever been inside a cell?
Uh-uh.
There's no fresh air.
There's no trees.
Only nature you get
is cockroaches.
And everything's hard
like concrete.
Even the people.
I haven't seen anything
beautiful in seven years.
It's like, all this time
I've been cravin' things
I can't have.
And it's, it's just
been getting built up.
So I got to watch myself.
[Damon] Anybody home?
[chuckles]
Nice to meet you, Tiffanie.
[Trey] Yeah, somebody home.
[laughing] Oh, my dawg!
Ah...
Oh, I missed you, man.
-I missed you.
-A lot.
A lot of nice things here, man.
-I missed you, man.
-I missed you, too, brother.
-Look at all this, man.
-Let me show you something.
[Trey] Yeah, you got this. Yeah.
[instrumental music]
Half-back option pass.
The bottom line is...
You've always been a better
defensive player than offense.
Stop deflecting.
You had everybody
in the class believin'
that you were
the principal's nephew.
And even had the teachers
believing it.
Oh! That sounds like Damon.
Out of control. He'd been
out of control since then.
Hey, D, remember our first deal?
-Don't you tell that stor--
-Oh, bro, they jacked us--
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
We don't talk about...
I don't talk about that.
Especially in front of my lady.
Okay. My bad.
So, Tiffanie, how'd he bag
a dime piece like you?
I worked at King Enterprise.
That's how we met.
That's right, the first day
she was in the boardroom
trying to run things.
My pitch
made your company money.
You still work there, Tiff?
[Damon] No, she's about
to open up her own joint--
Hey, my man,
let your woman talk.
I'm excited, but all I can see
right now are problems.
Baby, I told you,
I can help you with that,
it's okay. I got you.
You can't just write a check
for everything, Damon.
So, D, how's your
mom and pops, bro?
They're happy that I'm finally
getting married.
Tiffanie,
your parents excited, too?
Well, her grandparents
raised her.
This tea, right here, dawg,
this tea is crazy, man. You...
-Can I get some more of this?
-Of course.
Baby, ba... Relax.
I'll go get it.
I'll get the tea.
-What happened to your finger?
-I cut it earlier.
-Oh.
-Baby, it's okay.
Uh, hey. Do not believe a word
that this man is telling you.
-I got you.
-Man...
-[Damon laughs]
-This guy right here, man.
I lost my parents, too.
[sighs] My mom was in a car
accident when I was a kid.
-I'm sorry to hear that.
-[Tiffanie] Thank you.
You know, Damon,
he was raised by the Huxtables,
you know what I'm saying?
At least when the Huxtables
meant somethin'.
Messed my boy,
I love him to death,
but... he don't know real pain.
Damon has a good heart.
Next to my grandfather,
he's the best man I know.
No doubt.
If you ever need to talk...
What'd I miss?
Here you go, bro.
Oh, thank you, brother,
appreciate that.
-I have to go.
-Babe, wait.
Where you going? Chef Louise
is about to hook up some steaks.
-Trey, you hungry?
-I can eat. I can always eat.
Yeah, I've got to meet
grandmother at the, uh,
the bridal shop.
I'll be back.
Uh-uh.
-I'll text you.
-Okay.
Bye, Tiffanie.
Mm-hmm. Mm.
Ain't got to make love
to it, man.
Man, you just don't know.
[chuckles]
Make sure you save some room
'cause Chef Louise is gonna
bring out that double-chocolate
pudding.
I'm telling you now, it's nuts.
Look, bro, I appreciate you
hooking up this trip.
Man, my room,
my room is something like
Obama was staying in.
You know what I'm sayin'?
It is crazy, bro!
I tell you, that's, uh,
Tiff's and I's favorite spot.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
Yeah, she's gonna be there
the night before our wedding.
What can I say?
My girl's traditional.
How traditional?
[laughing]
You know, I, I appreciate
all this, man. Yeah.
Trey... I got you, man.
You sure about that?
I know we got
some unfinished business.
But let's take care of it
after the wedding, okay?
-Fair enough.
-[chuckles]
-Hey, grams.
-Hey, bride.
-Oh. I'm so happy you're here.
Oh. I'm so happy, too. Oh.
We will see you at your final
fitting in just a few days.
And here's that other order.
Would you like me
to get you some tea?
-Uh, yeah. Tea would be nice.
-Mm.
Uh, Tiffanie, what's happening?
For you.
It's...
It's beautiful!
Oh!
Oh. I hope you and Damon
didn't spend a fortune on this.
Come on. Nothing is too good
for my grams.
[chuckles] Love blue,
love sparkles.
What's the matter?
Okay, come on.
Let's go sit down.
[Tiffanie] I was
clearly desperate.
Talking
to my saintly grandmother
about what was going on
in my head...
But that's how rattled I was
after meeting Trey.
So what's going on?
I'm going to tell you.
But you're not allowed
to smack me, grandma.
I'm grown now.
I can always smack you.
[laughs]
I'm not a virgin.
[coughs]
[laughs]
Did you think
I didn't know that?
Well, Damon is the only man
I've been with.
-Well, thank God for that.
-Yeah.
And I don't have anything
to compare him to, so this,
this is purely a gut feeling...
but I think our sex life
might be lacking.
Oh.
Well, before we go down
the Viagra route--
No! Uh-uh! No.
That's not the problem.
I thought... I can't talk to you
about this.
Well, maybe I can help.
Was there ever a time
that you wanted to experience
another man?
I married your grandfather
when I was just a girl.
And I wouldn't change that.
But, yes,
there were some times when...
I became interested
in other men.
And that was challenging.
Was there a someone
that you ever felt a,
like, a real connection with?
"Walk in the Spirit,
and you will not give way
to the desires of the flesh."
Our marriage vows
are not just for our husband...
they're for God.
And whenever I was tempted,
I reminded myself of that.
Is there someone
that you are craving for?
No.
No, grandma.
Do you love Damon? Hm?
Yes.
Do you feel it in there?
Mm-hmm.
Then it's real. Mm.
God made this union, baby.
He wants you and Damon
to be together.
But you watch out.
You watch out for the devil
because he will be on the hunt.
So you watch out for him.
You hear?
[Tiffanie] Was Trey the devil?
Was he sent
as some kind of test?
I don't know, but I intended
to avoid him
at all costs.
[instrumental music]
[whirring]
Let me hire more people,
I'll get you up and ready
by opening day.
[clears throat]
Were you supposed to be
in this meeting?
Well, hello to you, too.
Warner, can you do me a favor
and brief Tiffanie?
Yeah, sorry to make you recap,
Warner.
No problem.
The patio can't be salvaged.
And we're blowing circuits
all over the place,
so I suggest
we rewire the whole place.
-Ah...
-Mm.
How much?
Uh...
[chuckles] We are hemorrhaging
money at this point.
Let me take care of the tab.
[clears throat]
I, I can do the rewiring.
Yeah, I mean,
just buy the supplies.
I won't charge for labor.
I can set up each room
on its own GFI outlet,
um, that way, like, let's say a
circuit blows in this room, th--
[Tiffanie] We could keep
the spa running.
Yeah. Exactly.
Well, hell,
if you won't hire him, I will.
Man knows his stuff.
So what's it gonna be?
We need a beat to discuss.
Uh, that's fine, but if you
wanna be ready and open,
I need to know ASAP.
Okay. Can you guys
just give us a moment?
-Please?
-Sure.
-Why didn't you wait for me?
-Time is money, Tiff.
And you were late.
We had to start the meeting.
I don't want you
to use Trey, okay?
-Why?
-'Cause I wanna offer him a job.
I need to see
where his head is at first.
-I'll hire someone else.
-Mm-hmm.
You just work out your stuff
with Trey.
[Damon] Do you know
how much I love you?
Mm-hmm.
Okay. Go, go, go.
Go. I've gotta get to work.
[Rhona] So if the role play
don't work,
we're gonna bring out
the big guns.
Don't fret, baby,
we're gonna change
that funky sex life around.
You see these pills right here?
It's gonna get you just right.
-[clears throat]
-Trey!
[Rhona] So if the role play
don't work, we're gonna change
that funky sex life around.
You see these pills?
[clears throat]
Uh, that was,
I was, uh, researching.
Uh, so what are you doing here?
I've been thinking about you.
Tiffanie, you need me.
You need me to...
you need me
to do your rewiring.
Oh.
Mm-hm.
Right. Rewiring.
-What's all this?
-Oh, these are essential oils.
We use them for treatments.
Yeah.
That's eucalyptus.
[sighs]
It's very therapeutic and, uh...
They actually, they smell
way better on the body.
-You got some on?
-Mm-hmm.
My, uh, my wrist.
Mm.
-You got something else on?
-Lavender.
-Ah, yeah.
-Yeah, it's calming. Mm-hmm.
Man, that's nice, that's nice.
Well, look, I'm not leaving
until you say yes.
-Okay. I'll see you tomorrow.
-All right.
Yeah, can we just, uh,
keep this between us?
Until I tell Damon, that is.
-Oh. It's cool.
-Okay.
Let's do another one, um...
How about this one right here.
This looks like rose.
-That's rose. Mm-hmm.
-That's rose?
[instrumental music]
Um...
-[Tiffanie clears throat]
-That's nice.
That's real nice.
[Tiffanie] I should have said no
to Trey.
But my common sense
had been hijacked.
I was in the throes of lust.
[exhales sharply]
Must've been some night.
What do you mean?
You slept in your clothes.
Here.
[sighs]
I'm so tired, babe.
[exhales sharply]
You know, everybody wants to be
a entrepreneur.
They all want the glory,
but they don't wanna
put in the work.
But you, you been grindin'
since day one and...
I'm so proud.
Thank you, Damon.
You know, I was up late
last night, too.
I just kept replaying
that look on your face
when, uh, you walked in
to the meeting. You were hurt.
And I was the cause of that.
And I don't ever
wanna hurt you, Tiff.
It wasn't intentional.
No. I could do better.
I'm gonna take a step back,
you hear me?
And if you want my help,
you're gonna have to ask for it
from here on out.
Deal.
So what's the plan today?
My surprise bridal shower
is today.
Wait.
You already know about it?
Sonia knows I wanna look good.
[chuckles]
Well...
Mm-mm! I haven't brushed
my teeth yet, baby.
-You think I care?
-Oh, you should.
All right.
[inhales sharply]
Mm!
-Lavender.
-Mm-hmm.
[cell phone beeps]
[Tiffanie]
Hey Sonia, something came up,
I'll just be a few minutes
late. okay?
[upbeat music]
[knocking on door]
[Trey] What up, Tiff?
Hey, I came by to talk
about the light fixtures.
You didn't have to come
all the way down here for that.
They're pretty important,
actually,
the fixtures, aesthetically.
So... can I come in?
Yeah. I'm sorry. Come on in.
[music continues]
So I know I said those first,
but I have landed on that one.
What do you like about that one?
Ah, it's delicate, but, um,
it seems pretty robust.
You know what I mean?
I m... I mean...
[winces] Oh, shoot.
-Hm.
-What's wrong?
Was playing a little basketball
and I think I pulled somethin'.
-Oh.
-Right there.
Hm.
Oh. Um...
Right there.
-Feel that?
-Yeah, actually, I, I do.
Okay.
Let me just, uh...
Right there.
-[cell phone beeps]
-[gasps]
[exhales sharply]
Um... I have to go.
You gotta go right now?
Yeah. Uh, I gotta go.
I mean, uh, can you believe
that she's on her third divorce?
-With six kids?
-Like, can you keep a man?
-Hey!
-Oh!
-Oh! Surprise!
-Surprise!
Oh, my goodness!
I had no idea!
-We know! We know.
-[chuckling]
-Hey, beautiful!
-Hey.
Oh, Sonia, when did you have
time to decorate?
-[chuckles] Whatever, Tiff.
-[chuckles]
[pop music playing]
So, and that's like, three
different kids...
My car wouldn't start.
Girl...
I know when you're lying.
This really is beautiful.
Well... wait till
you see the cake.
-[Brenna] Ooh!
-Can I say what this one is?
-Go out with a bang.
-Whoa.
-Oh...
-Mm-hmm.
-[Brenna] I got you lace.
-[laughter]
It's about being classy
and naughty.
-[laughter]
-[Tiffanie] So give me the real.
Does sex get better or worse
over time?
Oh, girl, every marriage
is different, right?
-Yeah, yeah, we schedule it.
-Wait, what?
Okay, wait, so I, you know,
I schedule nail appointments,
hair appointments,
but I have never scheduled a...
Yeah. Have three kids
and then come talk to me.
Oh, you got it. Okay.
Have any of you
ever had an affair?
Okay, you know what?
Ground rules.
Uh, no guilt-trippin',
code of silence.
-Okay.
Have you two done anything?
-He touched my wrist.
-[laughs]
Okay. Wait a minute.
It's not funny.
-We cannot laugh.
-No.
You mean to tell me
this man touched your wrist
and got you acting like that?
-I wasn't done. Um, he...
-Okay.
He grazed my neck with his...
-With his?
-With his, his what?
-His lips, Janice, okay?
-Oh.
-[laughs] Okay.
-Wrists and lips, girl...
Sometimes I wonder,
have I ever experienced
everything I need to experience?
I, um, ahem...
I stepped out on Drew.
What?
-[Sonia] When?
-Couple of years ago.
We've been trying
to work it out ever since.
Been to therapy,
couples retreats, you name it,
and it just hasn't been
the same.
Tiffanie, word of advice.
It's not worth it.
Okay, this is a bridal shower,
not Fix My Life.
[laughter]
-Tiffanie girl, we love you.
-Yeah.
-And Damon's a good man.
-Mm-hmm.
He's gorgeous,
and most importantly,
he loves some Tiffanie.
[Janice] Yeah. Yeah, he does.
[Sonia] He does.
Look, we are your tribe, girl,
and we are here to protect you,
so, ladies, let's make sure
we stay prayed up for Tiff,
all right?
You might wanna start
them prayers now.
-You think?
-After communion.
[laughter]
[Brenna] We love you, girl.
[Kaya] Love you.
♪ Tell me what you wanna do
yeah ♪
♪ Yeah is this
what you wanna do Yeah ♪
♪ Get me going get me up
'cause oh yeah ♪
Chef Louise, thank you.
[Damon] Come on now,
say something.
I never thought I could make
this kinda money going legit.
This is crazy!
But I got some things I gotta
take care of at the house.
Come on now, talk to me, man.
I ain't seen my son yet.
Wait.
Since you've been released?
Yeah.
It's been like four months, man.
What you been doing?
I've been working. I ain't
trying to go home empty-handed.
I was right there when your pops
pulled a no-show every weekend.
All those hours you waited
for his ass to show up.
You know what it's like
to not have a father around.
[Eric] Hey, hey.
-[Damon] Hey. Ah.
-Yeah, what's happenin'?
Hey, Trey, this is Eric,
my chief operating officer,
my confidante and all that.
Uh, Eric, this is Trey, that's
my brother from another mother.
Trey, yeah,
I've heard wonderful things.
-I'm honored.
-Well, listen, uh...
I come bearing exciting news.
We have landed Justus.
-Oh, yes! Ah-ah!
-Yes.
-Oh, man, I am so proud of you!
-[Eric] Hey.
-Thanks for giving me the shine.
-I knew you had it.
I knew you had it. Ah! Whoa!
I'm telling you,
let's drink to this.
Yeah.
This is it, Trey,
definitely wanna jump on there.
It's actually
a really generous offer, Trey.
Yeah, our entry-level positions
actually start out at half that.
Well, I'm worth it, though.
Ain't I, bruh?
Hey, bro, but how about
we have some sushi, huh?
-Mm. Hey.
-Yeah.
So where'd you go to school,
man?
Uh, Vanderton.
Well, for law school, that is.
-[Trey] Vanderton. Wow.
-Yeah. Uh-huh.
I'm trying for my GED.
You think I can get in there?
I mean, brother, I think
you could do anything you want.
-Yeah.
-[chuckles]
-[Eric] Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
-Yeah, right.
Oh, man, you know,
back in the day--
You know what?
Let's bow our heads, okay?
[Eric] Dear Heavenly Father,
please bless the food
that is on our plates and bless
the hands that prepared it.
In Your Son's name we pray.
Amen.
Like I was saying, you know,
back in the day,
the only lawyer
Damon ever needed
was a public defender.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Please, do not tell
those stories.
Ah, this-this one's funny, man.
Look, it was like
a buck twenty and--
Damn it! Trey, please.
I said enough.
Well, let's have some sushi,
all right?
[Damon] It's a good day. Hey.
[Eric] Yeah.
[Tiffanie] Do you think we
should have waited till marriage
to have sex?
Do you?
[Tiffanie] I don't know.
Maybe.
And why are you asking this now?
Hm, maybe we should try.
Try what, baby?
Celibacy.
Let's wait
until our wedding night.
You okay?
[chuckles]
That is just silly.
Why is it silly?
Because we're get married
in a couple of days.
-So what's the point?
-[sighs] Forget it.
Oh, what, what's goin' on
with you?
You have not been
acting like yourself lately.
What, is a wisp of hair
out of place?
Well, where are you going?
Back to your apartment?
[sighs]
Downstairs.
Cooling off.
[dramatic music]
Trey...
Yes.
[Damon] Tiffanie?
Compromise?
What?
Pastor Cooper said
that compromise
was one of the bedrocks
of marriages.
And if you wanna be celibate,
it's okay with me.
[sighs] Thank you.
The food tasting's at 4:00,
and I want you to come.
What? You actually
want to include me?
Yes. And I have a surprise
for you.
And if you don't show up,
I'm gonna start buying you
Prince CDs.
[both laughing]
Love Jones.
Come on, challenge me.
Tiff, you still love me?
Of course I do, silly.
Okay. I'll see you then.
[Damon chuckles]
[instrumental music]
-What are you doing?
-Nothing. Damn!
Since when did we start talking
to each other like that?
I don't have time for this.
You were supposed to wire me
the money.
We had to press pause
on some stuff.
I'll handle it.
-Are you sure, boss-lady?
-Yeah.
[Tiffanie] I was officially
in the danger zone.
Not handling my business,
being a bad friend
and a worse fiancee.
I didn't know this woman.
This self-destructive mess
was a stranger to me.
-I got two sandwiches.
-I can't. I'm meeting Damon.
Come on. Even CEOs got to eat.
All right. What you got?
This is the one
with him in his costume.
Aww, look
at your little superhero.
Aww, it must have been
really hard to be away from him.
It was.
So, why a spa?
Oh, self-care, you know,
it strengthens the foundation.
Alleviates stress,
which increases happiness.
You'd be surprised what
a simple head massage would do.
I've never had one.
-No way.
-Ever.
Come here.
Mm! Okay.
Damn, girl.
[intense music]
Trey, we can't.
Baby, we've already started.
[instrumental music]
[footsteps approaching]
[Phyllis] Everything is ready.
Heard anything yet?
You know, she's probably
just caught up at work.
Yeah.
Let's stick with the lobster.
Okay.
Well, the, uh, stylists
are on the way with the tuxes.
Thank you.
[intense music]
[Tiffanie] This is Tiffanie.
Please leave me a message.
-[voicemail beeps]
-Hey, baby.
[Damon on voicemail]
Uh, where are you?
[exhales sharply]
Trey, there's people
right outside.
I'm sayin', just one kiss.
Then I'll leave.
[music continues]
[Tiffanie] Wow.
Oh, Tiffanie,
you look so beautiful.
I can't wait
for Damon to see you in it.
-Aww...
-Oh, God! Damon!
-What?
-We were supposed to meet.
It's dead! It's dead!
Breathe, breathe, mama.
Sonia, I'm about
to screw everything up.
Listen, now, I'll call Damon
and tell him
you got held up at work.
-Just finish the fitting, okay?
-Okay.
You have some things
you need to work out,
but just not right now.
-All right. Hold on. Mm-hmm.
-I got you.
-Call him.
[sighs]
[mumbling]
Oh, yeah, it's gonna fit.
It is gonna fit nice.
I've been thinking about you
often, man, you know,
joining the company.
I'm in. I'm all the way in.
So the boys
are back together again.
[chuckles] Yeah.
At least
something's going right.
What you mean, bro?
Why you all gloom and doom?
Tiff. She didn't show up
for the tasting.
Well, she was at the spa
earlier.
-What were you doing at the spa?
-She didn't tell you?
Bro, I'm doing the lights.
Doing the lights, man.
[intense music]
But this Armani, though.
Oh, yeah.
[Tiffanie exhales sharply]
I'm sorry.
You don't wanna marry me,
do you?
Damon, all I did was forget.
Tiff, you didn't just forget.
Either you're distant
or you're annoyed.
You tell me you don't want
my help, but then I find out
that Trey's working
at Urban Utopia.
You can stop me anytime, Tiff.
I'm just so overwhelmed
with everything--
Baby... that song's played out.
Sometimes I think
we got together
for the wrong reasons.
What do you mean?
[exhales sharply]
Well...
You, you met me,
girl from the church, pure.
And you thought
I'd be good for your image.
That's not true.
I was a ball of clay
and you molded me into
your idea of the perfect woman.
And I let you.
Maybe we should think about
postponing the wedding.
Tiff, our wedding,
that's in 48 hours.
Now, I know we got some things
that we have to work out,
but we have
our whole entire lives to do so.
Baby...
please marry me.
[cell phone vibrating]
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
[Tiffanie] What do you want?
To show you this.
They're on a sensor.
What do you think?
I think you're fired. Get out.
You serious right now?
What's wrong?
I'm about to marry
your best friend, Trey.
-Yeah, but, Tiffanie--
-Leave.
Leave!
[sighs]
I told you to leave.
Look, I'mma make sure
you get to your car safe.
-And then I'm out.
-I don't need you.
Well, I'm gonna make sure
you safe.
Everything was fine
until you came around!
If everything was fine,
you wouldn't have kissed me.
-I don't do this.
-Maybe you've been hiding.
Maybe you're becoming
who you are.
You don't know me.
I hate you! I hate you!
[sobbing] Go!
[dramatic music]
[moans]
No.
[sobbing]
Tiffanie?
[indistinct chatter]
'Cause I want you to be
prepared.
-Yes.
♪ And you're getting married ♪
♪ You're getting married ♪
Your mama would be so proud.
-Grandma.
-I'm proud. Oh, golly!
-[laughter]
-Oh.
Well, I think I better get back,
go help Damon out.
-All right.
-All right?
-I'll see y'all tonight?
-Absolutely.
-Okay. Bye, baby. Bye.
-Bye.
[church bells tolling]
[sighs]
Trey?
What are you doin' here?
I'm not welcome at your church?
-Everybody's welcome.
-Amen.
[chuckling]
You at the Willard Park tonight,
right?
Your car's waiting.
I'll be at the bar
until midnight.
Bye, Trey.
[upbeat music]
[indistinct chatter]
Look at this. Look at this.
Look at this man right here.
[chuckles]
Hey, family!
We're not finished partying
just yet, okay?
But I do wanna take this moment
to thank you all for coming out,
supporting me
and my beautiful bride-to-be.
I'm grateful. Yeah.
And the reason why I'm grateful
is because of
this beautiful woman
right in front of me.
You know, I'mma save
all those poetic words
for my vows tomorrow.
But I do wanna take this moment
to acknowledge my queen.
Thank you for saying yes.
Look good tonight, Tiff.
[Damon] So in the spirit of
gettin' down,
I wanna dedicate this next tune
to my beautiful bride.
[instrumental music]
Hey.
[both chuckling]
These guys...
[indistinct chatter]
[Sonia] I'll be back.
[Sonia] But seriously,
this, this is beautiful.
[Tiffanie] It really is. Wow.
[Sonia] The views!
[sighs]
Oh, it's nice.
[Sonia] Oh...
[sighs]
Did you sleep with him?
No.
But I want to.
You want me to stay?
I think I need to be alone.
All right, remember,
tomorrow you marry the man
that you love.
-All right.
-Well, okay. Mm...
-See you tomorrow.
-All right.
-Thanks for everything.
-You're welcome, friend.
-Love you.
-I love you more, Sonia.
[sighs]
[Tiffanie] I fully admit it.
I was a mess.
Trey said he'd be at the bar
until midnight...
[instrumental music]
♪ Some people say I'm crazy ♪
♪ What am I to you lately? ♪
♪ This is more
than just a game to me ♪
♪ And every time
you smile babe ♪
♪ It brings joy to my face ♪
♪ I want for this to stay ♪
[music continues]
[Tiffanie] If only I stayed
in the bed that night.
If only, if only, if only...
But when I look back,
we were speeding towards
this moment the day we met.
[upbeat music]
[vase shatters]
[both moaning]
Tiffanie...
[cell phone vibrating]
[Trey] You want me?
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
How bad do you want me?
Bad. Take this off.
-Answer one more question.
-Mm-hmm.
What would Damon say
if he saw you like this?
What?
Damon was my brother.
I would have died for him.
I thought
he would've done the same.
But he screwed me over.
And all I've dreamt about
for seven years is revenge.
So when your punk-ass husband
brings you here
tomorrow night...
you think about this.
You think about me.
[sobbing] No...
No...
[Tiffanie sobbing]
[Tiffanie] Oh, no.
What have I done?
-[Tiffanie sobbing]
-[cell phone vibrating]
[knocking on door]
[grandma] Tiffanie? Tiffanie.
Oh, it's all right, she's fine.
Thank you.
Tiff...
Tiff?
Tiffanie, it's grandma.
Honey, what's the matter? Huh?
What's the matter, baby?
-Yo? What up, babe?
-Hm?
Come on, come on, come on.
It's time to get it right.
Yeah!
Met someone last night.
-At Willard Park?
-Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Beautiful, smart, kinky.
Oh, yeah? Already?
Oh, me, I mean,
you know how I do.
I mean, we played around
a little bit.
You know what I'm sayin'?
But, uh,
Tiff made you wait, huh?
-No, she made me work.
-Hm.
Yeah, you know, she gone
and asked me the other day,
"Baby, do you think we should
have waited?" I'm like...
-"What are you talking about?"
-Whoa, whoa, bro, bro, bro.
You goin' soft on me, man?
No.
I just don't want my lady
living with regret.
Trey, speaking of regrets,
seven years ago--
No. No. No! We're not gonna
do that today, bruh.
Look, about any of that,
what's done is done.
I feel a lot better
after last night, man.
I got a lot off my chest.
My brother.
Now, let's get to it.
Come on, man.
-It's your day, baby!
-Look at that, clean!
-That's what you doin'?
-Yeah.
That's what you doin'?
Hoo.
Well,
this is some revenge plot.
Trey must've been working
on this for a long time.
Seven years.
And why is Damon be so oblivious
to his hatred?
He had me fooled, too.
I think he's gonna tell Damon.
Well, he hasn't told him yet.
[sighs] Don't you let Trey win.
He's taken enough already.
Do you think I have time
to get my dress steamed?
[violin music]
Thank you.
[music continues]
[instrumental "Bridal Chorus"]
Well, go on, honey. Come on.
[Trey] You think about this.
You think about me.
[Tiffanie sobbing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Damon] Tiff?
[Cooper] Hold on a second.
L-ladies and gentlemen, listen.
We will, we gonna, we will be
right back. Right back.
[intense music]
[sighing]
[knocking on door]
[grandma] Tiffanie?
-Can I come in, please?
-I can't do it.
-[knocking on door]
-[Damon] Open the door, Tiff.
Baby, what's going on?
Damon...
Please, you can't tell me
you can't marry me.
I messed up.
What's wrong? What happened?
I was with someone.
[intense music]
You cheated on me?
Who is he, Tiff?
Who is it, Tiff?
It's over. It doesn't matter.
-I'm sorry, Damon.
-Yeah, you are sorry?
You couldn't tell me this
sooner?
I got a house full of people
down there!
My family's down there!
Was everything
not enough for you?
Because that's what I gave you.
You asked for it,
I gave it to you!
Before you came to think
about it, I gave it to you!
Why, Tiff?
I gave you everything!
[Cooper] Damon.
-[knocking on door]
-[Cooper] Open the door, son.
Listen to me, son. Listen to me.
-You're too angry right now.
-I'm so sorry...
Go back and talk later when you,
when you calm down, all right?
Pastor, I would never
put my hands on this woman.
I understand, son,
but you're angry.
And-and you wait till
you calm down and then talk.
I hope it was worth it, Tiff.
-I hope he was worth it.
-No.
-Stop--
-I'mma pack your stuff.
-[sobbing] Damon...
-It's okay, it's okay.
-Damon.
It's okay. It's okay.
[Tiffanie sobbing]
It is all right. It's all right.
It's all right. Baby,
it's all right. It's all right.
It's okay. You'll be
all right. It's okay. Shh.
[instrumental music]
♪ Baby I need some time alone ♪
♪ To be by myself by myself ♪
How's my girl today?
Grandpa already left
for the church.
I thought
we could go in together.
Good dose of the Lord
heals everything, baby.
♪ By myself ♪
Can you ask Him
when it'll stop hurting?
You ask Him yourself.
♪ Than I need
alone on the floors ♪
♪ So now I've forgotten
how to bleed ♪
♪ Careful what you wish for ♪
So, um, any idea
who it could be?
It could be somebody
you did wrong.
♪ Careful what you wish for ♪
I got somebody tracking her.
I spent ten years trying to bury
the old Damon King.
Oh, I didn't, I didn't know
you still kept a piece, bro.
It's been a long time
since I held one.
Yo, Damon, don't, don't point
that gun at me, man.
♪ I wish everything would ♪
And that's it,
the old Damon King is back.
[indistinct singing]
♪ Say He's great
and mighty yes ♪
♪ He's great and mighty yeah ♪
♪ Great and mighty ♪
That's all right.
That young lady really can sing.
The devil
don't come into your house...
-Unless you invite him.
-[congregation] Amen.
It's easy
to invite the devil in,
but it's hard to get him out!
-Amen.
-Mm...
Y'all know I don't like
to get too raunchy,
but sex feels good.
-Come on, somebody!
-[indistinct chatter]
[Cooper] But you know
what the problem is,
you got to pay the piper.
If you gonna invite
the devil in
and you gonna dance with
the devil, you gotta pay up!
You gonna pay the devil back
the way
he wants to be paid back.
And the reason for that is
because now the devil owns you!
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] Come on, pastor.
But I'm here to tell you,
God ain't going nowhere.
[congregation] Amen!
[Cooper] Now, you may, uh,
turn your back on God,
but you see, God ain't gonna
never turn his back on you.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[applause]
Hallelujah!
[Sonia] You seem better.
[Tiffanie] I am. I don't know
what's next, though.
Well, how about opening up
Urban Utopia?
You do remember the spa, right?
Your lifelong dream?
-I blew the opening.
-Look, we'll open when we open.
Enough, sis.
Look, you gotta stop
giving Trey all your power.
Okay.
-Let's do it.
Let's do it.
Hm. I got you, girl.
[Sonia] So listen,
I did get some things,
the color scheme
that you wanted.
Don't you even worry about that.
[knocking on door]
I came to say thank you.
When you said that I was hiding,
you were right.
I'm glad I could do you a solid.
Looks like my job is done here.
My only regret is that
I hurt Damon in the process.
He's a good man, Trey.
Whatever happened between you,
he would never hurt you
intentionally.
This girl
trying to guilt-trip me?
Just so you know, I didn't lose
a wink of sleep last night.
Okay?
-Father God in heaven--
-Oh, damn, here we go.
Please heal
Brother Trey's heart.
Please remove that anger.
-Set him free, Lord.
-Look.
Hey, get the hell
outta here with all that.
I'm not doin' all that.
Let him know
the way to freedom
is forgiveness,
because there is good in him.
-Leave.
-He's a good man, Lord.
He's just in pain.
Please let him know
that he's loved,
that he matters.
In Jesus' name. Amen.
-[sighs]
-[line ringing]
[Damon] You've reached
Damon King.
Please leave a brief message.
[voicemail beeps]
Um, I didn't wanna do this,
um, on your voicemail, I...
You just,
you won't take my calls. I...
And you have,
you have every right not to.
I want you to know, though...
I will never stop loving you,
Damon King.
Ever.
My soul has this...
this big, gaping hole in it
and...
[sighs] I'm so sorry.
I should have never tried to be
perfect, 'cause I'm far from it.
But I like this Tiffanie, too.
And, you know...
and I want you to meet her.
I hope you call me back, Damon.
Even if it takes 50 years,
I hope you call me back.
I love you, Damon.
[indistinct chatter]
[Trey] I don't know
what's up with your boys.
Wilding on me.
You better tell 'em who I am.
You slept with Tiffanie?
-You abandoned me that night.
-I told you to pack it in.
I gave you a call as soon as
I found out the place was hot.
-You left me a voicemail!
-I got two strikes!
And I wasn't doing life
for your greedy ass!
You know what your problem is?
You have always been hard-headed
and you ain't shit!
Your girl would disagree.
Look at you.
She got you whipped like that.
I didn't sleep with her.
I could've, though.
You should have came after me.
No fun in that, playboy.
You got to take better care
of your women, D.
This was like
taking candy from a baby.
Release.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[grunting]
[groans]
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct yelling]
I let you in my damn house,
Trey!
You want it? You want it?
-You want to die?
-Do it!
If I kill you...
that means your son grow up
without a father.
That's how much I love your son.
That's how much I love you, man.
Well, son or no son,
if I ever see you
in my city again...
There's something else
around here.
Let's go!
Move!
[car engine starts]
[instrumental music]
[Damon] Why Trey?
Damon, what happened?
Why?
He-he was just a deflection.
I just couldn't get a grasp on
what was happening between us.
And I, and honestly
I don't know if you...
if you saw me
for who I really am.
And that scared me.
You're an amazing man, Damon.
Please tell me
you didn't do anything stupid.
I came close.
But that's not me anymore, Tiff.
And if that's what
you want, Tiff...
I want you. You, Damon.
My, my heart
may never recover.
But I'm miserable without you.
Can we start over?
Hi.
My name is Tiffanie.
You're gonna let my hand,
my hand fall off?
[sobbing]
[Tiffanie] So we began again.
Can I just feed you cereal
every day?
-Hm?
-Mm-hmm.
[sighs]
And I ran point in my own life.
I was me.
Unapologetically me.
Uh, again, the spa is called
Urban Utopia.
And, uh, we service...
We were celibate.
I didn't do it for Damon.
I did it for me.
My relationship with God
needed a clean slate, too.
Then, one year later,
we were ready.
♪ I tried to write you a song ♪
♪ That no one's
ever heard before ♪
♪ Wrote lines
and words of our love ♪
♪ But somehow it needed more ♪
♪ Oh maybe the way
that our hearts became true ♪
♪ Is the same way they all do ♪
♪ When I wake up ♪
♪ I want to see the sun shine ♪
♪ Across your face ♪
♪ When I walk with you
I want your hand in mine ♪
♪ In your pocket space ♪
♪ Our love is typical ♪
It wasn't crazy lust
like with Trey.
This was something new.
Something we created.
Oh, and, uh, let's just say
there were no more problems
when it came to, you know...
[Damon] You ready? Car's packed,
just needs us three.
-Mm!
-Ooh.
[both chuckling]
-Are you ready?
-Oh, I could live anywhere.
As long as I have you
and peanut.
-What you got there?
-Oh.
Just a little something
for the new home owners.
They seem like
such a sweet family, baby.
Yeah.
-[Damon] All right.
-It's time to go.
-Let's get to our new home.
-[Tiffanie chuckles]
[vocalization]
♪ I tried to write you a song ♪
♪ That no one's
ever heard before ♪
♪ Wrote lines
and words of our love ♪
♪ But somehow it needed more ♪
♪ Oh maybe the way
that our hearts became true ♪
♪ Is the same way they all do ♪
♪ When I wake up
♪ I want to see the sun shine ♪
♪ Across your face ♪
♪ When I walk with you ♪
♪ I want your hand in mine... ♪