Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
She's here.
Welcome, doctor.
SEX, SHAME AND TEARS 2
Why did you take my...?
I already told you
not to touch my script, dad!
Can't you lock the door?
Can't you knock?
It's the third time this week.
It's the fifth.
Mom!
Ana...
Matilde, you're the one who came in.
I know, but...
Why do you take my things?
I just wanted
to read your play to support you.
It's poorly written, by the way.
I don't need your help
nor your comments, dad.
You should learn to lock the door.
You should learn to knock.
Hello.
I'm looking for Ana.
I'm Ana.
I'm Mateo, Tomás' son.
- London?
- Yes.
- How old are you?
- I'm 27.
No. It's not possible.
The dates don't match.
Tomás was not there by then.
I think the same,
but look at his face.
It seems Tomás came in here
20 years later.
I don't understand
why he didn't tell us
about his 7-year-old "son."
My father didn't know.
Is that what you think?
I know that story.
My mother never told him.
Who's your mother?
My mother?
Yes. Where's she?
She's dead.
I'm sorry.
Is that why you're here?
- You're trying to find Tomás.
- No.
Because if you're trying
to find Tomás, there's a problem.
No, I'm not looking for my father.
So?
I have an exhibition
by the end of next week.
OK. So?
Are you a photographer?
I'm a visual artist.
What's your last name?
Nava.
Are you kidding?
- What?
I follow you?
You've got to be kidding.
Did you do this?
What is it?
He's got
around five million followers.
Ana, do you know him?
Are you Tomás' son?
Yes, my father was a friend
of your parents.
But my father killed himself.
What?
Yes. In the elevator
of this same building.
Right?
That's why
you don't use the elevator.
Who told you that?
How do you know it?
My uncle told me.
You never told me
Tomás killed himself here.
Maybe what your uncle told you
is not exactly... I mean...
Did you come to stay here?
If you need to stay here, it's OK.
You can stay as long as you want,
while you...
Ana! Please.
Mati, show him the guest room.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
Are you crazy?
What's wrong with you?
Carlos, please.
What's Ram Dass Sangh like in person?
Ram Dass Singh.
- He's a good person.
- Really?
He likes my music.
He told me he studied in India.
Is he Mexican?
Yes, but he got enlightened.
In India?
Yes, that's what he told me.
What are you doing today?
I need to go to the doctor.
Remember we were going to borrow
some money from your mother.
Yes. She said yes.
Cool.
I'll pay her back after the retreat.
You'd better.
I love you.
Shut up.
Mom!
Come in!
Still in bed?
Look at the time.
Won't you be late?
- No, I can make it.
- No?
Good morning.
My sweetheart.
Listen, I need to borrow
the money I told you about.
- This girl.
- Come on!
- Hand me my purse.
- OK.
I'll pay you back.
- Of course, you'll pay me back.
- Yes, of course.
When?
I don't doubt you'll pay me back,
I just want to know when.
In one month. Give me a month.
We agreed you'd give me a month.
Don't take this for granted.
Nobody's going to lend you money
and give you one month to pay it back.
- I just want you to know that.
- But you're my mom.
You brat.
I'll leave you alone.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
All right.
Jeez, I can't take this.
Did she notice?
- I get too nervous.
- Why?
You know why.
I don't want to keep sneaking around.
- Where are you going?
- To take a shower. Get dressed.
I'll join you.
Look at this.
It's Tomás.
Is it Tomás? They're identical.
Listen...
- So, Tomás killed himself here?
- No...
Yes.
What's he here for?
It's just that when I look
at his face...
I thought I had already overcome
Tomás' death.
Why did mom act like that?
Those were complicated times.
Tomás and she were very close.
Is that why she's got that temper?
No, she's always had that temper.
Listen. Go talk to him.
Yes. Try to find out why he's here.
Go.
For Christ's sake, Beny.
PEDIATRICIAN
Your two prescriptions.
Two prescriptions?
Yes. One for you
and one for your girlfriend.
No, no. You've got to be kidding.
Why two prescriptions?
I don't need two prescriptions.
What am I going to tell her?
Off you go.
If I add some more thyme,
does it enhance its flavor?
- I don't think you should add any.
- OK.
Rigo, I need more eggs.
More eggs?
Yes, please.
All right.
He has been a bit whiny, hasn't he?
- Don't mention it.
- I think his boyfriend dumped him.
No, I mean it.
No, not in here. Not in here.
Why not?
This is not the place.
Someone might see us.
Andrea, if this is not
the place, where?
Because I'm tired
of hiding in the closet.
OK? What's the problem
if they know we love each other?
I don't know what to say.
Especially, if you tell me that here.
UNKNOWN NUMBER
I don't know who this is.
Then tell me, what do you think?
I don't know.
Back up, please.
It's not appropriate.
I don't know.
In this place...
Who's calling?
UNKNOWN NUMBER
Hello?
Good afternoon.
Yes, it's me.
How come?
But... María what?
It's almost a miracle.
She's got injuries
all over her body, but...
A sprain on her left knee,
a wound on her right shoulder.
But that's it.
From the fourth floor?
That's what the reports say.
What the hell was she thinking?
She was not thinking.
She needs to stay
under observation for a few days,
and receive psychiatric assessment.
- Don't leave her alone.
- No. Don't worry about it.
Thank you very much, doctor.
Excuse me.
You just showed up like that
without even calling.
You could have called first,
like normal people do,
and avoid making
this foolish entrance.
What the hell is going on?
María.
What are you doing?
Why don't you have an accent?
Because my mother was Mexican.
Are you kidding?
No.
Tomás traveled 5,544 miles
to sleep with a Mexican woman?
You should have seen
what a Mexican woman she was.
How do you know
he traveled 5,544 miles?
I'm good at geography.
- Was she beautiful?
- Very beautiful.
Do you want to go out?
Katia!
Girl, what the hell?
I sent you like a hundred messages!
We received a little surprise.
Mateo.
Hello.
Do you see this?
I thought no one was coming.
No one? Fatty's a freaking rock star
playing that shit
nobody knows how to pronounce.
Didgeridoo.
I'll go get a drink.
Do you want something?
- A beer.
- Same for me.
- OK.
- I'll go with you.
Who's the freak?
Mateo, Tomás' son.
Who's Tomás?
Tomás!
Did he have a son?
Yes. Tomás killed himself
in my building's elevator.
That's why your mother
doesn't use the elevator!
That's why!
- No way!
- Yes!
My dear, take it easy.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what happened to me.
I just got tired of everything.
I'm tired.
I'm tired of living.
I didn't think...
You don't have to speak.
You don't have to tell us anything.
Yes. I don't want more secrets.
We need to tell the truth.
María, listen to me.
You need to rest.
You need to sleep. All right?
We're here.
The three of us.
Hey, pretty boots.
Can you hold the door for me?
The lock is broken.
What are you doing in there?
What do you think I'm doing?
One of two things,
and I don't want to be in there
if you're taking a dump.
I'm peeing
almost half a gallon of beer.
- That's OK.
- Thank you.
What's your name?
Katia. And you?
Sam.
Hello, Sam.
Hello.
I'm done.
Thank...
Thank you.
OK.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Well, you told me
you were going to stay here,
so I brought you dinner.
How's your friend?
She jumped from the fourth floor,
and nothing happened to her.
What?
Thank you for dinner.
I love you.
- Andrea.
- What the hell? She scared me.
What is it?
Miguel?
No. Don't summon Satan.
He's Alberto.
You don't know him.
Miguel.
Yes, dear,
in your nightmares, he's Miguel.
YOUR DRIVER HAS ARRIVED
Samantha?
No. I'm Katia.
I'm here for Samantha.
I'm Samantha.
I'm sorry. I thought it was mine.
Don't worry.
Um... Do you want a lift?
I was rejected
by the hottest guy in the place.
I tried, but nothing worked.
I mean, who understands them?
What do they want?
Look at my shades, my hair, my top...
In tonight's
"Most romantic videos at midnight,"
a woman proposes to some guy
in the bathroom.
Smile, handsome!
What the fuck? Give me that!
Give me that! Come on!
Because, in the past, like...
20 years ago, I think,
I used to work around here.
This was my route,
from here to Polanco.
I sold oranges on a truck
with my husband.
But he died five years ago.
I didn't dare to come here
from the ranch
with the oranges on my own.
So I decided to learn how to drive,
sold the truck and bought this car.
Since then,
I've been working as a driver.
You were gone for a while.
Where were you?
I was drinking with a friend of mine.
Hey, there.
Hey!
Ohana, my friend!
Welcome, my brother.
- Have this.
- All right.
Here you go.
- Mati. My love, how are you?
- Hello. I'm fine, and you?
I'm fine. It's nice to see you.
Come on. Give me a strong hug.
- This feels good.
- How are you?
Hello.
Hello. How are you?
Come with me.
Let's give ourselves in!
Welcome.
We're ready to take off.
Let me introduce you to Mateo,
our new crew member.
You already know
this damn San Bernardo.
Finally, you brought a handsome one.
Hello, Mati.
What's that?
DMT.
Come on. Get over here.
Are you going to do it?
Definitely.
What about you?
That's my thing.
- Yes.
- That's nice.
What about you?
Yes.
All right.
Mateo!
Mateo.
I'm sorry.
Did the fool wake up?
Turn it off. Turn it off.
- Very good. Are you all right?
- Yes. I'm all right.
Can you make it home?
Yes. I think it's that way, isn't it?
Here, here.
Mateo.
Yes?
How did she die?
My mother?
Cancer.
I'm sorry.
Good night.
LORE NEW MESSAGE
Smile, handsome!
What the fuck? Give me that!
Beny.
What the hell?
The hell is this video
everybody's watching in the chats.
No shit.
This was last night, right?
You're wearing the same clothes.
Did Kat watch it?
She hasn't told me anything,
but she'll find out eventually.
Shit.
- Shit.
- Go see her!
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll go see her.
BENY INCOMING CALL
Good morning, Carlitos.
It'll surprise you
how much you're like your father.
I don't know. I didn't know him.
Do you live alone?
Yes.
On the weekends,
I visit my grandparents near London.
How long are you planning
to stay here?
I don't know. A couple of weeks.
Good.
What do you do?
I'm a writer.
What do you write?
Books.
Good morning.
Do you have rehearsal?
Rehearsal?
Theater.
Do you study theater?
It's a workshop.
You should come by.
Bye, mom.
Bye, Mati.
I'm going out to take some pictures.
OK.
Do you want to come?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
Let me get my shoes.
What?
What are you looking at?
Your ass.
You need to go back to the gym.
Maybe I'll go to the same gym
you've never been
in your damned life.
You curly asshole.
Let's go.
See you around, curly.
Listen...
Can I ask you a question?
Yes.
Your vagina is different, isn't it?
I'd say it's way too different.
Really?
Well, yes.
It wasn't always like this.
How "like this"?
It wasn't always a vagina.
What are you doing here?
What are you two doing here?
We're having breakfast.
She's Sam.
She stayed here last night.
I thought
you were exhausted last night.
Yes, but it was a last-minute thing.
Sam didn't have a place to stay.
Hello.
Well, I'll go get changed.
OK.
What is it?
Who's Sam?
She's a friend.
Why don't I know her?
Because she's not your friend.
Did she spend the night here?
Where did you spend the night?
At Mati's.
What did you do after the party?
That's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
Don't tell me you got a blowjob
and you were recorded.
How did you know?
50,000 people and I saw it.
Aren't you mad?
- No. Why?
- You're not breaking up with me?
Why would I do that?
I cheated on you.
No, you didn't.
I don't expect you to be faithful.
You're not a damned penguin.
But it would be great if you weren't
the GIF people send in their chats,
because we're together somehow, Beny.
A viral video is not the way
to tell people
we're in an open relationship.
Are we in an open relationship?
Yes.
Aren't we?
It's OK.
- Good.
OK...
As we're talking things over,
I want to seize the opportunity
to tell you
that you need to take some pills.
Hey, what are you doing?
You look a lot like your father.
I wouldn't know. I didn't know him.
He made me...
He made me feel... unique.
It seems he did that to everyone.
Let me take a picture of you.
No, I don't like it.
Stand there, and let me
take a picture of you.
No.
Were you there?
What?
When my father died.
Really?
Do you really want to talk about it?
Yes.
Where were you exactly?
At the apartment's door.
What's the distance
between the apartment's door
and the elevator's door?
How should I know that?
What about Carlos?
He was next to me.
- At the apartment's door?
- Yes.
What about Miguel?
Miguel?
At the apartment's door.
What size was that fucking door?
The three of you were
at the apartment's door,
and none of you did anything.
What were we supposed to have done?
- What?
- I don't know.
Maybe stop him from killing himself.
We had had an argument.
With my father?
Yes.
The three of you?
Your father didn't want
to be there any longer.
Did you want him to stay longer?
Your father was...
Well...
difficult.
That's why you kicked him out.
- What?
- Of the apartment.
Do you think that we kicked
your father out of the apartment?
I think my father wasn't well,
and you didn't help him.
Andrea.
We're leaving.
We're going to the...
Is he...?
I'm Tomás' son.
- María, Andrea.
- Yes.
Could you push her?
Yes.
- Listen, why did you bring him here?
- He wanted to meet you, guys.
Yes, but not here.
We're going to see the psychiatrist.
Well, that's why.
Hello.
So, my father and you...
Your father was terrible.
He was a mess.
That's enough, boy.
That's funny.
Fool.
You're the fool.
She's the real fool who jumped off.
Don't make me laugh.
SO EARLY AROUND HERE?
I'M BORED.
I CAN FIX THAT.
DO YOU PROMISE?
BOY SCOUT'S WORD.
HEY...
TELL ME.
I'M MARRIED. YOU DON'T MIND?
NOT AT ALL.
I'M IN AN OPEN RELATIONSHIP.
You slept with him.
I know it.
I can see it in your eyes.
We're not pure anymore.
Do you understand me?
Every time you touch me,
I'll be thinking you touched him.
We can start from scratch.
Start from scratch?
You cheated on me!
Please...
I didn't know what I was doing.
You didn't know what you were doing.
I've always given you everything.
- When...
- Sorry!
Can we stop?
Matilde, we've been
many times through this.
Yes. She always interrupts
when I'm about to start my monologue.
Let's do it again, please.
You slept with him.
I know it.
I can see it in your eyes.
We're not pure anymore.
Do you understand me?
No.
Sorry?
- It's ridiculous!
- What?
"What?"
Yes, Matilde, what?
I'm not following you.
What the hell do you mean
by "We're not pure"?
Can't he get over the fact
that she slept with another man?
It's just sex.
Some of us do want
a closed relationship.
That's why we broke up.
Matilde, doesn't an emotional
infidelity mean anything to you?
There are already apps
to screw strangers.
Are we still making a fuss
because of infidelity?
Isn't there anything more interesting
to tell about two people
who love each other?
Matilde, the play
is called "Infidelity".
Well, even the title is wrong!
OK. Well...
I think we've spent
too many hours working.
Let's wrap it up for today.
And once again,
I didn't do my monologue.
- Thank you, Mati.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes. Unfortunately.
We need another actress.
I like your progressive mentality.
It may have to do
with the fact that Jimmy,
Mr. "We're not pure anymore,"
is my ex-boyfriend,
who broke up with me
because I cheated on him.
And the director is one
of those idiots who write
about the experiences
of his actors.
Shall we leave?
Yes. I'll go get changed.
Fidelity is the way we've found
to hold on to someone enough time
to get old and have someone there
to feed us baby food
and change our diapers.
The truth is
that we're afraid of being alone,
and that's what we call love.
My mother wasn't
with anyone else after Tomás.
That's what you think.
They sure went to your house
and told you they were your uncles.
She called them "co-workers."
But they used to leave
in the same way they came in.
My mother wouldn't let them stay.
One way or another,
she was always with Tomás.
She ended up with a nurse
who fed her baby food with a spoon
and changed her diapers.
But she didn't regret a thing.
Some cycles need to be completed,
but it would be nice
to find someone to get old with,
a friend, a couple.
What do I know?
Isn't that Beny?
What the hell?
- What happened?
- Do you have something I can put on?
- I've got a dress here.
- Give it to me.
Hop on. Put the helmet on.
Hurry, hurry!
You son of a bitch!
Come back, son of a bitch!
Did you always know?
Yes, I've always known
since I have memory.
Since I was a child,
I've been like this. I've been Sam.
Everybody could notice, you know?
It's not like I've been
through such a big change.
In school, my friends, my family.
I met Fichas in elementary school.
We were the freaky ones.
- Is that so?
- That's why we got along.
What about your parents?
- They're cool with it.
- Really?
- Yes.
The truth is that I was very lucky
because it's not the usual reaction.
Right.
Cut it out, you fuckers.
Beny, you can join me later
in the bathroom. I saw this video,
and I thought of some
really good blowjobs we can perform.
You're so funny.
What...?
What are you doing here?
Sam is a friend of Fichas.
- She's Matilde.
- Hello.
- He's Tomás.
- Mateo.
I'm sorry, Mateo.
You already know the lady in dress.
Hello.
I'm Beny.
What's with the dress?
I was hot.
You have an exhibition coming.
Mati told me.
- Yes.
- What is it about?
I've edited some photographs
of people who've changed my life.
Do you mean your girlfriends?
Yes. My couples...
and people who've been with me
and taking care of me.
Like your parents.
Well, curiously,
I didn't know my father.
Really?
I didn't know mine, either.
What happened to him?
My mother told me
it was a romantic night,
she got pregnant,
and then he disappeared.
Just like Tomás.
Kind of.
So, you two never knew your fathers.
I've only seen him in pictures.
Is that so?
Yes, look. In fact...
I don't even have one.
I really don't need it.
Right?
- Do you want to get some drinks?
- Yes. Let's do it.
Cheers.
"Gringuito"!
You can sleep in Katia's bedroom.
She doesn't come home
to sleep as much as I wish.
But you'll feel great.
You can't drink.
I'm sorry. You can't drink.
- It's just that you can't.
- OK, OK, as you say.
Mateo knows Tomás killed himself.
I don't know why he's here.
To mess things up. What else?
Well, I don't really know.
He's just identical to her father.
That's the thing with kids.
They're an eternal reminder
of things we must get over.
They're also a reminder
of our secrets.
ALBERTO INCOMING CALL
ANDREA OUTGOING CALL
That chick's so hot.
What chick?
Sam?
Yes. Do you know her?
Do I know her?
She's like my best friend.
Is that so?
I've been with her
through all her transitions.
She's one of the first girls...
who transformed, dude.
Transformed into what?
How does it feel?
What?
Not knowing your father.
Have you been to London?
How does it feel not knowing London?
London's not my father.
It feels...
incomplete.
I read my father's diary, and...
It's like I've written it myself.
He felt lonely.
I've spent all my life
fighting the enemy.
I ended up becoming him.
I became everything I hated.
I became comfortable.
I got old.
But comfort is tricky.
It anchors you.
It gets you stuck.
I ended up entangled in a whirlwind
from which I didn't want to get out.
And I jumped off a building.
I jumped off a freaking building
and I didn't die.
Andrea...
I never apologized to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
- What's up?
I'm leaving.
Already?
- Yes...
- Are you all right?
Yes, I'm all right.
It's only that I don't want
to get too wasted today
because of the retreat.
I wanted to know
if you want to come with me,
or if I see you there.
- I'll see you there, OK?
- OK.
Listen, do you want
to spend the night with me?
I want to stay longer here with Sam.
OK.
Well, I'm leaving now.
Goodbye.
Cool.
You don't know
how to get into your house.
They're sleeping.
Good night.
Matilde.
Come with me.
I want to show you something.
This is my father's diary.
I found it here.
My mother and Tomás.
- Hello.
- Look at her.
- María!
- What a brat.
- No. Be careful.
- What's wrong?
- Easy, easy.
- What happened to you?
I was feeling a little sick.
Nothing happened.
- A little sick?
- We talk about it later, OK?
Are you all right?
I stumbled.
Did you use one of your seven lives?
Like three of them.
You're indestructible, María.
Exactly.
Sweetheart, do you want to stay
and sleep with us?
Yes, but I have to get up
early tomorrow.
Why?
Because Beny's playing didgeridoo
in a retreat.
What does he play?
Didgeridoo.
It's an instrument that makes
this sound
and puts people into trance.
It's a millennial thing, María.
Yes, it's millenary.
It's... It's curative.
OK.
Do you want to come?
What?
It can work for you.
To a retreat?
Yes. It's just for the weekend.
Think about it.
María, what were you doing
before jumping into a buffet?
I didn't know
they were having a buffet.
What happened to you?
You were a badass. You were going
to save the world, right?
As a zoologist, you helped primates.
You work at the San Diego Zoo.
I don't do it anymore.
No. I just sign papers now.
And I take part
in the exploitation of animals
and the destruction of the planet.
I've never earned
so much money in my life.
Then I started mixing
whisky with Rivotril.
I came to Mexico this time
to screw up the flora
and fauna of this country.
So, I preferred to smash
the continental breakfast.
Well, I used to be a man.
Mati?
What the hell?
Can't you knock the damned door?
I can't believe it.
This can't be happening!
We fell asleep!
Yes, honey.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
All right!
We had sex all night
and then we put our clothes back on.
We fell asleep!
We fell asleep reading Tomás' diary.
Do you have my diary?
- Your diary?
- Where did you get it from?
I found it with this.
Holy shit!
Did my father and you...?
You'll have to leave this house.
Why?
Because we're not going
through this again.
Just because you did
stupid things 20 years ago,
we have to suffer now?
Kind of. That's what
being a child is about.
- Ana...
- No! You have to leave now!
Father!
Matilde, you don't have
a say this time.
I know you don't want to experience
again everything that happened,
but I want an explanation!
That's why I'm here.
To understand Tomás.
Ana.
I grew up being the son of a ghost.
And now you're telling me I can't
know everything that happened.
Mateo...
I'm so sorry you didn't find
the answers you were looking for.
I'm sorry, but it's like
having your father here.
It messes things up,
and I won't let you mess things up.
You need to leave.
Things already were messed up.
Where are you going?
The exhibition organizers
offered me accommodation.
Let me know where.
Yes.
Come to the exhibition, OK?
Mateo.
Why did you kick him out?
No, sweetheart.
There are some things
you can't understand just yet.
Explain them to me.
Tell me.
- Sat Nam.
- Namaste.
God bless you.
Thank you.
It's prohibited
to contaminate the sanctuary.
Please, put your cigarette out.
There you go.
Yes, I'm the one you spoke with.
This is nice.
Under what name
did you make the reservation?
Katia Maldonado.
Your stay is covered
because it's on the house,
thanks to Benjamín.
But you'll need to pay two more rooms.
- How much is it?
- It's 9950 pesos, please.
Per person?
This is daylight robbery.
In this space,
thanks to the Master's teachings,
we consider that simplicity,
frugality and abstinence
are the right way to find oneself,
but to materialize it,
we need your donation.
- Do you want me to...?
- No, it's OK.
No, no. Don't worry.
It's on me.
- Really?
- Yes, of course.
Thank you, María.
- Do you accept credit cards?
- Yes, any of them.
Of course.
Could you hand it to me
with your right hand?
Hey.
- Hello.
Can I have a word
with my girlfriend, please?
Yes. It's OK.
I'll see you later.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
OK, I'll see you.
What's wrong?
Why did you bring her?
Sam?
Yes. Sam.
Well, we came here with María.
Didn't you see her?
Yes, I did.
Are you still mad about the video?
No. I told you
I was not mad about it.
So? I don't understand.
I think it's weird. I don't like it.
Why does it bother you
that I brought Sam?
Besides what's evident?
Yes, besides what's evident.
I've heard things about her.
That she has a dick between her legs.
Does she have a dick?
Yes, it's like 20 inches long.
- How cool.
- Yes.
Sweet.
No, she doesn't have a dick.
- What if she did? What's the problem?
- It's just that I don't understand.
I'd expect
that you weren't such an idiot.
Did you screw her?
Are you going to be
this kind of idiot?
- No?
- No.
No. I won't be that kind of idiot,
but I don't want you to screw him,
or her, or whatever she is.
I'm sorry. I can't deal with it.
Well, I think you've got
the wrong girlfriend.
Focus on your breathing.
Open your heart.
Expand your spirit.
Set your inner being free.
Prepare yourselves
for the Master's arrival.
- Sat Nam, Siri.
- Sat Nam, Master.
Sat Nam, sisters, brothers.
The being...
that can be divinely good alone,
will know how to be
divinely good accompanied.
We are here to find inner peace.
Who brought a cell phone
to the sanctuary?
Katia.
Katia, it's your phone.
Did anyone bring a cell phone
to the sanctuary?
Find it. Where is it?
Siri!
Hurry up. Find it.
Take it easy, Master. Your aura.
God fucking damn it!
I've got it. I've got it.
We have signs!
I've got it.
I turned it off. Sorry.
Miguel?
María?
What happened to you?
I got enlightened.
Yes.
What about you?
I took a beating.
Hi, Mati. What happened?
My parents kicked Mateo
out of the house.
- What?
- They don't explain me anything.
Since he arrived,
they've been acting strange,
and they won't let me go
to the exhibition.
Say what!
Yes, I know.
I wish you were here.
You don't know what happened.
What?
Miguel, my mother's ex-husband,
is the damned spiritual guide.
What?
He's the damned guru.
Are you sure?
María went pale when she saw him.
I've got to go. I love you.
I'll talk to you later, OK?
- Bye.
- See you later.
He said he was sorry,
and I gave him another opportunity.
- Don't come crying later.
- OK.
Where's Alberto?
- I don't know. He didn't come today.
- I know.
Why?
I don't know.
He's not even answering his phone.
Do you think I did the right thing
giving him another opportunity?
What?
Don't come crying later.
Sisters, brothers, Sat Nam.
Sat Nam.
You may sit, please.
Enjoy the dinner.
Couldn't you have found
an intermediate point?
Sorry?
You went from being
a cocaine-addicted publicist
to being a freaking Krishnamurti.
These have been...
very difficult times, María.
- Sure.
- Sat Nam, Master.
Satnam, Siri.
Is there something
in particular disturbing you?
- Do you want me to call the bouncer?
- The bouncer?
Everything is fine, my dear Siri.
Thank you.
- I'll be around in case you need me.
- Sure.
Serve the lady.
- Namaste.
- Thank you.
Is she your daughter?
Katia?
How long haven't you been Miguel?
A long time.
How old is she?
She's 20.
20 years old?
You're a spiritual guide now?
Yes. I mean, María, you know me.
You know my life.
I hit rock bottom.
All the relationships I had
made me sick.
So, I needed to leave.
I had to.
20 years old.
María...
Katia is our daughter.
- What?
- Katia is our daughter.
- No!
- Don't you realize?
- No, Miguel.
- It's been 20 years, for God's sake.
- She's not.
- Stop hiding it from me.
Miguel, let go.
You're hurting me.
Let go.
Miguel!
No!
- Sat Nam.
- Sat Nam, Master.
Master...
Hello, this is Andrea.
Leave your message.
Andrea, where are you?
Miguel is here at the retreat,
and he noticed Katia.
I don't know what to do.
I knew this was going to happen.
What should I do? Call me.
This shit...
Where the hell...?
María, is Katia our daughter?
Answer me! Goddammit!
Let go of me.
You haven't changed a bit
in the last 20 years.
What happened to us?
María, please, don't lie to me.
Is Katia our daughter?
No.
She's not our daughter.
Good.
She's not my daughter.
She's my daughter.
Katia's my daughter.
Andrea.
Miguel...
Miguel. Miguel.
Honey...
we need to talk to Matilde.
No.
Then, I'm going to talk to Mateo.
Carlos, stop it.
Stop it, stop it.
Stop stirring things up. Stop it.
Matilde's my daughter.
I'm protecting her.
Nobody's going to hurt her.
I love you, curly.
Master?
- What are you doing here?
Me?
I heard a noise,
and I'm making sure everything's OK.
- A noise?
- Yes.
What kind of noise?
Screams. Horrible screams.
Horrible screams.
In there?
Yes.
Is Katia inside?
Who? I don't know.
Beny, what the...?
What are you doing?
- Katia is...
- What?
You're spying on me.
That's the truth.
No.
No? What's wrong with you?
I wanted to talk to you.
What do you want to talk to me about?
- I mean, I wanted to see you.
- See me?
It's not what you think.
No. You're sick.
What's all this noise?
- No, no. Katia, I'm Miguel, OK?
- So?
I'm your father.
What?
You're my daughter.
María?
No.
- No, no! Get out of my way!
- Katia.
No! No!
Katia!
Get out of the way!
Are you OK?
Get out of the car.
Come.
Carefully.
Sit down.
Katia.
Katia, are you OK?
Are you OK?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me
Miguel was my father?
Why didn't you tell me?
Because it was not my place
to tell you.
I'm sorry.
Katia, it was not my place.
No, no, no.
No. I've never needed you!
I don't need you! OK?
This is so good.
Where did you get all this material?
I inherited it.
You do look like him.
He's my father.
Are you sure you want
to change it all at the last minute?
I'm sorry. The other one
doesn't make sense to me anymore.
Yes, but I'm worried
that the materials
might not be ready on time.
No, Gonzalo, please,
they must be ready on time.
Someone's looking for you.
Mateo...
Yes?
Can I buy you a beer?
I'd rather have
a shot of tequila, Carlitos.
OK.
You can call me "Carlitos."
Thank you.
Does Matilde know?
No.
Tomás didn't know about me, either.
My mother knew he wouldn't stay, so...
She always wanted a son, so...
He'd never stay.
He'd arrive, make a mess, and leave.
Just like you.
I just wanted to know.
It wasn't my intention.
I know.
You wanted to know,
but there are other ways.
That's why I'm here.
To tell you everything I know,
and everything you want to know.
Carlos...
I'm also doing this because
I don't want Matilde to get hurt.
Cheers.
Why didn't you tell me
Miguel is my father?
Answer me, mother!
Answer me!
Let's talk. Calm down.
No, I don't even know what to think.
I don't understand!
I didn't know what to do.
Beny...
Get out of my house, please.
Why didn't you tell me?
No, Andrea.
I beg you, please, to give me
a chance to talk to you.
Please.
What happened...
was terrible.
I haven't been able...
to forgive myself in all these years.
Get out of my house, please.
- We must give ourselves a chance...
- Please, get out of my house.
No.
I'm sorry.
Well...
I'm leaving now.
No.
What's wrong?
No. We can't do this.
Why?
Because of a number of reasons.
One of them is that I prefer men.
Hi, Kat. How are you?
Kat, I love you.
I'm very sorry
for what happened, and...
Answer me, please.
Tell me you're all right.
I'd like to propose a toast,
because we all are in the same place.
Finally, you are meeting Mateo.
Cheers.
Cheers!
For a successful opening!
MEDIA CAMPAIGN GROUP
You're not going, OK?
What? But you're going,
dressed like that, right?
I'm sorry. You're not going.
Do you want to talk now?
Why are you acting
as if Mateo were a rapist-killer?
You're not going. Period!
That's not how things work!
Tell me, or I'm leaving!
Hello, dear.
Is everything all right?
A dressing gown
at this time of the day?
My girl.
I've missed you so much.
Hello, grandma.
Why the long face?
Ana and I were having an argument.
You don't say.
What are you arguing about now?
She wants to go to this place,
but she's not going!
What place is that?
It's a photo exhibition.
For Christ's sake, Ana.
What's wrong with her
going to a photo exhibition?
- Have this, honey.
- She's not going!
Why does this house
always smell like gas?
You always ask me to respect
your freedom and sexuality,
and coexist with it.
Mom, you're an intelligent,
capable woman,
who makes her own decisions.
Don't you want the same for me?
- What happened to you?
- We need to talk, OK?
God, what happened to you?
Ana...
did you know Miguel is my father?
What?
We're leaving.
Matilde, don't go! Matilde!
Ana!
What's with
all these restrictions now?
It's a photo exhibition by Tomás' son.
Tomás' son.
Tomás?
Your best friend?
Why don't you all go?
Why don't you go with her?
VISUAL CULTURE CENTER
The search for identity
is a winding, lonely road
that sometimes leads us
to unexpected places.
But it also leads you to know people
who change the course of our lives.
The past is there
for us to learn from it,
to avoid repeating it,
to correct its mistakes.
We need to face it without taboos,
with all its pain and all its beauty.
We need to embrace it,
understand it,
and learn to coexist with it.
You'll see a fragment
of my intimacy,
of people who changed course
for my life to be what it is.
They're real people.
They've got different motivations,
and just like the rest of us,
they're trying to survive.
Welcome.
I know.
Sometimes, I know
you won't understand
why I've decided
or done certain things, but...
the only thing I want you to know is
that everything I've done
since you were born,
I've done it for you to be well.
I do understand.
I need you to understand
that you don't have
to hide anything from me.
- You can trust me, mom.
- Yes.
I'm your daughter.
I know. I know, sweetheart.
What is it? Why are you so nervous?
I need to talk to Matilde.
I need to tell her the truth.
Don't worry. I talked to Mateo.
You don't have to worry
about anything.
Dear.
It's all thanks to you.
Matilde, you can't be with him.
Ana...
Ana, please.
- Why?
- Just because. Because you can't.
Stop saying that I can't.
I don't give a damn he's the son
of the freaking love of your life.
You are, too.
You might be.
I don't know.
I'm not... I've never been sure.
We can go to a lab.
They have these tests, right?
Just to know.
I don't want to know.
You don't want to know
you're not my sister.
I don't want to know
I'm not my father's daughter.
Do you understand?
I don't want him to know.
Do you want to come with me?
What time do you have
to be at the airport?
In three hours.
What is it?
I quit.
Did you quit?
What are you going to do now?
I don't know.
You're happy!
But I do know
I don't only have myself.
I have you two.
What's left of us.
It's been a long time, right?
Portrait of three women.
Real women.
It is what it is.
You slept with him.
I know it.
I can see it in your eyes.
We're not pure anymore.
Do you understand me?
Every time you touch me,
I'll be thinking you touched him.
We can start from scratch.
Start from scratch?
You cheated on me!
I did.
There are many different ways
to love, Mateo.
So many, and so different,
that it's easy to feel astray.
The way to love doesn't run
in the blood we inherit, Mateo.
It's rewritten every time,
every moment...
for each one of us.
I kiss you in the wind, Mateo.
I kiss you in the breeze.
I kiss you when the sun rises,
and when the night falls...
in the waves of the sea...
in the forest's darkness.
I kiss you today
and always, Mateo...
as we invent our way to love.
COFFEE AND BOOKSHOP