Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[music]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[music]
[eerie sound]
Hey!
What happened?
Where did you come from?
What happened to you?
I came from back there.
What’s your name?
My name is Price.
What are you looking at?
What’s there?
I’ll tell you.
[eerie sound]
[eerie piano] Hey, you got a car?
Nope I'm on foot.
You’re like me taken it to the road.
Why don’t we work together and hitch a ride.
Me on this side, you on that side.
You don’t care which way you’re going.
Nah, as long as I catch a ride.
What are you doing?
Why don’t you answer me man?
Why are you smiling like that, man?
Fuck you, fuck you.
This will help you.
It’s all I have.
This is all you got?
I believe you.
[eerie sound]
[birds chirping]
Do you need help?
[eerie music] Are you hungry?
It looks like you don’t have any food or water.
I have some in my backpack.
Do you need food?
Do you need water?
I know who you are.
Remember me.
They’re out there.
[eerie sound]
[piano]
Do you know why I’m here?
He sent you.
Yes,
he did.
So, it’s that time.
Yes,
I’m here to lead you to where to go.
To prepare your mind for what is to come.
What is to come.
Yes.
You will save people.
Redemption will be through your leadership.
Will you be there?
No, you will do this alone.
But now you must go and fast.
Keep in mind you will be weak at times.
Even then I will be alone.
Yes, and after this time you will bring hope.
Then I’m ready because he is ready.
[eerie sound]
[eerie sounds]
Where’s my?
[birds chirping]
I left it.
Okay,
No watch, no compass.
[birds chirping]
That way.
[eerie music]
Keep moving.
Don’t stop, you can make it.
You got this.
This is what He wants.
What you want.
Look at it,
fresh,
clean, inspiring,
designed perfectly.
This is the best decision ever made.
Father you are right.
[thunder]
[eerie sound]
[owl hooting]
[birds chirping]
[bees buzzing]
[whispering voices]
[crow caw]
Hello!
[eerie sound]
[crickets]
[crickets-eerie sound]
[eerie sounds]
[Mary] One, two, look at you.
Three, four let’s walk some more.
There you go!
You must follow in the footsteps of your father.
You must see it through.
[eerie sound]
[eerie piano]
Hmm, that’s odd.
Where did he come from?
Hey, that’s my backpack!
[eerie sound]
I can’t believe this guy!
Tiring,
This is what happens when
you don’t eat for days Price.
Come on, come on
Everything’s still inside.
Why would he take my backpack and take nothing inside?
Why would he leave it on this rock?
Hey!
Hey wait!
Why does it smell like bread?
Go ahead eat it.
What?
Why would I, it’s a rock.
It could be whatever you want it to be.
It smells like fresh sweet roll.
You can do anything here.
If you want it to be bread then it’s bread.
Go ahead, take a bite of it.
No, I won’t.
If you don’t eat it I’ll use it against you.
What do you mean you would use it against me?
No!
[eerie sound]
Just what I thought,
I’m not scared easily.
[bobcat growling]
You have reached
66 miles.
view ahead.
[eerie piano] Pretty steep down there, huh?
Uh, huh.
Where did?
I didn’t see you.
Where did you come from?
It’s really not that steep.
How long have you been here?
I’ve manage to make it up and down several times.
Uh, yeah,
who are you?
I’m Natas.
Nai, N-a
tas, t-a-s.
But I can be whomever you want me to be.
Anything can happen here.
Why would I do that?
Why would I listen to you?
I’ve seen this before.
Who are?
If you’re truly special and have a purpose,
why don’t you jump down this cliff?
Won’t you be saved from harm since it’s not your time.
This is not funny.
I’m here to help you.
Yeah, I don’t believe.
Jump.
Where did he go?
Why did he do that?
Okay, breathe.
Focus.
[Mary] There you are.
[young Price] But, mother why are you so surprised?
Aren’t I suppose to be about my father’s business?
My father’s business.
That’s why you’re here
Price.
That’s why you’re here.
I’ve got to rest.
Just for a few minutes.
Price!
Price.
Price, remember where you come from.
It’s not about you.
It’s about Him.
It’s you again.
He has assigned you as my messenger?
He has,
and what you’re enduring can be endured through him.
You words are comforting and much needed.
I’ll do my best to move on.
Once you’re done here you are to tell the others.
Everyone that believes will have peace.
Show them how to overcome the madness in the world.
There is power in what is good.
[eerie sound]
[eerie piano] It’s you!
You look surprised.
We passed you awhile back, you saw us.
I…
Oh,
you thought you were alone.
Alone, yes.
Come on, you'll be surprised
you’re not alone.
No, it's okay, I’m good.
But you’re already here.
What do you mean I’m already here?
Look around.
You’ve reached
66 & 6 miles.
How wonderful it is to have it all.
To be in control of
everything and everybody.
This can happen.
I can make this happen.
Uh, no.
This
is not what He sent me for.
Why go about your father’s business when you can go about your own.
About my own business.
Look at what you can have.
Control.
I can make this happen.
The prize is within your reach.
Let me show you.
What are these people?
Are you ready to find out?
I don’t think I want to do that.
You don’t need to worry.
No one here is going to hurt you.
Why do you think they’re reaching out to you.
I don’t know? t.
They don’t seem righ
Sit,
to the left of me
and I’ll show you who they are.
No,
I think you can do that from here.
Let’s start from the beginning.
The world is a beautiful place.
With all of its
riches,
land,
soil,
nature is formed.
The birth of all things.
I can vouch for it
because I was there
I was always there
and I always will be.
But you can have all of this.
Power,
control,
wealth,
I’m coming
and have already been here.
Little signs here and there of
people doing this and that.
All a distraction of what’s to come.
Not you or anyone can change that.
There is an end to everything.
No one but my father.
I know Him,
I'm from Him
and He
sent me.
[eerie sounds]
Hey!
Are you okay?
[eerie sounds]
I see them!
Drive.
[music]
[piano]