[dramatic chase music]
♪
You following me around now?
What the hell, Chad?
- Sound like you and your friends
- is having fun.
- I told you that I don't want
- to see you this weekend.
Why?
- Cause you got guys
- up in there.
Ain't that why you dress
like... that?
No, all right?
It's just me and the girls.
And actually, so what
if there are guys there?
We broke up, remember?
After you cheated on me.
Go back to your cabin
and leave me alone.
Yeah, aiight.
- Go back to whatever you doing
- in there, ho.
Asshole!
['90s dance music]
♪
The booze is here!
[eerie music]
♪
Happy graduation!
[laughs]
- And all I got you was a gift
- card to Sam Goody.
Well now that you and Chad
are finally broken up,
you'll need it.
I thought you liked him.
[laughs]
No one liked Chad,
trust me.
- So did you ever figure out
- who he cheated with?
No.
- Well, maybe he had a good reason
- for doing it.
What?
- I'm just trying to make Trish
- feel better.
And you think that's helping?
- If the stupid car didn't break
- down the second we got here,
- We could at least go somewhere
- else, you know?
- The house the guys rented is
- on the other side of the lake.
- You don't have to see him
- if you don't want to.
- Yeah, and maybe you'll get lucky
- and he'll drown.
Diane!
[laughs]
♪
I love this song!
Come on!
♪
[chuckles]
This is my kind of party.
I love you.
♪
Yeah, you is a dirty ho.
[eerie music]
♪
Chad: Nah, is he for real?
Damn pervert.
[tense music]
♪
[eerie music]
Woah dog.
What are you doing with that?
[chainsaw whirring]
♪
[agonized screaming]
[timer rings]
Did you hear that?
- [music fades]
- ♪
Oh, my god.
The timer!
The brownies are done.
[laughing]
['90s dance music]
♪
Where'd you get that?
I got a welcome gift.
We're about to have brownies.
How are you fitting
all that in?
I have a stomach of steel.
Like Batman.
Superman.
- No, no, no. Like, like the man
- of steel, right?
But my stomach.
Yeah. That's Superman.
Uh, no.
It's...
[gags]
[vomits]
I think I'll go help Kim.
Yeah.
Super.
Oh my god, Kim.
Trying to burn down
the cabin?
Hey. You need help?
Oh, my god, Kim!
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
[intense music]
♪
[dial tone]
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
[eerie music]
♪
- [whispers]
- Diane?
Jackie?
Diane?
[gasps]
Someone killed Diane and I can't
stop vomiting on myself.
[crying]
-Oh, my god.
Kim.
She's dead too.
Why is this happening?
I don't know,
I don't know.
- We're going to get out of here,
- okay?
How? The car is busted.
Uh... We'll sneak out of here
- and then run to the first house
- we see for help.
Yeah?
One, two...
Wait.
Did you hear something?
No, uh, no. It's...
I slept with Chad.
What?
I was the one that slept
with Chad.
And I wanted you to know that
in case we die.
- -I'm sorry.
- -We're not going to die.
[sobbing]
Okay? We got this.
Let's just um, make sure
the porch is clear first
and let's...
Wait! Check first!
[tense music swells]
♪
[screaming]
Ahhhhh!!!!!!
- [shrieking]
- Ahhhhhh!!!!!!
[panicked breathing]
- [eerie music]
- ♪
♪
[dramatic music]
[chainsaw whirring]
[agonized screaming]
No! Please, please no!
No!
[whirring]
[sobbing]
- [tense music]
- ♪
- [screaming]
- No!!!
Help me!
[chainsaw whirring]
[screaming]
[softly]
I love you.
[crying]
[screaming]
[splash]
[eerie music]
♪
- Newscaster: - It was a neighbor's
complaint - Of missing dogs
- That finally led the authorities
- to the house
Of an unemployed handyman
named Russ Thorne.
Newscaster:
the Driller Killer.
Thorne would become known as
- The lone survivor of
- his night of terror
Was a 17-year-old girl
drinking with friends
at a rented lake house.
- Newscaster:
- And get this, George.
Apparently their drink
of choice was Cooler.
The world's first and worst
vodka cooler in a bottle.
[Newscasters laugh]
- Look, I'm not saying they
- deserved to die.
But with that booze
choice it was inevitable.
Newscaster: The crazy thing is,
Russ's body was never found.
- Police assumed he drowned
- in the lake.
- And his body was either
- eaten by bears
Or still decomposing
at the bottom somewhere.
Newscaster: Despite
thought he was still alive,
the survivor swearing she
but you know, Cooler.
[Newscasters laugh]
- Newscaster: Either way,
- Holly Springs,
Once a once bustling
vacation hotspot,
became a ghost town.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I called you a couple of times.
Your friends are here.
Okay. Thanks.
I want you to know, you can
skip it if you want.
Blame it on me?
And I don't want.
And we talked about this,
and you said you were going
to be cool.
I lied.
Dana, I know you know this,
but I just have to say it.
- Don't tell strangers
- where you're going.
- Keep your phone charged,
- keep all doors...
Mother. I love you like crazy,
but right now you are being
the opposite of fun.
I just want you to be safe.
And I am.
And I know how to be safe.
And you're safe too,
you know that right?
You are.
So just go do fun things.
Go live your life.
I know.
- And when was the last time
- you left the house?
I have everything
I need right here.
I love you.
But no crying.
Okay, I love you.
Stop. Don't make eye contact.
- It'll give her an excuse
- to give safety advice.
Oh shit.
Call me when you get there.
- And right before
- you go to bed.
And first...
I will.
Girls wait.
- What's the name of the town
- you're going to?
- Dana forgot to write it down
- for me.
- -Laurel.
- -Lester.
Laurel, right.
They start with the same letter.
I always confuse them.
Seatbelts.
♪
Athlete?
Yes.
Is she alive?
No.
Justin Timberlake.
Female.
It's a lady.
A dead lady.
Jackie Kennedy?
[phone buzzes]
JT. JT.
Dana, are you even playing?
Yeah.
Um, Junko Tabei.
Yes.
How'd you do that?
- She doesn't yell out random
- nonsense for one thing.
All right. Dana,
pick another one.
Someone the rest of us
might actually know.
[clattering sounds]
- Uh, Dee, can you make sure
- everything's okay back there?
I don't want any of our party
supplies falling out.
Oh, my god.
- Could you imagine if we got
- pulled over?
We're not getting pulled over.
We'll just invite the police
to the partay.
[giggling]
None of that is funny.
[beeping]
Hey, seatbelt!
Do you know how often
accidents happen
- when someone temporarily
- takes off their seatbelt?
Well, I can't check
with it on.
That is so not better.
[laughing]
[screaming]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
What?
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
[screaming]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
What is happening?
There's someone in the back!
- Oh, my god, your faces
- are hilarious.
That was totally worth
all the hours of leg cramps.
Alix! What the hell?!
You told me I couldn't come.
What was I supposed to do?
Not come?
This is our special trip
that you are not invited to.
I know. That's why I'm here.
- You have no idea
- what you've done.
Just get in the back seat.
We have to go back.
Drop her off.
- If you're driving?
- We'll lose the day.
Breanie's right.
You drive like a granny.
- We're getting to the house
- just before dark as it is.
Maybe it's a sign.
- Maybe we should forget it
- and go home.
- Hey. You've been on board
- since the beginning.
Don't chicken out now.
I still am.
- I don't want Maeve's kid
- sister ratting us out.
She wouldn't.
She's like us.
- I don't know,
- it's not that...
Look, you know if
we turn around now
- we're never going
- to come back.
This is the weekend.
The only weekend.
Yes, Alix can be a pain
in the ass.
Um, I can still hear you!
But...
She deserves to be a part of
our epic girls weekend.
We all deserve it.
A weekend of...
Partying?
Self-discovery.
To dig deep into our souls and
pull out all the fear and anger,
and put it towards
something real.
- So that our futures can be
- brighter than anything
We could ever imagine.
You guys are talking about
doing drugs, aren't you?
Alix won't be involved
in any of the drugs.
How about that?
[sighs]
- I think we should totally
- vote on it.
Yes!
- I don't even know what we're
- talking about anymore.
That's a yes.
Yes.
Yes!
[sighs]
Fine.
But no drugs for Alix.
Okay.
[cheering and laughing]
- I think you have a leak
- in your radiator.
No. I just had the car serviced.
I don't know what to tell you.
- You're going to have
- to replace the hose.
Okay. Go ahead and replace it.
Garage closed years ago.
This is a gas station.
It's not an auto body shop.
- So we drive to an auto
- body shop.
You're not going
to make it to one.
You've lost a lot
of fluid.
My friend's got a shop.
He's got the part.
I could get it for ya.
Maybe by tomorrow?
No. We rented a house.
We have to be there tonight.
- You're not going
- to make it tonight.
What about... now?
- I don't see how that's going
- to help.
Whatever. I have to pee.
I'll go with.
I'll meet you back here.
Yep.
[bell jingles]
♪
Aww.
Babies.
♪
[laughs]
Look at this.
I've seen bigger.
Of course you have.
What is up with this?
People steal a lot of dogs
around here.
Nah.
[girls gasp]
They just get eaten by bears.
Wow, you came out
of nowhere.
Thanks.
Bears eat dogs?
That's so sad.
I know, honey.
The world's a sad place.
Our car is giving us issues
- and we need a place to stay
- for the night.
Uh, I like this one.
- Oh, you don't want
- to stay here?
Our lakes are a dump.
- We don't really have
- a choice.
Unless you know of someplace
else we can stay around here?
Not really.
[clinking]
You doing okay back there,
Peaches?
Yeah. All good thanks.
Just, just browsing.
Well, it's available.
What a surprise.
No offense.
I'll check you in.
- Do you want the penis man
- or no?
I mean, obviously.
[door creaking]
Ugh.
[machine grinding]
[eerie music]
♪
[drill whirring]
[Maeve screaming]
Maeve?
Maeve! Are you okay?
No!
I think I just stepped
in human poo.
Ugh. It's so demoralizing.
It's not funny.
I probably have E.Coli.
I'm sure you'll live.
Come on.
[eerie music swells]
♪
[drill whirring]
[ominous music]
♪
Jolly Springs?
Why does that sound familiar?
Never heard of it.
Where did you get those?
I swear I would've left money,
- but I didn't want Kay to be
- complicit in selling to a minor,
So I stole em.
It works out for both of us
that way.
Stealing is still a crime,
Alix.
Oh, my god.
Is that the house?
[eerie music]
♪
[eerie music swells]
[door creaks]
♪
Watch your steps.
Some of the planks are rotten.
They catch all these
in the lake?
That's a shark.
I know.
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
Alix, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
A raccoon was in the sink.
It ran out when I screamed.
[sighs of relief]
Oh, this town isn't what
it used to be.
- We get untoward characters
- here sometimes.
Stay inside, stay...
stay quiet and stay safe.
I'm not getting any signal.
Out here you won't.
Wi-Fi password's on the fridge
and my number's here too.
Text me if you have
any problems.
Thanks Kay.
We appreciate it.
I feel bad for her.
Me too.
Old people are depressing.
Shh. She can hear you.
Please. She can't hear.
She's old.
Well, now that we're here,
guess it's time to start
the slumber party!
[cheering and laughing]
Ew.
[dance music]
♪
[laughing]
Oh, you guys.
- I can't believe
- we're doing this.
I love you guys so much.
- -I want in!
- -Me too!
I love you guys.
[laughing]
♪
Woo. I love this song.
Ugh, I wish I never came!
♪
[car engine rattling]
[girls laughing]
♪
Shit.
Hey.
It's you.
My friend dropped off the
supplies on his way home,
- so I thought
- I'd drop it by
- In case they wanted to leave
- tonight instead.
- But I can bring it
- to them tomorrow.
They seem pretty busy
right now.
I'm just gonna get
out of here.
I'll uh, catch you later.
[eerie music]
♪
[dance music]
- [girls chanting]
- Chug it! Chug it!
- Chug it!
Chug it! Chug it! Chug it!
[scoffs]
Fail.
♪
Ugh. Boys.
[disturbing music]
♪
Ugh.
How do you guys think
he's not cute?
He wears sports jerseys.
Like, for formal wear?
[laughing]
- You have sauce
- on your chin.
Oh, where?
Thanks.
Hey.
Want pizza, nerd?
Alix?
Where'd Alix go?
[eerie music]
♪
[rustling]
Hello?
- [eerie music]
- ♪
♪
[gasps]
Are you okay?
- [eerie music]
- ♪
[screaming]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
- Alix, I told you not
- to go out!
I was freaking...
- [panicking]
- Get inside, get inside!
Alix? You're bleeding.
- It's not my blood.
- Check all the windows.
What is going on?
- -Now!
- -Okay.
[disturbing music]
♪
The guy from
the gas station?
He's dead.
What do you mean?
- I mean like someone
- murdered him.
Oh, that's so sad.
Are you joking?
Why would I joke about
something like that?
I saw him in his car,
he's dead, this is his blood.
Maybe he was murdered
by a bear.
- Kay did say there were creepy
- people around here.
I think it's bigger
than that.
You think?
- I knew certain things seemed
- familiar about this place
And I couldn't put it together,
until I remembered this one
Crime Bandits podcast episode.
I know it's hard to hear,
but I think, I think
the Driller Killer is here.
But he's dead.
I should've known when Ashley
mentioned the dead dogs.
A bunch of kids in the '90s
were murdered by this dude
Russ Thorne, and their car broke
down as they got here.
Just like ours did.
And they were having a slumber
party in pajamas.
Eating pizza and drinking
stupid drinks.
- He murdered someone
- from outside watching them,
- And then when one of them
- went to go get the brownies
From the kitchen,
- he just snuck in
- and started killing.
[oven dings]
- Oh my god,
- you assholes!
All: Pillow fight!
[laughing]
[upbeat dance music]
♪
[laughing]
You came here on purpose?
What is wrong with all of you?
We're going to be murdered!
Sorry Alix.
We didn't tell you
because we didn't know
- if Russ would really
- be alive.
And no offense, you weren't
supposed to come.
Look, don't worry.
When he comes for us,
we are going to kill him.
If he comes for us.
We're kind of brilliant
if you think about it.
Did everything almost
exactly the same.
The PJs...
- The leak in
- the radiator hose.
The drinking.
[laughs]
It's water.
Yep. The only thing different
is the house.
Oh no, don't look at me.
It wasn't on the board.
Maybe they don't rent out
the murder house anymore.
So what?
- We just wait here
- until he comes barging in?
Yeah. And then we kill him.
We've been planning this
for a year.
No matter what he does,
we are ready.
[knocking at door]
So, are you ready when
he comes knocking?
Maybe we should open it.
- You can't open the door
- for a murderer.
- A murderer isn't going
- to knock.
Yeah, Breanie is right.
- We know everything
- about him.
He's not a knocker.
Woah.
Hey, uh, I mean hi.
I'm, I'm John.
Didn't mean to disturb you,
I just, I saw one of you on
the dock a little earlier.
That was me. Hey.
Alix forgot to mention that.
I had other things
on my mind.
Hi.
- Okay. Well like I said, I didn't
- want to disturb you.
- It just seems like we're
- the only ones here
- For the big Jolly Springs
- re-opening
So we thought we'd be good
neighbors and come say hey.
This is Matt.
I have a girlfriend.
- You guys really shouldn't be
- out there.
Yeah? Why?
- Because it's dark and you don't
- want to get lost.
Yeah. Please, come in.
- Seriously, come in,
- come in.
- -No, we...
- -Bro.
Come in. Come on, yeah.
Awesome.
[sighs]
Oh.
Sorry. Didn't realize you guys
were getting ready for bed.
We don't mind.
- Are you guys staying in
- the house across the lake?
Yeah.
Five of us.
Yeah, yeah.
We like this podcast
called Crime Bandits.
- John's kind of obsessed
- with it.
- Okay, I'm not obsessed
- Well... we do this weird murder
- tour thing.
- People were murdered in
- the house we're staying in.
- It's way more boring
- than you think.
Which is why we thought
we'd come and say hey.
So... hey.
So uh, why am I asking?
What are you guys
doing here?
Our car broke down, so
we're staying the night.
- I mean, you guys can come
- and hang out with us...
- [nervously]
- No!
Um, we can't.
It's a girls' weekend.
No boys.
So... Thank you for coming by.
Okay, yeah sure. Yeah.
- [mutters awkwardly]
- Oh no, wait.
- Can I just talk to you guys
- for a sec?
[clears throat]
We have to tell them
what's going on.
- We can't tell them we're here
- to murder someone.
We can't let them
be murdered either.
He doesn't want them.
He wants us.
I don't know, Dana.
- He seems pretty
- equal opportunity
When it comes to murder.
- [whispers]
- Let's go bro.
What? No.
Anyway, we gotta go.
I don't think you should leave.
I agree.
- No, no. We really
- have to go.
- Wait, seriously guys.
- You shouldn't.
The other guys will know
if we're gone too long,
so, so take care.
What are you?
- You might've just sent them
- to their death.
- We cannot veer
- from the plan.
- That is the only way
- it will work.
The plan was for no one
to get murdered.
[sighs]
Fine.
We'll go after them.
[giggling]
Should I go get
the brownies first?
Hey, what was that about?
- I think they're those man-haters
- you always hear about.
What?
- They had knives hidden
- in pillows.
- -Matt, that is ridiculous.
- -Come on.
- What do you mean they had
- knives in pillows?
- Knives, in their pillows,
- like kitchen knives.
- Okay, what is this
- really about?
It's about knives
in their pillows.
- -I don't want to die.
- -Look, you're not going to die.
Guy: Look man.
- I'm not saying climate change
- isn't real.
I'm saying Mars, right?
- It's going to be terraformed
- in like 10 years.
So what's the big deal if we
just let this planet go to shit?
That's a really dumb thing
to say, Guy.
Well, I'm sorry, Guy Two.
But I refuse to be insulted
by a bro wearing makeup.
Ohhhhh...
[laughs]
It's tinted moisturizer.
- A lot of men wear it
- these days.
I don't think they do, dude.
I don't think they do.
[laughs]
Come on!
- Hey. Where'd you get that,
- Shaun?
- I found it in the closet.
- Sick, right?
Oh yeah.
Oh!
Chug it.
- There you go.
- Come on.
Hey.
[groans]
I gotta piss.
Dude.
Bathroom's inside.
The world's a toilet,
my man.
How'd it go?
Don't ask.
You two are all charm.
Yeah, Guy Two, you remembered
to turn the stove off, right?
I forgot.
I forgot. I'm sorry, dude.
I asked you to do one thing!
Wait, he actually made dinner?
Yeah.
I thought he was joking.
Yeah, well we have
to eat something.
Yeah.
That's why I brought chips.
[sighs]
- [groans in pain]
- Oh!
Ahh!
What the hell, dudes?
Hey asshole!
You want a piece of this?
Big mistake, mother...
Woah.
- You're not Russ Thorne,
- are ya?
[laughs]
Oh man!
Oh, my buddies and I, we
came here because of you.
Obviously we didn't think
you'd actually be alive.
You see man, we do
this murder tour thing.
[eerie music]
♪
Anyway.
- Man, it was, it was nice
- meeting you.
Really nice meeting you.
Shit!
[groaning]
Help!!!
[whirring]
[dramatic music]
♪
Help me!!!
No, no, no, no!
No! No!!!
[agonized screaming]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
[grunting loudly]
[laughing]
Why is that so hard?
I'm telling you Shaun,
my girlfriend read all about it
and she said it can't be done.
- She also says blowjobs
- cause cancer.
So there's that.
You try, bro.
No.
- Good call,
- 'cause it can't be done.
All right.
Well, I'm doing it.
What are you going to do?
- -Here we go!
- -Come on, come on!
Go, go!
[grunting]
- [chanting]
- Go, go, go!
[grunting]
[cheering]
[laughing]
- I understand why Dana
- is doing this,
But why are you?
- We're friends. We support
- each other.
Yeah, I get that.
- But I feel like you can
- support someone
Without agreeing to help
them murder somebody.
Look, he killed four people
and just got away with it.
- Probably more
- over the years.
- Do you know how many young
- women have gone missing
In a 20 mile radius of Holly
Springs in the last 30 years?
No.
Over 20.
[agonized screaming]
Ahhhh!!!!!
[dramatic music]
♪
[cheering]
Are they out-slumber
partying us?
- Is this what guys actually do
- when they're alone?
It's so... depressing.
So we just knock on the door
and tell them Russ is alive?
Just like that?
I think...
- [eerie music]
- ♪
He's here.
Come on, we can get him!
Dana! Dana!
Not part of the plan.
What the?
Oh, my god.
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
What's going on?
- Does anyone know where
- the breaker box is?
- Someone just stepped
- on me!
What's going on?
- [yells]
- Alix?
[screaming]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
Who said that?
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
[screaming]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
[drill whirring]
[screaming]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
[gps
Woah!
Found the breaker box.
[yelps]
Guy Two, are you okay?
Guy Two?
Oh!!!
[gasps]
I think he's dead.
He is dead.
He is definitely dead.
Lady killers!
It wasn't us.
We came to help!
Then whose blood is that?
It's Dave's.
Dave?
Who the hell is Dave?
Oh, my god.
Why is Guy Two dead?!
All dead is too dead!
Boys: What?!
I don't know.
Maeve, Breanie,
check the perimeter.
Guys.
- They had knives when we were
- at their place.
Stay away from us!
Yeah!
Look. We didn't do this.
We came here to warn you
that Russ is alive and killing.
It's clear.
Here too.
Wait, Russ Thorne?
Like THERuss Thorne is,
what, alive?
Oh shit!
We gotta warn Guy!
Yeah!
I thought that was Guy.
There are two Guys!
There are four of you.
No, there are five of us.
There are two Guys.
I just don't think we should be
joking about this right now.
Guy One, Guy Two!
- Okay, but when did Guy Two
- go out?
No.
Guy Two is dead!
Guy One is...
is out there.
This is so messed up.
We have to do something.
We have to find Guy
and take this asshole down
- before he comes
- for the rest of us.
Yes!
Get on the offensive.
Yeah! Yes!
Okay. And we will tell
our plan.
There's three of us.
We outnumber him.
There's eight of us.
[grunts]
You'll need weapons too.
Okay, but we have weapons.
- And we can't just go running
- out there.
Russ knows we're onto him.
- That is not going to work
- against a power drill.
- We just need to scare him off,
- get Guy,
- And get the hell
- out of here.
- Okay, well it isn't
- as easy as that.
John, you take the trail
down to the water.
Look for Guy by the shore.
- Matt, you take the right side
- of the house,
I'll take the left side.
- Splitting up is not
- a good idea.
Guys, I, I think, I think
the ladies know
- what they're talking
- about, right?
[muttering in agreement]
Yes, thank you.
Totally. Uh...
Got it.
You girls stay here.
We'll go get Guy
and come back for you.
- We're going out the door
- on three.
That is a bad idea.
- -On three.
You should not go with them.
Yeah, I know.
- But my toxic masculinity is kind
- of forcing me into it.
John. You're a man.
[grunts]
I'm a man.
You're a man.
- -You're a man.
- -I am a man.
Yeah, yeah!
Yeah!
Ready?
Yeah.
One, two...
Guys, thanks.
Yeah well,
they're going to die.
[clears throat]
Feathers.
I can't believe these dudes
are beating us out
on being murdered.
Like honestly, their privilege
is just ridiculous.
- What are we going
- to do now?
- We go back to
- the original plan.
Finish what we started.
Or we call the police?
- We don't have time to wait
- for the police.
- We can't take
- any more chances.
Maybe Ashley's right, Dana.
We lured him out, the police
can find him and arrest him.
Either way it'll be over.
We won.
And how do you know they won't
say that we lured him into it?
That it was our fault?
- He could say it was
- self-defense.
We chose to come here,
we brought weapons.
And that's if they find him.
- He's gotten away
- once before.
And nothing will change.
Absolutely nothing.
I mean, we are these
smart, tough,
incredible, kick-ass women,
and we do not need to let
some asshole with
power drill scare us off.
a battery operated
- Because we can take him
- down, right?
For my mom, for us, for
everybody else he's terrorized.
And when we do it
we'll show him
- and every other dick-obsessed
- murderous asshole
That there are consequences,
yes, and we are
those consequences.
[cheering]
Yeah! Yeah!!!
Yeah!!!
Okay. I get it now.
She's good.
Okay.
So let's go.
Yes!
[cheering excitedly]
Okay.
Where'd the guys go?
- If we stick to the plan,
- maybe we can save them, okay?
- But that is the most
- important thing,
- That no matter what,
- we stick together.
[whirring]
He's here!
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhhh!!!!!
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
- Come back!
Don't... split up.
[panicked breathing]
Okay.
You can do this.
[loud noise]
[gasps]
Brady?
[yells]
I'm not afraid of you!
[distorted eerie music]
♪
I'm not afraid of you.
You know you want it.
[whirring]
[grinding]
Performance issues?
[screaming furiously]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
[gasps]
[whirring]
[dramatic music]
♪
[grunting]
Back off, freak face.
[whirring]
- Don't worry,
- I got this.
Shaun, wait!
[fighting grunt]
No!
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
[whirring]
- [screaming]
- No!!!!!
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
- [screaming]
- No!!!!!!
- [dramatic music]
- ♪
♪
- [screaming]
- Help!!! Help!!!
♪
- [screaming]
- Help!!! Help!!!
I messed up the plan!
[screaming hysterically]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
♪
[breathing shakily]
[sniffing]
[clanging sounds]
- [quietly]
- You're pretty.
All of you.
Very pretty.
[eerie music swells]
♪
Gotcha.
Diane sends her regards.
Hey!
Kim wanted a word.
[grunts]
And Jackie needed
some closure.
And, and this is for Trish
Deveraux, my mother.
She'll take her life
back now.
[whirring]
- [hysterical screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
It takes a lot of love
for a person to do this.
[whirring]
Dee!
[gasps]
Okay.
But I love you.
Yeah.
Well, the feeling isn't mutual.
[gurgles]
[laughs]
[screaming]
Ahhh!!!
[grunting]
Sorry.
Didn't want to be left out.
[laughs]
[cheering]
[sighs]
Well, I can finally
get rid of these.
- Playing the hot girl
- is exhausting.
The lady doth protest
too much.
Fine!
Next time you deal with
all the slut shaming.
There won't be a next time.
We did it.
It's... it's done.
We did.
Where did you get that?
Oh.
- Kay left them at the door
- for us.
She's lucky Russ didn't murder
her when she dropped them off.
[eerie music]
♪
There you are.
Yeah, I'm still not sure
they didn't do this.
We never saw Russ Thorne
kill anyone, you know.
It's just their word.
[grunting]
Woah, uh, he's dead, Dee.
Yeah well, they never die
just once.
Well technically he died twice,
so I think we're good.
[sighs]
How can you eat right now?
I'm starving.
Plus, he's not getting
any less dead.
- We should get back to the cabin,
- call the police,
And lock ourselves inside
until they come.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah.
Hey!
- You shouldn't eat food
- from strangers.
Whatever, Grandma Maeve.
Is it time to call the police?
I want to get out of these
clothes and go home now.
You remember what to say?
Yup.
You coming, Dee?
- Do me a favor and watch
- the body?
He's dead.
I just think we should be
a little extra cautious
until the police get here.
Fine.
Oh good.
Watch the body.
But he's dead.
Just do it anyway.
- [eerie music]
- ♪
♪
This sucks ass!
[crows cawing]
What did the police say?
Um, I haven't called yet.
Ash, we need
to finish this.
- I don't have any bars and the
- Wi-Fi password isn't working.
I'm waiting for the modem
to reboot.
You think something's wrong?
Let's just get the hell
out of here.
Hey.
- [eerie music]
- ♪
- Looks like
- the Wi-Fi's down.
You smell that?
No.
It's gone now.
You want a beer?
- I need something to calm
- my nerves.
No.
- I'm going to go find service
- somewhere else.
It's not working
inside anymore.
There's that smell.
Dude, I don't smell anything.
Be careful.
Those creepy girls
could be anywhere.
- Hey, I think
- I'm getting a bar.
[sniffs]
Ugh, gross.
♪
♪ This is love ♪
♪ You are like ♪
♪ I think ♪
♪ we wasted the same time ♪
♪ It kills me♪♪
♪
♪ It kills me ♪
♪ That you're ♪
♪ right here tonight ♪
[eerie music]
♪
[creaking sound]
♪ I'm crying
for your love ♪
♪ I need you here tonight ♪
♪ To warm my heart
and hold me tight ♪
♪
[screaming]
Ahhhhhh!!!!
[groaning]
[dramatic music]
♪
Thanks.
- It's a good thing you know
- how to fix cars.
Hey.
We did good.
- [quietly]
- Yeah.
You need anything else?
Nope.
I know what I'm doing.
Yeah, you do.
[eerie music]
♪
Bree, I might need
a hand here.
Ahhhhh!!!!!
Ow.
Help!
Help, Bree!
[starts engine]
Help!!! No!!!!
- No, no, no, no, no!!!
- Stop!!!!
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
Stop!!!!!
No!!! Stop!
[shrieking]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
Guys.
- Who moved everything
- in the kitchen?
Our weapons are gone.
- They messed up
- the crime scene.
Alix?
- I didn't. You asked me
- not to.
- That never stopped
- you before.
- I don't know,
- maybe it was Ashley.
She wouldn't.
Guys, something's wrong.
I think we need to leave now.
- Well Ashley should be done
- with the car any minute.
Oh.
- And who's watching
- the body?
I asked Alix to do it.
- He's dead.
- I got bored.
Shit.
Dana, he's dead.
Oh, and his body is gone?
No, no, no, no, no!
He was just there.
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
Maeve!
[screaming]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
- Someone is still
- after us.
You think?
[sobs]
Where's Ashley?
- [screams]
- Nooooo!!!!
He got Ashley!
- Breanie, get away
- from the window.
[gasps]
[glass shattering]
Shit, that was so...
[gasps]
No!
[panicked breathing]
[sobbing]
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
Breanie?
[sobbing]
Maeve?
We have to fight back.
He took our weapons.
We don't have anything
to fight with.
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[sobbing]
How the hell is he still alive?
What are we going to do?
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
You planned everything.
You're supposed to know.
How could I have known about-
[gunshot]
[gasps]
- You should've called
- the police
When Alix found
the first dead guy.
Now Breanie and Ashley
are dead.
This is all your fault.
We all did this.
We all wanted this.
Alix did it.
[gunshots]
- Yeah, it could it be one
- of the guys.
- They're obsessed
- with Russ.
Maybe, maybe they're doing
a copycat thing.
Maybe.
Maybe?
The best you can do is maybe?
- We need to get out of here
- before they murder us!
[gun shots]
Okay, okay, uh...
Alix.
- You said you found the dead guy
- in a truck.
The tires were flat.
Okay. The guys...
If their car is still here
we can run and take it.
- They could be the ones trying
- to kill us.
[gun shot]
And how do we get out of here
without getting hit?
I'll go out the side window.
If you distract him
I can slip out.
Fine.
You go.
Alix and I will stay.
No.
It's okay, I'm going
to protect you.
Like that?
Then you'll protect me.
[gun shot]
[yells]
Hey asshole!
I think I figured out why
you're doing this.
And I would tell you to go
to hell,
but I can bet you
you'll get there very soon.
Come on!
Come get me!
I'm ready!
Come get me, you loser!
Go!
Go! Go!
[panicked breathing]
Maeve?
I'm not feeling so...
[vomits]
[panicked breathing]
Okay.
Shit.
[panicked breathing]
[gasps]
- Both: Why are you trying
- to kill us?
Both: What?
Both: You!
You killed Matt!
And I found Guy
dead in the cooler!
Guy died in the house.
No, that was the other Guy.
There were two of them!
Okay, well you killed
Ashley and Bree!
I didn't kill anybody!
Okay, well neither did we.
Okay, well we did kill the guy
killing people,
but people are still dying.
- Yeah. 'Cause it's part of your
- big feminist plot
To get rid of all the men!
[sighs]
That was a really sexist
thing to say.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
But that doesn't
change anything.
- Ugh, well this isn't getting
- us anywhere.
And if you aren't the killer,
then they're still
with my friends.
And I need to help them.
Okay.
You drop the stick
and I'll drive us there.
No!
No, no, no!!!
♪
[vomiting]
How many of the cookies
did you eat?
Most of them.
- Why? Do you think that's
- why I'm sick?
Maybe.
Please don't be mad at me.
I'm not mad.
I wish I listened to you.
I'm sorry I didn't.
I don't want to die.
I'm sorry I didn't turn around
to take you home.
- But you are not going
- to die.
- Dana's going to be back
- any minute now
And we're going to leave.
How do you know
she'll come back?
We take care
of each other.
That's what we do.
I love you, Maeve.
I love you too.
[vomits]
Kay?
Hey kid.
What are you doing out here?
I'm snail hunting.
- Did you see someone
- out here?
Just you.
- Okay, well there's a,
- there's a killer out here.
- And there was one,
- but now there,
Now there's another.
Are you okay?
There's no killer anymore.
There was one once.
- A lot of people heard about it
- because of this podcast,
But he died a long time ago.
- No, no, no.
- He didn't.
He didn't.
- He came back and he,
- he tried to kill us.
But then we killed him.
But then he, someone else is...
still trying to.
Please, help.
- [whispers]
- I'll help you, okay.
Okay.
That ridiculous podcast.
- We were finally getting things
- turned around here,
- Bringing back the real
- vacationers.
Then these idiots start talking
about this one time incident.
This one time.
Four people died.
It's a shame.
Did you live here
back then?
Yeah, still do.
Did you know Russ Thorne?
No.
He killed my mother's friends,
and he tried to kill her.
But she survived.
That is why I came here.
I wanted to help her
get over what happened
all those years ago,
because I thought that
it ruined her life.
But then one day I realized
that she had gotten over it,
and that it was me
who ruined her life,
because if I hadn't been born,
maybe she could've moved on.
But instead she just became
obsessed with protecting me.
That is why I came here.
I wanted to show her that
she didn't have to worry,
and that I could take care
of myself.
Mothers just want to protect
their children.
You brought over a container
of cookies last night,
and the Wi-Fi password
changed this morning.
[thwack]
Who the hell are you?
[sobbing]
I'm old!
You hit an old lady!
I'm sorry.
[yells]
My son deserved better than you
and your whore friends!
Your son is Russ?
I tried to help you.
- I tried to make it easier
- for you
Like I tried to help
the other ones.
You could've gone to sleep,
then you wouldn't have
tempted him,
showing yourselves off
like that.
What was he supposed
to do?
How about just
not kill people?
When did that become
so much to ask?
He was a grown man,
an adult,
and we didn't make him
do anything!
[screaming]
Ahhhhh!!!!!
[pained breathing]
- [dramatic music]
- ♪
Let me in!
It's me! It's me!
Let me in, let me in!!!
Let me in, let me in!!!!
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
Oh, my god!
Are you okay?
I don't know, I don't think
it's that bad.
Kay is Russ's mother.
Oh, my god!
I knew it. The bastard!
- [whispers]
- She's the one after us.
Is this because I stole
her beer?
No Alix, this isn't your fault.
This isn't any of our fault.
[groaning]
We can take her.
With a nail gun?
I didn't see a nail gun.
She had a knife, but...
[gasps]
I don't know.
Alix! Alix!
Wake up!!
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!
[pounding]
Alix!
No, no!
No!
Get away from my girls!
Mom?
Dana, you didn't call me!
Mom, we did it.
We killed Russ Thorne.
I know you.
You're the bitch who ruined
my son's life.
I have a name.
It's Trish Deveraux.
I stopped your son
from killing me.
- I'm going to stop you
- from killing my daughter.
- Dana, take your friends
- to the car and leave.
No!
- We're not going
- without you.
No!
- [screams]
- Ahhhh!!!!!
Get in the car now!
Mom!
Now!
[screaming]
[crash]
They owe me!
They killed my son!
They owe you nothing.
Russ Thorne was a murderer!
A predator!
[fighting grunt]
You made him do it.
[groaning]
This stops now!
Huh?
I don't have any feeling
in this hand.
You can thank your son
for that.
[fighting grunts]
[crash]
[out of breath]
Okay.
- I'm going to go back in
- and help my mom.
Take the keys and go.
Dana.
- [whispers]
- She's my mother.
She is the reason
that I came here.
To save her.
So I, I have to save her.
I'm sorry that I got you
into this.
I wanted to be here.
This is for my son.
[gasping for air]
No!
I'm not afraid of you!
Trish: Dana!
[screaming]
Ahhh!!!
Russ.
[sobs]
No.
Come on!
Look out!
Ow!
- [screaming]
- Ahhhhh!!!!!!
[gasps]
♪
It's over. It's over.