Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Look. It's snow.
Yes.
Here I come!
Heads up!
- We give up! We give up!
- Yeah!
Linus, watch out.
What? What is it?
- I just fluffed that pillow.
- What's gotten into you?
- The holiday spirit.
- Already?
It's the first weekend of December,
and that means Christmas and Grandma
will be here soon.
Well, I'm excited about
the Christmas part.
Linus.
I like seeing Grandma too,
but she's always trying to
get me to give up my blanket.
Enjoy that blanket while you can,
because you know what happens
when Grandma gets here.
Not if she can't find it.
- What are you watching, big brother?
- Citizen Kane. It's a famous old movie.
Why are you watching that?
It looks boring.
If you must know, it's almost Christmas
and that means New Year's
is right around the corner.
And I haven't completed any of
my New Year's resolutions from last year.
One of them was
"view a great work of art."
So I'm watching this.
"Rosebud"? What's "rosebud"?
I don't know, Sally. I'll tell you later.
Aren't you going to get that?
Andy, Olaf.
You're the first ones to arrive.
Snoopy's very excited to
have you all here for the holidays.
He's waiting for you in the back… yard.
Make yourselves at home.
- It's for you.
- How do you know it's not for you?
I'm indisposed.
Marbles. Long time no see.
Belle. Happy holidays.
Snoopy! It's your sister!
Spike. You're looking… good.
You're the last one to arrive.
I'll bet you're excited
for your family reunion to begin.
They're all in the back.
"Rosebud" was the sled.
So much for that resolution.
Five cents, please.
It's been a good year.
What seems to be the problem,
Charlie Brown?
Last year I made this list
of New Year's resolutions,
and I haven't accomplished a single one.
I feel like a failure.
It's more than a feeling, Charlie Brown.
Let me see that.
Here's your problem. These resolutions
are completely unrealistic.
You need to adjust your expectations
to match your abilities.
- What do you mean?
- Resolution number three,
"build the world's tallest snowman."
How about just "build a snowman"?
Or number nine, "paint a masterpiece."
Maybe just settle for
"do something remotely creative."
That doesn't seem very ambitious.
Exactly. All you need to do
is complete one realistic resolution
and you're covered for the year.
One realistic resolution? Why not?
Anyone can do that, even me.
Sensible mediocrity. That's the spirit.
Now, what type of gingerbread house
will Grandma like?
Traditional or something postmodern?
Grandma's coming to my house
La, la, la, la, la, la
Party gifts and hugs for me
Cookie here, a cookie there
Cookies all the way
Oh, what fun it is to laugh
When Grandma comes to stay, hey
Oh, Grandma
Brings comfort and joy
Linus, what are you doing?
I just made this room perfect.
A boy's gotta do what he's gotta do to
hide his blanket before Grandma visits.
Well, that's the first place she'll look.
No one outsmarts Grandma.
Hello, van Pelt's residence.
Happy Christmas Eve.
Grandma! I can't wait to see you today.
The decorations are up
and everything is ready.
What? What do you mean
you're not coming?
But we were going to bake cookies
and play games and go caroling.
But I've been planning all month.
I thought we were going to--
Oh, no. It's fine. I'm-- I'm fine.
Merry-- Merry Christmas, Grandma.
Lucy! Wake up! It's Christmas!
For you.
Happy holidays!
Six geese a laying
Five golden rings
Maybe Grandma didn't want to come.
Didn't she wanna see me?
Was it because of me?
She does love me, doesn't she?
Am I not lovable?
If my own grandma doesn't wanna see me…
how do I know
anyone really loves me?
Lucy, you gotta pull yourself together.
You have friends. Lots of them. Yeah.
That's right.
You are Lucy "Lovable" van Pelt.
And I know just how to prove it.
Linus. Wake up. Christmas was a letdown,
but New Year's is going to be perfect.
I'm going to throw a party!
Linus! Did you hear me?
Throw a party. Sounds like fun.
And you're going to help.
Do you promise?
- I promise. Just let me sleep.
- Deal.
It's not going to be just
any old New Year's Eve party.
It's going to be an elegant affair.
I'm calling it "Lucy's Gala: A New Year's
Eve Celebration of Elegant Perfection."
That's a mouthful.
I know. Impressive, isn't it?
And everyone's going to be there
to celebrate me.
I mean with me. You know why?
Because I am lovable!
There's so much we need to do.
Rise and shine!
That's enough sleep for one day.
What did I just get myself into?
As you know, Linus,
to make a perfect party,
everyone should dress up and be on time,
and good manners only.
Are you getting all of this?
"Good manners only."
And at midnight,
I want someone to sing that New Year's
song that people always sing.
"Auld Lang Syne?"
Should auld acquaintance be forgot
That's the one.
Hey, why don't you sing it?
Oh, okay.
But not with those dusty old lyrics.
Here. I wrote some of my own.
One thing should never be forgot
Lucy's party blew my mind?
- Really?
- Of course. I'm a lot of fun to be around.
I made some calls this morning
and rented a ballroom. Isn't this great?
I'm not even thinking
about Grandma anymore.
You rented a ballroom?
You wanna throw your party
in this crummy old building?
Well, it's a little rough on the outside,
but inside…
she's a real charmer.
How did you pay for a ballroom?
In nickels.
Charlie Brown has a lot of problems.
This is perfect.
The picture of elegance.
Can't you see it, Linus?
Oh, I see it. I just don't believe it.
Nonsense.
When we're done, it will be amazing.
All it needs is a few decorations,
some music and a lot of elbow grease.
I don't think I have enough elbows,
and it sure is a big space.
Of course it is.
I'm inviting all of my friends.
I can't wait to see their adoring faces
smiling back at me,
their gracious and lovable host.
Okay. I'm off to prepare the invitations
so I can deliver the good news.
The things a brother will do
for his sister.
Build a snowman.
That's a simple resolution. I can do that.
Rats.
Here's the carrot you wanted.
Today is your lucky day, Charlie Brown.
I've solved your resolution problem.
You have?
I'm inviting you
to my New Year's Eve party,
- and you're in charge of decorations.
- I am?
Am I invited to your party?
Can you stay awake until midnight?
If that's a challenge, challenge accepted.
You got some moxie, kid.
Okay. Here's your invitation
to Lucy's Gala:
A New Year's Eve Celebration
of Elegant Perfection.
That's a mouthful.
Do you wanna go or not?
Remember, elegant. Think silver and gold.
I want streamers, bows,
festive centerpieces,
and a balloon drop at midnight.
What does decorating
have to do with my resolutions?
Your list. Number nine.
Number nine, "do something
remotely creative." That's right.
Count me in.
And you'll be in charge of the snacks.
Can you handle that?
Yes!
- You can count on us.
- What do we bring?
Think "elegant." Finger foods
are the perfect way to go.
You two are in charge
of getting everyone up and dancing.
- I love to dance.
- Who doesn't?
See you there.
You are formally invited
to my New Year's Eve party.
Yes!
I was hoping you could make
an ice sculpture of the very lovable host.
- Who's that?
- Me!
That's it? No problem.
"Lucy's Gala: A New Year's Eve
Celebration of Elegant Perfection."
- That's a mouthful.
- I know!
At the party,
I want you to play something significant.
Do you have anything like that?
No. Do you have something with
a bouncy rhythm you can dance to?
That's it!
I can't stand it! I just can't stand it.
Musicians are far too temperamental.
Hey, now that's a beat
you can dance to.
What do you say to playing
my New Year's Eve party?
I can pay in dog biscuits.
Oh, a photo? I'd be delighted. Cheese.
Enjoy.
Looking good, boys.
You've really outdone yourself,
Charlie Brown.
Yeah. My resolution is within reach.
Hey, what's that?
That's the pull cord
for the balloon drop.
Balloon drop?
Of course.
Now let's go over the grand finale.
Charlie Brown, come listen.
Your role is very important.
As midnight approaches, Linus and I
will be on stage with the band.
And when I yell "Happy New Year
to you too," you pull that cord.
- Got it?
- "Happy New Year to you too." Got it.
Happy New Year to you too.
I've been thinking about
"Auld Lang Syne" too.
I'm not sure if we're doing it justice.
I agree. We should go back
to the original lyrics.
- They have a kind message all about--
- No. I mean the song needs a beat.
Now this is the kind of music
to start the New Year off right!
Yeah.
Lucy, "Auld Lang Syne"
is not a dance number.
It's a traditional song with deep meaning.
And it's depressing.
A grand finale requires a balloon drop,
flashy costumes and catchy music.
Do it for me, dear brother.
Catchy it is.
Perfect. Now I need to get home
so I can start getting ready.
Better pick up the pace if we're going to
be ready before our guests arrive.
Linus, how are you with knots?
I'm gonna dance all night.
You are lovable,
and this party is going to prove it.
Now! The event
you've been waiting for all week!
Welcome to Lucy's Gala:
A New Year's Eve Celebration of--
Elegant Perfection.
Party! Look at that! Let's go!
Come on, everyone!
Okay, let's get to work.
Work? I thought this was a party.
Enjoying yourself? Good!
Having a nice time? Wonderful.
- Good to see you.
- Don't you just love this party? Me too.
Have fun.
"Happy New Year to you too."
Where is my band?
Midnight, you're mine.
You said it, sister.
Boys!
The invitation clearly stated good
manners only. That means no running.
Vámonos.
What is this?
Where are the fancy little sandwiches
with the crust cut off?
I specifically asked for finger food.
You can eat jelly beans with your fingers.
- And tapioca pudding?
- Yes?
Forget it.
What are those?
I thought it would be nice if I brought
my world-famous mud pies for dessert.
Pigpen, you can't expect anyone
to eat this disgusting slop.
- They're delicious. Hey.
- Linus!
I was eating that.
- Here. Take these.
- Mud pies.
No, take these away.
We were just trying to help.
We wanted to bring fun party food.
This party is already fun.
Look at everyone having fun.
What is the meaning of this?
We wanted to dance.
So we brought our favorite music.
No, no, no. I have a real band coming.
Thank you.
Linus! Where's the band? Where's my music?
I'll go find out.
Mingle among yourselves.
Have fun!
Schroeder, you're having fun, aren't you?
Doesn't this elegant party
remind you of anyone?
I guess so.
I knew you'd think so. Would you say
this evening is lovable?
I'm gonna go check out
those chairs over there.
Nine o'clock.
Gonna stay awake. Come on, Sally.
It's only nine o'clock?
Being this lovable is exhausting.
Make way. Coming through.
My ice sculpture!
Gather round! Gather round, everyone,
for the big reveal!
Finally something exciting.
Drumroll, please.
What is so funny? Linus!
Linus, find somewhere
to put that… ice thing.
What? She didn't like it?
Where is my band?
- The band is here.
- Who's ready to dance?
- Come dance, Charlie Brown.
- I'll be right back.
- Is that a dog band?
- Why not?
Good. You're finally here.
Let's get this party started.
No, no, no. I didn't hire you for this.
Play something peppy
that everyone can dance to.
- I'm gonna sit down.
- I give up.
I'm back.
Nobody can dance to that.
Dog music stinks.
Linus!
I don't understand.
This party is the perfect reflection
of me, but no one is having fun.
- Why don't they love me?
- What?
My party. Why don't they love my party?
Maybe if you didn't have
so many expectations and rules--
With no rules, this would be a madhouse.
No. We are not trying hard enough.
- We?
- Yes.
The tone of an elegant party
is set by its hosts.
We can still save this night.
Time for a costume change.
You're gonna put that on?
Don't be silly. No, this is for you.
- This is for me.
- But I--
The future of my party
is depending on you.
Please, Linus.
If you don't wear this costume
and sing that song at midnight
for our grand finale,
the night will end in failure and this
whole thing will have been for nothing.
You promised you'd help me, so help.
I knew I could count on you.
And to think,
all my problems would be solved
if Grandma had just showed up
for Christmas.
Hey! No double-dipping, Maynard.
You're banned from the crudités.
No, no. I'm awake. I'm awake.
Quiet down, everybody.
Are you all having a good time?
Not really.
Well, it's 30 minutes until midnight
when we will count down to the New Year.
Won't that be fun?
Then Linus will lead us in singing
that "Auld Lang"-- whatever song.
Come on out here and show everyone
how excited you are for the New Year.
I don't want to.
Linus, get out here.
Oh, my goodness.
Are those feathers?
Go on. Say something.
My Sweet Babboo.
So much for elegant.
Linus, get up. You're ruining everything.
Lucy, I've done everything I can
to make you happy.
I worked all night, all week, even.
And now you're saying
I'm ruining everything. Me?
This could've been a fun party,
but it's you and your perfect rules
that have turned a perfectly good holiday
into a perfectly terrible party.
He's right.
That's right. I said it.
This party is terrible!
I hereby quit
your terrible party committee.
You can find someone else
to take for granted.
I'm done.
- He said it.
- That was a bust.
- Come on. Let's go.
- It's not fun at all.
- Wait.
- Come on. Let's go.
Go ahead. Leave! This isn't my fault.
I planned a perfectly elegant party.
- I never asked for disappointing snacks.
- Hey.
Or boring music.
And don't get me started
on that ice sculpture.
I thought it was good.
Oh, I almost forgot. Happy New Year!
Well, happy New Year to you too!
"Happy New Year to you too."
Good grief.
I'm awake. I'm awake.
Wait! It's almost midnight.
Please. Please.
Goodbye, resolution.
You left too?
Yeah. The party
kind of broke up after you left.
- I really hoped it would work.
- What would work?
I tried to help Lucy because she thought
that if she threw a party
and everyone showed up
and had a good time,
it would prove somehow that she is loved.
But that doesn't make any sense.
Of course she's loved.
You and I know that.
But our grandma didn't come for Christmas
this year, and Lucy took it pretty hard.
She thought it was because of her.
Well, that certainly explains a lot.
Poor Lucy.
"Should auld acquaintance be forgot
and never brought to mind?"
It's from the song "Auld Lang Syne."
I always sing along
and pretend to know the words.
Most people do.
As one year turns into the next,
"Auld Lang Syne" is a heartfelt reminder
that we should never forget our friends
or the good times we've shared.
And hopefully,
they will do the same for us.
That's a really nice idea.
Yeah. Lucy sure could've
used a reminder like that.
…eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
Should auld acquaintance be forgot
And never brought to mind?
- "Should auld acquaintance be forgot?"
- And days of auld lang syne?
For auld lang…
One happy New Year to me.
Lucy?
I'm sorry about your party.
I'm the one who should be apologizing.
I ruined everything.
I should've been more appreciative
of everything you did. Sorry.
Here's your blanket.
I should've known my party
was going to be a bust.
I'm just… unlovable.
That's not true.
I love you.
You're my brother. You have to love me.
Actually, that's not true either.
But I do.
And so do a lot of other people.
Like who?
Like me, Lucy.
Good old Charlie Brown.
Linus told me about your grandma
and what that party meant to you.
I know what it's like when things
don't work out the way you'd hoped.
Can I ask you a question?
You fail over and over
and over and over and--
What's the question?
Right.
Well, how do you do it, Charlie Brown?
How do you manage to keep going
when life gets you down?
I remember that no matter how bad things
may seem, I can always rely on my friends.
Thanks, you two. But I'm not sure
how many friends I have after tonight.
Good night.
Lucy.
- Heya, Lucy.
- Good to see you.
Hey, old friend!
Wha-- What's going on?
Charlie Brown let us know
you were going through a hard time.
He did?
It's okay, Lucy.
Yeah. We all wanted to be here.
To remind you that you're not alone.
- But why would you--
- It's what friends do, Lucille.
- We're here for you.
- We love you, Lucy.
You do?
I'm… lovable?
- Yeah.
- Oh, come on. Don't be silly.
But midnight. The countdown.
The singing. You all missed it.
Because of me.
I'm so sorry.
Can you ever forgive me?
In case you hadn't noticed,
we already have.
Lucy, it's never too late
to make things right.
Ten.
Nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
Should auld acquaintance be forgot
And never brought to mind?
- Should auld acquaintance be forgot
- Who? Me?
And days of auld lang syne?
For auld lang syne, my dear
For auld lang syne
- Hey, Snoopy.
- We'll take a cup of kindness yet
For auld lang syne
Should auld acquaintance be forgot
You know what, Linus? I was wrong.
This song is wonderful, and it will always
remind me of all my friends.
I thought you might see it that way.
For days of auld lang syne
For auld lang syne, my dear
Now this is a perfect party.
Here. Write this down. "Be a good friend."
"Good friend."
- Now cross it off.
- But--
Go on. Cross it off. Good.
You may not have completed
any resolutions last year,
but you're already covered for this year.
Happy New Year, Lucy.
Happy New Year, Charlie Brown.
We'll take a cup of kindness yet
For auld lang syne
You should've seen it, Grandma.
We had food, decorations,
music and dancing.
And the best part,
all my friends were there.
Yes, Linus was there too.
He even led us in singing
"Auld Lang Syne."
No, he did not give up his blanket,
but we can work on that
when you visit for my birthday.
I love you too, Grandma.