(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
FATHER SERGIO: (IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH)
I remember the first time
I heard Robin play.
It was really
quite extraordinary.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(IN ITALIAN)
FATHER SERGIO:
SAGRAVAS:
LUCA:
CLAIRE:
Ciao.
LUCA: Ciao.
Sì, um...
(IN ENGLISH) Very informal.
A friend of mine from admissions
would like to hear Robin play.
Oh! When?
Uh, she has a small window
tomorrow afternoon.
Robin can leave
my class earlier.
That's good.
CLAIRE: Oh, there she is!
(SPEAKS ITALIAN, CHUCKLES)
You were so wonderful!
No, no. It's the best
I've ever heard you play.
Hey. Really proud of you,
sweetheart.
(ROBIN SIGHS)
(KISSES, SPEAKS ITALIAN)
MARCO: (IN ITALIAN)
ADRIANA:
(IN ENGLISH)
Well done tonight, Robin.
MARCO: (IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Well done.
SAGRAVAS:
MARCO:
(IN ENGLISH) So...
Pizza to celebrate, huh?
(ADRIANA SPEAKS ITALIAN)
I love pizza!
(IN ITALIAN)
(ADRIANA SPEAKS ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Uh, Claire,
you're more than welcome
to come with us, if you...
Oh, no, no. I'm gonna go home.
(IN ITALIAN)
ADRIANA: (IN ENGLISH) Sure.
Oh, she's saying
she has an algebra test.
LUCA: Yeah, I... I got it.
Come on, sweetheart.
I won't keep you up late.
Promise.
Of course! Go, go.
Go have fun. Go.
I'm so proud of you.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
Ciao.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
LUCA: (IN ITALIAN)
CLAIRE:
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SPEAKS ITALIAN)
(GRUNTS)
PATIENT:
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
CLAIRE:
PATIENT:
(YELPS)
(METAL TRAY CLATTERS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
CLAIRE: (IN ENGLISH) It's okay.
Give yourself a break, Claire.
You don't have to pretend
for him.
It must be exhausting.
You're here. It's more
than his own son ever does.
Thank you.
(PIANO PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(KEYS JINGLING)
(IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Robin?
Why is your bike in the hallway?
(PIANO PLAYING STOPS)
CLAIRE: Hmm.
CLAIRE: Audition? Hmm.
Is that what
Signor Sagravas said?
He said it was an audition?
Yeah, he did tell me
it was very informal.
CLAIRE: Conservatory.
That's a big step!
I know.
It's just all happening so fast.
Hmm.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(KIDS LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(SPEAKS ITALIAN)
Buongiorno, Signora Marino.
Buongiorno, Maya.
(IN ENGLISH) Still don't know
how you can take it.
Your mom's okay as a teacher,
but I would seriously suffocate
if my mom was everywhere I was.
EMMA: "A mourner walked
Among the children"
"I notwithstanding went about
As one bemoaning a dominion"
"Itself the only prince
Cast out"
"Elder, today, a session wiser
And fainter, too"
"As wiseness is"
"I find myself
Still softly searching"
"For my delinquent palaces"
"And a suspicion
Like a finger"
"Touches my forehead
Now and then"
"That I am looking oppositely"
"For the sight
Of the Kingdom of Heaven"
Beautiful.
So, a lot has been written
about the underlying melancholy
of this poem.
What do we think Emily Dickinson
is so sad about?
She lost something.
CLAIRE: Yeah.
What do you think she's
referring to when she says,
"Still softly searching
for my delinquent palaces?"
She's looking for the life
she had.
Yeah. She's looking
for the... the mystery
and the enchantment
of a world that's
no longer available to her.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
CLAIRE: Okay. So,
your poems are due on Friday.
Please, keep working on them,
enjoy the process.
If anybody has anything
you'd like me to read
in advance, you can pass it in.
(BOTH SPEAK ITALIAN)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MOUTHS) Good luck.
(RAIN PATTERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(BOTH SPEAK ITALIAN)
Did he show up
with the jail-bait wife?
Of course he did.
(GROANS)
Still look like you?
Of course she does.
When I was a teenager!
(BUS HORN HONKS)
VIV: Some men are such pigs!
(BUS ENGINE REVVING)
Especially the
ex-husband variety. Hey!
Wait! Wait!
NUN: (IN ITALIAN)
VIV: (IN ENGLISH) Wait!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
SAGRAVAS: Claire!
(DRAMATIC MUSICAL STING)
Claire. (SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
NURSE: No, no, no!
(IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH)
But I think my daughter...
(IN ITALIAN)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ALL SPEAK ITALIAN FRANTICALLY)
No, no, no, no...
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
(VENTILATOR HISSING)
(DR. STANCIK SPEAKS ITALIAN)
DR. STANCIK:
NURSE:
(SPEAKS ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH)
You can't stay here! Go!
(MUSIC FADES)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(CLAIRE SOBS)
(DRIPS ECHOING)
CLAIRE: God, please
don't take her from me.
LUCA: Claire...
(FOOTSTEPS ECHOING)
(IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH)
Claire, I'm so sorry.
(RAIN PATTERING ON WINDOW)
(IN ITALIAN)
(DEFIBRILLATORS ZAP)
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(CLAIRE SOBBING)
(SOBS)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(IN ENGLISH) Her finger moved.
Her hand moved.
Claire!
(GASPS)
(IN ITALIAN)
CLAIRE: Robin.
(IN ENGLISH) She was
clinically dead for 20 minutes.
The likelihood of brain damage
is probable.
It's a question of
to what degree.
We won't know
until she wakes up.
And when will that be?
DR. STANCIK: It's hard to say.
(IN ITALIAN)
DR. STANCIK:
(IN ENGLISH)
I'll leave you alone.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
OVER PA)
You should...
I'll just take them home
and come back, okay?
Claire.
I'm sorry, but I...
It's okay.
Okay. I'll see you soon.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(WATER BUBBLING)
(DRAMATIC MUSICAL STING)
(DISTORTED CHATTER)
(ROBIN BREATHES HEAVILY)
Oh, my God!
You're awake.
Hi, Mamma.
Your voice.
(SOFTLY) Yeah.
You're speaking.
You're back.
Yeah.
I'm back.
(PENLIGHT CLICKS)
DR. STANCIK: (IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH)
This is highly unusual.
Robin appears
to be functioning within
a completely normal range
in all aspects.
Other than scars and bruises,
at the moment,
she seems to be
walking away unscathed.
CLAIRE: Hmm.
LUCA: Right.
Since you say
she was verbal ten years ago,
the best I can surmise
is that the trauma to her brain
simply caused her to forget
she didn't want to speak.
(SPEAKS ITALIAN)
I'll let her go home today,
but she needs to take it slow.
It can take time
for the damage to show.
(CHUCKLES)
(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
Okay.
Here, I'll take those.
I can put them in the kitchen.
Want me to take
your coat, honey?
Oh, okay.
Um...
Should I put on
some coffee or...
No, I'll...
I should go. Thank you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
Thank you very much.
Thanks.
I'll call you tomorrow,
sweetheart, okay?
Okay. Bye, Dad.
Bye.
Ciao.
Ciao. Grazie.
(INDISTINCT AUDIO ON TV)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(ROBIN INHALES SHARPLY)
(UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING)
CLAIRE:
Holy Mary, mother of God,
pray for us sinners now
and at the hour of our death.
Hail Mary, full of grace...
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(MUSIC FADES)
(PIANO NOTE PLAYS, STOPS)
(PIANO NOTE RESUMES PLAYING)
Rob, what are you doing?
I want to go to school tomorrow.
Oh, the doctor says you need
to stay at home and rest--
Can you stop that, please?
ROBIN: I want to go
to school tomorrow.
Robin. Robin.
Tomorrow, tomorrow,
tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow...
Honey, okay. Let's...
Let's see how you're feeling
in the morning.
(PIANO PLAYING STOPS)
(KITCHEN TIMER BEEPS)
Thank you.
(UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
GIRL 1:
I saw it fly through the window.
GIRL 2:
Its neck is probably broken.
GIRL: It's only stunned.
(BIRD CHIRPING)
Stop! You're holding it
too tight! You're killing it.
I know a secret.
(IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) What do you mean?
I'll show you.
CLAIRE: What's happening?
Robin? What is it?
Please, make her let it go,
Signora Marino.
Sweetheart, put the bird down.
Birds can carry diseases.
Are you worried
I'll catch something?
And die?
(CHURCH BELL RINGS)
Robin, put the bird down.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
It's dead.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Come on, girls! Move along.
Come here.
Excuse me. Robin! Robin!
Claire! Claire! Walk with me.
No. Hey--
Walk with me.
No.
Please.
I spoke to Robin this morning,
and she seemed more confident
than before the accident.
I told her that my friend
from admission
could come here specifically
to hear her play.
Robin really wants to do it.
No, no, no, no.
She's not ready for that. I...
I don't want her
under that kind of pressure.
No pressure at all!
Listen. I would only have her
do the pieces
she could play in her sleep.
Ludovica is also aware
of what Robin's been through.
CLAIRE: Giacomo. No!
Think about it!
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)
Hello! Earth to Claire!
(CHUCKLES)
Sorry.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Where are you?
Hmm.
(SIGHS)
I had such a strange morning
with Robin.
She's been through an ordeal.
You both have.
She just seems like
a different person.
Teenage girls are a mess,
no matter how you spin it.
One minute sweethearts,
the next, le monstre.
All the surging hormones!
It's totally normal, Claire.
Mm.
You didn't grow up Catholic?
Hmm.
VIV: Well, I did. And listen...
a Catholic girl's inner devil
has to rear her ugly head
at some point.
I was Robin.
And look at me now.
I turned out all right, okay?
(BOTH LAUGH)
Hey!
Give her time
to process all this.
Do you think
maybe you're looking
for something to be wrong
because it's just so hard
to believe she could be okay?
Don't do that.
(HUMMING) Don't do that!
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC BUILDS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SNIFFS)
(LOUD THUDDING)
(IN ITALIAN)
(CAT SCREECHES)
(IN ENGLISH) Oh, shit!
(TEDDY BEAR SQUEAKS)
(MUSIC FADES)
Oh, my God! I can't believe
you've done all this!
Morning!
You're wearing your uniform.
I wanted to do
something nice for you.
Oh, it's so beautiful.
Here.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh...
Sit.
Thanks, honey.
Were you in the storage room
last night?
Which storage room?
The one up on the terrace,
where we keep our things. I...
The door was open when I had
to go in and wash the sheets.
It wasn't me.
CLAIRE: I thought,
because you were up...
You know,
when you came in my room--
ROBIN: I wasn't in your room.
Oh, you don't remember?
Did you have a nightmare?
Honey?
Why... Why don't you come sit
and talk to me?
(ROBIN GRUNTS)
We'll be late for school.
No, you don't have school today.
It's Saturday.
(DRAMATIC MUSICAL STING)
So talk.
Oh, uh...
Well, I just feel like you've
been through so much and...
now that we can
talk to each other,
I wondered what it
was like for you.
What what was like?
You know, sometimes they say
you can see a bright light or...
I don't remember.
Or you can look down at yourself
and it's peaceful, or... No?
I told you...
that I don't...
fucking remember.
Robin!
(CHURCH BELL RINGING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
GIRL: Signora Marino?
Sì?
(SPEAKS ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Um, I...
Could you come back
at lunch time,
and we can talk about this?
Grazie.
Yes.
(PIANO PLAYING)
(ROBIN HUMMING OFF-KEY)
(PIANO PLAYING STOPS)
(CHAIR THUDS)
Ludovica!
I'm terribly sorry, Ludovica!
I've never seen her
behave that way.
Giacomo. What's going on?
I told you, she's not ready.
Um...
Ludovica was in the building
dropping off some music, so...
I thought it'd be okay
if she listened to Robin play.
It wasn't.
I pushed that too fast.
Yes, maybe.
This was a bit premature.
Yes.
SAGRAVAS: Ludovica!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Ah! (INHALES SHARPLY)
(MUSIC FADES)
VIV: Got a minute?
Jesus! What happened?
Nothing. I just... I scraped it.
You okay?
CLAIRE: Yeah. Yeah.
What do you need?
Claire, maybe she wasn't ready
to come back so soon.
Of course she wasn't ready, Viv.
This isn't perfectly normal
teenage behavior.
Whoa! I'm not the enemy here.
I'm sorry, I'm just... I'm...
It's okay.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(IN ITALIAN)
GIULIA:
(IN ENGLISH)
I'll take him to bed.
(IN ITALIAN)
DR. ROMANO:
GIULIA: (IN ENGLISH) Claire.
They're getting him ready
for the night.
(IN ITALIAN)
EVA:
(IN ENGLISH) Dr. Romano is such
a comfort to her
and other residents.
Dealing with trauma,
or loss of loved ones.
Grazie.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
GRETA: (IN ITALIAN)
CLAIRE: Robin!
Robin!
(MUSIC STOPS)
(TEDDY BEAR SQUEAKS)
(WATER RUNNING)
CLAIRE: Robin!
Robin? Rob!
(IN ENGLISH) Rob! I'm coming in.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
Robin?
Honey. Oh, my God!
What are you doing?
Ah! (WHIMPERS)
That's boiling water, honey.
Get out. You have to get out.
Come on. You gotta get out.
Come on!
Out, out, out! Right now. Oh!
Oh, my God!
(ROBIN WHIMPERS)
Why was the water so hot?
ROBIN: I don't know, Mom.
CLAIRE: What's going on?
Robin.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
You're so needy, it's pathetic.
(SCOFFS)
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
FEMALE VOICE 1: Loser.
FEMALE VOICE 2: Coward.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
(ALL MURMURING, LAUGHING)
Quiet!
Pass forward your poems,
and turn to Whitman
in your anthologies.
(WIND BLOWING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
CLAIRE: My God!
Signora Marino.
Everything okay?
CLAIRE: No.
Why would you...
MOTHER SUPERIOR: What is it?
How dare you?
(MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY)
I don't understand.
They are just poems.
What? No, they...
No, they-- I...
No, they had written terrible...
MOTHER SUPERIOR: Signora Marino!
Claire!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SHUSHES)
Signora Marino!
(RAIN PATTERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
(LOUD THUDDING)
(CLOCK CHIMES)
Robin!
What's wrong?
Robin, you have
to tell me what's wrong--
Shut up!
Robin!
It's not Robin.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(KEYBOARD CLICKING)
Very good, Robin.
(IN ITALIAN)
CLAIRE: (IN ENGLISH)
Something's wrong with her.
DR. STANCIK:
She's getting better every day.
No, no, no, no. I mean...
Maybe... Maybe physically,
but... but...
her behavior is...
is not normal.
Normalcy will take time.
We talked about it.
But you said that...
that the damage
might show up later.
It's... It's showing.
I know you're worried
about Robin,
but don't forget
to take care of yourself.
I could prescribe an anxiolytic.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)
Wanna swing by Giolitti's
and get some...
gelato?
Robin, what's wrong?
Robin.
Robin, can you please try
to help me understand
what's happening?
(ROBIN HUMS)
Ever since the accident...
How come you didn't ask
if I saw her?
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
LUCA: She seemed fine to me
when I was with her.
You're not listening to me.
She's changed.
There's... There's something...
different since the accident.
LUCA: Well, she--
And...
she mentioned her today.
LUCA: Oh.
It makes sense, Claire.
What she's just been through,
of course she'd think of her.
Doctors always say
she doesn't remember.
(MAN SPEAKS ITALIAN)
Uh...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER IN ITALIAN)
(IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Um... Claire,
why don't Adriana and I
take Robin for a week, hmm?
Just to give you a break.
CLAIRE: I don't need a break.
I need my daughter back.
I really gotta go. Sorry.
I'll call you back, all right?
I gotta go. Ciao.
Ciao.
(INDISTINCT AUDIO ON TV)
(DRAMATIC MUSICAL STING)
Everything okay, Mamma?
Yeah. Everything's fine.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(GIRL BREATHING HEAVILY)
What's going on in there?
(DOOR SLAMS OPEN)
(GIRL COUGHING)
What's the matter, honey?
What happened?
What's going on?
She was choking me.
Robin...
I was only trying to show her
that death isn't the end.
Robin.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MUSIC FADES)
What Robin's been through,
it must have been
very difficult, for both of you.
But, Claire, I think even you
can agree that her behavior
is beyond the normal scope
of readjustment.
There's something wrong
with her.
I'm not saying that.
CLAIRE: I am.
There's something desperately
wrong with my daughter.
MOTHER SUPERIOR:
I'm going to recommend...
that you get Robin
some help readjusting.
Until then, Claire,
I think it's best
if she doesn't come to school.
You're expelling her.
That's a harsh way to put it.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CLAIRE SIGHS)
FATHER SERGIO: (IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Come on.
Let's go.
Oh, no.
Father, please help her?
Cara. What's the problem?
(ROBIN GAGS)
FATHER SERGIO: What's trouble?
Oh my God! Oh my God!
(IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH)
Claire, do you understand
what you're saying?
Yes, I do.
Have you spoken to Luca?
Luca doesn't listen.
Luca can't help.
Doctors can't help.
Only God can help.
Only the Church.
That's why I'm here.
That's why I came to you.
You don't understand.
I can't lose her.
Father, please.
Okay, okay, okay. Don't worry.
Go inside and stay with her.
I'll try to find someone.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Luca?
Father!
LUCA: Claire.
FATHER SERGIO: He's her father.
I felt he needed to be included
in this conversation.
An exorcism? Really?
Come on, sweetheart,
let's go to my place.
Luca, stop.
You don't know what's going on.
Please, let Father Sergio help.
I can't help her, Claire.
Not the way you want me to.
So you're not even gonna try?
You'll shrug it off
and put her to bed and hope
she's better in the morning?
That's not going to happen.
There's something wrong
with her.
And it's getting worse.
Claire, we've all
been through hell.
I get it.
CLAIRE: No.
No, you're not getting it.
You're not getting it.
Our daughter is not herself.
She's not right.
LUCA: And whose fault is that?
She's been with you
night and day.
Come on, sweetheart. Come on.
I... I think you both...
need some space.
(MUSIC FADES)
OMAR: (IN ITALIAN)
(CHURCH BELL RINGING)
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(IN ENGLISH) Claire, right?
Yes.
Listen, I haven't eaten all day.
I'm heading across the street
for a pasta. Join me.
CLAIRE: I was really moved
by the man
who talked about the hereafter
as very freeing and, um...
peaceful.
Omar.
A year ago, up in Livigno,
he was hiking around Lago Vago
with his grandsons
and found a baby deer stranded
on the frozen lake.
He went out to push it
to the shoreline,
but not before the ice broke.
His grandsons called 1-1-2,
but it was 45 minutes
before rescuers could get there
and break through
to pull out his body.
But paramedics
still performed CPR
while getting him
to the hospital.
And they were able
to bring him back.
How is that even possible?
When someone drowns
in freezing water,
they may appear clinically dead,
but in rare instances
they can be revived
with little
to no neurological defect.
The body attempts
to thwart the cold
and preserve blood flow
to the brain and the heart.
The doctors were able
to slowly warm him
and bring him back once he was
at the hospital. (CHUCKLES)
That's unbelievable.
One of the many fascinating
mysteries of the human body.
(SIGHS)
You mentioned...
your daughter's experience
on the other side was difficult.
Yeah.
I've heard many near death
stories over the years.
And in the less peaceful ones,
what comes up, time and again,
if someone dies with unresolved
issues, the journey becomes...
more challenging.
CLAIRE: And the journey...
What is that? Where do they go?
There's a place beyond this one.
At least according to those
who've been there and back.
Is there anything...
your daughter has been through
that she may have internalized?
It is usually some sort
of emotional trauma
that's been repressed.
A loss.
A trespass. Something...
Something difficult to discuss.
Claire?
Can you tell me...
about this place?
This place they go,
what it's like?
There is no simple answer.
CLAIRE: Is it...
loving and peaceful?
For some.
What are you
looking for, Claire?
(SIGHS)
But where are you going? Stop!
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
CLAIRE: What?
How many times have I told you?
(ROBIN WAILS)
LUCA: (FAINTLY)
What are you doing Claire?
(ROBIN SOBS)
LUCA: Claire, please...
Claire, stop!
(IN DEEP VOICE) Claire!
Claire, where are you going?
I did everything
to make this family happen.
There's no way you deserve us.
LUCA: Claire!
♪ Jingle Bells! Jingle Bells! ♪
ROBIN: ♪ Jingle all the way! ♪
♪ Oh, what fun
It is to ride... ♪
LUCA: (ECHOING)
♪ All the way. Hey! ♪
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CRIES)
(HORN HONKS)
(SCREAMS)
A mourner walked among
The children
(MUSIC FADES)
LUCA: (IN ITALIAN)
Ah!
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
LUCA:
(ROBIN LAUGHS)
ROBIN:
LUCA:
(SPEAKS ITALIAN) Ciao.
(ROBIN BABBLING)
(TV CLICKS OFF)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(MUSIC FADES)
(PANTS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHIMPERS)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
VIV: Jesus Christ, Claire!
(MUSIC FADES)
(COUGHS)
You were drowning six inches
from the edge of the pool?
What the hell is going on?
She was trying to kill me.
Who?
Nobody's here, Claire.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
VIV: Nobody's here.
(PHONE RINGING)
I think you need
to talk to someone.
(PHONE CONTINUES RINGING)
CLAIRE: I can't find my keys.
VIV: Are you going
to pick that up? (SIGHS)
Luca, it's Viv.
Yes, Claire is here with me.
But...
What?
Since when?
Robin's gone missing.
Luca?
Claire, let me drive with you.
I don't think
you should be alone.
Claire, wait!
Maybe you should've given a shit
and learned sign language.
LUCA:
Look, I'm doing my best, okay?
She was scaring Marco.
I stopped her and she ran off.
But you're right.
She isn't herself.
No. No, she's not.
I don't know who she is.
(RADIO CRACKLES)
RADIO ANNOUNCER: (IN ITALIAN)
Luca. Luca!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)
Luca!
RADIO ANNOUNCER:
(WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER RADIO)
ROBIN: (IN ENGLISH) Mamma,
are we going to hell?
(HORN HONKS)
(SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
CLAIRE: I don't know
what's happening anymore.
Do you believe in hell?
I'm not a religious man.
I don't see it in terms
of heaven and hell.
But I do believe we make choices
in life that might...
follow us.
But you've... you've talked
about unresolved issues.
And...
if love can become tangible
in the afterlife,
could that be true
for other emotions?
I'm not sure I understand.
CLAIRE: Well, I'm wondering
if that can happen
for other emotions, like guilt.
Because...
Can guilt...
You know, if you've...
Can your past sins
become demons?
I don't believe in sins
and demons.
But...
But guilt...
I've known it to take on a...
life of its own.
My daughter brought someone...
back with her.
From the other side.
(GIGGLES)
I think I know who it is.
LUCA: Beautiful Robin!
It's not mine! I'm Rose!
LUCA: Oh! You're Rose!
Oh, my God! I made a mistake!
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, this is for Robin!
(ROSE GIGGLES)
LUCA: Robins for Robin!
And roses for Rose!
ROBIN: Papa!
CLAIRE: They were in vitro.
Seven years of miscarriages
and false starts.
We lost all our savings and...
ended up moving back
to Luca's...
childhood home to take care
of his father here in Italy.
Luca didn't want to...
keep trying to get pregnant,
but I did, I needed it, I...
I needed those girls,
I needed that.
Our marriage needed it.
I really hoped that...
you know, that would fix
all the problems.
But where are you going
in the middle of the night
with the girls?
(DRAMATIC MUSICAL STING)
They were five when it happened.
The girls.
And Robin's twin?
Rose.
She died.
The doctors all said Robin...
was dealing with the trauma
of losing her twin
in her way, you know.
So, talking,
or not talking, is...
a way to control something.
So we moved to the city,
we moved to Rome.
We buried everything
about our life.
Robin found her voice
through the piano.
I found...
nothing, really.
Everybody kept saying,
"You have to move on," but...
I don't know how to do that.
How do you do that?
And...
And so I just started
to fake it.
Because it just makes it
more comfortable for everybody.
You have to make it
more comfortable,
so people don't feel awkward
over cocktails.
So, that's what I do. I fake it.
And we never speak of Rose.
Ever.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(HUMMING)
♪ ...what she could
See, see, see... ♪
♪ But all that she could
♪ Was the bottom
Of the deep blue sea, sea, sea ♪
(ROSE CRIES)
Please, stop, Rose! Please!
Please, stop!
(WAILS) I want Papa!
I don't want you!
(HORN HONKS)
(SCREAMS)
(ROSE CRIES)
I need to get your seat belt.
Give me your arm, please.
Oh! Okay, come on.
(ROSE CRIES)
Come to Mommy!
ROSE: Mom! Mom!
Come on, Rosie! Rosie,
we gotta get you out of here!
Please, stop!
Rosie! Rosie! Rosie!
I got this!
(CRIES)
CLAIRE: Rose! Please stop it!
Oh, my God!
Rosie! Come on!
(ROSE CRYING)
(CLAIRE YELLS)
Rosie! Please, Rose!
(YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
(CRIES)
You need to pull your arms out!
Pull your arms out!
Please, pull your arms out!
(MUSIC FADES)
(SOFTLY) I couldn't save her.
(SOBS)
I'm so sorry.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
I've never told Luca.
I told him I...
I couldn't remember the details.
But of course
I remember everything.
It's with me all the time.
The last words I said...
to my daughter...
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIREN WAILING)
I've done so much damage
to my girls.
(PHONE CHIMES)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
DR. ROMANO: Claire...
PARAMEDIC: (IN ITALIAN)
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
DR. STANCIK:
(MUSIC FADES)
(IN ENGLISH) No brain activity.
She's not in there anymore.
You have a difficult decision
to make. I'm sorry.
(LUCA SIGHS)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(WATER RUNNING)
OPERATOR: (IN ITALIAN)
OPERATOR:
(CLAIRE WHIMPERS)
(WHIMPERS)
(IN ENGLISH) ♪ A sailor went
Down to sea, sea, sea ♪
♪ To see what she could
See, see, see ♪
♪ But all that she could
♪ Was the deep blue
Sea, sea, sea ♪
(SIGHS)
(CLICKS TONGUE)
(PHONE DIALING)
CLAIRE: (IN ITALIAN)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(IN ENGLISH) I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
Stop it, Rose!
(HORN HONKS)
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
(BREATHES HEAVILY, GURGLES)
(PARAMEDIC SPEAKS ITALIAN)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(SIREN WAILING)
(WATER RIPPLING)
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
(GURGLES)
(MUFFLED SCREAM)
(MUSIC FADES)
(ROSE HUMMING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
CLAIRE: Forgive me.
(GASPS)
PARAMEDIC 1: (IN ITALIAN)
PARAMEDIC 2:
PARAMEDIC 1:
DR. ROMANO: Claire.
Claire!
(SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES)
PARAMEDIC 1:
PARAMEDIC 2:
(IN ENGLISH) Claire!
Claire, come back.
PARAMEDIC 1: (IN ITALIAN)
PARAMEDIC 1: (FAINTLY)
(IN ENGLISH) Claire,
can you hear me?
PARAMEDIC 2: (IN ITALIAN)
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
NURSE:
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
ROBIN: (IN ENGLISH) Ready!
Beautiful!
(ROBIN CHUCKLES)
Okay.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDS)
(APPLAUSE FADES)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)