Downloaded from
YTS.MX
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE THEY EVEN
ASKED ME?
>> NO, I DON'T DO STAND-UP.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
I GUESS THEY THINK I'M A
NATURAL, RIGHT?
LISTEN TO THIS JOKE: A BUFFALO
WALKS INTO A MEAT FACTORY AND
HE'S DENIED BECAUSE HE DOESN'T
HAVE ANY WINGS.
I MEAN, THAT'S GOLD, RIGHT?
THAT'S GOLD.
>> WE'RE HERE.
>> I GOTTA GO.
>> MY FIRST STAND-UP SPECIAL.
ACTUALLY, IT'S MY FIRST STAND-UP
EVER.
TIME TO GET IN THE ZONE.
♪ ♪
>> YEAH!
>> WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
>> YOUR NAME?
>> TONY HALE, HEADLINER FOR THE
NIGHT?
>> YOU'RE NOT ON MY LIST.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S GOOD.
THIS IS ONE OF THE BITS THEY AIR
BEFORE THE SPECIAL JUST TO GET
THE COMIC JUICES FLOWING.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
I'M GOING TO PLAY ALONG.
I'M NOT ON THE LIST?
THAT'S WEIRD.
THAT'S WE'RE.
KEN JEONG AND SOFIA VERGARA
OPENING FOR ME.
I'M HONORED.
>> TONY?
>> KATIE COURIC... YOU'RE A
COMEDIAN.
YOUR MATERIAL'S A LITTLE DARK,
DON'T YOU THINK?
>> I AM USUALLY TALKING ABOUT
THE NEWS.
>> I WANT TO TRY NEW STUFF AND
I'M NERVOUS ABOUT DOING IT IN
FRONT OF SUCH A HUGE AUDIENCE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THIS?
"HEY [BLEEP]!
WHAT THE [BLEEP] IS UP?
>> UH, TONY, IT'S NOT--
>> [BLEEP]
REESE WITHERSPOON IS DOING A
SET, TOO?
>> TONY, THIS IS "STAND UP TO
CANCER," AND THERE'S NO LIVE
AUDIENCE BECAUSE OF COVID.
>> YES, YES, I KNEW THAT.
YES, AND I HAVE A SET FOR THAT.
I CAN ADJUST MY JOKES.
>> HONESTLY, CANCER IS NO JOKE.
>> OF COURSE.
>> BYE, TONY.
>> THAT'S INTERESTING, ANTHONY
ANDERSON IS ON THE LIST.
HOW HOW DID HE GET?"
PLEASE, LET ME DO MY JOKE.
THERE HAS TO BE SOMETHING I CAN
DO.
>> THERE MIGHT BE ONE THING.
>> YES, YES.
>> READ THIS.
>> YOU HAVE TO BE KIDDING ME.
>> FROM DOWNTOWN LOS ANGELES
AIRING SIMULTANEOUSLY ON MORE
THAN 60 PARTICIPATING MEDIA
PLATFORMS ACROSS THE UNITED
STATES AND CANADA, IT'S "STAND
UP TO CANCER!"
♪ ♪
>> Witherspoon: THESE LAST 18
MONTHS HAVE TAUGHT US NOT TO
TAKE A SINGLE THING FOR GRANTED.
VALUE IT ALL.
VALUE EVERY SINGLE CHAOTIC,
BEAUTIFUL, COMPLICATED MOMENT OF
OUR LIVES.
AND THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE
TONIGHT.
UNFORTUNATELY, CANCER TOUCHES US
ALL.
WE'VE ALL GOT A STORY TO SHARE.
EVERY DAY FROM EVERY CORNER OF
THIS COUNTRY, WE LOSE 1,670
PEOPLE TO CANCER.
BUT WE CAN END THIS HEARTACHE BY
SUPPORTING "STAND UP TO CANCER."
AND WHEN YOU GIVE, 100% OF YOUR
DONATIONS RECEIVED TONIGHT GO
DIRECTLY TO FUND GROUNDBREAKING
CANCER RESEARCH.
WE'RE SO GRATEFUL THAT MORE THAN
60 MEDIA PLATFORMS HAVE DONATED
THEIR TIME TONIGHT TO HELP
ADVANCE THIS RESEARCH.
SO JUST STAND UP WITH US, AND I
DO MEAN US.
WE'RE CONNECTED AND SCATTERED
ALL OVER THE WORLD, BUT
TOGETHER IN SPIRIT AND COMMITTED
TO TURN EVERY CANCER
PATIENT INTO A LONG-TERM
SURVIVOR.
>> WE'RE ALL HERE TONIGHT FOR A
REASON TO "STAND UP TO CANCER."
SOME OF US ARE MISSING A LOVED
SOME OF US ARE HERE BECAUSE YEAR
MISSING A LOVED ONE DEARLY.
SOME OF US ARE HERE HOPING FOR
NEW ADVANCES AND TREATMENT AND
RESEARCH.
SOME OF US ARE STANDING UP FOR
SCIENCE.
I AM HERE TO REMIND YOU TO GET
SCREENED.
EVERY YEAR, I GET MY PAP SMEAR,
MY MOLES CHECKED, MY MAMMOGRAM.
I EVEN FROM TIME TO TIME GET A
COLONOSCOPY.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT THE
TESTS THAT ARE RIGHT TO YOU.
PLEASE DONATE.
WE ARE STANDING BY READY TO HEAR
YOUR RELATIONSHIP FOR STANDING
UP TO CANCER.
>> WE'RE HERE TO HONOR
TONIGHTY'S STEP-FATHER, MICHAEL.
IT'S NEVER BEEN EASIER TO GIVE
FOR SOMEONE YOU LOVE.
>> CALL THE NUMBER ON THE
SCREEN, VISIT THE WEBSITE OR USE
THE Q.R. CODE.
AFTER YOU DONATE, YOU'LL RECEIVE
A LINK ON YOUR DONATION RECEIPT
WITH THE CHANCE TO VIDEO CHAT
WITH ONE OF US.
>> I'M HERE TO "STAND UP TO
CANCER," TOO, BECAUSE IT'S TIME
TO STOP LOSING LOVED ONES TO
THIS DISEASE.
PLEASE DONATE AS MUCH AS YOU CAN
AND LET'S DO THIS.
LET'S STAND UP TOGETHER.
>> 100% OF YOUR DONATIONS
RECEIVED TONIGHT WILL SUPPORT
THIS RESEARCH.
LET'S END CANCER AS WE KNOW IT
AND TURN EVERY PATIENT INTO A
LONG-TERM SURVIVOR.
THIS IS WHAT'S POSSIBLE WHEN WE
WORK TOGETHER, WHEN WE "STAND UP
TO CANCER."
>> Witherspoon: OKAY, SO HOW
DOES "STAND UP TO CANCER" WORK.
BACK IN 2007, CANCER RESEARCH
WAS SILOED, AND ALL ABOUT
COMPETITION.
BUT THEN A GROUP OF WOMEN WHO
WERE FED-UP WITH LOSING LOVED
ONES TO CANCER PULLED TOGETHER
THE BEST DOCTORS AND SCIENTISTS
TO ASK IF THERE WAS A BETTER
WAY.
AND THERE WAS, BASED ON
COLLABORATION, NOT COMPETITION.
SO THEY CREATED A DREAM TEAM
MODEL COMBINING THE BEST DOCTORS
AND RESEARCHERS, SO THEY WOULD
SHARE DATA AND DISCOVERIES,
GOING AFTER ALL KINDS OF CANCERS
IN NEW WAYS.
TODAY, THERE ARE 120 DIFFERENT
RESEARCH TEAMS SUPPORTING
MORE THAN 2,000 SCIENTISTS AND
DOCTORS.
BUT WE NEED TO DO MORE TO HELP
OUR UNSTOPPABLE DOCTORS LIKE THE
ONE YOU'RE ABOUT TO MEET.
SO PLEASE DONATE NOW WHILE YOU
HEAR HER INCREDIBLE STORY.
♪ ♪
>> HI, MY NAME IS DR. RAYNE
ROUCE
I'M A PEDIATRIC ONCOLOGIST, BUT
I'M ALSO A PHYSICIAN SCIENTIST.
I THINK MOST PEOPLE HAVE SOME
SORT OF MORNING ROUTINE.
I CHANNEL MY INNER LEBRON.
I CHANNEL MY JIGGA QUEEN BEY.
I REALLY WANT TO COME INTO EVERY
DAY FEELING LIKE THERE WILL BE
NO BARRIER TO STOP ME IN
ACHIEVING WHAT I NEED TO FOR
MY PATIENTS AND THEIR FAMILIES.
♪ OUTSIDE, INSIDE
WE DON'T STOP
♪ GLOBAL WORLDWIDE
WE DON'T STOP ♪
I'M UNAPOLOGETICALLY ME EVERY
SINGLE DAY.
I MAY NOT LOOK OR ACT LIKE THE
CLASSIC SCIENTIST THAT PEOPLE
THINK OF, BUT WE'RE CHANGING THE
WAY.
THIS IS THE NEW FACE.
[ SCREAMS EXCITEDLY]
I TYPICALLY START MY DAY WITH
SEEING PATIENTS.
MY PATIENTS ARE EVERYTHING TO
ME.
THEY GIVE ME ALL THE STRENGTH TO
CARRY ON EVERY SINGLE DAY.
SO, I JUST GOT TO SEE ONE OF MY
PATIENTS WHOSE BIRTHDAY IT WAS.
WE GOT TO CELEBRATE, CAUSE YOU
GOT TO BE READY FOR COLLEGE.
LYMPHOMA DOES NOT STOP COLLEGE.
SO, EVERY DAY'S A LITTLE
DIFFERENT.
I LOVE NOTHING MORE THAN TO GIVE
MY PATIENTS GOOD NEWS.
HOPEFULLY YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO
GET CHEMOTHERAPY AGAIN.
WE ARE SPEAKING IT INTO
EXISTENCE.
>> WE CAN NOT STOP SMILING.
WE'RE SO GRATEFUL.
>> COFFEE TIME.
THERE CERTAINLY ARE SOME UPS AND
DOWNS WITHIN A MORNING OF SEEING
PATIENTS.
I USUALLY GO OVER TO THE LAB AND
CHECK IN.
WE'RE ACTUALLY PREPARING THESE
CAR-T CELLS TO BE INFUSED INTO A
PATIENT. INFUSED INTO A
PA
THIS IS THE CULMINATION OF
MONTHS OF WORK.
WE ARE CREATING REAL AND
SUCCESSFUL TREATMENTS THAT ARE
LITERALLY SAVING THE LIVES OF
CHILDREN WITH CANCER.
HERE THEY ARE.
I ABSOLUTELY DO STAY IN CONTACT
WITH FAMILIES OF PATIENTS WHO
HAVE PASSED AWAY.
I MISS YOU GUYS SO MUCH, HOW ARE
YOU DOING?
>> WE'RE OKAY, WE'RE CONTINUING
TO MARCH FORWARD.
>> TAKING IT DAY-BY-DAY.
>> YES.
YUP.
THAT'S THE WAY.
>> TELL US WHO YOU ARE.
[ LAUGHS]
>> MASON PARTICIPATED IN A
CLINICAL TRIAL.
AND I REMEMBER HIM TELLING ME,
"IF THIS WILL HELP SOMEONE ELSE,
I'M DOWN."
WHEN IT APPEARED THAT THE
THERAPY WAS UNFORTUNATELY NOT
WORKING IN HIM HE TOLD ME IF MY
PARTICIPATION CAN HELP EVEN ONE
OTHER CHILD TO NOT HAVE TO GO
THROUGH WHAT I'VE GONE THROUGH
THEN IT'LL BE WORTH IT.
I THINK ABOUT MASON AND I THINK
ABOUT YOU GUYS AND I THINK ABOUT
YOUR FIGHT AND I GET
REJUVENATED.
I CONSIDER IT A GREAT HONOR TO
WALK FAMILIES THROUGH WHAT WILL
UNDOUBTEDLY BE THE WORST THING
THEY EVER HAVE TO GO THROUGH.
>> THANK YOU FOR ALL YOU DO
DR. ROUCE.
YOU'RE UNSTOPPABLE.
WE WERE ALWAYS BLOWN AWAY BY
THAT.
>> I REMEMBER EVERY SINGLE LOSS
THAT I'VE HAD.
I USE THAT TO NOT TAKE "“NO"” FOR
AN ANSWER WHEN IT COMES TO
TREATING CHILDHOOD CANCER.
TODAY'S BEEN A PRETTY HECTIC DAY
AS PER USUAL.
MY JOB IS CHALLENGING, BUT I'M
NOT UNACCUSTOMED TO A STRUGGLE.
I HAVE SO MANY STRONG BLACK
WOMEN BEHIND ME WHETHER I KNOW
THEM OR NOT WHO ARE LIFTING ME
UP EVERY SINGLE DAY TELLING ME
YOU HAVE TO KEEP PUSHING
FORWARD.
SO, THAT'S WHAT I DO.
WE WILL NEVER GIVE UP THE FIGHT.
BUT WE NEED YOUR HELP.
PLEASE DONATE AND HELP ME AND
THE COUNTLESS OTHER DOCTORS,
SCIENTISTS AND RESEARCHERS WHO
ARE FIGHTING EVERY DAY FOR A
WORLD WHERE KIDS DON'T EVER HAVE
TO DEAL WITH CANCER AGAIN.
>> Witherspoon: THERE ARE TOO
MANY MOMS LIKE MASON'S OUT THERE
MISSING THEIR CHILD.
PLEASE SUPPORT ALL THE AMAZING
"STAND UP TO CANCER" DOCTORS AND
SCIENTISTS AS THEY WORK TO SAVE
LIVES.
CALL OR GO TO THE WEBSITE ON
YOUR SCREEN AND GIVE.
AND THEN SHARE YOUR STORY WITH
WE WANT TO HEAR FROM YOU.
US AND FOLLOW US @SU2C ON
INSTAGRAM, FACEBOOK, TWITTER,
TIKTOK, AND YOUTUBE.
>> I'M CODY SUMMERS, FLIGHT
ATTENDANT FOR AMERICAN AIRLINES
AND A BREAST CANCER SURVIVOR.
AT AMERICAN AIRLINES OUR
PURPOSE IS TO CARE FOR PEOPLE ON
LIFE'S JOURNEY, A MISSION
THAT EXTENDS BEYOND THE AIRLINE
AND INTO THE COMMUNITIES WE
SERVE.
THAT'S WHY WE ARE PROUD TO JOIN
WITH STA
WITH "STAND UP TO CANCER" IN
THEIR EFFORT TO TURN EVERY
CANCER PATIENT INTO A LONG-TERM
SURVIVOR LIKE ME.
WHEN YOU DONATE $25 OR MORE YOU
CAN RECEIVE 25 AMERICAN AIRLINES
AADVANTAGE MILES FOR EVERY
DOLLAR YOU GIVE TO "STAND UP TO
CANCER" IN THE UNITED STATES.
LEARN MORE BY GOING TO THE
WEBSITE ON YOUR SCREEN.
AND WEN YOU USE YOUR MASTERCARD
TO DONATE FOR MILES, AMERICAN
AIRLINES, WITH SUPPORT FROM
MASTERCARD, WILL MATCH WHAT
YOU GIVE DOLLAR FOR DOLLAR, UP
TO ONE MILLION DOLLARS.
HOW AMAZING IS THAT?
SO, PLEASE GIVE NOW AND SUPPORT
THIS LIFE-SAVING SCIENCE.
[ LAUGHS]
>> YOU WANT ME TO LOOK AT THE,
LIKE, RECTANGULAR BOX?
>> SO, YOU WANT VERY SHORT
ANSWERS?
>> COME ON.
[ LAUGHS]
>> YOU WANT ME TO DO IT AGAIN?
>> REPEAT THE QUESTION.
[ LAUGHS]
>> THIS IS NOT MY FORTE.
[ CLAPPING]
>> MY NAME IS JOHN DAVID
CARPTEN.
>> DR. KIMBERLY STEGMAIER
>> DR. EDITH PEREZ
>> I'M ANDREW CHAN.
>> DR. BRIAN WOLPIN
>> I'M A MEDICAL ONCOLOGIST.
>> AND I FOCUS ON CANCER
PREVENTION.
>> PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS ASKING ME--
>> WHY?
WHY?
>> WHY DO I DO THIS WORK?
>> TWO WORDS COME TO MIND FOR
ME.
ONE IS RESPONSIBILITY.
>> MOSTLY I'M EXCITED TO HELP
PEOPLE.
>> THE OTHER IS PURPOSE.
>> EVERY DAY I THINK OF THE
FACES OF PATIENTS WHEN I SEE
THEIR SMILES.
THE SMILES FROM THEIR RELATIVES,
WHEN I TELL THEM THAT NEW
TREATMENTS ARE HELPING THEIR
LIVES.
>> I'VE SEEN TOO MANY PEOPLE'S
LIVES CUT SHORT BY CANCER.
>> I LOST MY FAVORITE FAMILY
MEMBER TO CANCER.
>> THERE WAS A CHILD THAT, YOU
KNOW, I TOOK CARE OF AND ADORED
AND SHE SAID TO ME, "DR. KIM,"
YOU KNOW, "WILL YOU REMEMBER ME
FOREVER?"
>> THEY DO THIS SO THAT THE NEXT
GENERATION OF PEOPLE DON'T HAVE
TO HAVE THE SAME FIGHT AGAINST
CANCER THAT WE DO.
>> SORRY.
IT'S BEEN A HARD YEAR.
>> WHY AM I...
>> WHY AM I EXCITED ABOUT CANCER
RESEARCH TODAY?
>> IT'S JUST INCREDIBLE TO SEE
THINGS MOVE FROM THE LAB TO
HELPING PATIENTS IN THE REAL
WORLD.
>> THAT'S THE BEST FEELING IN
THE WORLD.
>> IT'S JUST SO INSPIRING TO DO
RESEARCH THAT IMPACTS HUMAN
LIVES.
>> CANCER RESEARCH SAVES LIVES.
>> WHY AM I PARTICIPATING
WITH...
>> STAND UP TO...
>> CANCER?
>> IT'S BECAUSE WE CAN'T FIGHT
CANCER ALONE.
>> "STAND UP TO CANCER" HAS BEEN
A CRITICAL PARTNER IN ADVANCING
RESEARCH FOR CANCER.
>> THE MESSAGE FOR TODAY NOW IS
HOPE.
>> SO, PLEASE, HELP US FIGHT IN
THIS BATTLE AGAINST CANCER.
>> NOW THAT WE'VE TOLD YOU WHY
WE DO WHAT WE DO.
>> IT'S TIME...
>> FOR US TO FIND OUT...
>> YOUR WHY.
>> WHY ARE YOU WATCHING?
>> WHY DO YOU THINK YOUR
CONTRIBUTION MIGHT BE NEEDED?
>> WHY HAVEN'T YOU DONATED YET?
>> AND IF YOU HAVE DONATED...
>> WHY DON'T YOU DONATE AGAIN?
[ LAUGHS]
>> IS THAT A WRAP?
>> YES!
>> ALL SET?
>> WE DID IT. WRAP?
>> THAT WAS LIKE THE HARDEST
THING SOMEONE'S ASKED ME TO DO.
>> HOPEFULLY I KNOW MY WAY BACK
OUT OF THIS PLACE
>> I LOVE THOSE DOCTORS AND
SCIENTISTS.
IN ADDITION TO DONATING TO
"STAND UP TO CANCER," THERE ARE
OTHER WAYS FOR YOU TO GIVE AND
HELP SUPPORT OUR INCREDIBLE
SCIENTISTS.
IF YOU'RE A CANCER PATIENT OR A
SURVIVOR, YOU CAN JOIN A
RESEARCH INITIATIVE CALLED
"COUNT ME IN" AND SHARE YOUR
MEDICAL AND CLINICAL
INFORMATION, WHICH MAY HOLD
PRECIOUS CLUES TO UNLOCK NEW
DISCOVERIES.
THOUSANDS OF PATIENTS HAVE
ALREADY JOINED COUNT ME IN TO
CHANGE THE FUTURE OF CANCER
RESEARCH.
YOU CAN, TOO, BY VISITING THE
WEBSITE ON YOUR SCREEN AND
JOINING COUNT ME IN.
LET'S BUILD A WORLD WHERE CANCER
IS NO MORE.
EVERYONE'S THINKING ABOUT
SOMEONE THEY MISS AND CHERISH
TONIGHT.
I KNOW I AM.
SO, LET'S KEEP STANDING UP
TOGETHER FOR THEM AND GIVE
WHAT YOU CAN.
>> TONIGHT, I'M HERE TO HONOR MY
SISTER, JAIME, WHO PASSED AWAY
AS A TEENAGER FROM
RETINOBLASTOMA, A RARE FORM OF
EYE CANCER.
JAIME MIGHT HAVE PASSED AWAY
OVER 20 YEARS AGO, BUT TODAY I'M
SHARING MY STORY BECAUSE I KNOW
THAT TOGETHER, OUR SUPPORT OF
"STAND UP TO CANCER" MIGHT HELP
SAVE YOUNG GIRLS LIKE MY SISTER,
AND MILLIONS MORE.
MUSIC HAS ALWAYS HAD THE POWER
TO INSPIRE CHANGE, AND TONIGHT I
WANT TO CELEBRATE AN ARTIST WHO
USED HER PLATFORM TO FIGHT FOR
SOCIAL JUSTICE AND EQUAL RIGHTS,
MS. NINA SIMONE.
♪ ♪
♪ I WISH I KNEW HOW
IT WOULD FEEL TO BE FREE
♪ I WISH I COULD BREAK
ALL THE CHAINS HOLDIN' ME
♪ I WISH I COULD SAY
ALL THE THINGS THAT I COULD SAY
♪ SAY 'EM LOUD, SAY 'EM CLEAR
FOR THE WHOLE ROUND WORLD
♪ TO HEAR
I WISH I COULD SHARE
♪ ALL THE LOVE
THAT'S IN MY HEART
♪ I WISH I COULD GIVE
ALL THEM CHAINS
♪ THAT BIND US APART
I WISH YOU COULD KNOW
♪ WHAT IT MEANS TO BE ME
THEN YOU'D SEE, YOU'D AGREE
♪ EVERYBODY SHOULD BE FREE
I WISH I COULD GIVE
♪ ALL I'M LONGIN' TO GIVE
I WISH I COULD LIVE
♪ HOW I'M LONGING TO LIVE
I WISH I COULD DO
♪ ALL I WANTED TO DO
THOUGH I'M WAY OVERDUE
♪ I'D BE STARTING ANEW
WELL, I WISH I COULD BE
♪ LIKE A BIRD IN THE SKY
HOW SWEET IT WOULD BE
♪ TO FIND THAT I COULD FLY
I'D SOAR TO THE SUN
♪ AND LOOK DOWN AT THE SEA, THEN
THEN I'D KNOW
♪ YEAH 'CAUSE I'D KNOW
I'D KNOW HOW IT FEELS
♪ AND THEN I'D SING 'CAUSE
I'D KNOW, YEAH
♪ I'D KNOW HOW IT FEELS
TO BE FREE
♪ HOW IT FEELS
OHH-OH
♪ THEN I'D KNOW
HOW IT WOULD FEEL
♪ NOT TO BE AFRAID
OF ANYTHING
♪ OF ANYONE
OF ANY-ANYTHING I'D KNOW
♪ HOW IT FEELS
TO BE FREE ♪
♪ ♪
>> YOUR DONATIONS CAN LEAD
DIRECTLY TO CANCER TREATMENTS
THAT
>> CAN LEAD DIRECTLY TO CANCER
TREATMENTS THAT ARE GIVING
FAMILIES MORE OPTIONS AND HOPE.
SO, PLEASE, DONATE NOW.
>> Anderson: YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
NINA SIMONE SANG MORE THAN 60
YEARS AGO?
A CIVIL RIGHTS SONG SHE WROTE
THAT HAD THE LYRIC, "“YOU DON'T
HAVE TO LIVE NEXT TO ME, JUST
GIVE ME MY EQUALITY."”
WHAT A YEAR WE'VE HAD GOING
AFTER THIS THOUGHT.
AND IT DOES GIVE ME SOME HOPE
THAT WE'RE ALL STARTING TO
HAVE "“A TALK"” TOGETHER.
WHEN IT COMES TO HEALTHCARE AND
CANCER RESEARCH EQUALITY, LOOK,
I'M JUST A KID FROM COMPTON.
NO ONE CAME AROUND AND TALKED TO
US ABOUT TAKING CARE OF OUR
HEALTH.
NO ONE ASKED MY FAMILY TO GET
SCREENED FOR COLORECTAL,
LUNG, BREAST, PROSTATE, OR SKIN,
ANY KIND OF CANCER.
I LOST MY BIOLOGICAL FATHER AND
THREE OF HIS SIBLINGS TO CANCER
IN THE SPAN OF 18 MONTHS OF ONE
ANOTHER.
WE GO TO DOCTORS WHEN WE'RE
SICK, WHEN IT'S TOO LATE.
I STAND HERE TONIGHT BECAUSE
"STAND UP TO CANCER" IS
DETERMINED TO CHANGE THESE
DISPARITIES.
A CRITICAL PIECE TO ENSURING WE
HAVE MORE EQUALITY IN THIS
COUNTRY INVOLVES ADDRESSING
HEALTH DISPARITIES HEAD ON.
THAT'S THE REASON "STAND UP TO
CANCER," WITH HELP FROM A
NUMBER OF DONORS, LAUNCHED ITS
HEALTH EQUITY INITIATIVE, TO
WORK TOWARD BETTER AND MORE
EQUAL ACCESS TO CANCER CARE
FOR ALL CANCER PATIENTS.
WE NEED TO TRULY DISRUPT WHAT'S
GOING ON, ESPECIALLY WITH
CLINICAL TRIALS.
HERE'S SOMETHING I JUST LEARNED
AND YOU OUGHT TO KNOW TOO.
"STAND UP TO CANCER" IS WORKING
WITH GENENTECH TO MAKE THIS
HAPPEN.
THIS IS GENENTECH'S MISSION:
THEY TAKE INTENTIONAL ACTION TO
HELP BUILD A WORLD WHERE
EVERYONE HAS ACCESS TO QUALITY
HEALTHCARE.
THEY'RE COMMITTED TO A FUTURE OF
SCIENCE THAT'S MORE DIVERSE,
INCLUSIVE, AND EQUITABLE.
AND THEY WANT TO ADDRESS HEALTH
INEQUITY FOR ALL PATIENTS FACING
SERIOUS AND LIFE-THREATENING
DISEASES.
THIS IS GREAT.
WE ALL HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER.
AND THROUGH A TRANSFORMATIONAL
GRANT BY GENENTECH, STAND UP TO
CANCER LAUNCHED A HEALTH EQUITY
BREAKTHROUGH TEAM CALLED THE
DISRUPT TEAM.
IT WILL INCREASE DIVERSE
PARTICIPATION IN CLINICAL TRIALS
AND MAKE THE COMMUNITY THE
NEWEST DREAM TEAM MEMBER,
INVOLVING THEM IN CANCER
RESEARCH AT THE BEGINNING.
CONTINUE THE SUPPORT NEEDED TO
PUSH THESE EFFORTS FORWARD AND
CALL THE NUMBER ON THE SCREEN TO
GIVE NOW.
>> WHETHER YOU'VE SURVIVED
CANCER, ARE GOING THROUGH
TREATMENT, OR HAVE A LOVED ONE
OR GOOD FRIEND WHO'S
FACED CANCER, THE REALITY IS IT
TOUCHES US ALL.
THE GROUNDBREAKING RESEARCH
>> PLEASE SUPPORT THIS AMAZING
WORK.
>> I'M HERE TO STAND UP TO
CANCER, TOO.
IT SEEMS EVERY COUPLE OF YEARS,
I HAVE A FAMILY MEMBER DIAGNOSED
WITH CANCER.
WE'VE ALL GOT A STORY, AND WE'RE
HERE TO HEAR YOURS TONIGHT.
>> TONIGHT, I'M STANDING UP FOR
ALL THE CANCER PATIENTS WHO ARE
PART OF THE L.G.B.T.Q.+
COMMUNITY.
BE BRAVE, BE STRONG, AND KNOW
THAT WE ARE CHEERING YOU ON.
WE NEED TO SUPPORT THIS
LIFE-SAVING RESEARCH SO EACH AND
EVERY ONE OF YOU CAN BECOME A
LONG-TERM SURVIVOR.
>> WHEN YOU DONATE TONIGHT,
YOU'LL
YOU'LL RECEIVE A LINK ON YOUR
DONATION RECEIPT WITH THE CHANCE
TO VIDEO CHAT WITH ONE OF
US.
YOU CAN CALL THE NUMBER ON THE
SCREEN, GO TO THE WEBSITE, OR
TAKE YOUR PHONE AND USE THE Q.R.
CODE BELOW.
>> SO PLEASE GIVE WHAT YOU CAN.
WE'VE ALL GOT SOMEONE WE'RE
STANDING UP FOR TONIGHT.
MY BEST FRIEND LOST HIS SON TO
CANCER.
AND I LOST MY AUNT TO CANCER.
SO, LET'S STAND UP TOGETHER AND
FIND A WAY TO SUPPORT THIS
RESEARCH AND SAVE LIVES
>> I'M STANDING UP TONIGHT FOR
MY UNCLE RAUÚL.
WE LOVED HIM.
HE HUNG THE MOON.
HE MADE OUR FAMILY DINNERS AND
PARTIES THE BEST IN THE WORLD.
PLEASE GIVE WHAT YOU CAN TO THE
LIFESAVING WORK OF "STAND UP TO
CANCER."
>> 100% OF YOUR DONATIONS
RECEIVED WILL GO TO THIS
INCREDIBLE RESEARCH.
WE'RE STANDING BY TO VIDEO CHAT
IF YOU DONATE NOW.
LET'S DO THIS.
LET'S END CANCER AS WE KNOW IT.
>> Anderson: HEY, EVERYONE.
SO, I DREW THIS MAP OF THE
UNITED STATES.
HERE'S WHY: YOUR ZIP CODE IN THE
U.S. SOMETIMES HAS EVERYTHING TO
DO WITH WHETHER YOU LIVE OR DIE
FROM CANCER.
"STAND UP TO CANCER" WANTS TO
CHANGE THAT.
LOOK AT THESE THREE ZONES.
YOU HAVE ONE IN LOS ANGELES,
ANOTHER IN BOSTON AND ANOTHER IN
THE GREAT PLAINS TRIBAL
COMMUNITIES IN SOUTH DAKOTA.
SOME AREAS IN THESE ZONES HAVE
LOW SCREENING RATES AND HIGH
MORTALITY RATES FOR COLORECTAL
CANCER- ESPECIALLY FOR PEOPLE
OF COLOR.
TONIGHT, I'M HONORED TO ANNOUNCE
THAT "STAND UP TO CANCER" HAS
CREATED THE CARES DREAM TEAM.
IT'S A GROUNDBREAKING INITIATIVE
STARTING IN THOSE THREE
UNDERSERVED ZONES.
THEY'LL OFFER FREE COLORECTAL
SCREENINGS AND COMMUNITY
EDUCATION.
THEY'RE GOING TO HELP PREVENT
THIS CANCER OR CATCH IT
EARLIER WHEN TREATMENTS ARE
OFTEN MOST EFFECTIVE.
AND EVENTUALLY, "STAND UP TO
CANCER" WILL CREATE SIMILAR
ZONES
FOR OTHER CANCERS IN ZIP CODES
ALL ACROSS THE COUNTRY, SO
THE MAP WILL LOOK LIKE THIS.
ONE UNITED ZONE, GOING AFTER
CANCER, BRINGING EVERYBODY
IN EQUALLY.
GUESS WHO SUPPORTS THIS NEW
WORK?
EXACT SCIENCES.
THEY'VE JOINED WITH STAND UP TO
CANCER TO LAUNCH THESE ZONES,
WORKING TO PROVIDE COLORECTAL
CANCER SCREENINGS AND DIAGNOSTIC
TESTS EARLIER, ENABLING PATIENTS
AND PROVIDERS TO TAKE ACTION
SOONER AND SAVE LIVES.
THEY'RE USING SCIENCE AND
TECHNOLOGY TO FIGHT CANCER.
GUESS WHO ELSE IS STANDING UP?
PROVIDENCE AND PROVIDENCE SAINT
JOHN'S HEALTH CENTER IN LOS
ANGELES.
THEY'RE ALSO SUPPORTING "STAND
UP TO CANCER" ZONES TO GET
SCREENING RATES UP, INCREASE
HEALTHCARE EQUITY, AND PREVENT
CANCER OR CATCH IT EARLIER.
THAT MEANS MORE PEOPLE HAVE
BETTER ACCESS TO LIFESAVING
TREATMENTS.
THANKS TO THEIR SUPPORT AND
YOURS, THESE ZONES WILL TURN
THE PROMISE OF EQUITY INTO MORE
CANCER SCREENINGS AND
LONG-TERM SURVIVORS.
YOU CAN BE PART OF THIS.
PICK UP THE PHONE.
GO TO THE WEBSITE ON YOUR SCREEN
AND GIVE NOW.
AND DON'T FORGET: MY FRIENDS ARE
WAITING TO VIDEO CHAT WITH YOU
WHEN YOU DONATE NOW.
♪ ♪
>> I'M YAPHET SMITH.
>> I'M KELLY SMITH.
>> AND WE WERE HIGH SCHOOL
FRIENDS, AND TEENAGE
SWEETHEARTS, AND WE MET
SOPHOMORE YEAR IN '98.
AND THE TEACHER ASKED IF THERE
WAS A SEAT AVAILABLE.
AND I SAID THERE'S ONE RIGHT
HERE BY ME.
AND KELLY CAME AND SAT BY ME.
>> AND I LIKED HIM THE MOMENT I
MET HIM.
[ LAUGHS]
I DID.
>> SINCE THEN IT'S BEEN 32
YEARS.
>> 32, 31, 32.
>> WE WENT TO OUR 30th HIGH
SCHOOL REUNION.
IT WAS A GREAT NIGHT.
AND THEN, A FEW DAYS LATER,
YOU'RE IN THE EMERGENCY ROOM.
>> EVERYTHING CHANGED.
>> THE DOCTOR CAME INTO THE
ROOM, ASKED OUR CHILD TO LEAVE
THE ROOM.
AND THEN HEART KIND OF STOPS AT
A MOMENT LIKE THAT.
AND THAT'S WHEN WE FIRST HEARD
THE WORD "CANCER."
KELLY GOT DIAGNOSED WITH
MYELOMA.
>> YOU'VE GOT A CANCER WITH NO
CURE.
UM... THAT'S REALLY HARD.
I HAD ALL KINDS OF THOUGHTS GO
THROUGH MY HEAD, YOU KNOW, HOW
MUCH TIME DO I HAVE LEFT WITH MY
CHILD, WITH YOU?
>> WE REALLY ARE STRONGER
TOGETHER IN THE FIGHT AGAINST
CANCER.
I JUST KNEW I COULDN'T COLLAPSE.
YOU KNOW, FOR OUR CHILD, FOR
YOU, AND SO, I DID RESEARCH.
THROUGH THAT PROCESS WE REALIZED
THAT WE NEEDED TO GET TO A
MYELOMA SPECIALIST, THAT GREATLY
INCREASES A PATIENTS CHANCES OF
SURVIVAL, REMISSION.
WITHOUT RESEARCH I WOULD NOT BE
IN REMISSION.
I TOTALLY BELIEVE THAT.
BECAUSE IT'S THE RESEARCH THAT
DRIVES NEW MEDICATIONS AND NEW
TREATMENTS THAT ARE MORE
EFFECTIVE AND THAT LEAD TO
YOU KNOW, LONGER AND DEEPER
REMISSIONS.
>> WHAT IS REALLY GOING ON WITH
MYELOMA, WITH PEOPLE THAT END UP
GETTING MYELOMA SO THAT WE CAN
PREVENT THE KIND OF PAIN THAT
KELLY FACED.
SINCE AFRICAN-AMERICANS AND
FAMILY MEMBERS OF MYELOMA
PATIENTS ARE MORE AT RISK FOR
THE DISEASE, NOW WE CAN TEST
THEM AND LOOK TO INTERCEPT THE
CANCER BEFORE IT STARTS.
♪ ♪
THE THING I'VE LEARNED ABOUT
CANCER IS THAT IT'S NOT A DEATH
SENTENCE.
AND I THINK IT HAS ALSO REVEALED
HOW CLOSE WE ARE.
>> HE JUST REALLY MADE SURE THAT
I WAS TAKEN CARE OF.
I NEVER DOUBTED THAT YOU LOVED
ME, BUT NOW I REALLY KNOW, LIKE,
BECAUSE YOU, YOU HAVE DONE SO
MUCH.
I DO THINK YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
UMM...
>> YOU COULD BE A CAREGIVER OR
YOU COULD DONATE TO A CHARITY
LIKE "STAND UP TO CANCER" TO
MAKE SURE THAT WE ALL WORK
TOGETHER TO MAKE THINGS BETTER.
>> Anderson: THERE'S JUST A LOT
OF DUST IN MY EYES RIGHT NOW.
WHAT A LOVE STORY.
SUPPORT DURING A CANCER JOURNEY
IS CRITICAL TO MAKING IT
THROUGH, BUT SOME PATIENTS FACE
MORE BARRIERS TO CARE THAN
OTHERS, WHICH IS WHY SUPPORT
FROM DONORS LIKE BRISTOL MYERS
SQUIBB IS ALSO CRITICAL.
THEY'RE COMMITTED TO ADVANCING
HEALTH EQUITY ALONG WITH STAND
UP TO CANCER.
LUNG CANCER IS THE NUMBER ONE
CANCER KILLER IN THE BLACK
COMMUNITY.
BRISTOL MYERS SQUIBB IS FUNDING
LUNG CANCER RESEARCH TEAMS, AND
EDUCATIONAL CAMPAIGNS TO ADVANCE
CARE AND INCREASE CLINICAL TRIAL
ENROLLMENT IN UNDERSERVED BLACK
AND RURAL COMMUNITIES.
BRISTOL MYERS SQUIBB IS
TRANSFORMING LIVES THROUGH
SCIENCE AND PLAYING AN IMPORTANT
PART IN WORKING TOWARDS
CORRECTING DISPARITIES AND
REDUCING DEATHS.
I'M PROUD TO STAND HERE TONIGHT,
TO KNOCK DOWN HEALTHCARE
BARRIERS, BRING MORE EQUITY, AND
REAL CHANGE TO OUR LOVED
ONES.
STAND UP, TOO.
IF THE PHONE LINES ARE BUSY,
KEEP TRYING!
GO TO THE WEBSITE NOW!
JOIN US AND SHARE YOUR STORY.
WHAT SHOWS MORE INDIFFERENCE
THAN CANCER?
IT'S NOT CONCERNED WITH WHERE
YOU LIVE, WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE,
HOW OLD, OR YOUNG YOU ARE.
IT PAYS NO MIND TO HOW MUCH
MONEY YOU MAKE AND DOESN'T CARE
WHETHER YOU'RE A MOTHER IN SOUTH
L.A., A BEST FRIEND IN BROOKLYN,
OR AN INTERNATIONAL SUPERHERO.
MANY OF US WERE DEVASTATED TO
LEARN OF CHADWICK BOSEMAN'S
TRAGIC PASSING AFTER HE'D
PRIVATELY GRAPPLED WITH CANCER
FOR SEVERAL YEARS.
THE WORLD LOST AN INCREDIBLE
ARTIST AND A TRUE HERO, BUT
BEFORE HE WAS A PUBLIC FIGURE,
HE WAS A PERSON LIKE YOU OR ME.
A SON, A BROTHER, UNCLE,
COUSIN, FRIEND, COLLEAGUE,
HUSBAND.
MANY OF US ARE ALL TOO FAMILIAR
WITH THE FRACTURE A DEARLY LOVED
ONE'S PASSING LEAVES IN THE
LIVES OF THOSE WHO LOVE THEM.
HERE TO PERFORM A SONG ABOUT
LIVING WITH THE REALITY OF LOSS
AND FINDING A WAY FORWARD IS
CHADWICK'S WIFE, SIMONE.
♪ ♪
♪ I'LL BE SEEING YOU
IN ALL THE OLD
♪ FAMILIAR PLACES
THAT THIS HEART OF MINE
♪ EMBRACES
ALL DAY THROUGH
♪ IN THAT SMALL CAFE
THE PARK ACROSS THE WAY
♪ THE CHILDREN'S CAROUSEL
THE CHESTNUT TREE
THE CHESTNUT TREES
♪ THE WISHING WELL
I'LL BE SEEING YOU
IN EVERY LOVELY, S
♪ IN EVERY LOVELY SUMMER'S DAY
IN EVERYTHING
♪ THAT'S LIGHT AND GAY
I'LL ALWAYS THINK OF YOU
♪ THAT WAY
I'LL FIND YOU IN THE MORNING SUN
♪ AND WHEN THE NIGHT IS NEW
I'LL BE LOOKING AT THE MOON
♪ BUT I'LL BE SEEING YOU
♪ ♪
♪ I'LL BE SEEING YOU
IN EVERY LOVELY SUMMER'S DAY
♪ IN EVERYTHING
THAT'S LIGHT AND GAY
♪ I'LL ALWAYS THINK OF YOU
THAT WAY
♪ I'LL FIND YOU IN
THE MORNING SUN
♪ AND WHEN THE NIGHT IS NEW
I'LL BE LOOKING AT THE MOON
♪ BUT I'LL BE SEEING YOU
>> WE'VE ALWAYS HAD VILLAINS TO
FACE.
>> BAD GUYS TO TAKE DOWN.
>> BUT YOU.
>> YOU'RE WORSE THAN ALL OF THEM
PUT TOGETHER.
>> YOU ARE THE MOST HORRIBLE OF
ALL.
>> JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE TOUGH, IT
DOESN'T MEAN WE CAN'T BEAT YOU.
>> WE'RE NOT HERE BECAUSE WE
HAVE TO BE.
>> WE ARE HERE BECAUSE WE HAVE
HAD ENOUGH OF YOU.
>> IT'S NO FUN HAVING TO SHOW
YOU WHO'S BOSS.
>> EVERY SINGLE ONE OF US IS
MORTAL.
>> EVEN ME.
>> ESPECIALLY ME.
>> BUT INSIDE OF US...
>> WE ARE ALL HEROES.
>> ONE PERSON IS NOT A TEAM.
>> BUT WHEN WE JOIN TOGETHER.
>> TOGETHER.
>> YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
>> WE ARE GLORIOUS.
>> WE'RE RESILIENT.
>> WE ARE POWERFUL.
>> AND WE WILL WIN.
>> WE ALL HAVE THE POWER TO DO
SOMETHING.
>> TO CHANGE SOMETHING.
>> TO "STAND UP TO CANCER".
>> SO STAND UP WITH US!
>> STAND UP TO FIGHT.
>> STAND UP TO WIN.
>> IT ALL HAPPENED AT ONCE-- I
QUIT MY DAY JOB, TRANGOT
PREGNANT WITH TWINS, TWO
BEAUTIFUL GIRLS, ALEXA AND
ZOOEY, AND THEN SHE FOUND A LUMP
WHILE BREAST FEEDING.
>> Ho: I WAS YOUNG AND HAD NO
FAMILY HISTORY OF BREAST CANCER.
I THOUGHT, "“THERE WAS NO WAY
THIS COULD BE CANCER."”
BUT IT WAS.
I WAS DIAGNOSED WITH STAGE THREE
TRIPLE-NEGATIVE BREAST CANCER.
WHEN I ASKED MY ONCOLOGIST IF I
WAS GOING TO BE OKAY, HE
COULDN'T ANSWER ME, AND THAT'S
WHEN I KNEW I MIGHT NOT SURVIVE
THIS.
>> Jeong: EVERYTHING IN OUR
TRACKS STOPPED.
>> Ho: I IMMEDIATELY THOUGHT
ABOUT MY GIRLS AND KEN.
WHAT ARE THEY GOING TO DO IF I
DON'T SURVIVE THIS?
I HAD TO CONFRONT THE
POSSIBILITY OF MY OWN MORTALITY.
>> Jeong: TRAN WAS JUST SO
STRONG.
IN FACT, TWO DAYS BEFORE
STARTING CHEMO, SHE TOOK HER
MEDICAL BOARD RECERTIFICATION
EXAM-- AN EIGHT HOUR TEST, AND
PASSED IT WITH FLYING COLORS!
>> Ho: THE CHEMOTHERAPY I WAS
STARTING WAS NEW AT THE TIME.
WE HAD A LONG ROAD AHEAD OF US,
BUT TAKING THIS TEST WAS MY WAY
OF SAYING, "I'M GOING TO BEAT
THIS!"
I'M PROUD TO SAY THAT I'M
CANCER-FREE 13 YEARS AND
COUNTING.
>> Jeong: YOU ARE THE REASON I
GOT INVOLVED WITH "STAND UP TO
CANCER."
CANCER" IN THE FIRST PLACE.
AND I AM HERE TO CELEBRATE YOU,
BECAUSE YOU COMPLETE ME, HO!
>> Ho: WE'RE HERE TONIGHT
BECAUSE WE BELIEVE IN THE WORK
THAT "STAND UP TO CANCER" IS
DOING.
IT'S SIMPLE: SCIENCE SAVES
LIVES.
SCIENCE SAVED MY LIFE
>> Jeong: AND SCIENTISTS ON ALL
THE DIFFERENT "STAND UP TO
CANCER" RESEARCH TEAMS CONTINUE
TO WORK BEHIND THE SCENES ON
SOME REALLY GROUNDBREAKING NEW
STUFF.
THEY'RE TRAINING ARTIFICIAL
INTELLIGENCE TO DETECT LESIONS
UNDETECTABLE TO THE HUMAN EYE,
OTHERS ARE REPROGRAMMING YOUR
T-CELLS INTO CANCER FINDING
MACHINES.
AND TOGETHER WITH THEIR PARTNERS
AT THE VAN ANDEL INSTITUTE,
"STAND UP TO CANCER" HAS A DREAM
TEAM EXPLORING SOMETHING CALLED
IMMUNOEPIGENETICS THAT INVOLVES
ACTIVATING YOUR IMMUNE SYSTEM
AND SWITCHING KEY GENES
ON OR OFF TO HELP DESTROY CANCER
CELLS.
AND THEIR LONG-TERM PARTNERSHIP
IS MAKING A DIFFERENCE IN
PATIENTS' LIVES.
>> Ho: IT'S TRULY INCREDIBLE.
DOCTORS, SCIENTISTS, AND
RESEARCHERS ARE THINKING OUTSIDE
THE BOX.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S GOING TO TAKE
TO END CANCER; THAT'S WHAT IT
TAKES TO MAKE THE IMPOSSIBLE
POSSIBLE.
>> "STAND UP TO CANCER" CAME AT
A VERY CRITICAL TIME.
>> EVERYONE WAS SILOED AND
SHARING DATA WAS A VERY
DIFFICULT THING.
>> NOW WE CAN CREDIBLY SAY...
>> IT'S A COLLABORATIVE EFFORT.
>> DREAM TEAMS.
>> IMMUNOTHERAPY.
>> CONVERGENCE.
>> INNOVATIVE APPROACHES.
>> TECHNOLOGIES AND GENETICS.
>> PRECISION MEDICINE.
>> PHARMA.
>> CLINICAL TRIALS.
>> INTERCEPTION.
>> FUNDING.
>> MOMENTUM.
>> HOPE.
>> "STAND UP TO CANCER" REALLY
ALLOWS US TO TAKE CHANCES, AND
THEY ARE OKAY WITH NOT ALL
THE IDEAS WORKING TO GET THAT
SPECIAL ONE THAT'S GOING TO MAKE
A HUGE DIFFERENCE.
>> THE WAR ON CANCER STARTED IN
1971.
WE DID NOT THINK WE HAD THE
TOOLS TO CURE CANCER.
WHAT'S ACTUALLY CHANGED?
>> CANCER DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
THAT DEATH SENTENCE THAT WE USED
TO THINK ABOUT 10 YEARS AGO.
>> IT'S SCIENTISTS.
IT'S TECHNOLOGISTS, ADVOCATES.
IT'S PATIENTS.
WE'RE ALL WORKING TOGETHER.
>> "STAND UP TO CANCER" HAS MADE
TEAM SCIENCE THE NORM.
>> AND THAT'S WHY "STAND UP TO
CANCER" IS THERE SHOUTING, "“NOW,
NOW, NOW!
LET'S GO!
>> THE FIRST TIME IN THE LAST
FEW YEARS WE'RE STARTING TO SEE
LIGHT AT THE END OF THE TUNNEL.
>> I'M LOOKING AT AN AMAZING
ARSENAL OF DIVERSE WEAPONRY.
>> QUANTITATIVE WAYS OF
THINKING.
>> COGNITIVE THERAPY.
>> COMBINATION THERAPIES.
>> TUMOR MICROENVIRONMENT.
>> BIOINFORMATICS.
>> GEONOMICS.
>> LET'S JUST PUSH IT AND SEE
WHAT HAPPENS.
LET'S MAKE THE IMPOSSIBLE,
>> WATCH WHAT'S POSSIBLE WHEN
TEAMS COME TOGETHER AND THEY'RE
FUNDED BY SOMEONE WHO CARES.
>> "STAND UP TO CANCER" STARTED
THE REVOLUTION, BUT IT'S AN
EVOLVING REVOLUTION.
>> THERE'S NO TURNING BACK.
>> Ho: ONE THING THAT MAKES
"STAND UP TO CANCER" UNIQUE IS
THAT THEY BRING EXPERT VOICES,
DIVERSE DONORS, AND
COLABORATORS TOGETHER TO
DEVELOP THE MOST GAME-CHANGING
RESEARCH.
>> Jeong: THANKS TO THEIR NEWEST
DONORS, THIS YEAR STAND UP TO
CANCER WILL LAUNCH TWO NEW
CATALYST TEAMS AND A NEW
RESEARCH TEAM DEDICATED TO
FINDING TREATMENTS FOR HEAD AND
NECK CANCERS, WHICH ARE
DIAGNOSED IN ABOUT 67,000
AMERICANS ANNUALLY.
BUT IT'S NOT ALL ABOUT THE
NUMBERS, IT'S ABOUT THE PEOPLE'S
STORIES THAT BRING THE REALITY
OF CANCER'S IMPACT INTO FOCUS.
>> Ho: ON THE SHOW IN 2012, A
WIFE AND MOTHER HAD JUST GIVEN
BIRTH WHEN SHE FOUND OUT SHE HAD
STAGE FOUR PANCREATIC CANCER.
>> Jeong: SHE UNDERWENT AN
EXPERIMENTAL CHEMOTHERAPY, WHICH
WAS APPROVED BY THE F.D.A.
THANKS, IN PART, TO STAND UP TO
CANCER-FUNDED RESEARCH.
AND SHE BEAT THE ODDS.
BUT AS IT IS TOO OFTEN WITH
CANCER, IT CAME BACK LAST YEAR.
>> Ho: FORTUNATELY, ELIZABETH
O'CONNOR ONCE AGAIN RECEIVED
NEW CUTTING EDGE TREATMENTS AND
THE MOST PRECIOUS GIFT:
MORE TIME.
>> WHEN I WAS FIVE-YEARS-OLD MY
MOM WAS DIAGNOSED WITH CANCER.
AFTER SHE HAD MY BROTHER I JUST
REMEMBER HER BEING SICK A LOT.
AND IN AND OUT OF THE HOSPITAL.
>> PRESS THE RECORD BUTTON.
YOU PRESS IT?
OKAY, THERE WE GO.
>> NOW I GOT IT.
>> I'M ABIGAIL O'CONNOR.
>> HI, MY NAME IS ANDREW
O'CONNOR.
>> I'M 15 YEARS OLD.
>> I'M 10 YEARS OLD.
>> AND I WANT TO TELL YOU ABOUT
MY FAMILY.
ABOUT 10 YEARS AGO MY MOM WAS ON
"STAND UP TO CANCER."
I REMEMBER THEM COMING TO OUR
HOUSE AND FILMING.
AND THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME I'D
TRULY SEEN MY MOM AND DAD CRY.
>> WE'VE HAD SO MANY GOOD
MEMORIES OF THE FAMILY THE PAST
10 YEARS.
>> MY FAVORITE MEMORIES GROWING
UP WAS TAKING TRIPS TO DUSTIN,
BECAUSE MY BIRTHDAY USED TO
ALWAYS BE THAT WEEK.
SO, IT WAS LIKE I GOT TO GO TO
THE BEACH FOR MY BIRTHDAY EVERY
YEAR.
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY DEAR ABIGAIL
>> BEING ABLE TO FISH WITH MY
DAD.
>> YOUR TURN, DADDY.
>> GOOD JOB, BUD.
>> ONE OF MY FAVORITE TRIPS WAS
WHEN WE WENT TO DISNEY IN 2018.
IT WAS OUR CHRISTMAS PRESENT.
>> WE GET TO GO TO DISNEY WORLD!
>> IT'S VERY EXCITING RIDING THE
ROLLERCOASTERS WITH MY MOM.
HER LAUGH JUST KIND OF LIKE
CARRIES, LIKE "“HA-HA."”
[ LAUGHTER]
>> THAT'S WHY WE MAKE HER LAUGH,
TO HEAR IT, 'CAUSE MAKES
EVERYONE ELSE LAUGH.
[ LAUGHTER]
>> MOM, HOW VALUABLE DO YOU
THINK TIME IS?
>> IT'S A GIFT, REALLY.
>> CANCER RESEARCH HAS
DEFINITELY MADE AN IMPACT ON MY
MOM.
>> WE'VE BEEN VERY FORTUNATE TO
BE A PART OF A LOT OF NEW
TREATMENTS THAT HAVE GIVEN
ELIZABETH TIME TO GET TO THE
NEXT BEST THING.
>> IT'S UNHEARD OF TO LIVE 10+
YEARS FOR PANCREATIC CANCER.
>> MY MOM IS A FIGHTER.
SHE IS ALWAYS TRYING TO FIGHT
FOR HER LIFE SO SHE CAN BE HERE
WITH US.
>> PUSH, PUSH, YOU GOT IT.
[ SCREAMS]
[ LAUGHTER]
ABIGAIL, YOUR BROTHER.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I CAN'T PUT IT INTO WORDS HOW
MUCH IT MEANS TO ME TO SPEND
MORE TIME WITH MY FAMILY, TO NOT
HAVE THAT FEAR THAT I WOULDN'T
BE AROUND.
>> THAT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING TO ME, IS THAT SHE'S HERE.
>> TO PEOPLE WATCHING AT HOME I
WOULD SAY THANK YOU AND PLEASE
DONATE SO YOU CAN HELP MORE
PEOPLE LIKE MY MOM.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW MY LIFE
WOULD BE WITHOUT HER.
>> YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW HOW
MUCH TIME YOU HAVE LEFT WITH
SOMEONE, SO THAT TIME IS VERY
IMPORTANT.
>> I LOVE YOU FOREVER.
>> Jeong: ELIZABETH O'CONNOR'S
ACCESS TO THE LATEST
IMMUNOTHERAPY DRUGS WAS VITAL TO
HER.
"STAND UP TO CANCER," SINCE ITS
INCEPTION, HAS SUPPORTED MANY
TEAMS STUDYING IMMUNOTHERAPY,
ONE OF THE MOST PROMISING AREAS
OF CANCER RESEARCH TODAY
>> Ho: HOWEVER, IN 1998,
PANCREATIC CANCER PATIENTS HAD
PRACTICALLY NO EFFECTIVE
TREATMENT OPTIONS.
>> Jeong: SINCE THEN, THE
LUSTGARTEN FOUNDATION HAS FUNDED
THE SCIENCE THAT HAS BEEN A PART
OF NEARLY EVERY SIGNIFICANT
ADVANCEMENT IN THE FIGHT AGAINST
PANCREATIC CANCER IN AN
EFFORT TO TRANSFORM IT INTO A
CURABLE DISEASE.
AND TOGETHER WITH "STAND UP TO
CANCER," THEY'VE CREATED THE
PANCREATIC CANCER COLLECTIVE TO
FUND EVEN MORE CRITICAL RESEARCH
TO GIVE PANCREATIC CANCER
PATIENTS, LIKE ELIZABETH
O'CONNOR TIME AND HOPE.
>> Ho: I JUST WANT TO TAKE A
MOMENT TO PERSONALLY THANK
EVERYONE WHO HAS ALREADY DONATED
TONIGHT.
>> Jeong: AND I'D ALSO LIKE TO
THANK SOMEONE WHO WAS THERE FOR
US, OUR GOOD FRIEND, BRADLY
COOPER.
>> THANKS KEN AND TRAN.
I'M HERE TONIGHT BECAUSE CANCER
TOUCHES ALL OF US.
I'M HERE BECAUSE WHILE THERE HAS
BEEN AMAZING PROGRESS IN HOW WE
TREAT CANCER, THERE'S SO MUCH
MORE THAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
AND I'M ALSO HERE TONIGHT
BECAUSE THIS YEAR MAKES 10 YEARS
SINCE I LOST MY FATHER, CHARLIE
COOPER, TO LUNG CANCER.
HE WAS MY BEST FRIEND, AND
THERE'S NOT A DAY THAT GOES BY
THAT I DON'T MISS HIM.
AND THAT'S SOMETHING THAT SONS,
DAUGHTERS, MOTHERS, FATHERS,
FAMILY, FRIENDS, AND NEIGHBORS
ALL AROUND THE WORLD CAN RELATE
TO.
CANCER TOUCHES ALL OF US, AND
IT'S GOING TO TAKE ALL OF US TO
CHANGE THAT FACT.
100% OF WHAT YOU GIVE GOES
DIRECTLY TO LIFE-SAVING RESEARCH
PROGRAMS, BUT THE TRUE
BUT THE TRUE IMPACT OF YOUR GIFT
GOES BEYOND THAT.
YOU ARE GIVING HOPE TO CANCER
PATIENTS AND THEIR LOVED ONES.
SO, PLEASE, GIVE WHAT YOU CAN
FROM YOUR HEART.
LET'S STAND TOGETHER, AND END
CANCER.
>> AND TO ALL MY FELLOW
CANADIANS OUT THERE WHO ARE
WATCHING THE BROADCAST AND WHO
HAVE BEEN TOUCHED BY CANCER AT
THIS HOUR, KNOW THAT YOU ARE IN
MY HEART AND I AM STANDING UP
FOR YOU.
THIS YEAR WE'VE MADE IT SUPER
EASY FOR YOU TO DONATE.
GO TO THE WEBSITE, CALL THE
NUMBER, OR USE THE Q.R. CODE.
DO IT NOW.
AND WHEN YOU DO, YOU'LL RECEIVE
A LINK ON YOUR DONATION RECEIPT,
AND THAT LINK WILL GIVE YOU THE
OPPORTUNITY TO VIDEO CHAT WITH
ONE OF US TONIGHT.
>> STAND UP WITH US.
WE ALL HAVE A STORY.
I HAD A COUSIN NAMED OWEN.
HE HAD RED HAIR AS A LITTLE BOY.
HE WAS A SERIOUS KID AND HE
LOVED BIRDS.
IN HIS 28 YEARS, HE TAUGHT ME
IN HIS THIRD YEARS, OWEN THOUGHT
ME HOW TO LIVE WELL.
I'M SO LUCKY TO HAVE GOTTEN TO
KNOW HIM AND LOVE HIM DURING HIS
EXTRAORDINARY LIFE.
>> MY FATHER STARTED CANCER
TREATMENT EARLIER THIS YEAR
DURING WHAT WAS ALREADY A VERY
DIFFICULT YEAR.
KNOWING THAT 100% OF THE MONEY
DONATED TONIGHT GOES TO FUND
RESEARCH AND CANCER TREATMENT IS
TO KNOW THAT, THAT MONEY MIGHT
GO TOWARDS HELPING MY DAD, OR
YOUR DAD OR ANYONE IN YOUR
FAMILY WHO HAS BEEN TOUCHED BY
CANCER, LIKE SO MANY OF US HAVE
JOIN US, DONATE TONIGHT, AND
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> I'M A SURVIVOR.
I WENT TO THE DERMATOLOGIST FOR
A SCREENING.
AND THEY FOUND A BASAL CELL
CARCINOMA.
THEY REMOVED IT AND I'M OKAY.
LET'S GIVE IN HONOR OF ALL THE
SURVIVORS OUT THERE.
>> LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT TWO
PEOPLE I'M THINKING ABOUT RIGHT
NOW.
MY LRS ALEXIS WHO PASSED AWAY
FROM BREAST CANCER, AND MY
FRIEND WHO IS GOING THROUGH
TREATMENT AS WE SPEAK.
TELL EVERYONE TO GET SCREENED,
TOO.
EVERYONE, PLEASE, GET ON YOUR
FEET AND STAND UP TO CANCER.
>> Ho: "STAND UP TO CANCER" BY
DONATING TONIGHT, AND BY
REDUCING YOUR PERSONAL RISK OF
DEVELOPING CANCER EVERY DAY.
IF YOU SMOKE, QUIT.
WATCH YOUR DIET AND GET ACTIVE.
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY, STAY ON
TOP OF YOUR CANCER SCREENINGS.
>> Jeong: "STAND UP TO CANCER,"
AND OUR SUPPORTER, RALLY HEALTH
WANT TO HELP YOU REDUCE YOUR
RISK OF CANCER BY ENCOURAGING
YOU TO GET APPROPRIATE TO
SCREENINGS WHICH CAN DETECT
CANCER EARLY AND SIGNIFICANTLY
INCREASE THE LIKELIHOOD OF
BEATING CANCER AND LIVING
LONGER.
GO TO THE "STAND UP TO CANCER"
WEBSITE TO FIND OUT WHICH
SCREENINGS ARE BEST FOR YOU.
>> Vergara: AT 28 YEARS OLD,
DURING A ROUTINE DOCTOR'S VISIT,
MY DOCTOR FELT A LUMP IN MY
NECK.
THEY DID A LOT OF TESTS AND
FINALLY TOLD ME I HAD THYROID
CANCER.
WHEN YOU ARE YOUNG, AND HEAR
THAT WORD "CANCER," YOUR MIND
GOES TO SO MANY PLACES.
BUT I TRIED NOT TO PANIC, AND I
DECIDED TO GET EDUCATED.
I READ EVERY BOOK, AND FOUND OUT
EVERYTHING I COULD ABOUT IT.
I WAS FORTUNATE TO HAVE CAUGHT
IT EARLY, AND TO HAVE THE
SUPPORT OF MY DOCTORS AND, MOST
IMPORTANTLY, MY FAMILY.
I LEARNED A LOT DURING THAT
TIME.
NOT JUST ABOUT THYROID
CANCER, BUT I ALSO LEARNED THAT
IN TIMES OF CRISIS, WE ARE
BETTER TOGETHER.
WE HAVE ALL WITNESSED THE POWER
OF COMING TOGETHER JUST
THIS PAST YEAR.
SCIENTISTS AROUND THE GLOBE
COLLABORATED IN UNPRECEDENTED
WAYS TO DEVELOP THE COVID-19
VACCINE IN RECORD TIME.
HUMAN RIGHTS ACTIVISTS TOOK TO
THE STREETS ALL OVER THE WORLD
TO SUPPORT SOCIAL JUSTICE AND
EQUALITY.
AND PEOPLE EVERYWHERE STEPPED UP
TO SUPPORT SMALL BUSINESSES AND
ENTREPRENEURS IN THEIR
COMMUNITIES.
WE'RE BETTER TOGETHER, AND IF WE
ARE GOING TO END CANCER, IT'S
GOING TO REQUIRE A TEAM EFFORT.
>> I'M TREY MANCINI, INFIELDER
FOR THE BALTIMORE ORIOLES.
MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL IS ABOUT
TEAMWORK, BOTH ON AND OFF THE
FIELD.
AS THE FOUNDING DONOR OF "STAND
UP TO CANCER," M.L.B. HAS HELPED
BUILD CANCER AWARENESS THROUGH
THE ICONIC PLACARD MOMENT,
P.S.A.s, AND FUNDRAISING EVENTS.
IT'S SO POWERFUL TO SEE
EVERYBODY UNIFIED, STANDING UP,
AND SHOWING THEIR SUPPORT.
I'M PROUD TO BE A PART OF MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL NOT JUST
AS A PLAYER, BUT ALSO AS A
CANCER SURVIVOR.
MY BATTLE WITH STAGE THREE COLON
CANCER WAS THE HARDEST FIGHT OF
MY LIFE LAST YEAR, BUT I'M
STANDING HERE TODAY AS LIVING
PROOF THAT CANCER RESEARCH SAVES
LIVES.
LET'S MAKE IT MAJOR AND KNOCK
CANCER OUT OF THE PARK.
>> Vergara: "STAND UP TO CANCER"
IS THRILLED TO TEAM UP WITH
MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL TO PRESENT
BID TO END CANCER, AN
EXTRAORDINARY AUCTION EXPERIENCE
POWERED BY OUR FRIENDS AT
HERITAGE AUCTIONS.
GO TO
standuptocancer.org/auction TO
LEARN HOW YOU CAN PARTICIPATE IN
A SERIES OF AUCTIONS FEATURING
EVERYTHING FROM SIGNED GAME-WORN
JERSEYS, AUTOGRAPHED
COLLECTIBLES AND THE ONCE-IN-A-
LIFETIME CHANCE TO THROW OUT THE
FIRST PITCH AT GAME FOUR OF
THIS YEAR'S WORLD SERIES.
NOW, TONIGHT IS NOT JUST ABOUT
RAISING MONEY FOR CANCER
RESEARCH AND RAISING CANCER
AWARENESS.
IT'S ALSO A CELEBRATION OF
SURVIVORS.
AND I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE YOU TO
MY FRIEND, NICK PIFANI, WHO'S
HERE TO SHARE HIS STORY.
>> I'M NICK PIFANI- HUSBAND,
FATHER OF TWO GREAT KIDS, AND A
PANCREATIC CANCER SURVIVOR.
WHEN I WAS GOING THROUGH
TREATMENT, I PROMISED MYSELF
THAT WHEN I MADE IT THROUGH, I
WOULD SHARE MY STORY TO HELP
INSPIRE OTHERS.
I'M GRATEFUL TO BE ABLE TO KEEP
THAT PROMISE THANKS TO THE
PROGRESS IN CANCER TREATMENT.
I'M ALSO PROUD, AS A MASTERCARD
EMPLOYEE, TO STAND UP WITH
MASTERCARD BECAUSE FOR OVER 10
YEARS, THEY'VE BEEN SUPPORTING
THE RESEARCH BEHIND NEW
TREATMENTS BY DONATING TO "STAND
UP TO CANCER" ON BEHALF OF THEIR
CARDHOLDERS AND EMPLOYEES, LIKE
ME AND IMPACTING CANCER
PATIENTS.
THEIR DONATIONS HAVE SAVED
COUNTLESS LIVES AND GIVEN CANCER
PATIENTS AND THEIR FAMILIES
SOMETHING TRULY PRICELESS: HOPE.
KATIE?
>> THANKS, NICK.
AND WE ARE THRILLED NICK IS
DOING SO WELL.
AS YOU ALL KNOW, CANCER HAS
AFFECTED SO MANY PEOPLE.
AND LIKE COUNTLESS OTHERS,
CANCER HAS AFFECTED ME IN A
DEEPLY PERSONAL WAY.
I LOST MY HUSBAND, JAY, IN 1998,
TO COLORECTAL CANCER, AND
WHEN HE WAS JUST 42.
SHE WAS 54.
A FEW YEARS LATER, MY OLDER
SISTER, EMILY, DIED OF
PANCREATIC CANCER.
I REALIZED I HAD TO DO
SOMETHING.
I JOINED FORCES WITH EIGHT
REMARKABLE WOMEN AND WE LAUNCHED
"STAND UP TO CANCER" WITH A
MISSION TO MAKE EVERY CANCER
PATIENT A LONG-TERM SURVIVOR,
THROUGH THE POWER OF
COLLABORATION BOTH INSIDE AND
OUTSIDE THE LAB.
WHEN BUD SELIG AND LEW WOLFF SAW
HOW "STAND UP TO CANCER" BROUGHT
TOGETHER SCIENTISTS AND DOCTORS,
THEY DECIDED TO DO THE SAME.
THEY WANTED TO MAKE SURE THEY
WERE PART OF "STAND UP TO
CANCER'S" LEGACY.
AND SO, THEY FOUNDED THE LEGACY
CIRCLE, AND INVITED LIKE-MINDED
INDIVIDUALS TO JOIN THEM AND
SUPPORT THE CRITICALLY IMPORTANT
RESEARCH OF "STAND UP TO
CANCER."
WE'VE BEEN FORTUNATE TO HAVE
COMMITTED PARTNERS SINCE THE
BEGINNING OF "STAND UP TO
CANCER," INCLUDING OUR
SCIENTIFIC PARTNER, THE AMERICAN
ASSOCIATION FOR CANCER RESEARCH.
WITHOUT THEM AND THE SCIENTIFIC
ADVISORY COMMITTEE, WE WOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO DO THIS LIFESAVING
WORK.
TOGETHER, THEY HAVE HELPED GUIDE
OUR MISSION AND DEVELOP OUR
RESEARCH PORTFOLIO.
AND THE WORK WE DO THROUGH
"STAND UP TO CANCER" IS INSPIRED
BY ALL THE INCREDIBLE
SCIENTISTS, DOCTORS, NURSES,
CAREGIVERS, AND PATIENTS WHO
CHAMPION THE FIGHT AGAINST
CANCER.
IT TAKES ALL OF US AND ALL OF
YOU.
SO PLEASE DONATE NOW.
>> HEY, EVERYBODY.
I'M IAN HECOX.
>> I'M SHAYNE TOPP.
>> I'M COURTNEY MILLER, AND
WE'RE SMOSH!
>> MUCH LIKE MANY OF YOU OUT
THERE, WE ALL KNOW SOMEONE
WHO'S BEEN AFFECTED BY CANCER,
AND WE WANT TO DO OUR PART TO
KEEP THOSE DONATIONS COMING IN
SO WE CAN CHANGE THAT.
SO, WE'RE THROWING AN AWESOME
SO WE THOUGHT WE'D THROW A
LITTLE PARTY AND WE'D INVITE YOU
GUYS.
YEAH.
THERE'S NO R.S.V.P.
>> AND
TIE OPTIONAL, WE JUST HAVE ONE
SIMPLE REQUEST: GIVE!
WE'RE ALSO GOING TO BE
JOINED BY AMAZING GUESTS.
>> WE MADE IT SUPER EASY FOR
YOU.
JUST HEAD TO
twitch.tv/smoshgames!
>> SO, NO EXCUSES.
WE'LL SEE YOU THERE!
IN THE MEANTIME, BUCKLE UP AND
GET READY FOR FUN AND GAMES!
TOGETHER WE CAN MAKE AN IMPACT.
WE'LL SEE YOU THERE.
>> Vergara: A DOLLAR HERE, A
DOLLAR THERE.
IT MAY NOT SEEM LIKE MUCH.
BUT ALL THOSE DOLLARS ADD UP.
PLUS, AMERICAN AIRLINES, WITH
SUPPORT FROM MASTERCARD, WILL
DOUBLE THE IMPACT OF DONATIONS
FOR MILES MADE WITH A
MASTERCARD.
CALL OR GO TO THE "STAND UP TO
CANCER" WEBSITE AND JOIN
THE MOVEMENT.
IN TIMES OF CRISIS, WE ARE
BETTER TOGETHER.
>> I'M MATTHEW McCONAUGHEY.
NOW, I FIRST GOT INVOLVED WITH
"STAND UP TO CANCER" BEFORE
CANCER AFFECTED ME PERSONALLY.
BUT SHORTLY AFTER I DID, DEAR
FRIEND AND MENTOR OF MINE,
PENNY, WAS DIAGNOSED.
NOW, AS TOO MANY OF YOU KNOW,
NOTHING CAN REALLY PREPARE YOU
FOR THAT NEWS.
ONE: IT'S SCARY.
TWO: IT'S OVERWHELMING.
THE BARRAGE OF INFORMATION, ALL
THE NUMBERS, THE VARIABLES, IT'S
A LOT.
I DID WHAT I COULD TO SUPPORT MY
FRIEND THE BEST WAY I KNEW
HOW.
I ASKED THE HARD QUESTIONS, I
GOT AS EDUCATED AS I COULD, I
LEARNED ABOUT THE NEWEST
TREATMENTS.
AND I TRIED TO WALK THAT TIGHT-
ROPE QUESTION THAT WE ALL HAVE
OF QUALITY VERSUS QUANTITY OF
LIFE.
SADLY, MY FRIEND IS NO LONGER
WITH US, BUT I WAS AND STILL AM
FOREVER GRATEFUL FOR THE TIME
THAT WE DID HAVE TOGETHER.
I'M ALSO GRATEFUL THAT THERE'S
AN ORGANIZATION LIKE STAND UP TO
CANCER DOING THE WORK THAT NEEDS
TO BE DONE SO WE CAN STOP LOSING
SO MANY FRIENDS AND FAMILY
MEMBERS TO THIS DAMN DISEASE.
SO, IF YOU CAN, PLEASE DONATE.
TOGETHER, THIS KIND OF
HEARTACHE, IT CAN END.
JUST KEEP LIVING.
>> THE STORIES WE'VE HEARD
TONIGHT FROM DOCTORS, PATIENTS,
SCIENTISTS, AND LOVED ONES ARE
JUST A FEW EXAMPLES OF THE
TRUE POWER OF THE UNSTOPPABLE
HUMAN SPIRIT.
ON BEHALF OF ALL OF US HERE, I'D
LIKE TO THANK ALL OF YOU OUT
THERE FOR DONATING TO SUPPORT
LIFE CHANGING AND LIFE SAVING
RESEARCH.
I WANT TO SEND A SPECIAL THANKS
TO ALL OF TONIGHT'S
STORYTELLERS, AND I DEDICATE
THIS PERFORMANCE TO THEM AND TO
ALL OF THE CANCER PATIENTS AND
SURVIVORS WHOSE COURAGE IS AN
INSPIRATION TO US ALL.
♪ ♪
♪ I'M RIGHT HERE IN THE FLESH
YOU CAN TAKE IT OR NOT
♪ I'M NOT CLAIMING, PRETENDING
TO BE WHAT I'M NOT
♪ I AIN'T NOBODY'S ANGEL
WHEN THIS WORLD
♪ TRY TO CHANGE YOU
WHO YOU ARE, JUST EMBRACE IT
♪ STAY COURAGEOUS
UNAPOLOGETIC, UNASHAMED WITH IT
♪ TIMES IN LIFE, I CAME WITH IT
WHEN THE UNSEEN BECAME VIVID
♪ OF DIFFERENT FLESH
SAME SPIRIT
♪ IT'S LIKE A LYRIC
BY STEVIE WONDER
♪ THROUGH INNER VISIONS
YOU CAN SEE THE WONDER
♪ SPENT TIME IN LIFE
BEING A RUNNER
♪ COULDN'T RUN FROM WHAT
I'VE SEEN THIS SUMMER
♪ TRYNA UNDERSTAND
WHERE WE ARE IN TIME
♪ LOOKING AT THE WORLD
KEEPING GOD IN MIND
♪ I KNOW IT'S A PEACE
IT'S HARD TO FIND
♪ I WENT OUT THERE
AND FOUND MINE INSIDE
♪ I'M ALIVE ON ARRIVAL
MY LIFE IS MORE THAN SURVIVAL
♪ YOU CAN LIVE AND BE LIVE TOO
THAT'S HOW HEAVEN
♪ WILL DESCRIBE YOU
IF YOU WANT SOMETHING, BE IT
♪ I'M RIGHT HERE IN THE FLESH
YOU CAN TAKE IT OR NOT
♪ I'M NOT CLAIMING, PRETENDING
TO BE WHAT I'M NOT
♪ I AIN'T NOBODY'S ANGEL
WHEN THIS WORLD TRY
♪ TO CHANGE YOU
WHO YOU ARE, JUST EMBRACE IT
♪ STAY COURAGEOUS
>> THE INCOMPARABLE STEVIE
WONDER.
♪ ♪
LOOK LIFE IN THE EYE
♪ I CAN SEE CLEARER
A KINGDOM'S COMING
♪ YOU CAN HEAR IT NEAR US
STAY CLOSE TO THE SINCEREST
♪ THOSE THE ONES
THAT BECOME MIRRORS
♪ SPEAK NO HATE
LET LOVE HEAR US
♪ TIMES I'M ME IS
WHEN I WAS FEARLESS
♪ THERE'S A SELF
I GOTTA TAKE CARE OF
♪ SO WITH THE WORLD
I CAN TRULY SHARE LOVE
♪ AND BE A BEARER OF FRUIT
ON THE PLANET
♪ GUIDED STEPS
I DON'T TAKE FOR GRANTED
♪ TIME IS MANIC, WE INTERNALIZE
HONOR THAT LITTLE BOY
♪ OR LITTLE GIRL INSIDE
PRAY THESE WORDS'LL
♪ RISE TO THE EARS OF ANGELS
WE LET GO OF FEARS
♪ THAT WE CAME THROUGH
CHANGE IS BEAUTIFUL
♪ AS IT IS PAINFUL
THE WORLD IS YOURS
♪ DON'T LET IT CHANGE YOU
DON'T LET IT CHANGE YOU
♪ I'M RIGHT HERE IN THE FLESH
YOU CAN TAKE IT OR NOT
♪ I'M NOT CLAIMING, PRETENDING
TO BE WHAT I'M NOT
♪ I AIN'T NOBODY'S ANGEL
WHEN THIS WORLD TRY
♪ TO CHANGE YOU
WHO YOU ARE, JUST EMBRACE IT
♪ STAY COURAGEOUS
♪ ♪
>> TO ALL THE SURVIVORS AND
THEIR FAMILIES, WE HONOR YOU.
WE SUPPORT YOU.
WE BELIEVE IN YOU.
WE APPRECIATE YOU.
WE LOVE YOU.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org