Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[chuckles]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
♪ It's time to shine ♪
-♪ Gonna save the world ♪
-♪ Fly ♪
-♪ Superhero girl ♪
-♪ Get tough ♪
♪ Small and mighty ♪
♪ It's time to shine ♪
♪ StarBeam ♪
[caws]
[kids]
Beaming In The New Year.
A very happy New Year's Eve to you all.
Ava Peyton here
reporting to you live from City Hall,
where the citizens of Somerset
are getting ready
to ring in the new year.
[horn blows]
[laughs] You see what I mean?
And if you look behind me
at the top of City Hall,
you can see the world famous
Heart of Somerset.
[panting]
[Ava Peyton]
A symbol of peace and goodwill,
the Heart of Somerset
is made of solid diamond.
Every New Year's Eve
it drops at the stroke of midnight,
signaling the arrival of the new year!
[groaning]
Gah!
Look out!
-[screams]
-Look out!
[grunts]
[cheering]
[giggles]
-Yeah!
-Whoo-hoo!
Gah! Heh.
[cheering]
[man]
Way to go, StarBeam!
Happy to help!
There's no way I'd let anything ruin
the big New Year's Eve party.
Happy New Year, everyone!
[giggles]
[munching]
Nice save!
Thanks!
Now that the Heart of Somerset is safe,
I can spend the rest of the night
ringing in the New Year as regular Zoey.
Mom's finally letting me stay up
until midnight!
[sniffs, gasps]
-[Gramps whistling]
-Mmm!
Gramps, your special New Year's
soup smells so good.
Mmm, mmm!
How do you make it so good?
Heh. Wish I could tell you, Henry,
but it's a secret ingredient.
[chuckles]
Is it… pepper?
Huh?
Uh… no!
-It's pepper.
-Yep.
So, Henry, you making any
New Year's resolutions?
Resolutions?
You know, like, are you planning
on doing anything
big or special in the new year?
[caws]
Huh?
-[items crashing]
-[animal noises]
[Kipper]
Ah-ha!
"Find a buried treasure.
Run a marathon…"
Uh, Kipper?
Is this the New Year's resolution list
you made last year?
Uh-huh.
Have you done any of these things?
Uh-uh.
Well, this is a pretty long list.
[muttering]
I'm not sure
you're going to be able to
finish everything on your list
before midnight.
[grumbles]
[squawking]
Good luck, Kipper!
[giggling]
So, how long until your cousin Zara
gets here?
My mom went to pick her up a while ago.
They should be here soon.
You're gonna love Zara.
She's so smart and so cool.
Hmm. How cool are we talking?
Well, she has really rad hair.
She plays electric guitar.
She rides around on a super-fast scooter.
And she has a super cool dog named Riff.
[howls]
Okay. She does sound really cool.
[laughing]
[mutters]
Diving for treasure, Kipper?
Okay, that's one resolution down…
a lot more to go.
[squawks]
[laughing]
[ominous music plays]
Miserable Marla reporting in.
This be Fishbeard awaiting orders.
[mystery villain] Where is the big
muscly one with the horrible haircut?
[sighs] Cosmic Crusher?
We tried to teach him to use
the communicator,
-but I--
-[horn blows]
Happy New Year!
[gibberish]
[groans] I'm muting you now.
Anyway, everybody's in position.
Good.
And you have the device I sent you?
You mean the party favor?
No! The Glowing Gizmo of Power!
It's right here with me.
Excellent! We'll need that
to pull off our plan.
Citizens gathered at City Hall tonight
will witness you finally defeating
the Beam Team.
That's when I'll make my grand entrance.
That's right, my favorite group
of super scoundrels,
before the clock strikes midnight,
the villains will be in charge,
and Somerset will be ours!
[evil laughter]
[whistling, chuckles]
[whistles]
Uh, try this. Tell me what you think.
[slurps] It's great, Gramps!
Is it great,
or is it the greatest soup
in the history of soup?
Uh…
Hmm?
Greatest soup in the history of soup?
You hesitated.
Uh, maybe more pepper.
[electric guitar playing]
What was that?!
[gasps] Zara's here!
Hello, family!
[giggles]
Zoey!
Zara!
[giggling]
[barks]
[panting]
You must be Riff.
Whoa! Ugh!
[laughing]
Nice to meet you too.
Gramps!
Ha ha ha ha!
So good to see you, Zara Bear.
[whistles]
[whines, barks]
And you must be Henry.
Yeah, good to meet you.
[Mom] Sorry we're late, guys.
I would have called,
but my communicator got zapped.
I can fix this with the Beam Computer.
Hey, is it true that the Beam Computer
can fix anything?
You know it!
Come on, I'll show you.
Don't take too long!
Soup's almost ready.
[slurps] Ah!
Actually, uh, take your time.
[laughing]
Come on, boy!
[barks]
[laughing] Whoo-hoo!
Welcome to Beam Control.
Ooo!
Wow. Look at this place.
[gasps]
And look at that! And this!
Oh, it's the coolest place I've ever seen.
[whines, grunts]
[snores]
[Henry] Just got to plug this cable
into your mom's communicator…
And spingo-spango, yup!
This should just take a second.
So, Zoey, any new superpowers?
Oh!
What's the biggest Beam Bubble
you can make?
When you're flying really fast,
is it hard to avoid swallowing bugs?
[giggles]
All really good questions.
Wait, I don't understand.
Uh, Zara,
don't you have superpowers?
Oh, I wish I had powers.
That would really rock.
Except for the whole bug-swallowing thing.
Zara, you do have powers!
You're super smart,
you're a super good guitar player,
and you're a super cousin!
-[alarm blares]
-[Over P.A.] Alert, alert.
[alarm blaring]
Miserable Marla is causing trouble
at Somerset City Hall.
The heart of Somerset.
I bet Marla's trying to ruin
the big countdown tonight
so no one has any fun.
Time to shine!
♪ It's time to shine! ♪
♪ Gonna save the world ♪
♪ Superhero girl ♪
♪ Shine! ♪
♪ StarBeam! ♪
♪ Small and mighty ♪
♪ It's time to shine! ♪
Whoa!
Now that is cool.
I already saved that heart once today,
I'm not about to let Miserable Marla
mess things up,
and ruin my one chance
to stay up past midnight.
-What's happening?
-We heard the alarm.
Nothing I can't handle.
Just have to take care
of one little problem
before we start our holiday fun.
-[alarm blares]
-Alert.
Cosmic Crusher is making
trouble at Somerset Park.
Okay, two little problems
before we start our holiday fun.
-[alarm blares]
-Alert.
Captain Fishbeard
causing chaos at the wharf.
Really?!
How many bad guys are out tonight?
Don't they know it's a holiday?
Looks like you're gonna need a boost,
StarBeam.
You're not going without me!
Let's go, WonderBeam!
You guys are so cool.
I wish I could come with you and help.
Me too. But we'll be back
as fast as we can.
It's Beam Time!
[sighs]
Ah, don't you worry, Zara Bear.
You'll have fun here with me and Kipper.
Hey, where is Kipper?
[caws]
[squeaks]
[ringing]
[Fishbeard]
Hello, Leonard?
What? I can't hear you, Leonard.
Oh, right. You don't talk.
Have all the do-gooders
left the lighthouse?
Good.
Call back when you be in position.
[playing sad melody]
Not many folks who can play the guitar
like you do, you know?
Nothing like great music and great soup,
I always say.
Ha!
Now, how's about strumming something
I can really stir this soup to?
Sure thing!
[plays upbeat tune]
Yeah, now we're cooking!
[doorbell rings]
Oops, can't stop stirring.
Can you get that?
No problem, Gramps.
Hmm…
[electronic voice]
Security system deactivated.
Huh?
[electronic voice]
Security system reactivated.
Huh?
There you are!
All right, Marla,
I don't know what you're up to,
but I'm not gonna let you
ruin New Year's Eve.
Hey, Marla!
Huh?
Crusher!
Gotcha!
[gasps] Wait a second.
Okay, Fishbeard.
Uh-- you're not Fishbeard!
[coughs]
Ugh!
[gasps]
A stink bomb!
[all] We've been tricked!
-[doorbell rings]
-[barks]
Happy New Year!
It's Cosmic Crusher,
Captain Fishbeard,
and Miserable Marla!
What do we do, Gramps?
[barking]
Nothing to worry about.
There's no way
they're getting in here
as long as Beam Security
is activated.
[chiming]
[electronic voice]
Beam Security deactivated.
Eh, that's not good.
[whining]
Who deactivated my security system?!
[powers down]
[giggles]
[laughs]
[evil laughter]
I know I should tell all of you
to turn right around
and vamoose,
but… would you like
some New Year's soup?
[snarls]
[Gramps/Zara]
Whoa-oh-oh-oh!
[grunts]
[electronic voice]
Security system activated.
[whines]
I take it back--
no soup for you!
They can't lock us out of our home,
not on New Year's Eve.
That door is no match for StarBeam!
[grunting]
Whoa!
Oh, honey, are you okay?
-I'm okay.
-Good.
Because that door is no match
for WonderBeam.
[gasps] Whoa!
Stop.
Stop it!
None of you can get past that door.
I should know. I programmed
the security system myself.
I thought for sure one of you
would be able to break through.
Hmm.
Not one of us,
but maybe all of us.
They beat us because they worked together,
which is what we should do.
They tricked us into splitting up,
but we're better together,
as a family.
As a team.
As the Beam Team.
StarBeam.
WonderBeam!
Boost… Beam.
And… AlphaBeam!
Dad, are you sure?
[sighs] Three villains
just took over my home.
They have access to our technology,
our superhero secrets,
and… they refused
my generous offer of soup.
Yes, I'm sure.
AlphaBeam, power up!
Okay, hang on, hang on, I got this.
Eh, just a little rusty. Heh heh.
I said, AlphaBeam,
power up!
[chuckling]
I'm back, baby.
[gasps]
Um, Dad?
The door?
Right.
-Whoa!
-Wow! There's two of you!
That's my clone beam.
Comes in handy
when you need a little something--
Oh! Or someone extra.
[breathing heavily]
Hey, look at that.
Kipper's getting in shape
so he can help us too.
Actually, I think he's trying to cross
"run a marathon" off
his New Year's Resolution list.
[exhales]
[grumbling, shouting]
[groaning]
Yarr!
Ha ha!
-[grunts]
-[shouts]
Yarr!
Well done, Leonard, well done.
[laughs]
There it is, boys, the Beam Computer.
-Ooh!
-Shiny!
Oh! Oh! Does it play video games?
'Cause I crush it with video games!
Ugh! We're not here for games.
We're here for this!
The Glowing Gizmo of Power
is our key to finally beating
the Beam Team.
Tonight, all of Somerset
will see who's really in charge!
[evil laughter]
Looks pretty busted.
Which is why we need
this computer to fix it.
Apparently,
the Beam Computer
can fix anything.
[Crusher sighs]
It looks like it's gonna
take a while.
Aye!
If only there be something fun to do
while we wait.
Fine.
One video game.
[laughing]
My bubble will keep you and Riff safe
while we take back the lighthouse.
BubbleBeam Blast!
Sorry I don't have any cool powers
to help you guys out.
That's okay, Zara.
But actually,
you know what might help?
Cool battle music!
That I can do!
[rock music plays]
All right, Beam Team,
combine super energy on "three."
-One.
-Two.
Three!
[rock music playing]
Arrgh!
Take that, you scurvy dog.
Ha ha! I am crushing it!
[electronic voice] Alert!
Intruders detected at the front door.
Alert!
Hey! Who changed the game?
Who cares?
This game looks way better.
That's not a video game,
you confetti-brained ding dongs!
[groans]
Keep going! We're almost through!
They're gonna break through
the front door
before we're finished fixing
the Glowing Gizmo of Power!
Hmm. Let's see what else
this computer can do.
Uh-oh. They've accessed
the primary security software.
We're in big trouble
if they figure out how to use it.
[groans] They figured it out.
Whoa!
Eh! Ugh!
Come on, Beam Team.
We can't give up now.
Batter up!
[shouting]
What was that?
Oh, boy.
Ha! Missed!
[all]
Try to find the real me!
Ha! Missed again!
Now, let's do this!
What the--!
Yes! They're retreating!
[electronic voice]
Security system deactivated.
Now it's our time to shine!
Oh! They've activated my zap traps!
Zap traps?
I designed them to trap bad guys.
Don't touch the beams or you'll get…
zapped.
Boost, we have to save them.
We have to do something!
StarBeam!
You kids need to get out of here!
But Mom, we can help!
StarBeam, please do as I say.
It's not safe to stay here.
But, Mom!
Zoey, please!
Oh, no. What are we gonna…
doooooooo?!
[cheering]
Ha. Look, they're running away.
We did it. We did it!
We did it!
Okay, fine, mostly you did it.
[squeaks]
[sighs] That could have gone better.
I have to go back
and save Mom and Gramps.
You can't go by yourself.
I'm coming with you.
And I'm coming too.
[barks]
You too are gonna need
all the help you can get.
But, Zara,
you don't have any super powers.
Neither do you.
Hm. That's true.
Look,
I don't know much about BubbleBeams
or GoSneaks,
but I do know about sound and music.
And I bet you that if you can make
your shoes super powered,
then you can help me
make my music super too.
Hmm…
If I can connect the guitar
to something that generates
echo beams of energy,
we just might have something!
Yeah!
[barks]
Good thing I brought my Boost Box
mini lab.
[barks]
[whines]
Zara, yes!
We did it, Zara!
I'm not Zara,
call me… EchoBeam.
[rock music playing]
[squawking]
Whoa!
[squawks]
Eat the sandwich. Eat the sandwich!
Doh! The sandwich, not the hot dog!
A hot dog is a sandwich!
By the billowing winds of Neptune,
it most certainly is not!
Yarr!
[mystery villain]
What is taking so long?
Is there a problem down there?
Yes there be a problem, all right.
This blubbering blowfish
thinks a hot dog is a sandwich!
-[air rushes]
-Whoa!
No problems at all.
The Beam Computer
is almost finished repairing
the Glowing Gizmo of Power!
Hm! Good.
I don't want to be late
for my grand entrance.
When we show up,
the Beam Team will follow
like moths to a flame, and--
-[chiming]
-Uh-oh.
What "uh-oh"?
Um, no "uh-oh." We're all good.
We seem to be-- [imitates static]
losing-- [imitates static]
recept… [screeches]
Talk to you later. Buh-bye.
It looks like StarBeam
and her little sidekick
are back for round two.
[typing]
And they brought a friend.
[low rumbling]
Uh-oh. Is that more Beam weapons?
Ha! It's the kids!
Wait, is that Zara?
Hi, Auntie WonderBeam.
Hey, Gramps.
I'm EchoBeam now.
-[barks]
-Boost and I worked up an upgrade.
I'd say so!
Impressive!
-[gasps]
-Oh, no!
I told you, you kids shouldn't be here!
Don't worry, we have a plan.
Uh-huh. The energy
that made these zap traps
is tuned to a particular sonic frequency.
Which means…
We can take 'em out
if we blast them with sound.
Let 'er rip, EchoBeam!
[barks]
It-- It didn't work.
Sometimes, all you need to do is…
take a moment, take a breath,
make a plan and try your best.
Try it!
[inhales, exhales]
I think…
a higher sonic frequency
might do the trick.
Something like…
[rock music playing]
[both]
She did it!
-Whoo-hoo!
-Ha ha!
Whoo!
All right, now let's get our house back!
[all] She did it!
Shiver me timbers,
they're coming this way!
Do something, you Miserable Marla!
[Riff barks]
[rock music playing]
Ohhhh!
Uh, I-I'm sorry,
are ye… rocking out?
[singing]
Oh, uh… sorry.
[rock music playing]
Ha ha ha! Rock and roll!
[gasps] They're inside the lighthouse!
Where are they?
[all] Beam Control!
[beeping]
Oh, no. We're locked out!
Not for long!
Come on, come on!
Come on…
come on…
[gasps] Yes!
Now let's go down to Beam Control
and show those baddies
who's in control.
Wait a sec, Riff.
You say here and guard my soup.
[grunts]
[chiming]
Yes!
The Glowing Gizmo of Power is fixed.
Ohh!
Blimey!
Do we have to do anything
to make it work,
or does it just--?
[evil laughter]
Pow, pow, pow!
Yarr, har, har, har!
I feel the power.
So… much… power!
[gasps] Jumpin' Geehosofat!
What's happening to them?
You'll never be able to stop us now,
Beam Team!
[evil laughter]
What just happened?
And where did they go?
-I can't believe they got away.
-For now.
The important thing is we're
working together as a team.
Whatever this thing is,
I think it gave them those
extra-strong super powers.
But where did it come from?
And what are they up to tonight?
I bet we can use the Beam Computer
to reprogram this thing
to take those powers away.
Boost, I like the way you think.
All right, Beam Team, here's the plan.
Boost, you and Gramps stay here
and work on this device
so we can turn those super villains
back to normal villains.
We'll go try to find them
and figure out what they're planning to do
with their new powers.
And stall them long enough
for you to reprogram that device
to help us save the day.
Hopefully before midnight,
because I really want to see
that heart drop.
Beam Team on three!
One, two…
Wait! I just remembered something.
You know what to do.
Well, uh, somebody's got to watch my soup.
Ava Peyton still coming to you live
from Somerset City Hall,
where we are just moments away
from the New Year's countdown.
And what are you looking forward to
this evening?
Um…
the dawning on a new era
in which all the villains
are in charge of everything.
[nervous laugh] Okay.
Wait a minute. Are we on TV?
[chuckles]
Hi, Mom!
[giggles]
[horn blows]
[screaming]
Aw, come on, friends,
this party is just getting started.
Aye!
You haven't even smelled
me new
super duper
stinky superpowers!
[evil laugh]
[grunts]
[loud rumble]
[laughs]
Can we make a cool entrance
or what?
Yeah, well, so can we.
[cheering]
Well, well, right on schedule.
It's over, Marla.
You can't beat the Beam Team.
Sorry,
but you're gonna have to go through
the Mean Team first.
Yeah!
Uh… when is the Mean Team
gonna get here?
[groans] We're the Mean Team!
[squeals]
-What?
-[crying] I'm sorry,
I-I-I've just never
been on a team before.
Can we just battle the good guys?
Please?!
Okay!
[strains]
Ahhh!
Ugh! [sighs]
Huh? [screams]
[grunts]
Hyah!
Huh?
[laughs]
[shouts]
-[guitar chord plays]
-Yeah!
Okay,
I know we be battling each other
and such,
but can I just say,
that be a very cool guitar.
Thanks!
-[grunts]
-[evil laughter]
This is not how I expected the family
to spend New Year's Eve.
You think Kipper's having
as much fun as we are?
[teeth chattering]
[caws]
[squawks]
[mystery villain] Excellent.
It won't be long now
before Somerset is ours.
All ours!
[evil cackle]
[grunting]
Oh! They're too strong for us
with their new superpowers!
We can't give up now.
We have to buy Gramps and Boost
some more time.
Whoa!
Whoa-oh-oh!
-[evil laugh]
-Ahhh!
[gasps]
[ominous music plays]
What is that?!
That is our leader,
someone who can help us defeat
the Beam Team
once and for all.
Hey, guys, I don't mean to rush you,
but these super-duper-powered villains
are pretty tough
and oh, by the way,
there's a big spaceship in the sky!
We managed to reconfigure the device.
It should take away their superpowers.
But it won't work
unless we find something
to replace the crushed crystal.
What kind of crystal?
We used the Beam Computer
to analyze the broken fragments.
It needs to be something clear and solid.
But strong enough to focus the energy.
Strong, clear, and solid.
Hmmm.
Huh?
What about that?
[gasps]
Yarr! Hoo, hoo, hoo!
Yarr!
[grunts]
[shouts]
[gasps]
[crowd gasps]
Ow!
[Marla laughs]
Face it,
you're never gonna be able to stop us.
Time for you do-gooders
to step aside once and for all.
It's our turn to rule!
[sniffs]
[coughing]
Fishbeard!
Can't you control yourself?
[Boost] StarBeam!
It's all ready to go.
Just connect the wires to the heart
and then press the button.
Then the bad guys will go back to normal.
Got it!
Hmmm.
What are you up to, StarBeam?
[gasps]
The Glowing Gizmo of Power!
On the top of City Hall.
StarBeam has the device!
Do not let her activate it!
[groans]
Ahhh!
What? Whoa-oh-oh!
[grunts]
Ahh!
WonderBeam!
You've got to get it
to the Heart of Somerset!
I don't think so.
AlphaBeam, catch!
Got it!
Huh?
[loud belch]
[groaning]
Don't got it.
[evil laugh]
Oh!
Guess it's up to me.
GoSneaks, let's go!
GoSneaks, let's bounce!
Whoa!
Ha! Made it.
[grunts]
Let go.
Hmm. Okay.
Huh?
Yah!
-[screams]
-[gasps]
EchoBeam, you have to get
that thing to the heart!
How? I don't have flying powers!
Just my guitar.
Use your guitar on Marla
so I can get out of this tornado!
[gasps] Right!
Let me see that!
Ha ha ha!
[grunts]
[laughs]
Rock and roll!
[gasps]
Oh, no!
Ah!
[screams]
[all screaming]
You can come down now!
I've got everybody trapped.
They can't stop us now.
[mystery villain]
Well, what about the guitar player?
Eh, don't worry about her.
Crusher smashed the guitar.
She doesn't have any powers.
The plan is working!
Now that we can finally overpower
the Beam Team,
nothing can stop us!
[worried chatter]
[screaming]
You have to do something!
[exhales]
Take a moment, take a breath,
make a plan and try your best.
Focus. You just need to focus.
What was that?
I… am… EchoBeam!
How is she doing that?
They smashed her guitar.
[Boost] Unless…
that super energy wasn't
coming from the guitar.
It was coming from Zara!
Whoa!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
So that means…
Zara has had super powers this whole time!
What are you waiting for?!
Stop her!
[war cry]
Ahhhh!
Yarr!
[rock music plays]
Yarr?
Yeah!
[rock music playing]
Ugh! Ahh!
Yeah! EchoBeam!
That's my granddaughter!
[cheering]
Ready for the big finish?
Ready!
-Uh-oh.
[powering up]
Whoa!
Ahhh!
[mutters]
Ahh!
Ugh!
Yeah!
[mystery villain]
Noooo!
They've ruined everything!
We lost our powers.
Gone! All gone.
[StarBeam]
Which means,
you three are no match
for the Beam Team.
Maybe so,
but you're forgetting about our super
powerful leader up there
in that space ship.
Whoa.
You guys are on your own.
See ya!
Ooo! Man overboard!
Um…
Okay, I guess I'm leaving too then.
Good day to you.
Ha!
-Yay!
-[man] They did it!
[cheering continues]
Nice job, Beam Team.
You did good, kid.
I knew you had it in you, Zara.
Thanks, Zoey.
It feels really good
to help save the day.
And to have real super powers.
And we did it all before the New Year.
[gasps] How long until midnight?
About 10 seconds.
Ah.
[gasps] Gah!
Ten seconds 'till midnight, everybody!
We need to drop the heart.
Bubble Beam Blast!
[townspeople]
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two…
one… Happy New Year!
[cheers]
[gasps] Kipper!
[panting]
[thuds]
[caws]
You did everything on this list?
In one day?
You must be exhausted!
[sighs]
Well, Cousin-- Uh, EchoBeam--
it sure feels good
knowing there's gonna be
another superhero out there
to help save the day.
Yeah, I think we're gonna need it.
Whoever gave that device to the bad guys
must have access to all kinds
of dangerous technology.
Enjoy your victory, Beam Team,
because I'll be back,
and next time,
I'll handle things myself.
Happy New Year, StarBeam.
[upbeat tune playing]
Wait!
You can't go to sleep
until you try my soup.
Oh, boy!
-Huh?
-[gasps]
[squawks]
[all laughing]
♪ It's time to shine ♪
-♪ Gonna save the world ♪
-♪ Fly ♪
-♪ Superhero girl ♪
-♪ Get tough ♪
♪ Small and mighty ♪
♪ It's time to shine ♪
♪ StarBeam ♪
♪ Oh ♪
-♪ It's time to shine ♪
-♪ Oh ♪
♪ StarBeam ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Small and mighty ♪
♪ It's time to shine ♪
♪ StarBeam ♪