Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
You ready?
Come on.
Do I have to do this?
A family wants you, Ben.
I really thought
you'd be excited.
I mean, I'm almost 18,
can I just stay here?
No, you can't, you need a home.
No, I don't.
Look Ben, there's four other
kids there just like you.
Mr magdalena's gonna be
a great foster parent
and he's someone you
can really trust,
can't you just try
to give him a chance?
Okay, come on, let's go.
Sam?
Yeah.
Ben, this is mr magdalena.
You can call me Sam.
It's Benny, right?
Just Ben.
Right, just Ben.
Oh yeah.
Thank you.
Should be good to go.
Look, I understand this
is kind of happening fast,
and it's gonna take a minute
to get used to things.
Yeah.
You of course, you
don't have to call me dad
or anything like that.
Yeah.
I get that you're older.
Thanks.
Well, it looks like
I got everything,
you guys are all set.
Great.
Well, let's take you home.
Sure, yeah.
Hey Sam, don't
worry, he'll do great.
Thanks.
I heard you got quite the
record of running away.
If you don't wanna
talk, it's fine.
I'm sorry, I just kind
of prefer to be alone.
I get that.
My wife, Evelyn, she
used to be like that too.
She also grew up in the
whole foster system.
Didn't have the best
experience to say the least.
But yeah, after we
met, we got together,
we wanted to start a family and
wanted to give back somehow,
then we thought
becoming foster parents,
it's kind of the best scenario.
It's just me now though,
it's been that way for
the past six months.
You're gonna love
the group though,
let me tell you, those
kids are a cracker.
They're a handful,
but you'll love them.
And you are just in
time to help us unload.
Hey Sam, is that the new kid?
Yup, this is Ben.
Hey man.
Hey, hi.
Come here.
Why don't you give
him a tour, Rick,
show him around the
house and all that.
Come back once you're done.
Sure thing.
So, welcome home.
Thanks.
Do you get any more
bags or stuff, I can-
- this is all I have.
Cool, just before
we go in though,
I just need to talk to
you about something,
pineapple or no pineapple?
I'm sorry?
Pineapple or no
pineapple on pizza.
This is just an determine
whether we make you
sleep outside for the
first night or not.
Ben, it's a joke.
We're not that cruel, but we
are gonna get pizza later,
I was thinking
pineapples, no pineapples?
Sorry, no, no, no
pineapple on pizza.
Good man, come on.
Hey, ozzy, comes say
hi to the new kid.
You're the kid who
runs away a lot, right?
I guess, yeah.
Well, that's good.
Means we don't got to
worry about you for long.
Jeez, ozzy, at least pretend
not to be a dick for a bit.
Hey man.
Yeah, whatever.
I mean, why?
It's nice to see a
new face around here.
Plus it be good to
have extra help-
- we're doing just fine.
Don't mind him, oz,
he's always like that.
Oh well, don't
think I'm gonna have
much trouble remembering him.
That was Morgan by the way.
Oh yeah, she seems cool.
And do not get on her bad side.
Ozzy will be the least of
your problems if that happens.
Come on.
That's pretty cool, huh?
Oh, yeah.
There's a room upstairs for you.
Well.
Hey Rick.
Yeah.
Who's that?
Oh, that's just Bella,
she's the new kid before you.
She likes to be alone
a lot, now she's cool.
There you go.
We didn't have a mattress.
Yeah, I can tell.
You and Izzy are the
only ones up here,
so it should be pretty
quiet most of the time.
I'll be downstairs.
Oscar, who you texting?
I think his girlfriend.
Does he have a girlfriend?
I think he has a girlfriend.
I think his date didn't
go well the other night.
Ozzy's not said anything.
Hey Ben.
Wanna join?
I just came to get a slice.
Pineapple or no?
I already asked him, he said no.
You said no?
Thought you were cool.
Hey Sam.
Hey guys.
Hey Ben, warming up to them?
Slowly.
Did Isabella come eat?
I'm not sure.
Well, if you're headed back up,
do you mind taking her a slice?
Yeah, no problem.
Thanks.
Watch your head.
Hi.
I brought you a slice
of pizza if you want it?
Oh, I'm not that
hungry, but thanks.
All good, I'm sure
one of them will eat it.
Most likely.
I'm Isabella, by the way.
I'm so sorry, I'm Ben.
Feel at home yet?
I feel this is the home I
was always meant to be with.
Oh really?
Yeah, yeah,
just couldn't be better.
Oh, we're that bad, huh?
Well, I don't know about
you yet, we just met.
We did, but I can
definitely tell you're lying.
It's not what I mean,
you guys seem really cool.
It's just-
- hey, I get it can be weird
living with a different
family, we all do.
Yeah, I actually never-
something up there?
There shouldn't be.
You got a flashlight?
What's all this?
Not ours, whoever
lived here before
must've left it behind.
Oh, just left it behind.
Did you say something?
What?
No.
Oh.
Did you hear that?
No.
It's coming from the-
What are you guys doing?
Didn't here you come up.
Did I seriously scare you?
You kind of did.
What's going on up here, guys?
That's what I'm
trying to figure out.
We heard something up
here, so we decided to look.
And you weren't
gonna tell anyone?
Yeah, I mean, what if
there was a psychopath
who's been living
up here for years
and runs through the
walls, eating our food
and just wants to
murder us in our sleep?
What kind of horrible
experiences have you had?
Okay, I'm just
saying, never know.
Okay, what are you looking at?
Yeah, that's not creepy at all.
Who would want that?
I don't know.
Okay, can we actually
get down though,
it smells like shit up here?
Just leave that here, please.
I guess we'll never know.
Come on.
Isabella?
Ben, what are you doing?
Were you down here a second ago?
No, why?
I thought I saw.
Why you up anyways?
You weren't exactly quiet.
What are you doing?
Nothing, I just found this.
Maybe they were playing
and just left it there.
Ben.
What?
What the hell are you two doing?
I'm sorry, I thought I
left something down here
and I asked if she
could help me find it.
At 3:00 in the morning.
What could be so important
at three in the morning?
Go to bed.
Ben, you need to
eat, come on get up.
Hey Ben, come on, we're
gonna go get breakfast.
Was that really necessary?
Hey, you didn't wake up
the first time we did it.
You made me do it.
Okay look, we're all
extremely hungry,
and I kind of want
some pancakes,
so I'm gonna do what
it takes to get you up.
You're a piece of
shit, you know that?
Yeah, come on sleepy head.
Dude, what are you doing?
I'm sorry, I was-
- Rick's losing his
mind, we gotta go.
Where's Izzy?
Speak of the devil.
Come on.
Dude, get your ass over here.
I'm sorry.
- I want pancakes.
- I'm coming, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
So you guys excited to start
a new school next week, again?
It's been the third move,
so kind of getting used to it.
As long as the
baseball team's good.
Yeah, well, try not to get
kicked off the team again,
how about that?
The guy wanted his ass kicked.
The way I remember it,
you were the one getting
your handed to you.
It was pretty funny.
Isabella.
Ow.
Sorry.
Hey, what happened last night?
I don't know.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
You sure?
'Cause you've been in a
pissy mood all morning.
Sorry Izzy, but I gotta
agree with him, what's wrong?
That doll didn't scare
you that bad, did it?
What doll?
They found a doll in
the attic yesterday.
Scariest shit
I've ever seen, man.
You're scared of a toy?
Yeah a toy that probably
belonged to a demon.
Where's this doll now?
Still up there, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Well, we should clear
that space out today anyway.
Maybe there's some Bible stuff.
It's probably
all worthless, Sam.
Well, we don't know
that until we look, huh?
I don't think any of this is
gonna be worth anything, Sam.
Probably not.
Hey, you never know, we
could end up getting lucky.
Izzy-
- if you're gonna ask me
if I'm okay, I'm fine.
Look, I know we met
literally last night,
but I can tell you're lying.
What did you see?
Whatever it was, I'm
sure it wasn't real.
Okay, so can we drop it?
Drop it?
You're look like you're
about to pass out.
I said drop it, Ben.
Whoops.
I'm guessing that's the
doll you were talking about?
Pretty, isn't it?
Yup.
You should just get rid of it.
Well, hold on,
remember we can sell it.
No, actually, I agree
with Izzy on this one,
I think we should just
probably get rid of it.
Why?
Scares you?
Okay, how does that not
make you shit our pants?
Because it's a toy, it's
not going to do anything.
Well, that's two
for stay, two for go.
So Ben, you're the
tiebreaker, what do you say?
Let's get rid of it.
All right, fair's fair.
Rick, take it outside.
Why do I have to do it?
Because you're the
one that dropped it
and voted it out, dumb ass.
They voted the same, so.
You're closer.
Fine, fine, I'll do it, fine.
You suck.
The hell is that?
It's a doll they found.
God, that's creepy.
Hey man, do you wanna come up
and help sort
stuff in the attic?
Ozzy?
Oscar?
What the hell was that?
Oh my god,
what the hell did you do?
I don't know.
Hey, look at me, look at me.
Look at me.
Look at me, it's okay.
You're okay.
Rick, what happened?
Rick, talk to me, what
happened, what happened?
I saw a lady.
And she grabbed my neck.
Okay, hey, look
at me, look at me.
You're okay, right?
You're okay, bud.
Let's get you inside, all
right, let's get you inside.
Come on, come on.
Morgan, can you
grab an ice pack?
I got you.
You're okay.
Hey Rick.
You okay?
Just leave him, Morgan.
He's gonna be fine.
That was fast.
Yeah, well, the police station's
only a few blocks away.
So what happened?
I reported it, I gave
them a description,
they said they would start
a search party as
soon as possible.
Do they know who
they're looking for?
Described it the
best I could, Morgan.
Do they know where to start?
Do they know anything right now?
Morgan, they're the police,
they handle this sort of thing.
Look, I know you're
worried, I am too,
but they'll figure it out.
All right guys, well, I
start a new job tomorrow,
gotta be there at 6:00 am.
So while I'm gone, look
after Rick, will you?
Yeah, okay.
You're starting
that job already?
Someone's gotta pay the bills.
Is there anything
we can do to help?
Like you care.
Look, man, I'm just
trying to be helpful.
Well, you're not.
What's your problem?
What?
What do you mean what?
Why are you being
such an asshole?
Oh, I'm the asshole?
Yes.
I don't get what your deal
is, he didn't nothing wrong.
Exactly, he did nothing.
Okay.
You did nothing.
Just stood there
looking like an idiot
while Rick was losing his shit.
Ozzy.
Now it makes a little
more sense why you're alone.
Oscar.
All right, fine.
Ben, i-
- it's okay.
Sorry.
New watch?
No.
It belonged to my father.
It's all I have
left of my parents.
What were they like?
They're kind, caring.
They tried their best.
Hey, don't let what
he said get to you.
Just give him time,
he'll warm up to you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey man.
Hey.
Can't sleep either?
Guess not.
Me neither.
I know everyone
thinks I'm crazy,
but I understand, I
don't know what happened.
Hey, hey, I'm sure
no one thinks that.
Where you going?
Just about to go on a walk.
At 2:00 am with a backpack?
Snacks?
You're leaving.
I don't belong here, Rick,
this whole family
thing, it isn't for me.
Why?
It's barely been two days.
Exactly, it's
barely been two days
and one of you already hates me.
That one up there
is acting all weird.
And you, you're-
- what?
I barely know any of you.
We quite literally just met,
why do you care that I leaving?
I mean, 'cause you're one of us.
No, I'm not.
Look, look, no
one's gonna miss me.
You'll forget I even existed,
you'll have one less
person to worry about.
And then what?
You're going to spend the
rest of your life alone
missing the chance to
be a part of a family?
Which a lot of foster kids
our age don't get, by the way.
And just not care
about anybody else?
That doesn't sound too bad.
Okay.
Okay, okay, how about this?
Just stay one more day
to see how it goes.
Dude, come on, man, come on.
If you don't know,
just stay one more day
and see how it goes,
you don't like it, you leave.
Fine.
Fine, one more
day, one more day.
One more day.
One more day, one more day.
You do know I'm gonna
prove you wrong.
Don't push it, don't push it.
Sorry.
Hey, hey man.
Hey.
Gonna do that every time?
Oh, sorry, just me being polite.
Yeah.
Hey, you feeling better?
Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
Good, good.
Hey, I was actually
thinking we play this game,
it's kind of like a
team-building exercise thing.
Okay, so basically one
person has the bomb
and the other person
has the instructions
on how to be disabled the bomb.
It's super fun.
I think I'm gonna take
a walk, Rick, wanna join?
Actually, is it okay
if I sit this one out?
Okay.
Maybe Ben can join you?
Oh no.
Actually, sure.
I just got-
- well, I actually
insist, so come on.
So, do you think he
actually imagined it?
Look, I'm only gonna
ask you this once.
Got it?
Are you messing with him?
What?
Is this some stupid
joke you pulled?
'Cause if it is, you need
to tell me right now.
Okay, what are
you talking about?
Piece of paper, that wasn't you?
What piece of paper?
What joke?
What are you talking about?
Rick found that on the floor
in his room this morning.
Ben, I need you to promise me
that you didn't do this
because this isn't funny.
I promise you this wasn't me.
Why would I leave
this piece of paper
with this word on it anyways?
Besides, he didn't seem
too freaked out just now.
He thinks someone's
playing a sick joke on him,
so he's not taking it seriously.
Besides, I'm usually the one
who does most of
the worrying anyway.
Well, what if it is just a joke?
Can't be.
Why not?
When Rick was little,
his real mom and dad
took him to the mall.
They took him to
the big toy store,
got him what he wanted,
when he wasn't looking,
they walked away.
They left him there.
Why?
He doesn't know.
He just remembers feeling
lost, scared, abandoned.
Well, that still doesn't explain
why can't just be a sick joke.
'Cause I'm the only person
who's ever told that story to.
I know you couldn't have
done this, I'm just worried.
Stupid as he is sometimes,
he's always been there.
I don't want him to
feel like that again.
Seems like he trusts you a lot.
So why you telling me?
'Cause he trusts you too.
To be honest, I'm not sure why,
you've only been here two days.
Yeah.
So what do you
think is going on?
I mean, first is he starts
acting all weird for no reason.
And now Rick thinks
he saw a woman,
maybe he is actually
losing his mind.
I don't think he is.
What do you mean?
The first night I got here,
I saw someone walk around
the house with the doll.
What?
Izzy and I saw someone in
the window that night too.
And it looked like a woman.
Ben, are you serious?
It sounds insane, I know.
Why didn't you
say anything sooner?
Would you really
have believed me
if I told you there
was a mysterious lady
walking around the
house with the doll?
Okay, fair enough.
Exactly.
So what are you saying?
Are you saying that there's
a person in our house
or are you saying that
our house is haunted?
All I'm saying is it's
pretty weird for Rick
and I to have possibly
seen the same person.
So what do we do?
Well, there is still one place
we might be able
to find something.
What exactly
are we looking for again?
Anything that looks
older, creepy pretty much
or anything that looks
like what you saw.
Okay, if you think I
actually saw a ghost,
that's the stupidest
thing I've ever heard.
Oh, you shouldn't be talking
considering you're
afraid of a child's toy.
How long do you plan
on rubbing that in?
Till you die.
Right.
Anything?
Just some old photographs.
What do you think they are?
I'm not sure, maybe
they're the people
who lived here before us?
Some have dates on
the back of them,
like this one's
from June 7th, 1985.
And this one's from
December 26th, 1973.
Why would they
leave all this behind?
That's what I'm wondering.
Ben, do you think we
really saw something?
What if we did just imagine it?
I thought we did too,
it doesn't make sense
for us all imagine
the same thing.
Whoa, guys, look at this.
What the hell?
Guess someone
really likes dolls.
And what's all this?
Just some more old papers.
What does it say?
They're journal entries.
Maybe they're from
whoever lived here last.
No.
Guys, whoever wrote this,
the date they put was 1692.
May 5th, 1692,
fire rages within me.
They say what I've
done is a curse.
They mock me for it,
call me inhuman, a demon.
They will not understand
that what I've done
is not a curse, but
rather a gift of life.
They believe they can
burn all of my work,
destroy what I've created,
but I won't let them,
if they come from me, I will
set the fires of hell on them.
Whoa.
What?
They spelled inhuman wrong.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Yeah, look.
Oh yeah, they really did.
These all have a lot
of spelling mistakes.
People in the 1600s weren't
exactly the most intelligent,
I guess it makes sense.
What are you guys doing?
I mean, that was-
- terrible.
Amazing.
I mean, bravo.
Okay, yeah.
Whatever, all right.
What is all this?
This is stuff that's
been sitting in a suitcase
in the attic for
about 300 years.
And still smells better
than you right now, so-
- shut up.
Oh, oh, seriously though,
take a shower or something.
Whoa, whose are these?
Oh, those were also in the case.
So what, now there's four dolls?
Well, three, I put the
other one in the trash.
Why are you guys going
through the stuff anyways,
I thought Sam said
to wait for him.
Well, we think that
maybe whatever Rick saw
might have something
to do with this stuff.
So what, you guys think
our place is haunted now?
Ben.
What's wrong?
Look.
What's it say?
December 1st, 1692,
there was a great sickness
in the world, one
so cruel and evil,
it is willing to
leave its innocent
children to suffer
and feel hopeless.
A child, which I found today
believed he would
never feel loved
for his mother
had abandoned him.
He thought no one could
save him but I did,
this child along with my own
will never have
to endure the pain
and the evil of this world,
they shall always be with me.
Everyone on the
outside calls me sick,
evil, a witch, but
they know nothing.
They never will.
They can hang me,
burn me, torture me,
I will always care
for my children,
for I will always have them
tied to the end of my strings.
What the hell was that?
That came from my room.
Okay, this is one
of you guys, right?
Someone doing a prank?
What?
I'm not stupid, this
is one of you guys.
No it wasn't.
This is bullshit.
No, no Oscar.
Ozzy wait, don't go up there.
Don't go up there.
Ozzy.
Yeah, pretty funny guys.
Which one do you sit
the doll in there?
So who was it?
That wasn't any of us.
Really?
'Cause my money's on you.
You know what?
Screw this.
- No, no, Morgan.
- Stop.
None of this is real, this
is all just some stupid joke.
No, Morgan.
Look, see?
Just a stupid toy.
Morgan.
Hey, open the door.
I'm trying.
Morgan.
Open the door, Morgan.
Guys.
Hey, hey, hey, Morgan.
Hey, move.
Move.
No, no, no, Morgan,
Morgan, open the door.
Morgan.
It's me, it's me.
It's okay.
So you're saying
there's an evil doll
and a woman in a red dress
walking around our house.
Haunting us right now?
When you say it like that,
it makes us sound stupid.
Okay, look guys, I
know since Evelyn died,
it hasn't been easy and we've
been moving place to place,
I've had to leave
at least five years-
- no, Sam, we're not
imagining things.
Ben and I saw a
woman in the window.
Rick said he saw another woman.
And now Morgan saying
she saw the same one.
And on top of that, we found
a case full of creepy stuff,
I mean, we're not
making this up.
Ben, is it true?
Why are you asking him?
What's wrong with me asking him?
Why do you hate me so much?
Ever since I got here,
you've done nothing
but talk shit about me.
If I've done something
wrong, I'm sorry.
Now is there any
way we can help-
- runaway, like you always
do, that would help a lot.
Oscar, what the hell
is wrong with you?
He's family now, you
got a problem with that,
you come talk to
me, I'm always here.
That's the thing,
Sam, you're not.
You're not always here.
You never listen.
I told you so many
times after Evelyn died,
don't take him in.
You haven't been able
to keep a steady job,
you've had to move
from place to place,
and now you're just adding
another mouth to feed.
Watch it, Oscar.
He's been acting more
like family than you have.
What?
You heard me.
Okay guys, this
is an important right now.
Oh, so what?
Guy's been here for two days
and what, he's
your boyfriend now?
He's my brother and so are you,
but you haven't even
given him a chance-
- a chance to do what?
Last thing we need in this
house is another runaway.
What?
Oh, she didn't tell you?
She ran away from her
home just like you.
I was a kid when that happened.
Well, you haven't changed.
Guys, come on.
You're still that little kid
who's too stupid to
think for themselves.
Watch it.
Or what?
Maybe you really are the
reason your mom killed herself.
Izzy.
Izzy, it's me.
I don't know if you can hear me
or if you're ignoring
me, which is fine too.
But I'm sorry.
I was seven when it happened.
I was playing outside
with my friends,
we had this game where we
would jump over a skateboard
we found with our scooters.
I used to record
everything then.
We thought it was so funny
when we would just fall.
That was the last
time I saw them.
After that I went
inside to show my mom.
When I found her,
she was injecting herself with something.
She was lying on the floor
reaching her hand out to me.
She asked me to help her.
I just got so scared
because of how she looked.
And I ran.
And I kept thinking to myself,
what have you stayed
and not so scared
and had you weren't so stupid,
you could've saved her.
I never knew my parents.
I know I told you earlier
that they were kind and caring,
but that's just
how I imagine them,
and all they left
me was this watch.
And I waited and I
watched time pass
by on this stupid watch
and all I did was wait
for them to come back.
When I was adopted for the
first time, I hated it,
I was so used to being on my own
and I hated when it changed.
So I ran.
Did the same thing
with the next one.
How come you
haven't left us yet?
To be honest, I don't know.
I know I'm not going to.
Hey guys, there's something.
Am I interrupting anything?
No.
Are you sure-
- no, you're okay.
- You're fine.
Okay, cool.
Because there is actually
something I got to show you guys.
Both of you.
Come on.
Okay, I was reading the
entries you made around earlier
and I noticed something.
In each one of these, it was
dated in either 1692 or 1693.
And then on this one, she said,
"they call me sick,
evil, a witch."
Guys what happened
in 1692 and 1693,
the Salem witch trials.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I looked it up.
So what are you saying
that this person is a witch?
Maybe.
But I think it's the
woman we've been seeing.
How is that possible?
This was hundreds of years ago.
Each person in this
room has seen her.
Okay, earlier today we saw a
door opening close on its own.
I don't think the
idea of a witch
sounds impossible right now.
Well, is there anything else?
After that she wrote, "I will
always care for my children",
"five of them tied to
the end of my strings."
What do you think that means?
Hold on, you're
saying that's a person?
Wild guess.
How would you even
do something like that?
Okay, I'm not sure, but
I have this feeling that.
Hey.
Is she dead yet.
Hello, who are you?
Where am I?
Hey.
Hey, it's okay.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Where did you come from?
So I'm just gonna
ask one more time
to make sure before I go,
do you have any idea where
he could have come from?
No, not exactly sure
how he got in the house
in the first place.
Well, I spoke with
a kid and he said,
apparently he's been
here the whole time.
Sure you don't have anybody
else you're hiding in here?
No, we weren't hiding
anyone in the first place.
Look, officer, if you
don't mind me asking,
did he tell you his name?
Yeah.
John marsh.
Ring any bells?
No.
Well, I'm gonna have to
take him into the station,
gonna see if anybody's
looking for him.
Thank you, officer.
Oh, and don't leave
town until we fix this.
What are you looking at?
I googled his name.
Find anything?
Yeah.
Anyone wanna explain to me
how a random kid got in here?
I'm thinking of something
to do with the doll.
Stop it, Rick.
What?
Just stop with
this whole doll thing
and tell me what the hell
is it going on with you?
No, we told you, we found-
- I'm not talking
about all that.
What's wrong with you guys?
And who hell was that kid?
Sam.
Look, I'm trying here.
Just pick this crap up.
Is there anything we can do?
Leave him, let him
breathe for a while.
Let's just call it a night and
figure the rest out tomorrow.
I don't think any of us are
getting any sleep tonight.
Better than sitting
here and doing nothing.
What if something happens?
What if we all slept
out here tonight?
That way we're still together.
Where are you going?
To sleep in my own bed.
Morgan.
Guys.
This is a bad idea.
Afternoon.
What time is it?
1:00.
Was getting a bit worried,
started to think you died.
You got worried about me?
Didn't wanna carry out the body.
Hey, where's Rick?
I don't know.
Well, did you see him?
Where's Sam?
No, I haven't seen him.
And Sam left for work hours ago.
Well, did Rick go with him?
I have no idea.
So you don't know
if Rick left with Sam?
I already told you,
I haven't seen him.
Guys, guys,
guys, wake up, wake up.
Rick's not here.
What?
Rick, he's gone.
Oscar, can you please
help me look for him?
I already told you
I haven't seen him.
Have you really forgotten
everything that's been going on?
No I haven't, but-
- then what's the problem?
Can you just predict you
hate me for 10 minutes
and help me look for him?
Please.
All right, fine.
I really don't know
where he could be,
he's probably just
goofing off somewhere.
Where are the dolls?
We have to find him now.
What do we do?
Call Sam.
It's his phone.
Hey Morgan.
Sam, you need to come home.
I'm already on my way home.
I told you guys I had
a short day today.
Something wrong?
Rick's missing.
What do you mean his missing?
He's-
Morgan?
Yeah, I'm here, his-
Morgan, are you okay?
Izzy.
What the hell was that?
It's her, just go, go.
Hey.
Hey, hey, you okay?
Okay.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
I'll come back.
Get her out of here.
I can take her, go.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come
on, let's go, let's go.
What happened?
The woman.
Morgan, honey?
Hey.
We gotta get her to a hospital.
No, everyone's still inside.
Son of a bitch.
What do we do?
I don't know.
Come on, come on.
Oscar, come on, let's go.
Anything?
His not in the house.
So what's gonna happen?
They're sending
out a search party.
We should go with them.
They won't let us leave
until they find him.
We can't just sit
here and do nothing.
Okay, maybe they
don't let us go,
but why not you?
You're the father.
I'm not his real father.
Sam, what did they tell you?
Child services is
getting involved.
They wanna put you guys
back in the foster system.
What does that mean?
It means they'll
take us away from Sam
and we'll all be separated.
If they don't find
him in 24 hours,
that's exactly what will happen.
I'm sorry.
You have to try.
The second night I was
here, I tried to leave.
I didn't wanna have anything
to do with you guys,
so I tried to runaway.
That's really heartwarming, Ben.
Rick asked me if I wanted
spend my whole life alone,
no family, no friends,
no one to care for.
And I just keep thinking, what
if I hadn't listened to him?
He didn't quit on me and
I'm not going to quit on him
when he needs us the most.
Come on guys.
His right.
We have to try.
We all know Rick
would do the same.
Wait.
Wait, hold on, you
just agreed with me?
Get over it.
Well, what else is
there that we can do?
You know what?
If Rick's not in the house,
where else can he be?
Well, he has to be at the house,
Ben found his phone upstairs.
The cops just said
they looked there.
Besides, even if
we were to go back,
the witch was able to
pick us off one by one,
how do we get past her?
We saw what she can do.
She's right, she knew
how to separate us.
She attacked us one by one
and she knew what
we would do next.
"Tied to the ends
of my strings."
What?
That's it.
The doll.
What if we broke the doll?
Wait, how would we do that?
I don't know, smash it?
How do we know that would work?
The kid, the one
from last night.
Rick looked up his name,
apparently the kid's family
was extremely wealthy
and the last known member
of the family line
died in the 1700s.
So he was one of
the kids she took.
Maybe.
And you breaking
the doll let him out.
How'd you know that was
going to work, by the way?
Wild guess.
Okay, but how do we
get past the burnt kid?
Burnt kid?
Yeah, the kid
that was all burned,
the kid that was
crawling towards me,
trying to end my life, that kid.
You guys serious?
Ben, you were up there with
me, you didn't see that?
I didn't.
So what, she's making
us see things now?
Actually, maybe.
Morgan, when Rick was attacked,
you said he felt like he did
when he was at the store?
Yeah.
Well, Oscar, was there
ever a moment in your life
where you saw this burnt kid?
Well, the whole reason I
was put into the foster system
was because my family
was killed in a fire.
I was the only one
who made it out.
So she's controlling
what we see.
But that doesn't help us
figure out where Rick is.
Yes, it does.
Maybe the police did
look in the right spot,
but she just made them
see something else.
We have to go back.
And this time, we know that
whatever we see isn't real.
We stick together,
that's the only way
we're gonna find him.
Come on guys.
Wait, wait, okay, hold on.
Where am I during all this?
They're not just going to
let you leave, much less me.
I think I know of
a way you can help.
Excuse me, officer.
How's it going?
Remember me?
Of course you do.
Anyway, so I got a bit of
a stomach issue happening,
you ever feel like the
insides of your stomach
are just slowly dying?
Of course you
don't, look at you,
perfect specimen like yourself?
Nah.
But, my stomach is about to
go through the gates of hell
and I was just hoping you
could help me out with that?
The bathroom is over there.
Right, you see,
I don't necessarily
have to use the bathroom,
I guess I was just wanting
to get your advice.
We're not really qualified
to give that type of advice.
Sure you are.
Come on.
Strapping officer like
yourself, what do you bench?
400?
Don't touch me.
Okay, okay.
All right.
Well, yeah, I just
figured you two,
you're out in the
field, professionals,
maybe you had lunch,
you got the enchiladas,
you know you shouldn't
have got the enchiladas,
but you did anyway.
So you're at this house
and all of a sudden,
"ooh, what is that?"
"It's a rumble in my stomach."
And you ask yourself,
"who do I call?"
"911?"
You are 911.
So I just figured that
maybe you two pros
just might know a solution.
We have to go.
You don't say?
Yeah.
Hey, hey.
Let's go, let's go.
Hey.
Remember, whatever we
see in there isn't real.
Stick together and
we'll find him.
Where do we go?
Upstairs, that's where
we found his phone.
Okay.
Dad?
Dad.
Go.
Get Morgan.
No.
- That was my dad.
- No, it's not.
She's making you see it.
It's not real.
Hey, it's not real.
Hit it.
Where?
Anywhere.
I don't wanna hit you.
Izzy.
Shit.
Sorry.
Ozzy.
Oscar.
Hey, hey.
I think you got it.
Okay.
Remind me not to
piss you off again.
So what now?
His not up here.
There's still
one place we haven't looked.
Where?
She brought them back up here.
He's not here.
He has to be.
What are you thinking?
You wanna see her, you have
to get her attention, right?
What are you doing?
Getting their attention,
it's the only way
we're gonna find him.
No.
No, no.
Izzy.
Izzy?
Hey, hey, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, wake up.
Nothing.
You are nothing.
You will always have nothing.
Come to me, I can
give you a family.
No.
You can't trick me anymore.
You got it.
Okay, now destroy it.
Hey.
Heads up.
Izzy.
No.
Rick.
Hey.
Hey, hey, come on, man.
Wake up.
Wake up, Rick.
- Come on.
- Come on, wake up.
Come on man, wake up.
Come on, Rick.
Come on man, come on.
Come on Rick, wake up.
- Come on.
- Wake up, Rick.
Who the hell did that?
What the hell was that?
Hey man.
Come here.
Get in here.
I missed you guys.
Okay, Rick, what
are you talking about?
You're not making sense.
Is there a red wire?
No.
Is there a blue wire?
Yes.
Are there any white wires?
No.
Cut the blue wire.
We blew up.
Son of a bitch.
What?
You told me to
cut the blue wire.
How many wires were there?
There were four.
You literally told
me five earlier.
Oh my god, can you
two shut up already.
He gave me the wrong information
and now we're dead.
Okay, now it's my
fault you didn't listen.
Listen man, I'm
telling you four wires.
Hey, don't you
guys start at 8:00?
We have a late start on Fridays.
Oh, what time you start then?
10:00.
It's 9:30.
Oh shit.
All right, we are off.
- See you tonight, Sam.
- See you Sam.
See ya.
What's wrong?
There's actually
something I got to do.
Okay, but hurry up,
we're running late.
Yeah.
Hey, Sam.
Yeah, what's up?
I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
For what?
When you brought me home,
you told me about everything
you did for everyone
and about Evelyn, and I
never got to say I'm sorry.
She would've really like to you.
I'm sure I would've
loved her too.
Hey, Ben.
Yeah, yeah, I'm on my way.
See you later, Sam.
See you.
So can I get a bed now?