.
[woman vocalizing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[mellow music]
[siren wailing]
[zipper whirrs]
[birds chirping]
Ready when you are, Ms. King.
Thank you.
I'll be right there.
Students,
we are honored to have our guest speaker with us today.
She made waves with her early backing
of Generation Coders, a groundbreaking company
that empowers children to become AI pioneers.
Not only is she an influential investor in the tech industry,
she's a visionary leader with a track record
of nurturing innovations into global success stories.
It is my pleasure to welcome Ms. Veronica King.
[applauding]
Thank you.
It inspires me to be here as well.
You were the driving force of the next wave of technology.
It is important to learn early how to invest in...
Nice of you to join us, Mike.
As I was saying,
I, uh...
it is important to learn early
how to invest in low-risk portfolios.
-Good to meet you. -Yeah, nice to meet you, too.
[camera clicks]
Thank you.
Thank you so much for having me. It was a pleasure.
Ms. King...
I feel really bad for interrupting your presentation,
so I wanted to say sorry about that.
It's not a problem.
Mike Sheppard.
Hi, Mike.
I've been following your career since you invested
in this finance app I use, JumpFunder.
Don't tell my friends, but I'm kind of a fan.
[chuckles] I won't tell anyone.
Okay, so, look, I'm actually working on an app myself
to promote healthier lifestyles.
Would you by chance be offering any mentorship programs?
No, sorry, not at the moment,
but definitely keep going with that idea.
It sounds like a game-changer.
Well, it was worth a shot. Thanks anyway.
Really great presentation too, by the way.
Thank you.
Greg, I can't believe how much he puts me
in the mind of Jayson.
It's not necessary looks.
It's his mannerism.
[Veronica] He has such a confidence in himself.
You sure putting yourself in that environment is a good idea?
It feels good knowing that I'm helping kids Jayson's age.
[Greg] Understood.
And you've been handling everything very well.
It's just that I wouldn't want to see you
go back into that dark period.
[Greg] I wouldn't mention it if I didn't care about you.
I know. Come by later?
You got it.
Ooh.
Here we go. [gasps] There's something on your face.
[sighs] Bye.
Excuse me.
Oh, you're Veronica King.
I watched your interview last week on TEDtime Live.
Thank you.
I couldn't help but notice your companion.
Babies. [chuckles]
No sense in being shy about the truth.
When it comes to my age, you stop worrying about
what people think and focus on being happy.
And those two... [sighs] make mama very happy. [chuckles]
You're dating both of them.
Oh, no, I ditched that.
I thought I was looking for love,
but really, I just wanted companionship.
So now I focus on the sugar baby apps.
It's kind of like a "pay-to-play" relationship.
Like picking from a menu.
-What's the name of the app? -[chuckles]
[Andrew] Uh, yes, I was just checking in
to make sure we were still good for 1:00.
-Sugar Finders. -Yes.
-Uh. -What?
This app. Have you heard of it?
Well, a little too young to be a sugar daddy.
So, it's for older people?
Yeah, specifically,
one looking for the company of a much younger persuasion.
You know, you pay them for their time,
attention, affection, sex, whatever you need.
You interested in that?
What in the world would I do with a sugar baby? No.
I think it would be a potential investment opportunity.
Just business.
My shero.
All business, all the time. [chuckles]
Just don't forget about me
when you're handing out promotions.
Of course.
Run some reports for me on this app.
If it's that popular, I think it could be worth looking into.
[engine revving]
[doorbell rings]
[door opens]
[whimsical music]
Beverly, I'm glad you're here.
I missed you.
I'm gonna cut right to the chase.
What's up?
It's clear that your personal life
has become a distraction
from your responsibilities to me.
I'm trying the best I can.
I'm juggling you, school, and everything.
Oh, and I wish you well with your... education,
but I'm terminating this agreement.
Whoa, whoa. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're right, okay?
Let me make it up to you. What I gotta do?
[chuckles] Nothing my new sugar baby can't handle, dear.
Wait, what about the rest of my money?
You still owe me eight grand.
You get paid for our service when you complete the service.
Our business has concluded,
and I don't owe you another penny.
Good luck, Mike.
[exhales]
[Gia] Do you think she figured out
we were dating and not roommates?
[Mike] I doubt it.
Beverly was too damn clingy anyway.
Forget her, I'll find somebody else.
Babe, we needed that income.
We have tuition due in two weeks.
I know, I know.
-Do you think I need to-- -No.
We agreed that I would do these arrangements,
so you won't be involved in anything dangerous.
Look, maybe I can pick up a few more hours tutoring.
I want to help you, okay?
I don't want this to be too much on you.
Babe, I got it, all right?
I'll make sure I do what I gotta do
to take care of us, I promise.
You want a slice of cheesecake
from that bakery you like on campus?
-I love you. -I love you more.
[dramatic music]
[doorbell rings]
Coming.
-Good evening. -[creaks]
I got some reports on the Sugar Finders app
like you asked.
[Greg] Hey-hey, Andrew.
[laughs]
-Mm. -Mm. [chuckles]
I'm on call tonight, so I gotta head out.
You promise you call me if you need anything?
Of course, as I always do.
Mm-hmm.
Have a good night, Andrew.
Okay, let me see what you have.
[Andrew] You and Greg seem pretty close.
Greg is and always will be my best friend, that's it.
I just mean it's nice to see
a man putting a smile on your face.
Even though everything happened with your husband
before I came around,
I've seen the toll it's taken on you.
What'd you find out about the app?
Numbers look promising.
In the first year,
they're anticipating to generate five million in revenue
with a gross profit margin of 75%.
Their user acquisition is aggressive,
but we have to trust market research.
Very true, especially with a startup so new.
It would be ideal if we could locate one of their users,
you know, maybe talk to them, get some first-hand knowledge.
-What are you doing? -A field test.
I need to find out for myself how this thing works.
Simplistic interface,
-visually appealing... -Yep.
...organized, unique scheduling features...
in-app messaging.
I'm curious if--
What, what's wrong?
Nothing. I was just saying
I'm curious if they have high subscription retention.
Find out if we can set up a meeting
with the app executives.
[soft music]
-[keys clicking] -[phone vibrating]
Babe, look at this. Come here.
Look.
Veronica King? Since when is she a sugar mama?
I don't know, but this could be our answer.
-Mm -This could set us up
to where I don't even have to do this no more.
You think she'll be interested?
Trust me, I'll make sure she is.
I'll do whatever she says
and give her all the attention she needs.
This one gonna take care of us just like I promised.
[soft chuckles]
[calm music]
"He longed to become real to know what it felt like.
He was a Real Rabbit at last,
and at home with the other rabbits."
I love you, my sunshine.
Good night.
[phone chimes]
[dramatic music]
[Sharon] How has it been since our last session, Veronica?
The grief comes in waves.
Sometimes it's so heavy
I don't know how I'll get out of bed.
[Sharon] You have to be gentle with yourself.
I know I've been saying that ten years is a long time,
but it doesn't really seem like that
when you're trying to survive living without your husband.
How's your son coping with the death of his father?
-Is he still traveling? -Yeah.
It's hard for him, too.
Have you spoken with him lately?
Yes. He's on one of those alphabet trips.
A location for each letter.
I think he's in Dubai now.
Egypt is next.
And how is he feeling?
Not too good.
I just want to protect him.
Do you have kids, Sharon?
[chuckles] Ah, I do. Two little girls.
So I know exactly what you mean by wanting to protect your son.
A mother's unconditional love is a powerful thing.
Do you ever feel like you're not a good mother?
[Sharon] Yes.
And those feelings are completely normal.
Any setbacks are valuable life lessons
that could lead to development and resilience.
They're opportunities for growth.
And you learn a lot more about yourself in the end.
You know, it was good to see your profile on the app.
I didn't know you were into this kind of lifestyle.
I'm not actually.
I'm looking to invest in Sugar Finders.
So I was just doing some research.
Wait, so you're not interested
in an arrangement with a sugar baby?
So why did you agree to me?
[Veronica] We might as well talk about it, Mike.
Especially since you mentioned an interest
in a mentorship anyway.
We'll both have a glass of Chateau D'Anielle
and oysters topped with caviar.
Wow. You have nice taste.
I like to think so.
So tell me how you found your way on Sugar Finders.
Well, honestly, I need to do this
to finance my education.
And I also want to start up my own tech business
after college, so...
Ambition.
Admirable.
Do your parents agree with your job?
My mom left me and my dad when I was about five years old.
And I don't have any brothers or sisters, so...
I'm sorry about that.
-Are you and your dad close? -Not really.
He was a military guy, so he was kind of a hard-ass.
I never really got much love from him.
We don't talk much, so I pretty much do everything in my own.
How about you?
Not much to tell. I'm a widow.
I have one son who's about your age.
He's my world. So, Mike, how does this work?
This is all new to me.
Okay, so, basically,
you would pay me to do whatever it is
you need me to do.
-And if you ever get lonely or-- -No, nothing like that.
I'm not looking for companionship.
Let's just be clear.
That's fine.
So what exactly are you looking for?
I told you I'm looking to invest in Sugar Finders.
I was thinking you can act like my field test.
Helping me to delve further into the app's operations.
Yeah, that's easy.
You could also accompany me to tech events,
to network and connect.
You could provide me feedback about your experiences
and further influence my decision.
Okay, now that, kind of, sounds like companionship,
-wouldn't you say? -Absolutely not.
This is strictly business, understand?
Whatever you say.
So when do we start?
What's your fee?
Ten thousand for three months and I'm all yours.
Ten thousand?
I thought it was going to be much more than that,
to be honest.
[phone vibrates]
One more thing.
I'm paying you for your accessibility.
I want to be sure you're focused.
Do you have any distractions, relationships,
other sugar mamas or anything that might interfere?
If so, tell me now. Before I waste my time.
Not at all.
I'm focused and ready.
-[phone ringing] -[sniffs]
[sighs]
-Hello? -Good morning.
I didn't wake you, did I?
No, I'm up. What's good?
I have a tech fundraising event to attend this weekend
and I think it's a good idea if you come with me.
[Mike] For sure. Yeah, sounds fun.
It's a gala.
Do you have something formal to wear?
Uh...
I mean I can wear the same suit I wore last night to dinner.
Text me your address.
I'm sending a car in an hour so we can do some shopping.
[Mike] All right. Cool.
[upbeat music]
I told you this is a gala,
which means we need something that makes you look like a boss.
Like you belong in that room.
[scoffs] Okay, cool.
So what else you need me to do there other than network?
I'll be looking for you to give me
a different perspective on the tech landscape.
Observe the guests, their behaviors,
their trends, and interactions.
It will help me when I'm doing my investing.
All right. Got it.
We need something that says elite.
Something that commands attention.
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Confidence on a heartbeat ♪
♪ Living life like I want it ♪
♪ I'mma stay and enjoy it ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Better call up the booties ♪
♪ Place your bets On the new me ♪
♪ All the eyes looking to see ♪
♪ Cheers to me ♪
♪ Ready for the world to see ♪
♪ I'm exactly where I knew I'll always be ♪
♪ Oh, we ♪
♪ Cheers to me ♪
♪ Ready for the world to see ♪
I'm gonna need a bigger closet for all this stuff you bought.
You're more than welcome
to keep some of the stuff at my place, Jayson.
Who's Jayson?
My son.
-I'm sorry. -Nah, it's all good.
-Where is he? -Traveling.
I can't really keep up with him anymore.
Wait for me outside
and I'm gonna use the restroom and call the car.
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
Are you nervous?
I just want to make a good impression, that's all.
Babe, you're gonna be fine.
Okay?
Relax and give them that winning personality
that I fell in love with.
[chuckles] All right.
So, I picked this one out for you tonight.
I think this color looks amazing on you.
Yeah?
Um... Veronica wanted me to wear this one.
It's her favorite and, you know, I gotta please the client, so...
-Mm-hmm. -Yeah.
Oh, I almost forgot.
When we were shopping, I saw this and I thought of you.
Mm-hmm.
Babe, you shouldn't have.
Well, I didn't. Veronica did.
[chuckles] I'm a bit old for you.
Here we go. There.
All right, so it'll probably be late tonight,
so don't bother waiting up, okay?
-Okay. -All right.
All right, it's about that time. Wish me luck.
Good luck.
You look wonderful, Andrew. As do you.
This is my friend, Mike.
Mike, this is my assistant, Andrew.
So, Ms. King, I have some good news and some bad news.
The good news is you're on the VIP list.
The bad news is you're only allowed one guest.
I'm sure there's space for one more.
I'm so sorry.
It's a very strict list, ma'am.
Veronica, you only asked me to reserve two tickets
and I thought I was your guest.
I understand, but Mike here is joining me tonight.
Consider it a paid night off.
We'll touch base in the morning.
Have a good day, sir. Right this way.
[rock music]
Good to see you, Rob.
This is my friend, Mike Sheppard.
This is Mike Sheppard.
He is so smart, so tech-savvy. So tech-savvy.
He is extremely tech-savvy. Extremely tech savvy.
This is Mike Sheppard. Mike Sheppard here.
-Yeah. -Good to meet you all.
So this is an app I created and patented called WellMentor.
It's a comprehensive health app
that tracks various health metrics.
One really cool thing about it
is you can put in your own blood type.
So, for me, I would select O negative from the dropdown,
and it gives personalized recommendations
for optimal health and fitness plans
tailored to your genetic profile.
Can you grab me something to drink
while I talk more with Bernard?
Sure.
[music continues]
[sighs]
Let me get to it, please.
Appreciate it.
My, my.
You are certainly looking like a million bucks, Mike.
Beverly, I didn't think you would be here.
Well, my company is catering,
so I thought it would be a good reason to party
with the tech snobs.
So who are you here with?
Uh, just a friend.
Replaced me already.
I see.
Well, if things don't work out with you and your friend,
why don't you give me a call?
And maybe I'll let you convince me
I made a mistake.
Didn't your parents teach you to keep your hands to yourself?
Ooh, Veronica King.
Well, you know, I can't say I'm surprised,
but you're experimenting with new things now.
That's none of your business.
Mikey is here with me.
-Mikey? -Yeah.
Well, you know, I certainly meant no disrespect.
We all know your men usually have a wandering eye,
so I didn't think it would be an issue.
Hey, forget her.
I'm with you.
[rock music]
One of your sugar mamas, I presume.
Yes, but I swear.
I had no idea Beverly's company would be catering.
I didn't plan on seeing her again.
She sure didn't act like things were over.
It is.
My loyalty is with you now.
Other than that, I'm having a great time.
You certainly are the life of the party.
[chuckles]
I'm just glad you invited me.
I didn't realize that app of yours was such a great idea.
Where did you come up with it?
It's because of my dairy allergy.
I had a really severe reaction when I was little
that almost killed me.
So I figured this app would help.
Definitely.
And Bernard was impressed, too.
How'd you learn to charm people?
Well, my dad and I traveled a lot.
He was military, so I always had to make new friends.
It helped so I wouldn't feel so lonely.
Lonely?
That's one I know all too well.
Do you ever think about taking trips with Jayson?
Always.
But I like to let him have his little adventures.
Jayson always said he wanted to be a pilot.
But life had other plans for him.
And then his dad.
I'm sorry for your loss, Veronica.
Everybody's staring.
That's because they like you.
No, I mean staring at us.
Aren't you used to this?
You've done this before, right?
I was thinking...
Do you mind coming back to spend the night with me?
Things get lonely in that big house by myself.
I'll pay extra.
Uh... Yeah, yeah, sure.
One sec.
I have a quick call to make.
Okay.
[phone chimes]
[dramatic music]
Wow.
[door creaks]
Welcome to your new room.
Let me draw you a bath. Do you like bubbles?
I don't need a bath.
It'll relax you. Help you sleep better.
I have basketball shorts
and a T-shirt for you to sleep in.
Unless you prefer something different.
Nah, it's fine. Listen, Veronica,
I just want to thank you again for everything.
It means a lot to me to have you around.
[slaps]
What the hell are you thinking, Jayson?
-It's Mike. -This is not what we agreed to.
-Is it what Beverly had you do? -My bad.
I thought that's why you wanted me to stay the night.
You thought wrong.
Don't ever disrespect me like that again.
[suspenseful music]
[eerie music]
[rattles]
Who's there?
[tense music]
Is anyone there?
[thuds]
Hello?
I'm warning you. I have a gun.
[tense music]
[screaming]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[music continues]
[rattles]
Uh.
[creaks]
Hello?
[thuds]
[music continues]
[creaks]
Shit, Veronica.
You scared me. What are you doing here?
I couldn't sleep.
I-I'm not used to having people in the house.
I wanted to apologize about earlier.
I didn't mean to snap at you.
I-- and I certainly had no business in hitting you.
I was just shocked.
Hey, it's cool.
I'm the one that should apologize
because I'm the one that crossed the line.
I'd never disrespect you.
I know.
And from here on out,
I swear I won't do anything that you don't want me to do.
I'm grateful for you, Mikey. Truly.
Let me tuck you in.
What bedtime story
would you like me to read you tonight?
I'm good. Thanks.
[music continues]
Good night.
[sighs]
Is everything okay?
Of course.
It just helps me to relax
to know that you're getting some sleep.
[music continues]
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
[exhales softly]
Good morning, sleepyhead. How'd you sleep?
Fine.
Mikey, this is my dear friend, Greg.
Greg, this is the young man I've been telling you about.
Veronica's been telling me
that you've been studying computer science?
Mikey wants to start his tech business
after graduation.
He created an app
that provides personalized health recommendations.
Mm. Sounds interesting.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Uh, I didn't know what you'd like,
so I just made a little bit of everything.
Well, actually, I have that dairy allergy, remember?
Juice, then.
You know what, look, don't even worry about it.
I actually have to get going.
No, not until you eat everything.
I mean...
eat while I call you a car.
Okay.
Don't mind Roni.
It's not very often she has company.
I find it easier just to let her do her thing.
[scoffs]
How long have you known her?
About 20 years or so.
She invested in my online pharmaceutical company
back in the day when I was just a resident doctor with a dream.
Been friends ever since.
I like to think that I owe everything to Roni
for just believing in me.
Look, forgive me for asking,
but are you two, like-like, a thing?
It's complicated.
At the end of the day,
I like to think that we're best friends.
I see that you're not unfamiliar with complicated relationships.
What exactly is a sugar baby?
I get hired as a companion to do whatever they need me to do.
Well, oh, sort of like a male prostitute, basically.
Actually, it's a little bit more than that.
[chuckles]
Hey, no judgment.
I'm not here to interfere with whatever
you and Veronica got going on.
Just don't play with her emotions.
Understand?
Greg, you feel threatened by me or something?
Like I said, we're just friends.
And I care very much about her health and well-being.
And unlike you my care for her isn't tied to her bank account.
[groans]
You better take care of that.
What happened? Are you hurt?
It's all right. He just cut his finger.
Put some direct pressure on that.
I have an emergency kit in the guest bathroom.
Yo, go ahead.
I'm gonna stay here and clean up.
-There we go. All better. -Thanks.
My driver just had a few errands to run for me,
but he'll be back in a few minutes.
Thank you for staying.
You know you can come over whenever you want.
My home is your home.
Okay.
Veronica, it was just us here last night, right?
Yeah, why?
I don't know. Um...
I thought I heard something in the basement.
Oh...
Lord, I hope we don't have raccoons like the time before.
I'll have to get Greg to check it out.
Okay.
I'm all done cleaning up in there.
I gotta run.
I just got paged at the hospital.
Okay, I'll walk you out.
Nice meeting you, Mike.
[sighs]
Driver just pulled up.
Thank you.
Your extra, just like I promised.
I'll talk to you soon.
[door shuts]
Why didn't you come home last night, Mike?
I texted you to let you know what was going on.
I got your damn text.
What I don't understand is why didn't you come home?
Staying the night at Veronica's? Are you crazy?
That was not a part of the plan.
Babe, relax.
We didn't even sleep in the same room.
So nothing happened?
Just some weird stuff.
She kept trying to do everything for me
like I was a kid or something.
Doesn't she have a son?
Why is she treating you like hers?
I guess she misses him.
I don't know, babe.
That doesn't sound right.
Are you sure she doesn't have
some type of mental issues or something?
I don't know.
But, hey, if she gets off on pretending to be my mom,
I don't care.
Especially because she pays extra.
Now you know our relationship is strictly platonic.
But how much longer are you guys going to be doing this?
[female reporter] Breaking news.
Beverly Garrison's body was just discovered
in her lakeside home this morning.
The millionaire restauranteur
appears to have been the victim of a home invasion.
We're going to be live on location
to bring you updates as we receive them.
Next up...
He tried to kiss me. [sighs]
I don't know what came over him, but it felt so wrong.
Do you have feelings for this young man?
Obviously, he is physically attractive,
but I can't bring myself to see him in that way.
Those feelings are completely normal,
and I don't want you to let age be a deterrent.
I think it's okay to explore this possible relationship.
I do want a relationship with him,
just not an intimate one.
You think it would be cheating on Richie?
No, not Richie.
Jayson.
I understand.
Veronica,
I want you to consider this relationship with Mike
as an opportunity for you to find yourself
and to explore what makes Veronica happy.
Then you can make the best decisions for Jayson.
It's such a relief
to hear another mother understands.
[suspenseful music]
It doesn't seem weird to you?
I mean you just saw her the night before at the gala,
and now she's dead?
It was just a sad coincidence, babe.
That's a big coincidence.
I mean what other explanation can it be?
She was rich.
I'm sure she had run-ins with other idiots in the past
trying to rob her.
It just sucks she had to lose her life for it, you know?
Mikey, I was looking for you.
Veronica, hey, this is my friend, Gia.
I remember you from when I gave my speech.
You're in Mikey's class, too, right?
Yeah.
You want to grab some ice cream?
Oh, actually, he has a dairy allergy.
-Yeah. -Right, of course.
I remember that.
How about a smoothie?
You know I actually have to get to class.
Won't keep you long.
I just missed you and wanted to see you
before I headed to a meeting.
Okay. I'll see you later, Gia.
[sighs]
Good, huh?
Not really a fan of strawberry.
It was Jayson's favorite flavor.
Gia is pretty.
How long the two of you have known each other?
Not really long. Why?
You can't tell she likes you?
I haven't really noticed.
What's wrong?
You look down.
Did you hear about Beverly?
I did.
I'm sorry.
By the way, did Bernard Klein say anything else about my app?
He sure did.
-He loved it. -[chuckles]
He even mentioned calling you to come in
to intern for him in the fall.
I am so proud that he recognized how special you are.
Yes!
[laughs]
Are you serious?
I don't know what to say.
No, don't worry. I cleared it up.
I told him that you're not interested.
Why would you say that?
Because you'll be busy with school.
Besides, don't I pay you enough to mentor with me?
Why would you make a decision like that
without discussing it with me first, Veronica?
I was looking out for you.
How? By sabotaging my future?
I didn't know it meant that much to you.
-Why wouldn't it be? -It's a career opportunity.
Ain't that why you wanted me to come with you to that event?
-Please don't be mad. -No!
Back up, Veronica.
I'm out.
Mikey, I'm sorry.
[intense music]
I don't get it.
She tells me this arrangement we have
is an opportunity for me to network,
but then when I do, she gets in the way.
Maybe Veronica's not a good match.
I'm starting to get bad vibes from this.
I don't know. I wish I could just talk to Mr. Klein myself,
tell him it was a big misunderstanding.
Maybe you should just not mess with her altogether.
I mean just think about it.
She's being weird when you're staying the night,
and she's having you miss class to hang out with her,
and now this?
She's too controlling.
Babe.
I wasn't trying to end the arrangement, Gia.
Maybe we can find somebody else.
That pays as good as her? I doubt it.
Look, remember,
this is Veronica's first time doing this,
so I don't think she realizes how she's coming off.
So I'll just talk to her.
Don't worry about her, babe.
I'm not worried about her, okay?
I'm worried about you.
Well, don't be. I'm a big boy.
[chuckles]
Come here.
♪ I think you and I are high ♪
What's wrong?
Uh...
Nothing, nothing. Come here.
♪ I think [inaudible] ♪
-[phone chimes] -Babe. Your phone.
[sighs]
[phone chimes]
[phone rings]
What's up, Veronica?
[Veronica] I couldn't leave us on such a sour note.
Can we talk?
Maybe later. I got 11:00 a.m. class.
[Veronica] I have something for you here at the house.
Can I send a car to come get you?
And afterwards, if you never want to see me again,
I'll understand.
Just please, let me make it up to you.
[sighs]
All right. I'll be ready in 30 minutes.
We have an exam this morning.
It'll just be a minute, I promise.
Then I'll have Veronica drop me off on campus.
-Mike... -Gia, relax, all right?
I already got Veronica hounding me.
I don't need you to do it, too.
[suspenseful music]
Thank you for coming.
Listen, we gotta talk about everything that's been going on.
And we will, I promise.
Just let me show you this first.
-What is this? -Yours.
-For real? -Oh, what?
Oh, my gosh.
I thought you'd like that.
Something that reminds you of your dad.
Thank you, Veronica.
This means so much to me.
Wanna take it for a spin?
I don't know. My class starts soon.
[joyful music]
All right, just a little bit. [chuckles]
-See you later, okay? -See you later.
Gia?
Do I know you?
No, no, I'm-I'm-I'm Nora.
I follow Veronica King online.
I saw she posted a picture of a speech
she gave to your computer science class.
You were tagged in it.
Oh, okay.
Is there somewhere we can go and talk?
I think you might be in danger.
[tense music]
I've been following Veronica for years,
and I saw she was out with this guy Mike.
Then I saw you and Mike together, so...
So I knew I had to say something.
I couldn't let another woman end up like my sister.
Wait, why were you stalking Veronica?
And what do you mean end up like your sister?
I've been watching her for something
that I can use against her.
I can't prove it,
but I think Veronica had something to do
-with my sister's death. -What?
About ten years ago,
my sister Carla worked with Veronica's husband Richie.
She was his publicist.
One night they died in a car crash.
What made you think Veronica had something to do with it?
Carla told me that she and Richie...
had an affair.
Supposedly, it was a one-time thing,
but Carla had a crush on him,
and they spent a lot of time together.
And apparently,
it was something that Richie and Veronica argued about
all the time.
So you think Veronica found out something about them that day?
Like I said, I can't prove it.
And the police haven't been any help.
They just labeled it as a car crash.
But if I'm right,
and Veronica finds out that Mike is cheating with you,
-she may snap. -He's not cheating.
I know.
But, this is a lot to digest.
I tried to warn my sister to back off of Richie.
I couldn't protect Carla,
so the least I can do is just try to protect you.
There is no telling what Veronica is capable of.
[music continues]
Nora...
Hmm?
[screams]
[sighs] Come on, pick up.
[Mike] You've reached Mike. Drop a message or hit me later.
Babe.
Babe, where are you?
Call me back. Please, I'm worried.
[keys clicking]
[line ringing]
[screams]
-[thuds] -[sobs]
I'm impressed. This looks good.
If it tastes the same... I haven't made this in years,
so it might be a little rusty.
All right, let's see.
Mmm. All right, I see you.
[both laugh]
-Great news. -Yeah?
I have a business meeting
with the executive of Sugar Finders tomorrow.
So I want you to come with me,
since you've been instrumental in my decision to invest.
That's a smart move.
You're gonna make a lot of money with this app.
It's only at the beginning.
I see you as the future of my investments.
So I want to make sure we have a plan in place
for you to get the experience,
especially for your own app.
That's one of the reasons why
I reached back out to Bernard Klein.
I told him you were interested in the internship.
Yes!
Thank you, Veronica.
It's the least I could do,
especially since I messed everything up the first time.
[phone chimes]
Something wrong?
Listen, Veronica,
I gotta be completely honest with you.
The girl I was with the other day, Gia?
[sighs] She's my girlfriend.
You lied to me.
Look, I'm sorry, all right?
You're sorry? You think that makes it better?
Well, you said this wasn't a romantic thing anyway,
so why are you so upset?
It's not a romantic thing. I wanted all of your time.
Isn't that what I'm paying you for?
Okay. You're right.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have done that.
But it's not like it matters anymore anyway.
She just broke up with me.
Apparently, she's been trying to reach me all day
and now she's pissed.
She kicked me out.
Move in with me.
I have plenty of rooms.
In fact, last surprise.
I promise. Close your eyes.
What is it this time?
Okay, open up.
Don't you just love it?
Uh...
Wow.
Yeah.
[suspenseful music]
With your investments,
we intend to expand our marketing efforts
and hire a few different developers
to increase the platform's functionality.
I love that.
I'm interested in contributing beyond just capital.
I see Sugar Finders as the pay-to-play relations app
that will dominate this market.
Yeah, I totally agree.
-Cheers. -Cheers.
[sighs]
Well, Mr. Sheppard,
looks like we have you to thank for onboarding Miss King
and showing her
what a valuable asset she could be to our operation.
Yes, sir. I'm just glad it worked out.
I think that you will get a promising mogul
-on your hands here. -[chuckles]
I couldn't imagine doing it without him.
If you two will excuse me.
[suspenseful music]
[line ringing]
[Gia] Hey, it's Gia. Leave a message, or don't.
Babe, please call me back.
Look, I'm sorry I didn't realize you tried to reach me yesterday,
but I should have communicated better.
Look, I was wrong.
Just hear me out. I promise to do better.
I love you.
I see you're still hanging around.
Yo, what's your problem, Andrew?
You. Stealing my spot with Veronica?
Ever since you came around,
she's just been pushing me to the side.
Veronica and I have a business arrangement.
That's it. I ain't coming for your spot.
Bullshit.
Until you came into the picture,
all of Veronica's business was with me.
All right, well, I can't help you with that.
That's between you and her.
[groans]
Get off me!
[both grunt]
Oh, fucking leave him alone.
All right, get up. Damn! Hey!
How is he?
He'll be fine.
Tests came back normal.
Why'd you have to draw blood?
Standard procedure.
We check for internal injuries, infection,
and your blood alcohol level.
In case Andrew tries to say that you initiated the attack
because you were under the influence.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Sorry to bother you.
-Your patient is awake. -Thank you, nurse.
[gloomy music]
Mike, there's something else I have to tell you.
It's about Gia. She was attacked last night.
-Gia? -Mike, thank God.
-You okay? -I was worried.
[sobs]
What happened to you?
[gasps]
Someone attacked me on campus last night.
Babe, I'm so sorry.
I should have been there.
I've been trying to call you ever since I got your text.
What text?
You said...
Look, it doesn't matter.
How you feeling? Can I get you anything?
How long do you have to be here for?
I'm okay.
I'm just glad you're here.
[machine beeping]
-Please don't leave me again. -I won't. I promise.
Sorry. I didn't mean to interrupt.
It's okay.
You remember Gia, right?
Of course. My goodness.
But what happened? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
She was attacked.
-You think it was Andrew? -Probably.
I didn't think he would come after people I care about.
Wait a minute. Who was Andrew?
And why would he attack me?
He's my ex-assistant.
Gia, I am sorry. This is all my fault.
I'll make sure to cover all of your medical bills.
Everything. You can stay with us to recover.
Us?
Veronica, can you give us a second?
[suspenseful music]
You have to get away from Veronica.
Okay? She's dangerous.
Dangerous?
She said she would pay for your medical bills.
Yesterday, a woman, Nora,
she came on campus looking for me.
She thinks Veronica has something to do
with killing her sister.
-What? -Babe, there was an accident.
Okay? A car accident.
Veronica's husband was killed, and Nora said that...
The nurses' station said that visiting hours are over.
Mikey, you have to come with me.
Mike, don't go. Okay?
Stay the night so that we can talk.
I'll bring him back in the morning.
-No. He has to stay. -Nurse!
Don't go, she's not what you think she is.
-No, babe, listen to me. -Relax, calm down.
You're in danger now. Get your hands off me.
Ma'am, I need you to calm down.
-No, get off. Babe... -Sir,
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
Please don't leave, Mike. Mike, Mike, please.
Mike, you're in danger. No, get your hands off.
Mike, listen to me. You can't go.
Mike, no. Please let go of me. Let go.
[screams] Mikey! Mike!
Please, no! No!
Please, Mike!
Mikey. No!
She's gonna be okay.
I just hated to leave her in that condition.
I'll call Greg personally. Make sure he checks in on her.
We can go right in the morning when you wake up, okay?
Okay.
Gia mentioned something about your husband Richie.
If you don't mind me asking, how did he die?
It was a traumatic accident.
It still hurts to talk about.
My poor Jayson.
I don't think he ever got over it.
I'm sorry to hear that.
And that's a lot to deal with.
When my mom left,
I used to sneak and look at old pictures
because I knew my dad wouldn't want to talk about her.
Do you have any recent pictures of Jayson?
I don't have any pictures,
but I do have postcards.
He sends them from his travels.
I should be getting another one in a few days.
[tense music]
Wanna watch a movie?
Yeah, sure. Why not?
[phone vibrates]
[woman] You have a collect call
from Monroe Park Correctional Facility.
Do you accept?
Sure.
Mike.
[Mike] How the hell did you get my number?
From Veronica's things. Listen, I don't have much time.
-I need your help. -So you attack me and my girl
and you think I'm gonna help you?
[Andrew] No, no, no. You got it all wrong.
I swear.
Please tell Veronica to drop the assault charges.
I was doing what she told me to,
but she didn't say nothing about jail.
What did she tell you to do?
[Andrew] To fight you.
Why would she tell you to do that?
[Andrew] She needed me to rough you up a little.
No big deal.
Can you bail me out?
Who are you talking to?
[Andrew] Mike, Mike, Mike, are you still there?
Andrew, this is your final warning.
Do not ever call me or Mikey ever again.
Do you hear me?
[Veronica] I'm not going to allow you to terrorize us
over your obsession.
Goodbye.
This is all my fault. I'm sorry.
I never knew Andrew was capable of any of this.
Did you put him up to fight me?
Is that what he told you?
You cannot trust Andrew. He spiraled out of control.
I realized he was jealous when you came into the picture.
He has always been loyal,
but I did not know that he could ever harm you or Gia.
If I'd known that, I never would've let it happen.
Did he ask you to bail him out?
And drop the charges.
See, he will say anything to you right now.
He is willing because he needs to get you to do what he wants.
Ignore him if he calls you ever again, okay?
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Okay, it's late.
Let's go to sleep.
Actually, I think I'm gonna go back to my place tonight.
Oh, Mikey.
You can stay here.
You can go straight from here to check on Gia in the morning.
Okay.
[tense music]
I love you, sunshine.
Good night.
[tense music]
[door shuts]
[sighs]
[machine beeping]
[groans softly]
Hey, sweetie.
How are you feeling?
What are you doing back here?
Where's Mike?
My son's right where he belongs.
Son?
He's not your damn son.
-You're twisted. -Not twisted at all.
Just a loving mother.
What are you gonna do, huh?
Brainwash him?
He's never gonna--
He's--
He's not... gonna...
pretend you're his moth-mother.
Sure he will.
[chuckles softly]
But you won't be around to see it.
[machine beeping rapidly]
[gasping]
-Veronica, what the hell? -I didn't mean to scare you.
You hungry? I made breakfast.
No, I have to go to the hospital to see Gia.
-Just try it. No dairy. -No, I said chill.
Look what you did.
I'll clean it up.
[suspenseful music]
Veronica.
Where is she?
Veronica, open the door!
It's not a game, Veronica.
[banging on door]
Veronica, where are you?
[banging continues]
[music continues]
[bangs]
Veronica! Open the door. Veronica!
[banging continues]
It's not a game.
Veronica, where are you?
Veronica.
[volume increases]
♪ I know that you'll be here For me ♪
[inaudible]
[crickets chirping]
[Veronica] No, I didn't hug him.
I... [inaudible].
I don't know if it's a good idea.
I'm not sure.
[opens door]
Hey, Mike.
What the hell is wrong with you, Veronica?
You know what? This is done. You hear me? We're done.
Mike, will you let me speak just for a minute, please?
Hell no. I'm trying to get to the hospital.
-She knows that. -This is wrong, and I'm sorry.
But Greg came to tell you something,
and I think you should listen to what he has to say.
I don't give a damn what he has to say.
It's about Gia.
What about Gia?
I'm sorry, Mike.
We called her parents already.
I came to talk to you in person.
[intense music]
Gia succumbed to her injuries last night.
She fought really hard.
But in the end...
she just didn't make it.
Look, Mike, we're here for you, man.
We're here with you, Mike.
We're here with you. Mike.
Mike.
-Mike. -Fuck!
-Mikey! -Stay the hell away from me!
You should have let me go this morning!
She tried to warn me about you!
Let's get you home, son.
Come on.
[sniffles]
[dramatic music]
[keypad clicking]
[tense music]
[Mike] I need time to myself, Veronica.
I'm not trying to see you right now.
Roni, it's going to work out.
I hope so.
Look, I'm going to New York for a few days
for a medical conference.
-Why don't you come with me? -You know I can't.
Hey, are you going to be okay until I get back?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Hmm. Okay. You know what?
You need to plan yourself a little getaway.
I think the time will do you some good.
Hmm.
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
You know what? You're right.
My son would absolutely love that.
[baby crying in distance]
-I'm surprised you came up here. -Cut the shit.
I need you to be straight with me and tell me the truth.
It's been Veronica this whole time.
She paid me to attack you.
Said you were being a nuisance,
and she wanted me to rough you up
so you back off some.
What about Gia?
Why would Veronica attack her?
Because Gia probably found out the truth about Veronica.
I've worked for Veronica for five years.
And in that time,
I've handled all of her personal information.
Records, phone logs, emails, messages, you name it.
I didn't think much of it at first.
Then I started to find things.
[phone vibrates]
[Andrew] Veronica found out her husband was sleeping
with his publicist Carla.
She was pissed.
What?
It's my publicist.
That's all you're gonna do is laugh?
[Andrew] But he didn't even seem to care.
Denied everything, even when she confronted him.
What happened after that, I'm not entirely sure about.
But one thing I do know,
you don't want to cross Veronica.
If your mother asks,
just tell her I had a meeting, son.
Your mom will be back in a couple hours.
She just ran to the store.
Look, just let him come, babe.
You don't want him to suspect anything.
Right.
All right, come on, go get dressed.
Come on.
[both laugh]
[tense music]
-What the hell? -Baby?
-Babe, what's wrong? -The brakes don't work!
Babe, come on! Please, please!
-What is wrong? -Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! I can't slow down!
Richie, please, please, please, please!
I can't slow down!
Please, baby, stop!
[screams]
Oh my God!
-Oh, my God! Oh, my God! -No, baby, please!
No!
[crashes]
[crickets chirping]
[groans]
[groaning continues]
[screams]
No! No! Baby?
[sobbing]
So, Jayson died too?
I read articles about the crash, but nothing mentions it.
There are no records of him online anywhere.
It's as if he just doesn't exist anymore.
I honestly think she just checked out from reality.
All right, look, I'll drop the charges and bail you out.
But for now I need you to go to the police.
[sighs]
[groans]
You didn't think I'd give you a call
and not be able to track you, did you?
My son, I've missed you so much.
[suspenseful music]
[rattles]
[groans]
Help!
Well, I am happy to see you in a much better mood.
Yes, very. My son's been traveling for a while,
but he's finally home and I couldn't be happier.
How wonderful.
Well, when do I get to meet him?
Hopefully soon.
I've actually booked his vacation to Aruba.
I am very proud of you, Veronica.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey!
I'm down here! Help!
[knocks]
Well, let me let you go.
I just wanted to stop by and check in on you. [chuckles]
[door creaks]
You need to eat.
Keep up your strength.
Why are you doing this?
Because you mean so much to me.
More than you'll ever know.
So that's your plan? Jayson dies
and you think you can just replace him with me?
-You're crazy. -No.
I'm a mother.
And a mother will do whatever she needs
to be with her child.
But I'm not your child, Veronica!
I know.
[sobs] But I need you.
Okay, wait, wait. Veronica!
Wait! Mom!
What did you call me?
I said, Mom, please, I love you.
Don't-don't leave me down here by myself.
You know I'm afraid of the dark.
Oh, baby.
I'm so glad to hear you say that.
I'll put you in your room after you eat your dinner, okay?
-Yes, ma'am. -I promise.
Okay.
Thanks, Mom.
Eat up now.
You need your strength.
Hmm-hmm.
I love you, my sunshine.
Good night.
I've prayed for this moment with you for so long.
And now, I'm never gonna let you go.
I love you.
[birds chirping]
I am being patient.
[clatters]
I just want it done already.
We're traveling soon.
Okay. I will.
[door opens]
Good morning, sunshine.
Good morning, Mom. How'd you sleep?
Wonderful.
Best sleep that I've had in years.
All because I finally have my Jayson back.
Mom, can you feed me?
Of course I can.
Come here. I-- Oh!
[tense music]
Mikey, you are grounded when I find you. Do you hear me?
[door creaks]
[suspenseful music]
[music continues]
[indistinct chatter]
Mikey!
[groans]
[panting]
Greg! Greg!
-Greg! -Mike!
It's Veronica. [panting]
She's holding me hostage. I saw a kid...
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on, son.
What did Veronica do?
We gotta go to the police, all right?
She killed Richie. She killed Gia.
And now she's trying to kidnap me.
[panting continues]
Oh, God.
Come on, son. Let's get you home.
Get your ass here.
[groans softly]
I'm sorry it had to come to this, Mikey.
But we had no choice.
You were the answer to my prayers.
It'll all be over soon.
I told you we needed each other.
You needed Mom and I need my son,
my Jayson.
[panting]
And because of your wonderful gift...
I can have him.
So Jayson died too?
I read articles about the crash but nothing mentions him.
[Andrew] There are no records of him online anywhere.
It's as if he just doesn't exist anymore.
Can you save him?
He's gonna need a new heart.
There was just too much damage.
But he's O-negative, which is a very rare blood type.
[Veronica] He showed me this app he's creating,
and he put his blood type as O-negative.
I'm gonna stay here and clean up.
[dramatic music]
[Greg] I confirmed Mike's blood type is O-negative.
But I'll need to run a few more tests
to make sure he's suitable.
Can you find a way to get him to the hospital?
I need you to do me a favor.
[Greg] He's a perfect match.
I'm sorry, Mike.
But when I found out you could save my son's life,
I did what I needed to do.
I'm a mother,
and I told you,
a mother will do anything to be with her child.
[sobs]
[breathing heavily]
Wait, wait, no, wait, please, wait!
[muffled groaning]
[Sharon] It's been a little minute.
[Veronica] I know, but things have been going so well.
And I can't thank you enough for your advice.
You helped me realize
what I needed to do to get back to myself.
Well, you are an amazing woman, Veronica.
People are lucky to know you.
No, I'm the lucky one.
Sorry, mama.
Am I late?
Not at all, my sunshine.
Well, you must be Jayson.
Your mother has spoken so highly of you,
I feel like I already know you.
It's nice to finally meet you.
You, too.
[Sharon] Well, I won't keep you.
I know you have a plane to catch.
So you two have fun and safe time in Aruba.
Oh, and get a slice of Kesio for me, please.
[Veronica] Oh, no, Jayson can't have that.
Dairy products don't really agree with him,
but we'll certainly enjoy the food, that's for sure.
I've been praying for this moment with you.
And now I'm never letting you go.
♪ I'm screaming ♪
♪ But no one's listening ♪
♪ Can't believe what I've been witnessing ♪
♪ It's a cruel world ♪
♪ But who deserves it? ♪
♪ Do I deserve it? ♪
♪ I'm screaming ♪
♪ But no one's listening ♪
♪ I Can't believe what I've been witnessing ♪
♪ I'm so lost in this paradise ♪
♪ It's my own little oasis ♪
♪ 'Cause I got it how I want it now ♪
♪ I'm never gonna get away from love ♪
♪ I feel so close to you like it's my time ♪
♪ Kiss me away ♪
♪ I wanna stay right there, baby ♪
♪ Twist me away ♪
♪ I'll know you'll stay right here for me ♪