Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[low ominous humming]
[intense music]
[motors roaring]
[low chanting]
[motor rumbling]
[music fades out]
[ominous echoing]
[bird screeching in distance]
[engine starting]
[thudding]
[haunting chord]
[objects crashing
and shattering]
[chair creaking]
[incessant thudding]
[ominous music]
[glass smashing]
[objects shattering]
[door creaking]
[smashing]
[sparking]
Modern technology
is the worst thing that ever
happened to the world,
and to promote its progress
is nothing short of criminal.
[footsteps clomping]
[deer huffing]
[water rushing]
[birds tweeting]
[door closing]
Thank you, Grandfather Rabbit.
[squelching]
Thanks for listening
to the local NPR classics.
KUHFN 91.7 Helena,
89.1 Missoula,
another hour of the baroque.
[lively classical
music playing on radio]
[blowing]
[woman singing opera music]
[engine rumbling in distance]
[engine revving]
[vehicle zooming away]
[clinking spoon loudly]
[mumbling] Technique five...
take the one.
Sixty-four.
2, 51, 2, 19...
18, 63, 2, 19...
18, 63, 3, 1, 51...
2, 19, 18...
[classical music on radio]
[water rushing]
[birds chirping]
[low, ominous music]
Yesterday was quite good.
The only disruptive
sounds were nine evil jets.
Today was
good in early morning,
but later in morning there was
aircraft noise almost without
intermission for I would
estimate about an hour.
In Lamborn, Illinois,
there's far more jet noise,
and at times
it is very annoying.
But it does not disturb
me nearly as much as does
the lesser jet noise here,
because here the noise destroys
something wonderful,
while in the city
there is nothing for noises
to destroy because one
is living
in a shit pile anyway.
[truck reversing]
[machine rumbling]
[saw buzzing]
[machinery clanging loudly]
[noise cuts out]
[gravel crunching,
bike squeaking]
[birds tweeting distantly]
[engines rumbling]
[coughing in distance]
[Ted muttering]
[eerie music]
[engines rumbling]
[phone ringing]
Excuse me.
Please deposit five cents
for the next three minutes.
If five cents is not
deposited within 25 seconds--
-Yeah, I did. I--
-...your call will
automatically terminated.
-Fuck!
Fuck!
[sighing]
[truck beeping]
[engine roaring]
[tree snapping]
[booming thud]
[tires crunching loudly]
[machinery stops]
[water rushing]
[Ted panting]
Need a ride, Ted?
-I can't get this,
uh-- I can't get this around.
-It's not--
-Ted, it doesn't work.
-Huh?
-It's broke, it's broke.
Just hold on real tight.
Whoa!
[driver laughing]
I couldn't help myself.
[laughing]
Sorry to-- Sorry, Ted,
I won't do it again, I promise.
Aw, shoot.
[driver resumes chuckling]
[somber classical music]
[bar din]
[patrons chattering
indistinctly]
The supertanker
bound for Long Beach,
California, ran aground
about 22 miles south of Valdez
early Friday morning
after loading a cargo of one
and a quarter million barrels
from the Alaska pipeline.
Oil poured into the sound
at the rate of 20,000
gallons an hour for 12 hours.
Exxon acknowledges
that the Valdez detoured
into treacherous water.
The Coast Guard says
the captain was trying
to avoid large chunks
of ice known as growlers.
[phone ringing]
-Seventy-five cents.
Hi. Hi, Ma, it's me.
It's so hot.
[unzipping]
No, it's okay, it's always--
it always does this,
but I only had $1.50
and I'm going to run
out of time before
we finish the conversation.
Nothing. I just...
I just want to talk to him.
I just turned my back on him.
Wouldn't talk to him.
Yeah, well, that's his issue.
He shouldn't--
He shouldn't have got married.
He shouldn't
have married her, Ma.
She's a bad influence on him.
If that's
not obvious to you now,
it will be in the future.
Well, I still love him,
Ma, but I don't--
I have nothing
in common with David.
He was jealous of the fact
that I could do most
things better than he could.
It's a simple fact, Ma.
Well, yeah, he was better
socially than I was, but...
Well, if you hadn't put me
two years ahead in high school,
perhaps I would have
the ability to-- to hold
a conversation with a woman
longer than 30 seconds.
Two relationships in my life.
Two. I only
got to first base, Ma.
You know what first base is?
Yeah, kissing, tongue rubbing.
Yeah.
I have tongue rubbed twice.
Twice. That's all. Nothing.
No-- no touching of breasts.
No sexual intercourse.
Well,
who do you want me to tell?
Who should I tell this to, Ma?
Fuck, there's people...
There's people listening.
I just need to know if you're
going to send me money, Ma.
Please, I'm desperate.
All right,
please send me a check.
Oh, for the love of God,
is that a yes or no?
Thank you.
And do not send--
no, do not send food
with the check,
just a check, Ma.
I have to go.
-[automated voice speaking]
The beeping-- The phone--
It's the phone company, Ma.
It's the phone company.
I can't. I have to go.
[somber music]
[low electric buzzing]
[bike squeaking]
[ominous music]
[juice dripping]
[keys clacking]
To the editor,
I would like to warn
people of the danger
of picking berries
in power line road cuts.
The Montana Electric Company
sprays cancer causing
herbicides without any
warnings to the public.
[chopping wood]
[pleasant classical music]
[panting]
[chopping]
[pole creaking]
[electric zapping,
pole thudding]
[birds twittering]
[wind blowing]
[leaves rustling]
[gulping]
[explosive whirring of jets]
[jets passing]
[thunderous roaring of engines]
Fuckin'-- fuckin'...!
Then there was a very
loud sonic boom.
This was the last straw.
And it reduced me to
tears of impotent rage.
But I have a plan for revenge.
[classical music continues]
[fire crackling]
[jets roaring in distance]
[dramatic operatic singing]
[objects clattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[dog barking in distance]
Shoo! Shoo!
Fuck off.
People say violence
and the taking of human
life is not a way to
resolve human problems.
[sawing]
It can't work.
As a matter of fact,
history shows
that it very often does work.
I want to kill some people.
Preferably a scientist,
a communist, businessman
or some other big shot.
Use shotgun powder
in the last hoping it would
do more
damage than rifle powder.
[explosion bursting]
Spent 350 bucks
on the last bombing mission
and barely blew
a finger off.
Absolutely frustrating.
I can't seem
to make a lethal bomb.
Seeming increasingly
infeasible without more money.
[machinery rattling]
[high-pitched sawing]
[machine rattling]
-Okay?
-There you go.
[vehicle rumbling on]
[vehicle reversing]
Hey, Ted.
You keep drawing like that,
you're gonna cut your nuts off.
-Yeah, I don't take
direction from women
on mechanical matters.
Please have your husband
advise me on how to work.
-Fuckin' asshole.
-Yeah, did you... you see that?
She tried to fire me,
I'm doing what I'm-- I'm doing
my job,
I'm doing what you told me.
Fucking--
-You know she runs
the show around here?
-What?
-She... she runs the show.
Get the fuck out!
[dramatic music]
There is a psycho-surgical
operation that relieves people
who get angry too easily.
They stick electrodes
into your brain and burn out
the gizmo that produces
the emotion of anger.
Of course,
I would rather be miserable
or dead than be relieved
by that humiliating method.
[curtain rustling]
[splashing]
[light chatter]
Excuse me.
How much... how much is this?
-25 cents.
-Okay,
I'll think about it.
-Doing some
entertaining there, Ted?
-No.
Just need cutlery.
-Don't have a wife
to chew my food and regurgitate
it into my mouth.
[chuckles awkwardly]
-Fair enough.
Since committing the crimes
reported elsewhere in my notes,
I feel better.
I'm still plenty angry,
you understand,
but the difference is that
I am now able to strike back
to a degree.
True, I can't strike back
to anything like the extent
I wish to, but I no longer
feel totally helpless,
and the anger doesn't
gnaw my guts as it used to.
Guilty feelings? Yes, a little.
Occasionally, I have bad dreams
in which police are after me,
or which I am threatened
with punishment
from a supernatural source
such as the devil.
But these don't occur
often enough to be a problem.
I am definitely glad
to have done what I have.
[music fades out]
[shovel digging]
[grunting]
[scraping]
[metallic clattering]
[thumping]
[scraping]
[soft, eerie music]
[exhaling]
[exhaling deeply]
[explosion booms]
[coughing]
Here comes a tough one.
So, four numbers.
Keeping the seven
in the same place.
Mm-hmm.
-Create the greatest
and the smallest number
in a combination
of those four digits.
I'm going to give you a hint.
The zero, seven, five,
four is a three-digit number.
Okay?
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah, what's the greatest
and smallest number
for those four digits?
Mm-hmm.
[chuckling softly]
Nice. Remarkable.
That's fantastic.
The smallest.
He's really coming along.
He is really smart.
I think you've
probably done enough.
Yeah. All this math
does give me a headache.
-That's what we want.
[all laughing]
In Montana,
if I went to the city to mail
a bomb to some big shot,
the driver would doubtless
remember
I rode the bus that day.
In the anonymity of the big
city, I figured it would be
much safer to buy materials
for a bomb and mail it.
[whistling "Ode To Joy"]
[owl hooting]
[Ted continues whistling]
[music playing distantly]
[high-pitched voice]
I wanna fuck you.
[low voice]
I want to fuck you too, yeah.
Nice ass. Nice tits. Face, meh.
[laughing softly]
I could end this bitch.
[moody jazz music]
[music fades out]
-What are you reading about?
-The psychology of women.
I'm reading, I have work to do.
I'm--
-Oh, yeah?
-[aggressively] Mm-hmm.
-What do you do?
-I'm a psychiatrist.
-No shit.
-Yeah.
Please do not
tell me your troubles.
-[both laughing]
-Right.
What do you...
what do you do for a living?
-I just got out of prison.
I gotta go get a job.
-Sure.
[pensive music]
-Maybe I'll go
be a psychiatrist now.
[passenger chuckling]
-Um, excuse me,
I have to--
Hey.
-I have to get
the fuck out of here.
Have a good trip.
[music fades out]
[door buzzing]
-Evening. I need a...
room for one.
-Name?
-It's Conrad. Joseph Conrad.
Um, how much?
-$19.95.
[rock music playing]
[key clanging]
-A nickel?
Change?
[nickel clanging]
Call me if you need anything.
-Mm-hmm.
... the face of winter
again here very, very shortly.
As if we aren't--
-[changing channel]
-... reconditioning
the America.
It's an even trade-off
with the other new carriers
proposed--
-[changing channel]
-...but sources tell us
the internal investigation
and report to council
raised many questions,
and it should be noted to date,
there has been no independent
investigation on why it took
more than a year to arrest
the son of a city councilman,
the son of a sheriff's deputy
and the son of Shipley's
administrative assistant
in connection with two
burglaries in the city.
[Ted sighing]
[uplifting music on TV]
-If you frequently
travel from one side
of the ocean to the other,
you'll find United's
vast 747 fleet to be
enormously pleasing.
In fact,
their superior comforts
and spacious surroundings,
combined with our renowned
international service,
make short work--
[TV shutting off]
[tap running]
[sirens in distance]
[mailbox door squeaking]
[ominous music]
[door bell chiming]
[indistinct chatter,
machines whirring]
[chatter grows louder]
[video game noises]
[indistinct chatter]
[high-pitched digital ringing]
[eerie chord]
-Looking for something
affordable, or, yeah...
What kind of things
are you looking to
do with a computer?
-Writing.
-Okay.
[clerk speaking indistinctly
[overlapping sounds]
-That'd be a PC18...
[clerk speaking indistinctly]
-...Microsoft Word...
...writing, typing,
word processing,
productivity
applications...
[clerk continues
speaking indistinctly
It can do a lot
more things than just
edit text and code.
I mean, you can--
The middle name is business.
Watch this.
If I'm typing away--
See, I made a mistake there.
I typed "A"
when I wanted an "S,"
so if I just hit this key twice,
backspace there, I could
change that "A" to an "S."
[voice distorting]
And away I go.
No white out,
no correction ribbon.
It's all in there.
-Are you the owner
of the store?
No, no. I just work here.
-Who is the owner?
-The owner is behind
the counter there
with the moustache.
Oh.
I mean, would you like
me to get him for you?
-Oh, no.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-This is interesting. Thank you.
I need to-- need to go.
But I'll think about
it and... get back to you.
Come back anytime.
I'm always here.
My motive for doing
what I'm going to do
is simply personal revenge.
I do not expect to
accomplish anything it.
Of course, if my crime
and reasons for committing
it gets any public attention,
it may help to stimulate
public interest
in a technology question
and thereby improve
the chances of stopping
technology
before it's too late.
But on the other hand,
most people will probably
be repelled by my crime.
The opponents of freedom may
use it as a weapon to support
their arguments for control
over human behavior.
With no way of knowing
whether my action will do
more good than harm,
I certainly don't claim to be
an altruist
or to be acting for the good,
whatever that is,
of the human race.
I act merely for my
desire for revenge.
[chatter over TV]
[Ted coughing]
-So, how'd we do
tonight, huh?
Oh, money, money, money, money.
Heh heh! I love it!
[coughs]
Nice cough. You all right?
-No.
-You don't look so good.
Here.
Here's 40 for tonight,
And get yourself something
else to drink, too, no charge.
And I got some Old Spice
back there, on the house.
[mysterious music]
[faucet running]
[rack squeaking]
At this hour,
police still have
no leads in the package
bombing in Lake Forest.
Chuck Goudie is here
with the latest
in the investigation
to that story. Chuck.
Jack, a couple
of days ago, Percy Wood
received a letter from somebody
named Enoch Fisher.
The letter informed
of when to expect a book
in the mail very soon.
But when he got the book
it blew up in his face.
The return address:
3414 West Ravenswood Avenue.
It didn't help much.
It's a vacant lot.
So, police are hoping
for better luck with clues
the explosion left behind.
Today, inside
Wood's home, investigators
finished picking up
pieces of the bomb.
That was nerve-wracking.
Metal fragments were scattered
throughout the kitchen and had
to be separated
from bits of glass and paper.
The evidence
recovered from the home
of Mr. Hood-- Mr. Wood was
in good condition and has been
dispatched by courier to
the Postal Inspection
Service Crime Laboratory
in Washington, DC.
The parcel wrapping,
the packing and portions
of the bomb itself
will be analyzed by
the laboratory technicians
and they will
furnish us a full report.
At this time, we are unable
to release any details
on the makeup of the bomb.
We have initiated
an intense investigation
to solve the attack
upon Mr. Wood.
Recently,
Percy Wood outfitted his home
with an electronic
security system
and he probably wouldn't
open the front door
if a stranger was outside.
Like most of us,
though, he opens mail.
Not knowing what's inside.
-"It will never happen to me,"
is the way that
most people look at it.
Yourself, how many times
have you opened your mail
and thought that there might
have been something in it?
[bang]
[grunts]
-Ugh!
[exhaling]
[groaning]
[news playing in background]
Helping hand.
You got a--
Yeah, I'm fucking angry
with the car, asshole.
You wanna know
who told us my wife?
Your goddamn brother.
[hanging up phone]
[classical music]
[engine rumbling]
Dynamite blast all over him.
Occasionally autumn at my cabin.
Exxon conducting
seismic exploration for oil.
Couple of helicopters
flying all over the hills.
Lower, I think,
dynamite on cable.
Make blast on ground,
instruments
smash through vibrations.
I camped out mostly in
what I call the diagonal gulch,
hoping to shoot up a helicopter
in an area east of Crater Mount.
[gunshot]
It proved harder than I thought.
Those helicopters
always in motion,
never know
where they would go next.
[sirens]
[gunshot]
Cocksuckers!
[whirring quiets]
[gunshot]
Fuck.
Desecration.
Where can I go now
for peace and quiet?
[somber music]
When I got
back to camp, I cried.
Partly from
frustration of missing,
but mostly grief about what
was happening to the country.
Fuck!
Fuck you!
It is so beautiful.
But if they did find oil...
disaster.
Even if not find oil, the blast
and helicopters ruin it.
Ted Kaczynksi
reporting for duty.
-[giggling]
-Hey, there, Ted.
-Hello, Mrs. Hill.
-I'm so glad you're here.
-You ready to work?
-Yes. What can I do?
-Let's head back this way.
I'm gonna put you
in the back with Becky,
and we have
this huge pile of books
that we have to sort through.
Unfortunately, we have
to get rid of all of them.
So I'm gonna have you guys
split them up by genre and...
[sighing]
[soft music]
-Hi.
-I'm Becky.
-I'm-- I'm Ted Kaczynksi.
They should really move
from the Dewey Decimal System
to the Library
of Congress system.
I'd suggested it a while back,
but they still haven't, so,
now we have
to do all this again.
[laughing]
Um...
No, we're--
[change falling in payphone]
[whispering] Fuck.
Ugh. Goddamn it.
Hi, David, it's me. Yeah.
Yeah, because I was...
I was calling to talk to you
and she picked up. And I--
Well, I thought... I--
I wanted to speak
to you, not her.
I've never met her.
I thought it was
a bad time to try
to meet her over the phone.
And so I... so I hung up.
Well, can I be trusted to say
the right thing to--
to a woman, David?
Especially Linda,
with the history, and...
Oh my God, is that her
in the background?
David, fuck.
Just tell her I apologize
and ask her to leave the room
so I can talk to you
in private, please.
You domesticated yourself.
You're like, like,
like a horse that's run
into a farmer's field and...
and volunteered for somebody
to jump on your back
and put a bit in your mouth.
Well, I thought that
we shared a lot of values
and I thought that we were on
the same page of
living in the wild.
Now you're living in a zoo like
a caged animal with a trainer.
A trainer who, uh,
who you need
to run everything by. Um...
I'm sure--
oh, I bet you have too.
Like if I--
if I asked you-- I was--
I was actually gonna call to ask
for some help,
some financial help.
I just wanted
a little money that I could...
that I could repay.
But I'm sure you have--
Yeah, you would have--
Yes, you would have to ask her,
wouldn't you?
Mm-hmm.
See, that's what I mean.
[hanging up]
[engines revving]
[tense classical instrumental]
Hey!
[whistling]
Get off my land!
Get off my property.
[shouting indistinctly]
-Ted!
Man in the cabin.
Ted.
-Good morning.
-Morning. Nice day.
Yeah.
-You know, just checking
through the pass
and a little investigation
I was hoping
you could help me with.
You seen anyone, anything,
people, fooling around
with any buildings around here?
-No, only those, uh...
kids who vandalized
that cabin a while back.
Nothing since then.
-Sure.
-You talk to Steve or Tom?
-Yeah, Steve said his mill
got wrecked a while back too.
-Yeah, a while ago. Yeah.
-Or, um, motorcyclers,
they hassling you nearby here?
-No, nothing like
snowmobile season, anyway, huh?
-Exactly. Right, um...
The reason I had to ask
was we heard you got
pretty upset with some riders
from up the creek.
-Yeah, I did. I did, yeah.
Yes, assholes, though.
A couple of punks tried to--
tried to come across my--
my property and, um...
Yeah.
I wouldn't call it anything
out of the ordinary, though,
I imagine if you were
in my position, you would...
You might act the same way.
-Sure. Yeah, that's fair.
I appreciate your time.
If you, uh, hear of anything
you let me know.
-Mm-hm.
-Have a nice day.
-See you, Ted.
[man speaking
indistinctly on radio]
[audience shouting]
[man speaking indistinctly]
-I don't want to
let them get their offer,
because they don't have
credibility with us.
Some think Earth First
is a terrorist organization,
and they've
not renounced violence.
They see a difference
between terrorism and sabotage.
-All kinds of operations,
I've taken a [indistinct],
I've spiked trees,
I've still painted
equipment that works.
-Thank you, David. Thank you.
What a guy.
-...the modern industrial
system as we know it,
and one reason why we see
the modern industrial system
as being so destructive
is because it's
based on the premise
that it is for human beings
that the world exists.
The idea that human beings
are just another species
among millions of others
on the planet.
-And reminder, David Foreman
will be in the Missoula area,
speaking on September 23rd
at the John Edwards School.
This is Tom Douglas
reporting of WCGR Montana,
NPR Radio.
[ominous instrumental]
[audience cheering]
-Action!
-Action of any kind.
But let our action set the finer
points of our philosophy.
We don't have
to figure it all out.
We all don't have
to be saints on this planet
to do something for it.
It's time for a warrior society
to rise up out of the Earth.
And to put ourselves in front
of the juggernaut
of destruction.
We need warriors,
we need people
and bodies out in the field
to take down the apparatus
of this mechanized destruction
of this precious planet
that we have.
That's what my life is for.
And that's what
your lives should be for.
If you consider yourselves
eco-warriors,
you have to get out,
put your-- stand your ground
and fight! Do something!
[audience cheering loudly]
Eco Fuckers hit list,
chevron 225,
Bush Street,
San Francisco, California.
Nine-four-one-zero...
[overlapping speech]
The National Lumber
Explorer's Association.
The next day,
I started from my own cabin.
My route took me past
a beautiful spot.
A favorite place of mine where
there was a spring of pure water
that can safely
be drunk without worrying.
I stopped
and said a kind of prayer
to the spirit of the spring.
It was a prayer in which I swore
that I would take revenge
for what was being done
with the forest.
[engine whining]
[intricate classical
instrumental]
The people who are pushing all
this growth and progress garbage
deserve to be severely punished.
But our goal is less to punish
them than to propagate ideas.
Introduction. One.
The Industrial Revolution
and its consequences
have been a disaster
for the human race.
We therefore
advocate the revolution
against the industrial system.
Thirty-seven: we attribute
the social and psychological
problems with modern society
to the fact that the society
requires people to live
under conditions
radically different
from those under which
the human race evolved.
Forty-six: in order to avoid
serious psychological problems,
a human being needs goals
whose attainment
requires effort.
Sixty-nine: it is true that
primitive man is powerless
against some of the things
that threaten him,
disease, for example,
but he can accept
the risk of disease stoically.
One-seventy:
"Oh!" say the technophiles,
"Science is going to fix that.
We will conquer famine,
"eliminate
psychological suffering,
"make everybody
healthy and happy."
Yeah, sure.
That's what
they said 200 years ago.
One-eighty:
When the system becomes
sufficiently stressed
and unstable,
a revolution against
technology may be possible.
One-eighty-one: The technophiles
are taking us all
on an utterly reckless ride
into the unknown.
One eighty-five: as
for the negative consequences
of eliminating
industrial society--
well, you can't eat your cake
and have it, too.
To gain one thing you have
to sacrifice another.
Becky.
[laughing]
I got a-- I got a fish!
I got one!
Yeah.
-Whoo! Good job!
-Yeah!
-Holy--
That's amazing!
[Ted chuckling]
It's big!
[ominous instrumental]
-No, no, there's nothing that
could ever be important enough
for you to get in touch with me.
Even if Mother dies,
I don't wanna hear about it.
Mm-hmm.
I have nothing more--
I have nothing more to--
David-- David.
I just need a yes or no.
Are you gonna--
Will you please
help me with money?
What do you want?
You want me to beg?
I'm begging, David.
I'm on my fucking knees,
right in a phone booth,
begging you.
Do you feel powerful, David?
Do you feel empowered?
The-- the strong, dominant male.
Finally, you have your brother
on his knees, asking for money.
Goddamn it, David!
Cocksucker, man!
I-- I'm asking for--
Yes. One thousand.
Thank you, David.
Yes, I know.
Yes, it is a brotherly act
and I-- it's noted.
You too.
Hugs and kisses to Linda.
[chuckling]
Okay.
[distorted instrumental]
Boredom is almost non-existent
once you've become adapted
to life in the woods.
If you don't have any work
that needs to be done,
you can sit for hours
at a time, just doing nothing.
Just listening to the birds
or the wind or the silence.
Watching the shadows move
as the sun travels
or simply looking
at familiar objects.
And you don't get bored.
You're just a piece.
[gunshot]
[airplane engine roaring]
[sound becomes distorted]
To the San Francisco Examiner,
we have waited until now
to announce ourselves
because our earlier bombs
were embarrassingly ineffectual.
The injuries they inflicted
were relatively minor.
In order to influence people,
a terrorist group
must show a certain
amount of success.
When we finally realized
the amount of smokeless powder
needed to blow up
anyone or anything
was too large to be practical,
we decided to take
a couple years off
and learn something
about explosives
and develop an effective bomb.
In closure...
the aim
of the Freedom Club
is the complete
and permanent destruction
of modern industrial society
in every part of the world.
... potentially
by long distance,
there's not a place
to have conversation between
the perpetrator and the victims.
So, the fact that we have
one eyewitness, which is just
luck on our part, is really...
We have looked
at all of the victims
meticulously.
As to any correlation, so far
it has just not being fruitful.
Well, you have--
you have a wide range,
actually, you have
corporate executives,
you have one bomb placed aboard
an American Airlines aircraft,
also in the late '70s.
There have
been college professors.
Two types of bombs
in the sense that about half
of them are mailed,
letter bombs or package bombs.
And about half of them
have been placed
in a position
where someone would, uh,
disturb the package.
[reporter continues
speaking indistinctly]
Well, as long as I'm going
to throw everything away anyway,
instead of having to shoot it
out with the cops or something,
I will go up to Canada,
and take off into the woods
with a rifle
and try to live off the country.
If that doesn't work out
and if I can
get back to civilization
before I starve,
then I will come back here
and kill someone I hate.
I need to renew my passport.
And...
Clearly, we are in a position
to do a great deal of damage.
And it doesn't appear
that the FBI
is gonna catch
us anytime soon.
The FBI is a joke.
FBI, suck my cock.
[explosion rumbling]
[alarm bell ringing]
[clearing throat]
[dinging bell]
-Morning.
-Uh, morning.
I have a complaint about
the Montana Telephone Company.
It concerns, uh, some of your
payphones in Lincoln, Montana.
These pay phones consistently
malfunction in such a manner
as to steal a caller's quarters.
You put a quarter in and then
it either gets jammed
or it doesn't register.
And then the coin release
doesn't work
so that either you can't
put the call through
and the quarters are lost,
or the call does go through,
but you end up paying 25 cents
or 50 cents more
than the price of the call.
This problem has persisted
for several years.
This is not the first time
that I have, uh--
that I have complained,
although it is the first time
that I've complained in person,
but I've spoken to
the operators about it
several times and nothing
has been done over the years.
The main offender
is actually the payphone
on the corner of Highway 200
and Stemple Pass.
I'm forced to use that one
on occasion because
it's the only one
that the company provides
that offers any level
of privacy at all.
But it steals at least
50% of my quarters.
It swindles me.
And the company is aware
of this offending booth.
That's a criminal act.
My money is being stolen.
-On behalf
of the Montana phone company,
I apologize
for your inconvenience.
Uh, do you happen
to have a record
of how much money
you've lost over the years?
I do. $5.75.
-$5.75?
-Yes. Yes, this year.
-This year.
-Yes.
-Hmm.
-I have a letter
which, uh, you could give
to your superiors,
and it contains all the details
that I have
just relayed to you now.
-I would love to give
it to my superiors, but...
we can only accept letters
through the post.
I can't hand deliver a letter.
Do you see the problem?
-I came in here to bring
you the letter in person.
-I appreciate that.
But I can't take it.
You have a wonderful day.
I'm gonna write to
my congressman about this.
Okay.
[dreamy, melancholic
instrumental]
[Ted]
During my romantic phase,
I continued to have fantasies
of a primitive life,
but I tended strongly
to embellish
this with romantic details
like horns resounding through
the forest, savage-looking
tunics and bearskin
and so forth.
Sequence of small advances,
there will be no rational
and effective public resistance.
It is not possible to make
a lasting compromise
between technology and freedom
because technology is by far
the more powerful social force
and continually...
erodes on freedom
through repeated compromise.
[muttering indistinctly]
As society
and the problems that face it
become more and more complex,
and as machines become
more and more intelligent,
people will let machines
make more and more
of their decisions for them,
simply because
machine-made decisions
will bring better results
than manmade ones.
Eventually,
a stage may be reached
at which the decisions
necessary to keep
the system running will be
so complex that human beings
will be incapable
of making them intelligently.
At that stage, the machines
will be in effective control.
People won't be able
to just turn the machines
off because they will
be so dependent on them
that turning them
off would amount to suicide.
[loud thud, horn honking]
[man groaning]
[men laughing]
[laughter continues]
[laughing]
-I must have been going
40 fucking miles per hour.
[laughing]
[chain clanking]
[screeching]
-You know, my parents...
pushed me so hard in academia,
I never really learned
to be at ease around women.
-Can you tell me your heart,
Ted?
You're quite right.
You love me.
-I do.
I do. See, actually, uh...
It's the truth. I love you.
I love you so much I'm gonna
let go of these handlebars.
-No, don't do it!
-I'm gonna let go!
-No, please don't.
-Okay, one hand.
Just one hand, okay?
Come on, there you go,
there you go!
-Put it down!
-Okay, okay.
Oh, the right hand come off!
You're my right hand.
You might have to be
the right hand of a man.
Okay, okay.
[both laughing]
[Ted whooping]
[laughing]
We are an anarchist group...
...calling ourselves...
Calling ourselves FC.
...FC.
Notice that the postmark
on this envelope
precedes a newsworthy event
that will happen about the time
you receive this letter,
if nothing goes wrong.
We are getting tired
of making bombs.
It's no fun having to spend
all your evenings and weekends
preparing dangerous mixtures,
filing trigger mechanisms
out of scraps of metal
or searching the Sierras
for a place
isolated enough
to test the bomb.
[explosion rumbling]
So we offer a bargain.
We have a long article
between 29,000
and 37,000 words
that we want to have published.
If you can get it published
according to our requirements,
we will permanently desist
from terrorist activities.
If the answer is satisfactory,
we will finish typing
the manuscript and send
it to you. If the answer
is unsatisfactory,
we will start building
our next bomb.
-[explosion rumbling]
-[objects clattering]
FC.
[chuckling]
I am choked with frustration
at my inability to get
my stinking fucking family
off my back once and for all.
No, it does include you, David.
It emphatically
and specifically
includes you, yeah.
Of course, you-- you're part
of my stinking fucking family.
It's not an emotional decision.
It's a logical decision, David.
It's logical.
Yeah, I have my own life.
I have my own life, David,
I think my own thoughts
and then I do what
I think I should do,
as opposed to
what other people--
Look, I'm not-- I'm not--
I'm not gonna do this again.
I'm not gonna do this again
with you, David. All right?
I do not want to hear
from you or any member
of my stinking
fucking family ever again.
Goodbye.
Hi.
[driver speaking indistinctly]
Yeah, yeah.
-This is CNN breaking news.
-Hello from CNN News Center
in Atlanta,
I'm Natalie Allen.
We're about to take live
a news conference
from San Francisco
headed up by the FBI today
concerning the bomb threat
that has come in.
The person behind the threat
may be the so-called Unabomber,
and the threat has resulted
in heightened security
at five airports in--
Small debris,
big debris, dust--
I'm relieved to
see a lot of security around--
...and determination?
-Well, our position is we will
keep the security measures
in place until
the matter is resolved.
It's been more
than five days since
the Unabomber threatened
to blow up an airliner
flying in or out
of Los Angeles by July 4th.
But after 17 years,
23 injuries and three deaths,
the Unabomber
is nothing to joke about.
Experts say the Unabomber
is stepping up his activities
because he's jealous
of the attention given
to the Oklahoma City bombing
which stole the thunder
from his last
package bomb explosion.
Experts also believe
the Unabomber
may be headed for a fall.
I think he's on a high now.
I think he's all pumped up.
I think he's intoxicated
with his own power,
and I think at this point,
he's most vulnerable.
[indistinct]
I think he might
have made some major mistakes.
The FBI is unable to catch him,
and now the Unabomber
has raised the stakes again.
In the letter sent
to The Washington Post
and the New York Times this
week, the Unabomber has pledged
to stop his murderous spree
if these leading American papers
will publish
a 35,000-word manifesto.
In the document the Unabomber
condemns modern technology
and says computers have
created a world in which humans
are mere cogs in the machine.
That proposal has led to a life
or death question
for The Post and
should they cave in to threats
and publish, or refuse
to let themselves be
used as a platform--
In paragraph 125,
we use an analogy of a weak
neighbor who was left destitute
by a strong neighbor who takes
all his land by forcing on
him a series of compromises.
But suppose now that
the strong neighbor gets sick
so that he is unable
to defend himself.
The weak neighbor
can force the strong one
to give him his land back
or he can kill him.
If he lets the strong man
survive and only forces him
to give his land back,
he is a fool,
because when the strong man gets
well, he will again take all
the land for himself.
The only sensible alternative
for the weaker man is to kill
a strong one while he has
the chance. In the same way,
while the industrial
system is sick,
we must destroy it.
If we compromise with it
and let it recover
from its sickness,
it will eventually wipe
out all of our freedom.
We're back
at CNN in Washington--
We hear somebody yelling,
"It ain't gonna happen."
Trying to catch back up
to O.J. Simpson heading past
LAX on the 405 freeway north.
Again, you see traffic
in the South lanes stopping
and looking,
police cars trailing,
other traffic, stopping off to
the right.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, Gilbert,
you should take this,
even though it isn't for you.
-Maybe it's a bomb.
You should send
that off to Bill.
Maybe it's a love letter.
Oh, it's Oklahoma City.
Oh, be careful.
This Postal
Service circulates a special
training tape illustrating
detection techniques.
It also graphically
demonstrates the power
of a mail bomb by use
of a dummy in a mock-up office.
He's matching
wits, he's matching wits
with everybody who comes
into conflict with him.
This is the arena.
This is the Coliseum.
"It's me against the lion."
Add to this
the letter received
by The New York Times, a letter
sent before the latest bombings.
It warned of a newsworthy
event and claimed responsibility
in the name of an anarchist
group calling itself FC.
We don't have
a shred of evidence
that he's connected
with any other people.
The FBI says
it's up to The New York Times,
whether they comply
with the Unabomber's
demand to publish
a long-written piece.
But the FBI seems
to doubt the sincerity
of the Unabomber's offer.
That's because,
in the same letter,
he reserves the right
to engage in sabotage
intended to damage
property instead of humans.
[somber music]
[birds chirping]
[ragged breathing]
[heavy breathing]
[flame whooshing]
[tense music]
[intense musical buildup]
[birds chirping]
This morning in Washington,
the news dominating
street corner conversation
was what was on the front page
of this morning's paper.
The Washington Post
had published a special section
containing the
35,000-word manifesto
of the serial mail bomber
known as Unabomber.
The post cited quote,
"Public safety reasons"
for its decision,
taken and paid for jointly
with The New York Times.
In an unusual joint statement,
publishers Donald Graham
of The Post
and Arthur Sulzberger Jr.
of the Times justified
publication.
Quote, "If we fail
to do so, the Unabomber--"
[laughing]
-Yeah! Yeah!
Unfortunately,
for attorney general and the FBI
have all surrendered
authority to the Unabomber.
I can see this fellow
who has to be right now
having a psychological orgasm.
They've elevated him
to controlling,
like a puppeteer, cities,
newspapers and everything else.
Where does it go from here?
It's difficult
to argue with his logic.
You can bet that neither
The New York Times
nor The Washington Post
would have published his essay
absent his track record
as a murderer
and his, therefore,
totally credible threat
that he would kill again.
[opera music]
[sighs]
[fire crackling]
"I disagree
with the popular belief
"that you are a serial killer
and should be treated like one.
"I pointed out that serial
killers derive the whole
"of their satisfaction
from the act of killing.
"In your case,
I suggested that killing
"was merely a means to the end.
"Your objectives are much bolder
and infinitely more elaborate.
"You want to change the world.
"Bob Guccione, Editor,
Penthouse Magazine."
[opera music continues]
[engine rumbling]
Please.
Sure. Sure, come over,
David. Please, yeah.
[sighs]
[plane approaching]
[footsteps retreating]
[metal clattering]
-Ted? It's Gary!
Hey, can you come
to show us your boundary?
We're trying to figure it out
where your property line ends.
-Morning, Ted.
-Morning.
-This is Bob and Mike.
They're miners.
-Good morning, Mr. Kaczynski.
We've been doing a little mining
in the area and, well, we just
got a little bit confused about
where your property line ends.
And we were hoping
that you could show us
exactly where this line is.
-Yeah. Yeah, no. All right,
let me just get my jacket--
Get your fucking hands off me!
Get your fucking
hands off of me!
-Mr. Kaczynski, we are the FBI.
We have a warrant
to search your cabin.
-Okay. Okay.
Yeah.
[shaky breathing]
-Got him!
[somber music]
...we're told
by federal law enforcement
officials is that they received
a tip on this person indirectly
from a family member.
This man's brother contacted
a prominent Washington D.C.
lawyer, who in turn
got in touch with the FBI
and told them about this person,
and they've had him under
surveillance now for about
a week or so, we're told.
They are preparing right now
to serve a search warrant,
or probably in the process
of serving it now.
We don't know whether this
person is at home,
or what they expect
to find there.
If they're just going to
find evidence that they would
take from the house,
possible evidence,
or whether they're actually
going to find something.
We don't know whether there's
been any arrest yet...