[dramatic music]
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
announcer: The following
is a presentation
of HBO Sports.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
- ♪ Mi mi mi mi mi mi mi ♪
♪ Mi mi mi mi mi mi mi ♪
♪ Love ♪
[trilling]
♪ Do re mi fa so la ti ♪
♪ Do ♪
[jazz music]
♪ ♪
- Folks, this is Clay Cooper.
You're listening to
"The Clay Cooper Experience,"
Grand Country Studios, 106.3.
And we're visiting
with Terry Bradshaw.
"The Terry Bradshaw Show,"
four nights only
at the Clay Cooper Theatre.
- How are you doing?
- Good.
- Welcome to one of
the greatest shows on Earth.
- On Earth.
- We've heard.
- This is the number one
question
people say...
- Okay.
- When they see
the Terry Bradshaw posters
and this and that.
They say,
"Terry Bradshaw's here?"
- "What's he do?"
- "Well, what's he gonna do?"
- I know.
♪ This is my blood ♪
♪ It's on display ♪
- I'm like, "Well, he's
gonna be Terry Bradshaw.
He's gonna entertain you."
- I bought my wife a water bed.
She calls it the Dead Sea.
- [laughter]
[rim shot]
- I got so many stories--
all the stuff I went through.
All right.
That's it for the warm-up.
And that's how the show goes.
You got a sample of
the greatness that's coming.
[upbeat music]
- Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen,
and welcome
to the Clay Cooper Theatre.
- Are you still
putting makeup on me?
- Yes. Well, you were talking.
- I mean, do I really need
that much makeup?
- You don't have that much on.
[indistinct chatter]
- I'll get your tickets.
- I wish I could bust loose
with some Pavarotti tonight
and really shake 'em up.
- Let's do it.
♪ ♪
- If I could do anything
in my life...
- Showtime.
- If, say, God says, "Terry,
I'm gonna start you over,"
what would you do?
[sighs]
This is what I'd do.
- Tonight, we are proud
to present
a man recently voted
sexiest man alive
by "Tractor Magazine"
three years in a row!
[laughter]
Please welcome to the stage
the one, the only...
Terry Bradshaw!
[cheers and applause]
- I always felt like
I was different and special,
even though I wasn't.
I'd done nothing.
But I didn't think
in my mind that I was--
that I thought
like normal kids.
Does that make sense?
I just felt different.
And...
I never--for some reason,
that never changed.
I still feel different.
[laughs]
I know I'm not normal.
The reason I know
I'm not normal--
too many people tell me,
"You're not normal."
[laughs]
[liquid splashes]
Oh, no.
I just spilled my coffee.
How did I do--
- That's all right.
- No. Okay, we're good.
- It's all right.
- We're good.
[upbeat music playing]
Hey, folks. How you doing?
♪ ♪
How you doing?
Good to see you.
Thanks for coming out!
♪ ♪
♪ Out in the country,
past the city-limits sign ♪
♪ Well, there's a honky-tonk
out near the county line ♪
♪ The joint starts hoppin'
every night ♪
♪ When the sun goes down ♪
[piano playing]
♪ They got whiskey, women,
and music and smoke ♪
♪ Where all the cowboy folk
go to boot-scootin' boogie ♪
You ready, Kelly?
- Ready!
both: ♪ Heel, toe, do-si-do ♪
♪ Come on, baby, let's go ♪
- Boot-scootin'.
♪ ♪
both: ♪ Cadillac, blackjack ♪
♪ Baby, meet me out back ♪
- We're gonna boogie.
♪ ♪
both: ♪ Well, now,
get down, turn around ♪
♪ Go to town,
Boot-scootin' boogie ♪
- All right, let's warm it up!
- Whoo!
[music continues]
- I didn't wanna go through
life...
without doing something,
accomplishing something.
You want to separate yourself
from...everybody.
And I think to myself...
"Have I done that?"
Well, maybe when I'd won
four Super Bowls,
I thought I had done it.
But Joe Montana tied it,
and Brady blew it away
and got seven.
He lost three too.
So that's not it,
so where else?
Well, I'm in television.
I look at humor
as opposed to Xs and Os.
In my first playoff game,
I about
tinkled down my britches leg,
I'm telling you.
[lively music]
I love entertaining.
♪ Ba ba ba ba ba ♪
I did movies.
Hey, Joe!
- Yeah?
- Tackle that car.
You choose things that
are extremely challenging.
[clattering]
You owe me, Bandit.
You think going out there
is easy on that stage?
[music continues]
That is not easy.
I do it
because it separates me.
It puts me in a different road.
I'm not gonna say
at a different level,
but it puts me
on a different path,
and I like that, you know?
Not everybody can do this.
♪ Heel, toe, do-si-do ♪
♪ Come on, baby, let's go ♪
Boot-scootin'.
♪ ♪
♪ Cadillac, blackjack ♪
♪ Baby, meet me out back ♪
We're gonna boogie.
♪ Yeah, take it down,
turn around, go to town ♪
♪ Boot-scootin' boogie ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Well, now, get down ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Go to town ♪
♪ We're doin'
the boot-scootin' ♪
♪ Boogie ♪
♪ ♪
All right!
[cheers and applause]
Thank you
for coming out tonight.
[organ music playing]
A lot of you
are probably wondering
why I wanna do
something like this.
Why not?
I just had to do it.
Is that how you say it?
There's just some things you
get an opportunity to do
in life.
You just have to do 'em.
And it's a story about my NFL
career and life, I guess.
It's been a lot of therapy.
[laughter]
I mean, as you can imagine,
God knows I've had
a lot of therapy.
And so it's gonna be fun.
And, uh, I think it's
important to know who you are.
Uh, I'm no Merle Haggard
or Glen Campbell.
I wish.
I'm just Terry Bradshaw,
a little simple guy
from Shreveport.
♪ ♪
I grew up with two brothers.
My mom's name
was Novis Genoa Gay.
My dad was William Marvin.
I have a older brother, Gary,
13 months.
A younger brother, Craig.
Um, three boys.
We're from Shreveport
in Louisiana.
[scattered cheers]
Growing up as a kid,
I spent most of my summers
on my grandparents' farm.
Watermelons and cotton.
They had two Clydesdales,
Tony and Shorty.
Um, we milked their Jersey cow,
and that introduced me
to farming, which I love.
Well, this thing's
just downright cute.
I'm not good
at a lot of things,
but I'm really good
at a couple.
Horses--
my uncles all rode horses.
So there was a love of horses
from the very minute
I touched one.
Hey, buddy. Hey, sweetie.
Singing, because my--
two of my uncles
had gorgeous singing voices.
And they used to sing
all the time.
And I--I would sing
And the football was just...
happened in P.E.
You ever had a first love?
- Yes.
- Yeah, who hasn't, right?
My first love was football.
I was raised five years
in Iowa, and...
- Yeah!
[cheers and applause]
- You from Iowa?
- Yes!
- Hey, man.
Let me as you something.
What do you think about
this electricity?
[laughter]
[rim shot]
[laughs]
That's just funny.
[laughter]
[laughs]
Oh, God. Quit it, Terry.
Nice to stand in front of
the Sears and Roebuck window
on Main Street
in Clinton, Iowa.
- I'm from there!
- You stood there?
You too? What is this?
[laughter]
- Whoo!
- Don't talk
unless I ask you to.
[laughter]
I'm being paid up here,
don't forget.
You're not getting paid.
No, you paid.
No, matter of fact,
you can talk.
I don't care.
[laughter]
But you stood there
at the Sears window?
And I looked in.
They had
all the Hawkeyes stuff.
And I loved--and get this,
it was like one of those,
what do you call it,
premonitions?
Is that what you call it?
- Premonitions.
- Yeah, that.
Who said that?
- Me.
- Where'd you graduate?
You got a college degree?
You gotta. That's a big word.
Premonition. Yeah, that's good.
Can you spell it?
- P-R-E...
[laughter]
- So I'm premon--I'm prema--
I'm premonitioning.
And I'm seeing that
black and gold helmet
and all that uniform.
And I see that football there
and I went,
"God, if Santa Claus
would bring me a football,
I'd be the happiest guy
in the world."
And I got it.
I got my first football,
and it was like,
you know, I smelled it,
put my hands on it.
I--it was just love
at first touch.
Every day, I throw a football
at my ranch
either against the house,
up on the hill,
or for the dogs to chase.
And tonight, I would like Kelly
to go out here
and just grab me someone.
And bring them up here, Kelly.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
- Yes.
He kinda looks
like a football player.
Okay. Oh.
There we go.
Terry, I found you a good guy.
- Oh, my God.
It's me!
Hey, it's me.
[laughter and applause]
What a good-looking man!
Lord bless you, brother.
Lord bless you.
God, I wanna thank you tonight
for sending
this really handsome man
up here to play catch.
- Amen.
- Amen, brother.
What's your name?
- Ron Close.
- Ron, Terry Bradshaw.
- And I've got a brother
named Gary.
- Gary Close.
- Yes, sir.
- Are y'all very close?
- We're real close.
[laughter]
[rim shot]
- Hey, what are you doing
back there?
[laughter]
Well, good.
- What do you think?
- I think a lot. Here.
Where you from?
- Guess where I played--
ask me where I played football.
- Oh, okay.
Where'd you play football?
- Pittsburg.
- Steelers?
[cheers and applause]
Did you?
Did you really?
I didn't play with you, did I?
- No.
- Huh?
- Pittsburg, Kansas.
- Oh! [laughs]
[rim shot]
Hey. Ron. Ron.
The jokes are mine, okay?
My dad knew how much
I loved football.
I would lay in bed,
and I'd throw it up,
and I'd see how close
I could get to the ceiling.
And I'd chunk it,
and I'd chunk it.
Thunk. I'd hit the roof.
"Terry!"
Yo!
"Stop throwing that ball
up against the ceiling!"
Yes, sir!
[snoring]
Thunk.
[laughs]
[upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
♪ Well, my papaw ♪
♪ He taught me about
workin' the land ♪
♪ How to drive a team
of Clydesdales ♪
♪ With the touch of his hand ♪
I remember when I was in
the seventh grade,
there was a guy out
on the recess,
and he was imitating Elvis.
♪ Not one TV ♪
And I got around
and watched this guy,
and I would marvel at--
he had, like,
50 people around him.
And it didn't faze him.
I mean, he was eating it up.
And I thought,
"Now, that's pretty cool."
♪ Humble beginnings ♪
Come on, Kelly.
both: ♪ Humble as pie ♪
♪ Simple and humble ♪
- So the only thing, since I
couldn't really sing...
♪ Lord, say your prayers,
boys ♪
That was like, well,
if I can't do this,
I can teach myself
how to throw a football.
♪ Humble beginnings ♪
♪ ♪
♪ For people like us ♪
[music slows]
Now, the best things in life...
[fiddle plays]
Are love and family.
Make it humble beginnings
for a poor old, fat,
water-retaining country boy...
[laughter]
♪ Like me ♪
[music continues]
Always wanted to be
a quarterback,
but I wasn't very good.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, yeah. There you go.
I wasn't good
in the seventh grade.
in the eighth grade.
I wasn't good
in the ninth grade.
Um, I wasn't good
in the tenth grade.
My body hadn't come together.
You know, I was just clumsy.
But I could throw
the football.
[crowd cheering]
My senior year,
after I played in the
all-star game in Louisiana,
I got a lot of offers.
And Louisiana Tech,
I was their number-one guy.
So I went to Louisiana Tech.
I went there on an academic
scholarship, and so...
[laughter]
There you go. Take a shot.
None of you--I'll bet you
anything I graduated
with a higher degree
than anybody in here.
3.98 was my GPA.
[scattered cheers and applause]
That's what I thought.
Not a lot of 'plauding now,
is there?
[laughter]
Yeah.
'Course, it's cumulative.
You add up my freshman,
sophomore, junior...
[rim shot]
[laughs]
You can use that.
That's a good one right there.
You can use it.
It's an original, too,
by the way.
I should have started
my freshman year,
but I didn't.
My sophomore year, I split time
with Phil Robertson,
the "Duck Dynasty" guy,
who I really liked
and respected.
Uh, but I knew he didn't care
anything about football.
He cared about duck hunting.
Two years,
I sat behind that guy,
and all he wanted to do
was shoot stuff.
And he'd come in,
he'd tell me--
My nickname was "Blond Bomber."
I had hair back then.
And he'd go, "Blond Bomber.
Hey. Blond Bomber.
"I'm gonna tell you right now,
buddy,
"uh, d--uh, d--[stutters]
"uh, ducks!
Dem ducks is flyin' high."
[chuckles]
"Hey, when practice is over,
we'll go shoot some of 'em.
You want to?"
No.
No, I don't want to.
I want you to get knocked out
so I can start.
[laughter]
And he did.
And I did.
Rest of my career was...
you know, was good.
[upbeat rock music]
♪ ♪
I didn't know anything
about reading coverages.
I could drop back and wing it
and let it fly.
♪ ♪
I just filled with confidence,
man.
I just--I got good.
I played in a couple
of all-star games
and was co-MVP
in the Senior Bowl.
Going up against
all the major--
you know, the "big" guys,
and you go,
"Hey, I can play
with these guys."
You watch them throw,
and you go,
"Jeez. That's nothing.
Watch this."
Phew!
- The 35th annual
National Football League
selection meeting
is now in session.
First choice, first round,
Pittsburgh Steelers.
Steelers select Terry Bradshaw,
quarterback, Louisiana Tech.
- Where'd that come from?
[laughing]
How was I--how did I get to be
the first pick in the draft?
I don't wanna be
the first pick in the draft.
Looking back on it now,
I'm like,
"Oh, that's kind of cool,"
but really and truthfully,
I shouldn't have been.
I went to this small school,
and...
So immature, so much to learn.
In high school,
I only started one year
and in college only two.
And so I can be patient.
Why would anybody pick me
in the first round?
I don't know why
Chuck Noll drafted me.
Let's turn the light up,
and let's take
some questions here.
- Who was your favorite player?
You were my favorite player.
- My favorite player
was Joe Namath.
[cheers and applause]
That was the guy I wanted
to be like was Joe Namath.
No second guy or third guy.
It was Joe Namath.
I wanted to be Broadway Terry.
[laughter]
Serious. I loved him.
I wanted to be adored
like Joe Namath.
He had the hunched shoulder,
you know,
and he had
the greatest release,
the coolest way of
getting rid of the football.
And he is just amazing.
And he did movies!
- You don't hit something
that looks that good.
- You know,
and he was charismatic
and everybody flocked to him.
I wanted to be that.
But my mom and dad...
"You be nice. You be kind.
You don't drink.
"You don't wear
white football shoes
"when nobody else
has got white football shoes.
And you don't talk about,
you know, sleeping with women."
- It seems almost un-American
to me for a bachelor not to,
you know, go around
having a drink with a lady
now and then.
- Do I wish I had that?
Absolutely, I wish I had that.
- Just trying to get by.
[balls clatter]
Look at that shot.
- I admired him so much.
I wanted to be that.
- Roll number two.
Could you repeat--
Could you say, "When I
found out I was number one,
that was the greatest day
of my life"?
- Sure.
[clears throat]
Being--when I
was drafted number one,
that was the greatest day
of my life.
There's no doubt about that.
- Try that once again.
Try to say it a little slower
and a little, uh...
- All right.
Being drafted number one
was no doubt
the greatest day of my life.
I wanted everybody to like me.
It's a great challenge,
and I love challenges.
It brings the best out of me,
and so I'm looking forward
to it.
I see those interviews,
I want to throw up.
That's why I'm going up there.
It's to make them a winner.
Nothing else.
"Duh. We gonna--we gonna--
Oh, we got a good team.
We're gonna win this year."
Oh...
I think I can do the job.
If I didn't,
I wouldn't go to Pittsburgh.
I wouldn't even play
professional football
if I didn't think I could
move right in and do the job.
Now, if I can't
prove it to Coach Noll
and to the football players,
then something's wrong,
'cause I believe I can do it.
- Amen.
- Whoo!
[cheers and applause]
- If you take 72-year-old Terry
and take him back
to 20-year-old Terry--
'cause that's how old I was--
it wouldn't be like that.
I would say
totally different stuff.
I had this goody-two-shoe--
I wish I'd have just said,
"Fuck ya!"
I wish I had just gone
into the NFL and said,
"Good to be here
with Pittsburgh,
this piece-of-shit team
that drafted me number one."
You know, "What the fuck
are we gonna do now?"
That is a part
of my personality
that I wish I used more.
You know, I wish
I'd have been like that.
But I wasn't.
- I'd like to introduce
the number-one draft choice
of the National Football
League,
Terry Bradshaw.
[laughter]
- I was just a man-child,
really.
- That was such a good take.
- How 'bout that, huh?
Whoo!
I had the size. I had the arm.
I had everything, but--
everybody knows this--
I was extremely immature.
Oh, baby, that's number one!
Got to go now!
No way mentally, emotionally,
socially
ready to be a professional
quarterback.
The football world
might as well wake up
and just take what I'm saying
and heed it,
'cause we're gonna be
a winner this year.
I'm sure of it.
I really,
really had to grow up.
And that was gonna take time.
[upbeat music]
- In the opener
against Houston,
he was caught for a safety,
and the Steelers lost.
The next Sunday in Denver,
they dropped their second game
and Bradshaw again
was thrown for a safety.
Incredibly, the next week
against the Browns,
he was caught for his third
safety in as many games,
and the team lost again.
♪ ♪
- If you could go back
and talk to that kid
right now...
- [laughs]
- What would you tell that kid?
- [sighs]
I would tell Terry,
"Hey, bub,
you'd better get tough.
"You'd better get emotionally
and mentally tough,
"'cause this is not
going to be easy.
It's gonna be like this...
and a whole bunch of that."
[dramatic music]
You drop back and you're
trying to figure out
what they do,
and you're sacked.
♪ ♪
You drop back, and you're
trying to figure out
what they do,
and you're forced to scramble
because you're not making
quick enough decisions.
And that's what I was doing.
♪ ♪
I had a rookie record
for interceptions.
I'm sitting there going,
"God. How bad can you be?"
I lost my confidence, folks.
I guess I got the twisties.
[laughter]
Seriously.
And to a point to where I...
I couldn't even throw
the football.
I couldn't deliver it
the way I did my entire life.
♪ ♪
I was having a hard time
of accepting the fact
that my ass wasn't that good.
I may be big and fast
and can throw it a mile,
but I wasn't that good.
And...it was embarrassing,
and it was disappointing.
Way beyond disappointing.
♪ ♪
I threw a lot
of interceptions...
which meant, you know,
I couldn't read coverages.
So therefore,
I'm not very smart.
They started calling me dumb.
That was a new one
right there,
the dumb image.
- The label of dumbness
gets placed on a quarterback,
it's not done by the fans.
It's done by the reporters
and the press
that feed these hungry people
information
which they're gullible enough
to believe.
They say, "Well, no wonder
we're not scoring any points.
"He's a dumb quarterback.
He can't even find his car
after the game, you know?"
And so that creates an image
and one that's hard
to overcome.
It was just--
you can tell,
my reaction right now--
not something I take kindly.
On the bubble--
go with the bubble.
They haven't seen it.
- Terry Bradshaw is a very,
very bright young man.
I think that, uh,
because he's from Louisiana
and he's a Southerner,
uh, you know,
and he doesn't talk, maybe,
the same as all of us,
the people have
the tendency to figure,
"Well, maybe he's not smart
because he doesn't speak
the way we do."
- I'd like to say hello to...
my Uncle Bobby and Aunt Margie
and my mother and dad
and my Uncle Duck,
all my friends
down in Holly, Louisiana.
I may be from the South
and I may not be
culturally, socially,
whatever it is you're wantin'
your quarterback to be.
But that was the one time...
That seriously,
I wanted to hurt somebody,
'cause that pissed me off.
I'd never been booed.
I'd never been benched.
I--all of these things
were so...
[crowd booing]
So, um...they were nightmares.
And I just didn't know
how to handle it.
And it seriously got to me.
[crowd booing]
I don't go out
to the restaurants
that I used to frequent.
Uh, don't read the newspapers
because they're gonna say
bad things about you.
So you're crushed
a little bit there.
You take my career
and take it now in the NFL.
I would've been cut
after three years.
Three years. Gone.
I've been told by my coach,
"You should--
"Why don't you study
like Unitas?
Why don't you study
like Bob Griese?"
Well, hell, I don't
know how they study.
How do they study?
It was so hard to learn
all the ins and outs
of football.
I don't recall studying
in college.
I--it was just like,
"You gotta do all this?"
[crowd cheering]
I've gotten very comfortable
with not being perfect.
And I don't have a problem
saying I have ADHD,
ADD--call it what you
wanna call it.
And I don't use it
as an excuse.
You can't say, "Oh, that's why
I didn't pass the ACT test."
"Oh, that's why I am
the way I am."
"Oh, that's why I'm
bouncing off walls,"
because those are excuses.
And I don't like
to give excuses for failures.
When I was being benched early,
I went in and asked
to be traded.
Kansas City wanted me.
[laughter]
And I wanted--[chuckles]
And I went and told Chuck,
I said,
"Why don't you let me go?"
and he told me, you know--
he told me how great I was
and I had to remind him
I was his backup quarterback.
[laughter]
I never got really
comfortable...
with my relationship
with Chuck.
Never was comfortable with him,
me and him.
Just uncomfortable.
I was scared shitless of him.
He scared me to death.
- How would you describe
your relationship with Terry?
- Businesslike.
You know, it was all business.
[lively music]
You know, I think you see
a lot of Terry
on TV right now.
He's fun-loving,
kind of devil-may-care.
And we couldn't have that
in our quarterback.
- I wasn't his kind
of quarterback,
and he wasn't my kind of coach.
♪ ♪
Taking me out of a game,
putting me back in a game,
would devastate me.
Grab me, yell at me--
devastated.
Make me stand up in a chair
while he chewed my ass out
in front of the team--
destroyed me.
Nothing good,
as far as I'm concerned,
comes from screaming
and hollering.
Not a--I never screamed
at a player in 14 years.
You love on me,
I do my best work.
You scream and holler at me,
I'm not very good.
I'm kind of a sissy about it,
I guess, but--
I'm a tough guy,
but I do get my feelings hurt.
He wanted players
that were committed,
that would work hard,
that hated losing.
He didn't want
to fall in love.
He didn't want to have you
over for dinner.
You know, he didn't want
to get like--
He didn't want
to get like this.
And once I realized that,
you know, then you just go,
"Fuck it."
[chuckles]
♪ Bye-bye, love ♪
♪ Bye-bye, happiness ♪
♪ Hello, loneliness ♪
♪ I think I'm gonna cry ♪
All the shit I had
to go through, you know,
to win his favor...
♪ Bye-bye, sweet caress ♪
♪ Hello, emptiness ♪
You re--you get the--
you get the feeling I'm having
a hard time describing him?
♪ There goes my baby ♪
He was a strange bird to me.
♪ She sure looks happy ♪
It's almost like he's glad
I'm second string
so I can sit there
and really suffer.
That's kind of the way
I look at it.
So I just hated him
even more, you know?
"Okay. Fine, asshole."
♪ Goodbye, romance
that might have been ♪
But he won, because you know
what he ended up doing?
He made me tough.
I became a real asshole.
But I had to, to survive.
- Bradshaw, still going.
Boy, he's a horse.
- ♪ Bye-bye, love,
ba ba ba ba ♪
♪ Bye-bye, sweet caress ♪
I just got hateful
in my spirit on the inside.
You understand what I'm saying?
Nobody knew.
It's just the way I felt.
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ ♪
All right!
[cheers and applause]
But early in my career,
I guess he just...
saw something different.
You know, talking about this
wears me out.
[laughs]
I mean, seriously.
Do you have any
Bradshaw Bourbon around?
[laughing]
Hey, if you buy
Bradshaw Bourbon, there's a--
there's a proof on there--
51.9%.
And the 51.9% is my
NFL completion percentage.
[laughter, cheers]
No, I know. And that's bad.
[laughter]
That's really bad.
- Here comes Terry Bradshaw
now.
Terry, Terry, Terry.
[paper ripping]
Good luck today, baby.
- Okay, Franco.
- Watch yourself.
- See you later.
We all have defining moments
in our life.
There's always something
that is a turning point.
Mine was
the Immaculate Reception.
[cheers and applause]
In the playoffs,
at home in Pittsburgh...
- It's down to one big play.
Fourth down
and 10 yards to go.
22 seconds remaining.
And Bradshaw back
and looking again.
Worst pass I've ever thrown
in my career.
And I was shooting it
out there
for a fella in a black jersey.
Didn't know who it was.
Jack Tatum hit Frenchy Fuqua,
knocked the ball back.
Franco Harris scooped it up.
Did he trap it
or catch it in the air?
I don't know.
Runs for a touchdown.
Still to this day considered
the greatest play
in the history of
the National Football League.
But I had no idea
what happened.
All I know is the ball
was going in the air,
and then I look up--
[clears throat]
I don't know
if I got knocked down or what.
But I look up,
and Franco is just taking
that Italian army
right down the sideline.
Man, I couldn't believe it.
It's fourth down.
When I moved out of getting
sacked, I just saw a blur.
I saw a black jersey,
and I threw to it.
- And his pass is...
broken up by Tatum!
Picked up!
Franco Harris has it!
- Wow. When I hit the ground
and heard the roar
of the crowd,
I gotta be honest with you,
folks,
I knew endorsements
were about to come my way.
[laughter]
I--[laughs]
I did.
I'm sitting down,
I'm laying on that field,
and I hear this roar,
and I'm just thinking,
"Golly. You son of a gun.
"You got that thing off
and you hit him
going across there,"
whoever "him" was.
"He--him caught it
and him went all the way."
And I just--I just felt
real good about myself.
And then we--
"It was unbelievable.
It was unbelievable.
Franco, man..."
I said, "Franco? Franco
was supposed to be blocking."
He's not--[laughs]
So anyway, that is definitely
a defining moment.
- What's the biggest thing
you've learned in football?
- Well, that's pretty easy.
Putting a team together
with people with the same
like interest,
same work ethic,
that's the thing I love
about football.
When I think about Chuck...
he's extremely smart.
He was a scary smart
human being.
Great coaches have a plan.
They have an eye for--
basically an eye for talent.
And he had an eye for talent.
They got me Stallworth.
They got me Webster,
Franco, Rocky, Swanny.
I mean, we've got
a chance to win.
I've got a chance to perform.
♪ ♪
The thing that made
the Steelers great
are great,
high-character people.
It's like you build a team
and they're always--
they're always there.
The same bunch.
- Here is Bradshaw
giving the ball to Bleier.
Bleier reverses it to Swann.
He gives it back to Bradshaw.
Bradshaw fires for Cunningham.
A Pittsburgh touchdown
to win the ballgame!
- Now I've got some confidence.
And today we threw a lot
of different stuff at them,
and we had success.
When I was born in 1948,
God made me a football player.
And He gave me a strong arm.
And I just had a hard time
throwing 5-yard passes.
I liked to throw
that sucker deep.
Throw it deep!
Anybody can throw wide.
Let's go deep!
You got a play in the huddle.
"Swann, let's throw a hook."
John would say, "Brad,
I got him on a deep curl.
50 yard!"
"Throw it deep!
Let's go deep."
[cheers and applause]
♪ Before I reach the end zone ♪
♪ Before my final goal ♪
♪ I want to throw the ball ♪
♪ That scores a touchdown
for my soul ♪
♪ Now, if life's
a game of football ♪
♪ I'll make my pass complete ♪
♪ 'Cause when you're sacked,
you win the game ♪
♪ By getting back up on your ♪
♪ Feet ♪
[lively music]
Oh, yeah.
I had all these players
for all these years.
Not to mention the fact
I could be aggressive...
♪ I'm going deep ♪
Because I had one of
the greatest defenses
ever assembled,
and I knew that.
Let's go, Joe.
- Let's go, T, baby.
♪ Well, I'm going deep ♪
I look back on that and think,
"I was the captain
of that ship."
To be in that huddle
and look at them
and talk to them...
♪ Not to settle for those safe
and dinky passes ♪
- ♪ And the Lord said,
"Bradshaw, as ye sow" ♪
- ♪ So shall you reap ♪
♪ So get ready for me, folks ♪
♪ I'm going deep ♪
Ha!
♪ ♪
It was just...fun.
So I had this reputation
of being dumb.
They said I couldn't
read defenses.
You drop back,
and Lynn Swann is open.
Phew-ow!
[scattered cheers]
Yeah, you know
what I'm talking about.
Boom! Let him have it.
Got four or five guys
hanging on him draped.
What do you do?
- ♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
- What do you do?
You throw it to him. Phoo-ya!
Make him jump.
Apologize to him later.
[laughter]
♪ ♪
I guess what I'm trying
to tell you...
- ♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
- They said I was dumb.
Hurt my feelings.
But eventually, I got over it.
And we started doing this show.
And the show was called,
"Terry Bradshaw: America's
Favorite Dumb Blonde."
[laughter]
♪ It's fourth and 10
on my own 25 ♪
♪ I got 30, 40 years
to be alive ♪
- There's the Blond Bomber.
- ♪ And miles to throw
before I go to sleep ♪
♪ Oh, yes ♪
♪ So get ready for me, folks ♪
♪ I'm going deep ♪
- ♪ Going deep ♪
- What an awesome
adrenaline rush.
I mean, fun.
And I'll tell you
what is even more fun...
crowd: Here we go, Steelers,
here we go!
- Was to go up against
an inferior team
and stride up
to the line of scrimmage
and look at the defense...
[laughing]
And see fear in their eyes,
knowing their ass
is gonna get beat.
That is just
such a great feeling.
I'd hate to have to play
against us.
We're gonna be hard to beat.
Hard to beat.
- What was the best part
of football?
Like, what was the best moment?
- Well, winning
the championships was the key.
You know? Winning. Winning.
[applause]
There are four great moments
that I can recall.
Super Bowl IX.
- Terry Bradshaw.
He's been booed for five years
in Pittsburgh.
He has come into his own
the last month.
Pittsburgh,
the Super Bowl champs.
- Super Bowl X.
- Here is Bradshaw.
Lynn Swann is open.
That's got to be
one of the great passes
in Super Bowl history
or in pro football history.
- XIII.
- Bradshaw.
It's going to Swann.
And Swann makes a circus catch
in the end zone
for the touchdown.
What a brilliant throw
by Bradshaw.
- XIV.
- Now Bradshaw pumping,
firing downfield.
There goes Stallworth.
He pulls it in, and it's a
touchdown for Pittsburgh!
- I played big in big games.
I wish, for ego's sake,
I had thrown for 400 touchdowns
and I wish I'd have completed
70% of my passes,
and just ego talking here.
But when I look
at my performance,
I'm--I look at it
like a business.
I was hired
to quarterback a team and win,
and you do that
by winning championships.
And so I did my job.
- In 1978, Terry Bradshaw
was football's
most prolific passer.
- I was the MVP in the league
that year.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
I set a new NFL/AFL merger
record for touchdown passes.
You want to know
how many it was, folks?
Twenty-eight.
[laughter, light applause]
No, no. Don't clap.
They do that in nine games now.
But back then, you know,
it was a big deal.
So I'm the Player of the Year
in the NFL,
and I played great
in the playoff games.
We get to Miami,
Super Bowl XIII,
and Thomas "Hollywood"
Henderson's going,
"He's so dumb,
he can't spell 'cat'
if you spot him
the C and the T."
And that's headline,
headline, headline.
Dumb me and Hollywood.
- Dallas linebacker
"Hollywood" Thomas Henderson.
He's stealing
the pregame publicity,
but his pregame noise
isn't bothering
the Pittsburgh players.
- I think--I think it's neat.
I enjoy--
You know, that's his
personality, and--and...
So I gotta take
the high road, right?
I'm not gonna get into
a verbal match with him.
Everybody has a personality,
and, we--
you know,
we know that's how he is,
and I find it interesting.
It's--I think
it's kind of uplifting.
And I was the MVP
in the game, so...
[laughs]
Took care of that.
I just love beating Dallas.
- The Pittsburgh Steelers,
the first team
in the history of the NFL
to win it three times.
But winning didn't satisfy you
because you--
you had to do it again.
Then if you did it again,
back to back...
- The Pittsburgh Steelers
are the champions
of the National Football
League for the fourth time.
- You can't enjoy it because
you have to do it again.
It's just like, "Ugh, God."
♪ ♪
As much as we accomplished--
[clears throat]
It was hard to enjoy.
♪ ♪
Winning is so consuming.
It's so stressful.
After Super Bowl XIV
I told my dad,
"Man, I need to retire.
I've had enough of this."
♪ ♪
My dad was always
a company man.
"The Rooneys
have been good to you,
the city's been good to you,"
and so on and so forth.
And I said, "Dad, four
Super Bowls in nine years."
I said,
"I like the sound of that."
I didn't have the balls
not to come back.
I was afraid of my future.
I was afraid of no future.
Insecure, you know?
God, I wish I'd have retired.
That'd have been--
that would have been so cool.
I had a bet with a guy
named Tillman Franks.
He said, "I bet you $100
you can't sing."
I said, "I'll tell you what.
I'll bet you $100
I can get
a recording contract."
And I go into the studio.
We do the album.
The album now,
the entire album.
How long do you think
it took me, R.P.?
- Five hours.
- It took four.
[laughter]
Four hours.
I was in and out.
And out of that session,
believe it or not,
came a song that I recorded
that went to number nine
on Billboard--
Billboard magazine's chart,
which was a shocker.
[applause]
["I'm So Lonesome
I Could Cry"]
♪ ♪
♪ Hear that lonesome
whippoorwill ♪
♪ ♪
♪ He sounds too blue to cry ♪
♪ The midnight train ♪
What was that, 27, 28?
♪ Is whining low ♪
All that hair.
Where have those days gone?
♪ I could cry ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I've never seen
a night so long ♪
Look how thin I am.
I'm, like, 205 pounds there.
♪ When time goes crawling by ♪
♪ ♪
both: ♪ The moon just went ♪
♪ Behind the cloud ♪
♪ To hide its face and cry ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ The silence of ♪
♪ The fallin' star ♪
♪ Lights up a purple sky ♪
♪ ♪
both: ♪ And as I wonder ♪
♪ Lord, where you are ♪
♪ I'm so lonesome I could cry ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'm so lonesome I ♪
- ♪ Could cry ♪
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- I have a question for you.
If you had a chance
to go back in time...
- Yeah.
- To one day in your life...
- Right.
- When would that be and why?
- One day in my life,
if I could go back
and change anything.
Golly.
[sighs]
Well, if I could start
with wife number one
and cancel that.
[laughter]
[rim shot]
Move on to wife number two,
eliminate that one.
[laughter]
- Whoo!
[rim shot]
And wife number three
cleaned my plow.
[rim shot]
That's three back-in-times
I'd like to eliminate
right there.
I--that's such a good question,
sweetheart.
Divorced three times.
Very embarrassed
and ashamed of that.
My first wife, I married--
it's embarrassing,
but I will say it--
was the fact that I'd come home
from the football season,
I was going through one
of my periods of depression
that I didn't even know I had,
and I was--I was angry.
I was hateful.
I didn't know I was in--
going through a depression.
I called this girl and--
wonderful girl, not her fault.
And I said,
"Let's get married,"
and we got married.
And the minute
I'm walking down the aisle,
I said, "Oh, my God."
"This is just wrong."
And I said, "Oh, my God,
what have I done?"
A year later, not even that,
it was over.
Then I met JoJo Starbuck,
the ice skater.
[classical music]
And what I saw in her,
I think,
was she was a star.
And so there
was excitement there.
She was a bigger star
than I was, you know?
And she was an athlete,
Olympic skater.
- He asked me to marry him,
and I said,
"Well, I couldn't possibly
tell you before Christmastime."
This is, like, in September,
and, uh...
- October.
- No, September.
And then three weeks later,
I said, "Yes, yes, yes."
- I can't tell you today...
whether or not
I was in love with her.
I thought I was.
I do recall telling my father
after the wedding,
I said, "Dad, I've never been
so happy in my life."
He says, "Great, son.
I'm proud of you."
And then six weeks later,
she leaves and flies off to LA,
and she can't stand the ranch,
and she was gone
the whole time.
'Cause I don't have anyone
to cook for me,
and I'm not
a very good cook myself.
- You don't have anybody
to cook for you?
- No.
- what do you mean?
- Well, I'm home, uh--
I'm home alone.
- A lot?
- Quite a bit.
- You leave...
- [laughs] But I'm happy.
I'm happy while I'm,
you know...
[laughter]
- Thank you.
- And then, um,
filed for divorce.
I was in a quarterback meeting,
and the sheriff
brought me the papers
while I was in
a quarterback meeting,
which highly pissed me off.
And then we played
a preseason game.
And I thought I was handling it
pretty well.
And right before half,
I'd just thrown a pass
and just got decked.
And it just stunned me,
and so everybody came out
to make sure I was all right.
And when they sat me up,
I lost it.
I just started bawling.
That was, um, not a good deal.
And so she divorced me, and--
and, uh--[clears throat]
And then Charlotte,
the wife of my kids,
was--was something
that started good.
And then she wanted
to go to law school.
And then law became what
I thought was more important
than anything else.
And I was pissed about that.
And I--I vented it, and, uh,
I told her, you know,
I told her one day,
I said, "You keep ignoring me,
I'm gonna have an affair.
I'm just telling you right now
I'm gonna have an affair."
And I did.
We had nothing--
nothing in common.
Zero in common.
We don't have anything
in common today.
We have two great kids,
and that's it, so...
I already told you
how immature I was.
Those are three good examples
of being extremely immature.
[applause]
Took my chair.
That's something I'm used to,
a woman taking away
my possessions.
[laughter]
[rim shot]
[laughs]
That's cute.
Don't you think that's cute?
I like that.
A lot of guys
are out there going,
"Yeah, yeah, I know what
you're talking about."
After the third--
the third wife,
I was an emotional wreck.
And when you've been divorced
and you've got children
involved,
it's not a happy place.
Um, not a happy place at all.
And I just said,
"That's just too much.
I can't go through this
again in life."
So I sought out help...
and went to therapy
for a long time
to figure out what the hell's
wrong with me.
We tend to wanna st--
bury everything,
'cause if you admit that
you're dealing with depression,
then what you're also admitting
is you have a weakness.
It is not a weakness.
It is a disease.
It's not--
it's out of your control.
And when I went to therapy
and learned that,
"It's okay, Terry.
It's not you.
It's the way God made you."
And when I started
going through that,
then I started saying, "Okay."
Um, one of the things
that I learned was,
after football season
especially,
is when I'm most vulnerable.
'Cause I would come off
of maybe not a great year,
but maybe, you know,
maybe a Super Bowl year,
and then I'd sink way down.
And it would take me forever,
forever to get happy, you know?
I never could--
I never could find my escape.
I couldn't find my comfort
to go and relax
and enjoy myself.
And it--and it just built.
You know, it's like
right now, talking about it,
I'm getting a headache
talking about it.
It's not--this isn't a good
moment for me right now.
Why would anybody care
that I deal with depression,
clinical depression?
Yeah, I have to get past that.
When I talked about it,
a dear friend of mine
just made fun of me like crazy,
and it--it set me back.
"Well, I don't want
to do that anymore.
I don't want to be laughed at."
I've had friends of mine--
I love them to death--
but they saw
an interview I did.
And they know who they are.
I won't mention their names.
And if they watch this,
hear me loud and clear.
If they watch this, this one
person is gonna make fun of me
for saying
what I've just been--
he's gonna do it.
He can't help himself.
But I did this interview,
and I broke down.
I even begged the doctor
at the hospital.
I said, "Put me out
for three days.
Please put--"
I mean, I get all emotional
talking about this.
- [quietly] Yeah.
- And they made fun of me.
[sobs mockingly]
And...
And it bothered me.
Still bothers me.
I never told them
it bothered me.
You just want relief.
- Yeah.
- You know?
People know they can put me
in positions
and insult me
and make fun of me,
and it's all good for Fox.
And I take it,
and then when I get on a plane
and go home,
I'm flying by myself,
I'll say,
"God, you know, that..."
Get a little tired
of that shit.
- Terry, first of all,
I want to thank you for, uh,
bringing out
the depression part
'cause I've gone through it
for 50 years.
- Oh, bless you.
- And, uh,
it's--you're a role model
for that.
- Well, bless you.
- So thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Appreciate that.
[cheers and applause]
There, see?
Now you know it's worth it.
Depression.
Fuck it.
[laughs]
[upbeat rock music]
After I'd come back
from Super Bowl XIV
and started playing,
I was playing really good.
And I thought to myself,
"Well, this is kind of fun."
And you know why it was fun?
Because we weren't really
gonna win the Super Bowl,
but we were putting
a new team together,
and they kind of needed me.
♪ ♪
So it felt good.
- Today's game
in the first round
of the AFC Super Bowl
tournament,
the Steelers host
the Chargers of San Diego.
- The playoff game
against the Chargers,
I threw an interception
that cost us the game.
[crowd cheering]
- Oh, intercepted
by the Chargers!
- And I'm not real proud
of that, I might add.
- Bradshaw
disgusted with himself.
- And then the following year
in training camp,
my foot slipped, and I tear
a muscle in my right elbow,
and it never got better.
"We'll just go in and, um,
sew it together,
and you'll be fine."
Okay.
I was told it would be
three months,
and it never was three months,
and it never was five months.
And I'm pushing it.
I was doing everything
to try to get back.
And it just never responded.
You're not getting any support
from anybody
because they've got
a football season.
And you're not a part of it
'cause you're hurt.
- A couple of thigs were...
- And then I had
a coach that--
"He's not here.
He's not on the team.
We're not talking about him."
- No.
- But I think
I wanted Chuck to say,
"Boy, we really need you, man.
"You just take your time.
Get well.
Whatever you gotta do,
get well."
That's when we started
in the paper, see?
That's when Noll and Bradshaw
started clashing.
I felt pressure--
not from anybody but myself.
"Boy, if I don't get back out
on that field,
"you know, Cliff Stoudt's
got this job,
and I'm history here."
I came back like Superman.
- And here comes Bradshaw.
He's back in there
trying to spur the Steelers
into the playoffs.
[wistful music]
- Threw across my body
to Gregg Garrity.
- In the end zone.
Touchdown, Gregg Garrity!
- When I threw back across,
I heard it snap.
I go to the sideline,
and I'm just sitting here,
and I'm just gritting my teeth.
It hurt so bad.
- They're working on the elbow
of Bradshaw.
- No, you're going to have
to get Terry out of there
with a baseball bat today.
- And I called
some running plays.
"Let's just run, run, run,
run, run, run, run.
Let's don't throw."
Third down, I drop back
to pass and--
[grunts]
And it was every ounce
of energy I had
to get that ball
out of my hand.
It hurt so bad.
- Calvin Sweeney
for a touchdown!
- And then that was it.
That was it.
And it was embarrassing
to come back, get hurt again.
I look back on that whole year,
and I just say,
"Why didn't you just not play?"
I remember when I told Chuck,
"You know,
I can't play anymore,"
and he shook my hand
and wished me well.
That was it.
So you look back on that,
you go, "Man, that was cold."
When my career was over with,
Glen Campbell called me
and said, "Yo, Terry!"
[laughter]
"Will you sing a song with me?"
Well, I love Glen Campbell.
Who doesn't?
And, yeah.
I absolutely love his songs.
And I said, "Well, let's do it.
What are we gonna sing?"
And he said, "How about
we sing this song
"'You Don't Know How Good
You Got It
Till You Ain't Got It
No More'?"
How apropos was that?
Let's have it, boys!
[lively country music playing]
♪ ♪
♪ At 32 in '82,
my future was bright ♪
♪ Had my youth
and my effortless charm ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Endorsements hanging off me
like a full head of hair ♪
Ha!
♪ On the strength
of my spectacular arm ♪
♪ So who would have guessed ♪
♪ That arm would fail
the test ♪
♪ How much could go wrong
with something so small? ♪
♪ Well, I threw back
and tossed ♪
♪ All that I lost
was my career ♪
♪ Gone away with the ball ♪
Here we go, now.
♪ Well, you'll never know how
good you've got it ♪
♪ Till you ain't got it
no more ♪
♪ ♪
- Steeler quarterback
Terry Bradshaw,
who played only one game
last season,
has officially retired.
- It's something
that I regret greatly,
but it's something
that has to be done.
♪ All I can do is just moan
the blues ♪
♪ And dream about what I had
before ♪
♪ You never know just
how good ♪
♪ You got it ♪
♪ Till you ain't ♪
♪ Got it ♪
♪ No more ♪
[yodeling]
♪ ♪
[music concludes]
All right!
Thank you!
People are nice.
[cheers and applause]
I retired from the NFL.
I needed to make $17,500
a month to keep my ranch going.
So I was taking
every job in the world
'cause I lost
all my endorsements.
I had nothing.
And CBS came and said,
"We'll give you $100,000
and a three-year guarantee
to do football games."
- I can't tell you
what a pleasure it is
for me to welcome you.
And, you see, after all you
accomplished on the field,
this is gonna be a snap.
- [laughs] Oh, this is so easy.
I did not know anything
about broadcasting.
I mean, nothing.
And, you know,
I really never thought
I could have butterflies
so big in my belly.
After my rookie year, I said,
"Shoot, it's gotta get
a little easier than this."
Now I'm starting
all over again.
I had no idea.
How do you see all these people
flying all over the place?
And who do you watch?
The offensive linemen
or the quarterback?
Do you watch where the ball is?
Do you look at the secondary?
[snorts] You know? It was--
I found it very difficult,
and it was just
a struggle for me.
When CBS lost football,
Fox saw me.
David Hill said,
"That's the guy
I want to build
our pregame show around."
- With your co-host,
Terry Bradshaw.
- What he saw, I don't know,
but it was the best thing
for me that's ever happened.
Hello, folks.
I'm Terry Bradshaw,
and this is a great moment.
We would like to welcome you
to the "NFL on Fox."
That's right.
You heard it right.
When I went to Fox,
I didn't give a shit.
You know, I want to laugh.
I want to feel good.
I want to have fun.
You ever been bass fishing,
and early--
- No.
- And then early,
you're catching those Florida
bass with the same lure
and you say,
"Boy, ain't this good?"
I know this kind of blows you
out of the water
a little bit, doesn't it?
But there's--fishing
and football do relate.
- Lucky Week 13.
Came out here on the 13th,
on flight 13th,
and sat in seat 13th.
- No, no, it's flight 13,
seat 13,
and you flew out on the 13th.
- You too?
[laughter]
- There you have it.
- I did do movies.
The first movie I did
was with Burt Reynolds,
called "Hooper."
- We may be in trouble.
- My association with him
started by him criticizing me
on an NBC show the night
before the Super Bowl,
Super Bowl X.
- Lance Rentzel wrote
his first book.
Pat Toomay wrote
Alex Karras wrote
his first book.
Terry Bradshaw wrote
his first sentence.
[laughter]
- He called me everything
in this skit he did--
dumb and just all the insults.
- If you're out there, Terry,
I'd like to say hi to you.
[slowly] Hi, Terry.
[laughter]
I'm on television.
- He sent a note saying
how sorry he was
that he did that to me,
and would I please come see
him on the set of "Hooper"?
Burt was seriously upset, um,
that he had done the piece.
He told me he didn't want
to do it because he liked me.
I--we became really good
friends, so I believed him.
And he wrote the script
for me on the truck
and put me in the movie
just to say, "I'm sorry."
And I ended up doing
five movies with him
because of that
right there, so...
[applause]
Yeah.
Burt. Burt, if you're watching,
talk to my agent
about my next movie!
- [laughs]
- Make it a Western!
- You gonna let me be in it?
- Yeah.
[glass shatters]
God dang, is that fun!
[laughs]
I'm no actor.
I just--I like meeting
those people.
Hi, Bandit. Hi, Frog.
- Hi, Terry.
- So I've done
quite a few role things.
- ♪ Give me
the microphone first ♪
♪ So I can bust
like a bubble ♪
♪ Compton and Long Beach
together ♪
♪ Now you know you
in trouble ♪
- Uh-oh.
Here we go.
Hey, Pop.
- ♪ It's like that
and like this ♪
[Terry laughs]
- You're naked.
[laughter]
In my room.
- Well, this is my Naked Room.
[laughter]
I mean, it's my house.
A man ought to be able to do
whatever he wants to do
in his own house.
Wore a suit for 40 years.
- All right.
I'm gonna let you get back
to feeding your fish.
- Thanks for stopping by.
[laughter]
[dramatic music playing]
♪ This is my butt ♪
♪ ♪
♪ It's on display ♪
♪ Yes, we have
pale white man butt ♪
♪ On sale today ♪
♪ When you've sold everything
there is to sell ♪
♪ It's time to shoot the moon ♪
♪ And not one moment too ♪
♪ Soon ♪
[laughs]
♪ ♪
Oh.
Oh, my God.
I got to tell you ladies
about that.
I did that naked scene
for one reason only--
that was for my mother.
[laughter]
All right, all right,
all right.
[rim shot]
McConaughey was just voted
Sexiest Man Alive,
and I'm naked in the movie?
[laughter]
Go figure.
If there's one thing
in my life
I do wish I had--
and I'll say this,
I'll say this--
I wish I was loved
and res--and respected.
And I understand--
I know I don't deserve this.
I just wish I had it.
Like Brady and like Peyton.
Roger Staubach.
[wistful music]
But when I sit back in my life
as a football player,
I never had that kind
of respect.
♪ ♪
And I wish I did.
I really do wish I did.
♪ ♪
When I left Pittsburgh,
I was angry.
I mean, I was pissed.
I didn't have a relationship
with the city.
with the ownership.
I didn't want
to face those people--
Pittsburgh fans,
the Pittsburgh press,
Chuck Noll.
♪ ♪
- Names from all over
the sports world
arrived in Pittsburgh today
to pay their respects
to legendary
Hall of Fame coach Chuck Noll.
Noll died of natural causes
Friday night
in his home
just outside of Pittsburgh.
He was 82 years old.
♪ ♪
- He passes away,
and I don't go to his funeral.
So I'm now being judged
by that too.
He's no longer living,
and he doesn't deserve
anybody to say
negative things about him.
And he was a great coach.
He just--
I just had a hell
of a hard time with him,
that's all.
He did his job with me,
I did my job with him,
and I left.
Why can't people accept that,
you know, for what it is?
Um...
♪ ♪
[whistling]
- There they are.
- You know, I'm doing football
on television.
I'm ranching, raising cows,
raising horses.
Hey, girls!
Got a great wife.
It's a great way to live.
[whistling]
- Can we meet your lovely wife?
- Yes!
[cheers and applause]
Yes, you can.
Here she is right here.
She is a beauty.
This is my wife, Tammy.
[cheers and applause]
You gonna sing?
- No.
[laughter]
Terry...
- All right.
- Beautiful wife.
- She is.
- This is my good wife.
[laughter]
Oh.
I can't do anything
without my wife.
I'm looking for her.
She's like--
She's like my--she's my rock.
[laughs]
- Hey, Quincy.
- I now get what marriage
really should have been.
Hey, Biff. Hey, buddy.
Hey, buddy boy.
She needs
to be your best friend,
and so thank God I finally
got that part right.
I married my best friend.
He's so sweet.
We do everything together.
You ain't cute,
I'll pay for lying.
Look at that thing.
- This is your show--
your champion, Barbie.
You showed her.
I just, like--God, I've just--
I've hit a gold mine here,
finally.
And then I tell myself,
"I deserve it."
I deserve to have a great woman
in my life.
I truly do.
And so I'm blessed by that.
And it's just--And I mean,
I told it to her,
you know, that,
you know, "When I close
my eyes for the last time,
"you know,
I want to have your hand--
I want to be holding
your hand."
You know? So...
[whistling]
You know, you don't have to
worry about, "Do I love her?"
Of course.
Do I have to worry
about her leaving me?
No.
Hang on just a second.
Is that right?
Got a thumbs-up over there.
And that's a good feeling.
["You'll Never Walk Alone"
playing]
♪ ♪
Let's get one thing
really clear.
God has blessed me
tremendously.
And I don't take that lightly.
I've grown as a person.
I have, at times,
shown that I'm...
I've got great character
and strength.
I know that.
I've also shown, at times,
I can push aside the kindness
and be a real dickhead.
♪ ♪
I don't like that part.
But all in all...
♪ ♪
Especially since I met Tammy,
I have become...
a very, uh, good man.
[applause]
My wife loves this song.
And this is a hard song
to sing.
But I'm gonna sing it
because I love her
and she means the world to me
and she wants me to sing it,
so I'm gonna sing it.
This is for all of you.
Listen to the words.
[cheers and applause]
[piano playing]
♪ When you walk ♪
♪ Through a storm ♪
♪ Hold your head up high ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And don't ♪
♪ Be afraid ♪
♪ Of the dark ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Walk on ♪
♪ Through the wind ♪
♪ Through the rain ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Though your dreams
be tossed ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And blown ♪
♪ Walk on ♪
♪ With hope in your heart ♪
♪ And you'll never walk ♪
♪ Alone ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You'll never walk ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
♪ Walk on, walk on ♪
Got an awesome wife,
two great daughters,
one awesome stepdaughter,
grandkid.
♪ And you'll never walk ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Alone ♪
♪ You'll never ♪
It's just been...
an amazing life.
♪ ♪
It has truly been
an amazing life.
♪ ♪
God bless you, folks.
Please be careful
going home tonight.
God bless you all so much.
Thank you so much.
All right, Joe!
Don't leave me hanging, baby.
Joe, let's go!
♪ ♪
[jazzy music playing]
I just wanna die onstage.
Look at the ratings
Fox will get
if I have a heart attack
right there on the spot.
Boom! "T.B.?"
I mean, through the roof.
That's good stuff.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
[applause]
announcer: This has been
a presentation
of HBO Sports.
♪ ♪