Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Each and every one of you
are a part
of the American dream
because you are entrepreneurs
and you own your own business.
And I will tell you, some days
are not so good.
But guess what?
So many days are so amazing.
You're
important to us.
It is the sisterhood,
it is the camaraderie, it is,
it is LuLaRoe.
The law of attraction
rules the universe.
I'm so blessed to be
a part of LuLaRoe.
You are planting seeds.
In the last 30 days,
I sold over $13,000 worth
of LuLaRoe clothing.
That is insane.
We love you,
we value you
in everything that you do.
Together, we're home!
It's given me my purpose back.
I knew that not only
was this special,
but this was something
that was gonna change
people's lives.
You do solemnly state
under penalty of perjury
that the evidence you
shall give in this matter
will be the truth,
the whole truth
and nothing but the truth.
Yes.
Can you please state
your full name?
DeAnne Stidham Brady.
Women are filing
a class-action lawsuit
accusing LuLaRoe of being
a pyramid scheme.
Can you please
state your full legal name?
Mark Allen Stidham.
The lawsuit
seeks a billion dollars
for a plaintiff
unknowingly recruited
into LuLaRoe's pyramid scheme.
I hate that I joined LuLaRoe,
I am embarrassed
that I sold LuLaRoe.
They got my money.
LuLaRoe won.
I actually,
literally despise them,
and it makes me angry.
According to
Washington Attorney General,
Bob Ferguson,
"LuLaRoe tricked consumers
into buying
into its pyramid scheme."
I wasn't alone in...
in receiving merchandise
that I just was not
able to sell
to anyone because it was crap.
I am stuck with thousands
of dollars
of inventory.
Even at my peak month,
I don't think I ever made
any money.
I was in a lot of debt that...
I was unable to pay back.
Disrupting that status quo,
we... we created enemies.
We were attacked viciously
on social media.
Why doesn't LuLaRoe
sell directly to consumers?
I don't know.
How many retailers
does LuLaRoe currently have?
I do not know.
Do you know
a ballpark?
- Nope.
How are you
currently compensated?
I don't know.
When did you start
asking others to sell
LuLaRoe clothing for you?
I never asked anyone.
Be happy.
Give yourself kudos
of the good things
that you are doing
and say to yourself,
"You know what?
I'm able to buy
better groceries.
I am able to make
the car payment."
Those are the reasons
why you got started
at LuLaRoe.
If the pitch was real
and I said to you,
"With no experience,
little money down,
you can run your
own business,
set your own hours,
spend more time
with your friends and family
and possibly
be a millionaire,"
and that is possible,
wouldn't you do it?
I'm super excited
because I just got
my initial inventory today.
It's a welcome card here
from DeAnne and Mark.
This is the planner.
This is so cute.
These are really pretty.
Hello, birds.
Purple birds.
- We have some busy bees.
- Do you like wearing
underpants?
'Cause this is what
it'll feel like.
Also, little extra tuck,
tuck for people like me,
like moms, who need it.
- Stickers. Stickers
- Stickers. Oh, my gosh.
LuLaRoe is a multi-level marketing
company.
They sell shirts, dresses,
all kinds of clothes,
but they're most known
for their leggings.
The leggings cost
around $25.
They have like a slightly
higher price point.
And I think
they were considered
a little more high quality
and a little more designer
than, you know,
just a random
pair of leggings.
People really loved
their really colorful ones
or they loved
the weird patterns.
They loved how soft they were.
And I remember the first time
I heard about LuLaRoe,
that's what people
were talking about,
was these leggings
are so comfortable
and they're so soft.
Buttery soft leggings.
LuLaRoe leggings,
if you haven't tried them,
are one of the most softest,
buttery things you'll ever
put on your legs.
- That buttery soft hand feel
that you all absolutely love.
- Buttery soft.
Like, what does buttery
even mean?
And I thought that was really
ridiculous, too,
until I felt them.
Now, let's go
to a little town
in New Jersey where things
are really popping.
Yes, there's a party going on
at Mrs. Betty Martin's house.
It's a Tupperware party,
and it's really fun.
The girls get together
and meet their old friends
and make some new ones.
Then there's a demonstration
by one of the Tupperware
dealers
who lives in your community.
♪ It's time to take time
out for beauty ♪
Avon calling
Growing up,
I remember my mom
going to a lot of Tupperware
parties.
My great grandma sold Avon.
My aunt sold Mary Kay.
Dishes in my grandma's house
were from like door-to-door
salesmen.
And you would see
a lot of products
in people's houses.
I thought it was just a fun...
...get together?
As a kid, I did not understand
about the recruitment.
Like, I really thought these
women were just, like,
running a business
out of their house.
The American dream
is that we all have
the chance to be rich,
and make it, you know,
we all have the chance.
We all grow up thinking,
"I'm gonna get famous
or I'm gonna get rich."
And we aren't discouraged
from thinking that.
Maybe you'd like to look
at this more closely.
I'll pass it around.
Yeah.
If you work
hard enough,
you will achieve success.
And these companies,
they're just exploiting
that hopefulness that we've
all been raised with.
LuLaRoe was founded in 2013
and grew extremely fast.
So, in 2015,
they only had around
1,000 consultants.
By April 2017,
they had over 80,000
consultants
and were making
a billion dollars in revenue.
So, that's 0 to 80,000
in five years.
You know, having come
from business,
I understand most companies
would kill
to have that kind of growth
year over year.
And so, uh, business processes
have been a challenge.
You know, when it was just
a small family business,
we all just, kind of,
rolled up our sleeves
and did what needed
to be done.
I first got
interested
in reporting
on multi-level marketing
because I had noticed
that a lot of people
that I knew from growing up
on social media had
been joining MLMs.
Hey, girl, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, ladies!
Hey, girl, hey, happy Friday!
The simplest way
to explain an MLM
or a multi-level marketing
company
is that they recruit
individual retailers
to sell a product.
And then those retailers
recruit other retailers.
The products can be anything.
It can be essential oils,
it can be herbal supplements,
it can be make-up
or it can be leggings.
LuLaRoe is the kind of MLM,
they have a product,
banana leggings,
and they're superior
to other banana leggings.
They're so superior
that you must sell them
door-to-door or to your
friends and family
or on a Facebook Live.
And that's how exclusive
this opportunity is.
And the way
the companies describe
how that works
is you buy in,
you get a bunch of banana
leggings,
you sell a bunch of banana
leggings.
All of your friends
at that party
that were buying
the banana leggings are like,
"Wow, this is an amazing
business opportunity."
And you're like, "I know.
Would you like to sign up
underneath me?"
So, you sign people up
underneath you,
and there's one rung
of people below you.
That's your downline.
Now, you're an upline.
And you get a slice of every
future purchase
that they make.
So, it behooves an upline
to encourage their downline
to stock up.
The sales pitch
from the MLM company
is that, that is supposed
to continue on,
kind of like a chain letter,
where you've got
your people under you.
Say you have ten, you know,
half of them are amazing
recruiters, they each get ten.
Oh, my gosh, now you have,
like, 60 people
that you're getting
a slice of.
Then those people are also
supposed to be
just as ambitious.
It's been a while
since we've shopped,
so I want to show you guys
what is new.
Do you have the daisies
in the medium?
I don't.
Here's another extra small.
It has cute little, uh,
typewriters
with little sweet notes on it.
I think that the Internet
helped people who pitch MLMs
as an opportunity,
as a business opportunity.
I think it helped them
over an early hurdle,
which is, who am I
gonna recruit.
Social media has been
like gasoline on the fire
of MLMs.
I am so beyond excited,
I'm about to spontaneously
combust.
I don't know what you get,
I don't know what I'm
gonna give away,
but it's gonna be something
good.
Instead of just
having a party at your house,
where you can invite people
who could physically
get there,
you can have an online party
where you can invite everyone
you know,
plus invite them to invite
everyone they know.
And, you know, you can get
these Facebook groups
that have like 30,000 people
in them.
So if you're thinking
about doing it,
I would encourage you to do it
'cause it's been such
a blessing.
So it just makes
it even easier
to recruit people.
If you are interested
in all of the opportunity,
please feel free to reach out
with me.
"Let me ask
you a question.
Have you ever thought
about potentially working
on a side hustle?
You're such a badass.
I think you would be amazing
at this opportunity
I recently got involved with.
I know this sounds crazy,
but I've made a little bit
of side cash.
Let me tell you more about it.
Lol.
Here's my number, call me soon
or text me, 'kay?"
Oh, my gosh, guys,
I got rained on so bad.
I was delivering LuLaRoe,
like all day.
I think LuLaRoe
is kind of an example
of like the American
work ethos on steroids.
Sometimes, you feel like,
"I only have this much
and I'm strung out.
I cannot do it anymore."
Get out there, get busy,
enjoy, have fun
and serve your customers.
Serve your community.
DeAnne and Mark Stidham
are the founders of LuLaRoe.
So DeAnne is Mormon
and she was raised
in a Mormon family
that's basically
Mormon royalty.
DeAnne's descended
from the brother
of the man who founded
the Mormon church.
Because of that relationship
to the founding of the church,
there would have been
a sense of exceptionalism
within the family.
There is a huge amount
of overlap
between Mormons
and the MLM community.
Mormons are born
and bred missionaries,
and that skillset
becomes really useful
when you're trying to get
people to join
this once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
I grew up in the same, uh,
Mormon circles
as DeAnne.
Like, I remember her presence,
I remember how her perfume
and makeup
and hairspray smelled.
She was incredibly outgoing.
There are some people
that just always seem
like they're selling
something.
And they're always trying
to convert you to something,
right?
And as a child,
I sensed that about her.
And I will tell you,
even if you're selling
ten items a day,
you're making a difference.
You decided that you could
the minute you said,
"I'm gonna do LuLaRoe."
I think the cult
of personality around DeAnne
probably helped
a lot in the beginning.
She is very flashy,
lots of jewelry,
lots of makeup.
She cannot stay off
of her phone
and posting pictures
of herself
and doing live videos
and being on Instagram Live,
and it's mesmerizing.
Hey, everybody.
I am so excited.
It is enthusiastic Thursday.
I am in love with this hat.
The origin story
of DeAnne's business,
it's attractive
to a lot of new recruits.
I had one kid
on a hip and I was pregnant,
and a couple of kids
in the stroller.
DeAnne has this very
humble and inspiring
origin story
that she is sure
to repeat all the time.
How she started
as this single mother
who was selling maxi skirts
out of the trunk of her car.
And I said,
"I'm coming.
Invite all your friends
and we're gonna have
a maxi skirt party,"
and they go, "Okay,
count me in, DeAnne."
And no matter how many I did,
uh, I just kept booking
more and more.
And we started
a conversation about,
"Don't you think there's
probably other women
that would want the same
opportunity you've had
to earn extra money
while still having the freedom
around their schedule,
to be a stay-at-home mom
or take care of their kids?"
The house parties
were making a lot of money
and the skirts
were very popular.
And soon other women,
like Brittany Hunter,
who was the first retailer
for LuLaRoe,
um, wanted in.
They wanted to know how
they could sell the skirts.
I'm the first retailer
of LuLaRoe,
but technically it wasn't
called LuLaRoe
in the beginning,
so it's been nine years.
And it was, um,
August of 2012,
I'm pretty sure,
when I had my very first
maxi skirt party with DeAnne
and loved it.
Absolutely fell in love
with people coming to my house
and the camaraderie
and the excitement.
I called her the next day,
I'm like, "I wanna do this.
I need more skirts.
How do I get more skirts?"
It was her and I just
selling maxi skirts,
and she was still doing
her parties
and I would do some
around southern Utah.
And, yeah,
that's kind of where it began.
So, it works very well
that as a part
of DeAnne's origin story,
this business
to recruit other people
or get other women involved
wasn't even her idea.
It just fell upon her.
It's this American dream saga.
She was just like you.
She wasn't special.
She wasn't rich.
She wasn't #blessed.
She just worked really hard.
She was your, you know,
your average suburban
wife and mother,
and look at everything
she accomplished.
But the story of Mark
and DeAnne and LuLaRoe,
it's not really about them.
It's really about
the thousands
upon thousands of women
who fell prey to the promises
of feeling worthy
and being a part
of something bigger
and having impact
and the sisterhood
and are now telling
their story.
Before I started
LuLaRoe in 2016,
I just felt kind of lost,
and I feel like
when I found LuLaRoe,
I'm like, "This is clicking,
like, finally,
this is something
that I can do."
I actually went down
to a convention
in Corona, California,
and there were so many
retailers from across
the country coming.
I was like,
"Wow, this is awesome.
I'm part
of this big movement."
DeAnne spoke
at that convention,
and I was eating up
every word she was saying.
I think I even got teary-eyed,
like, listening to her story.
You know,
when she was explaining
her struggles before starting,
I kind of related to that.
And, like, that's how
I got emotional too,
because I felt like I wasn't
where I was supposed to be,
until I found LuLaRoe.
And I just...
that really spoke to me.
This is LuLaRoe.
I have so much stuff. Sorry.
Oh, here we go.
This one has
the LuLaRoe logo in it.
Oh, and I have
matching leggings to this,
so you literally have a...
it's called a Lula outfit.
I knew it cost a lot to join,
so I went to my mom
and I asked her,
"Is there any way
that I could borrow $10,000?"
She was very skeptical
at first,
but when I was explaining it
to her,
I like, kind of
broke down in tears
because I just felt
so passionate about it.
And she agreed
and she agreed to take money
from her 401to help me.
Hi, guys, Jill here.
Um, I'm kind of testingsomething a little bit different today.
I'm going to be doing $5
off each Julia
and free shipping.
I had been hyping it up
on Facebook, social media,
and so I had friends
from high school and college
come and shop,
and that helped
push that first month
to $10,000 in sales.
So, up next, you guys, I have
an extra-large green Carly.
This is legging soft material.
It's a green heather.
I felt like
LuLaRoe's message
was "Everybody is beautiful."
Our size ranges
would go up to a size 18-20,
so I feel like
it was really size-inclusive.
And I felt like
that drew a lot of women in.
Carlies do run
two to three sizes big.
So, this looks really cute
with it knotted up, you know?
It was really cool.
It was so exciting.
My customers loved
the outfits I put together.
My second month,
I went to $15,000,
and I was just blown away
about, like, how much money
I could get by doing this.
So, these are medium
and it is dipped
with striped, stripes.
Super, super cute.
It was a whirlwind,
and our first month,
we sold $21,000.
And then it just grew so fast.
Take my challenge.
Get out there
and find five people a day.
Go out and talk to them.
I listen to DeAnne every day,
you know, on Instagram,
and it really gave me
a huge boost in confidence.
And your goal
is to develop a relationship
with those people that you
come in contact with, okay?
That was another aspect of
what was recruiting.
I had girls
who signed up under me.
I was able
to build a team of ten
to become the rank of trainer.
When you became a trainer,
that's when you got
the gold watch.
I couldn't wait to get
that gold watch.
It was a goal
I strived for,
like, "I have to earn
that watch."
Like, "I will do anything
to earn this watch."
I hit trainer. I mean,
that's where the money was at.
And then you didn't have
to stress on your sales.
And then we have this beauty.
So you start out
just as a retailer,
which means that you're just
selling for yourself
and you're getting
your own sales.
Then you can move on
to sponsor,
which means you have
people under you.
And then after that,
it goes trainer,
coach, mentor, ambassador.
And so basically,
all that really means is
you just have more
and more people under you.
Since the early MLMs,
one of the exercises
you do at the beginning
is writing down 10 or 50...
I think LuLaRoe does 50 names,
um, that you're supposed
to write down of people
you could possibly recruit.
In church communities,
Mormonism
especially, those networks,
it doesn't take
any time at all
to think of those 50 names.
And so DeAnne
was able to tap
into this preexisting
Mormon network
so that she could not
sell leggings
but sell um... like, hope.
LuLaRoe's
marketing strategy
was very family-oriented,
like so we could help mothers
support their children.
We have people
starting right now,
who are doing incredible
things for their family.
She wanted to be
a stay-at-home mom,
but has the freedom
to come and go
and do what she wanted to do.
How many women
would like an opportunity
to earn income
while staying at home?
I had title after title, mom,
sister, daughter, girlfriend,
but I hadn't figured out
what my individual
purpose was.
The idea of, um,
you know, making money
from home
with two small children
was ideal.
I was used to making money.
I was used to contributing
to the household bills
and everything,
um, and I wanted that answer
to staying at home
and still being able
to raise my daughter.
So, um, you know, I heard
the term "Moms Losing Money".
That's what MLM stands for,
is Moms Losing Money.
Um, and so it's not something
that appealed to me
because it...
it didn't make sense to me.
It didn't make sense or cents.
We started this business
on the premise
that you could make full-time
income on a part-time...
part-time work.
Yes, full-time pay
for part-time work.
It's... that's...
If that doesn't define an MLM,
I don't know what does,
because as
a "real" entrepreneur,
full-time pay, full-time work,
24/7, 365,
losing sleep, losing money.
That is the entrepreneur life.
I always say that besides
being an entrepreneur,
being a mother
is one of the loneliest things
you can do.
It costs more to keep
your kids in daycare
than it is for you to work
and then, you know,
pay for that.
So, it makes sense
for a lot of women
to stay home
and take care of their kids
and they... but they want
to feel productive, right?
They miss
their nine-to-five life.
They miss... you know,
once you become a mom,
it's a different
group of friends.
So, you miss that community,
a sense of community.
And so when you see
other moms being boss babes,
that's something
that you want.
Whatever I do in life,
I want to be
the very best I can be.
So, if I'm a LuLaRoe retailer,
I wanna be
the best one I can be.
If I have kids,
I'm gonna have 11.
Girls, bring him down.
I'm bringing him down,
see, he's pulling me.
Whoa. Slow down, baby.
It's pure craziness.
So, we're Christians,
we're members
of the Church of Christ.
We had four kids,
but then
we went on a mission trip
and we stayed in an orphanage.
I'm a stay-at-home mom
and Kenny had
a really good job,
so why not adopt?
That's how 11 happens.
So...
I would say
that our generation
is just a bunch of strong
stay-at-home moms
and a lot of us joined
LuLaRoe
and that's what grew LuLaRoe.
It was who signed up,
saw the business opportunity
and ran with it.
It's like a cool mom club.
When I started,
we didn't go live,
we just did in home pop-ups.
It was just girls shopping.
Just like a big party.
A lot of fun.
This is nice.
Is this the back or the front?
It's reversible.
I like options.
Wendi, Wendi.
I have
some of the best friends
from that because
I feel like, even though
LuLaRoe pushed community,
we had then to create
true community
to make it work.
I know, Tracy,
the Shirleys are on point
and I have a new box
coming tomorrow.
It's going to be good.
Your desire to succeed.
Your commitment
to your, to your goals
and your commitment
to not letting yourself down
will make
all of the difference.
Remember, your business
is not going to grow
without you.
Now, we also want you
to strive
for getting on the cruise.
It was a goal
to cruise qualify.
There was
three different tiers,
and so of course, I wanted
the highest ranking tier.
That meant you got
a better room in the cruise.
The cruise was actually
something you qualified for
if you sold $12,000
for six months in a row.
You are that person that gets
and deserves anything
that you choose for it to be.
Go, go, go.
Prizes, cruises.
I just really, really
enjoy working for that.
For something.
Because then it doesn't seem
like a job, then it was fun.
LuLaRoe cruise ship,
all LuLaRoe people.
And if you've been to any
LuLaRoe event,
you know at LuLaRoe
everything's a party
- and super fun.
- Yes, it's not the same.
You never wanna
miss a cruise.
And we can't wait to see you
on the next cruise.
We are so excited.
I'm always
trying to find things
on the Internet
that will resonate
with people.
So I cover influencers,
things going viral
on the Internet.
So, LuLaRoe in their heyday,
they had these cruises
that were like candy
for social media,
like, if you follow
all of the top sellers
of LuLaRoe on Instagram
and they're all on this cruise
at the same time,
and they're posting
#BecauseOfLuLaRoe,
"I'm having a pina colada
on the beach,
and I'm in the Caribbean
and I'm doing this
and I'm doing that."
And it's like, "Duh,
of course I want to do this."
And it's all part of just
like feeding into this notion
that if you work hard enough,
you will get all of these
amazing things,
like, you will get
this free trip,
you'll get to meet
Mark and DeAnne,
who are like superstars.
And there's this one clip
of LuLaRoe's cruise
and there's this scene
where, like,
they're all out on the deck
and they're all
dancing and partying,
and DeAnne and Mark
jump into the pool
that's in the middle
of this deck on this ship.
They're in the pool
in their clothes,
and it's just this like...
The Great Gatsby-esque shot.
They're just in the center
of this universe.
MLM conferences
are like a cross between
an evangelical tent revival.
You shall not die,
but you shall live.
A Tony Robbins conference,
a nightclub
discotheque extravaganza
and a Katy Perry concert.
In fact, Katy Perry did
perform at a LuLaRoe event.
So they're really
just there to inspire,
to create
that sense of transcendence,
to burn all of the messages
that have been
delivered virtually
into the recruits' brains.
When you participate
in a group language ritual
with other people
doing the same thing,
it has a physiological
de-stressing effect on you.
Your cortisol levels go down,
your serotonin
and dopamine spike.
This is why so many people
have profound conversion
events when they go to church
and listen to religious music
or speak in tongues.
These are bonding events.
It's about
that person up at the top,
speaking to their flock,
and in order
for that person at the top
to be rich and to give
blessings down below,
the people from the bottom
must give, they must tithe.
So you need recruitment.
It's not really
about the product.
They're selling a dream,
right?
They're just, they're not
selling the reality,
they're selling the dream.
Ready.
I do think LuLaRoe
was trying to sell
the American dream.
That was horrible.
I remember
their mission statement.
It was...
...bless... blessing, uh,
blessing lives
and strengthening families.
It was... nothing
but positivity and joy
and... and this could be you,
this could be you.
It really just seemed
like a wonderland.
Argh!
Let's go!
So the first time
I ever encountered LuLaRoe,
I was on a family cruise
and we were just
out on the beach
and enjoying,
enjoying our time.
And there was this guy
playing Michael Jackson.
And so I just go
and I start dancing.
This guy came
and approached me
and said, "Hey, if I give you
$100,
will you wear
some female leggings
and come and do
the same thing you just did
tomorrow morning
at this business meeting?"
And I was just like, $100?
Making money on vaca...
Yeah, yeah.
You best believe
I'm... I'm there.
So I showed up
and I just sat
in the back as a surprise.
Elijah! Elijah! Elijah!
He, you know, hyped up
the crowd and everything.
Give it up for Elijah!
And then
I come in there
and I do my thing,
you know, I just, I just
put it down, you know?
Full, like,
pop and lock dance,
the ladies went crazy.
It was so fun.
Oh, I loved it.
The whole atmosphere was just
full of joy
and excitement, like
overwhelming joy
and excitement.
Oh, not to mention,
it was a wholesome party.
There was no alcohol.
So, I'm just like,
"This is my place."
Like, you see how I am,
I'm a naturally just crazy and
full of energy, I don't need
anything to help me party.
Oh, my gosh.
Wow. Good morning.
Oh, we're just
getting started.
You have no idea
how many amazing things
we have planned for you today
and tomorrow. Oh, my gosh.
And that's where
I met DeAnne and Mark.
So they flew me out
to one of the conventions.
LuLaRoe! LuLaRoe! LuLaRoe!
And DeAnne
called me on stage
to tell my "why",
uh, and my mom
was in the crowd.
So, the "why"...
How can I describe
"the why", it was...
Everyone has a "why",
like a sob story to...
...make you relate.
I, uh, told this crowd
my "why",
I definitely got emotional.
'Cause all these people only
knew me as this hype man,
this...
crazy, rambunctious
kid that just
thrives on positive energy.
I got emotional because
my mom was out there
and I was just like,
"Yeah, I'm grateful for her.
I want to become
successful enough to...
for her
so that she
doesn't have to work
ever again in her life."
And...
that's when
DeAnne onboarded her.
She pulled my mom on stage
and then she onboarded my
mom to become a consultant.
And I was shocked.
I didn't know,
I was like,
"Me, a consultant?"
I don't even know
what LuLaRoe is.
I didn't know anything,
you know,
so I just went with it.
So, when they were
coming up happy,
I said, "Okay,"
you know, so...
What am I wearing?
The Amelia.
- Hey.
- How could you forget?
How could I forget?
I'm learning inventory.
This is my newfound business.
So my mom
became a consultant
and my sister
under my mom.
She saw me making money
and she was like, "Okay,
I want to do it.
I think I'm gonna
do it, Mom.
I think I'm gonna sign
on and everything."
I said, "Okay, well, make sure
you sign under me because
I'll gain a percentage
of your sales.
I'll make money off
the percentage of your sales."
And so, she said
okay and sure enough, she did.
Black and white cardigan.
You can match
with a lot of things,
like a mustard colored Carly.
What? You have to be fly.
You have to have that mindset.
You know, let's do this
and fight and work
real hard at it.
Yeah. We are so blessed.
You just don't know,
this company is the one.
For me,
that was when I felt, "Wow,
they really are blessing
and strengthening families."
I am a widowed single mom
and I am
a former LuLaRoe consultant,
and now I own
Decades Rock 'N' Pop.
Before that, it was
a LuLaRoe branded Airstream.
This is my new
boutique for LuLaRoe.
Everything on social media
was perfect with LuLaRoe.
She is about to push.
She is adorable.
A person would post
a picture of their new car.
♪BecauseOfLuLaRoe.
Their vacation,
#BecauseOfLuLaRoe.
Homes, events, parties, galas,
Always #BecauseOfLuLaRoe.
Of course me
with the Airstream,
because of LuLaRoe.
My entire lifestyle, really,
it all became everything
LuLaRoe.
There was definitely
a culture of toxic positivity
because of what you
were allowed to share
and what you weren't
allowed to share.
So you were allowed
to share everything positive,
but if anything negative
showed up on your pages,
under your comments,
under your sold comments,
you were
supposed to delete it.
It never happened,
it was never on there.
So when I get those messages
from my team that I go,
"Oh, my gosh.
Why has LuLaRoe done
this to me?"
Be an editor.
Use that delete button.
It's really powerful.
I could not
count the number
of times I was reprimanded
for being "negative"
because I was
trying to address
legitimate business concerns.
You know, if you complained,
then you should,
you should just be grateful.
If your business has
taken any kind of a dip,
it's because you took
a slow thought process
and got rubbernecking.
Got yourself thinking
about the negativity.
When I say, you had to
be sunshine and rainbows,
you did, no real talk.
Everything was boss
girl, boss babe.
Stay at home
and work in your pajamas.
Just... just like everything,
everything,
everything was fake.
It was very, very common
to see the higher ranks
sitting on a top of maybe
100 boxes of LuLaRoe
stacked up
in front of their house.
So the way LuLaRoe's
structure worked
was that it was
a surprise box.
You didn't know
what you were getting.
You could choose your styles,
but you never knew the print.
Today, I actually
have four boxes here.
Look how nice.
You would say,
"Hey, Tuesday night,"
I'm going to open
this box live, Facebook Live,"
and you'd be excited.
These are gorgeous,
these might,
might, might be my favorite.
And people would start
claiming the second
you opened it up
and they wanted it.
That's how big
the LuLaRoe craze was.
Favorite ever, you guys,
favorite ever.
But it also started
draining money right
from the beginning.
It was kind of like
playing a scratch off
lottery ticket
every time
you placed an order.
It was very, very addicting.
And then, once you
start getting good boxes,
you're like, "Oh, I'm gonna
order another one,
because I sold half my box."
Well, you sold half your box,
you're really
not making anything.
Oh, my leg.
- Got it?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mama, what's this one?
- Okay, so that
is the perfect tee.
- Yes.
That's actually what
I have on, but I tied it.
Yes.
Ma, do you have
any unicorn leggings?
- These... I had...
- Unicorn.
What do you think
about that, Zip?
Oh, I...
- These kiwis.
Hang on, let's see where.
So, what a unicorn is,
it would be like
a very unique print,
a hot commodity
that everyone had to have,
almost like you
can flaunt with it
and be like, "Yeah,
I got something
that you don't have."
This one is a...
Ooh. Those are kind of cool.
That's an owl with
the headphones on.
- These are huge unicorns.
- LuLaRoe.
Because it's the shades with
LuLaRoe emblem
on these things.
Come on now.
I know one for a fact was
all black leggings like,
if you got
all black leggings, then,
oh, you got it like, it
sold instantly.
- Oh, those are fly.
- I know these are fire,
but I don't know
if they would be unicorns.
- No, maybe not.
- They're unicorn to me.
Mmm-hmm
I mean, people would tell
they had like
hundreds of pairs of LuLaRoe,
like more leggings
than you could ever wear.
It was like
a collecting kind of craze.
They created their own,
um, hysteria around
these leggings.
You know,
as a business person,
I'm like, I was like, smart.
- Do you wanna follow us?
- Yeah.
Do you wanna follow us
through the warehouse
a little bit?
You have to see the amazing
pieces that are here.
Look at these.
DeAnne just scored two
Tie Dye Carlys.
Yeah. Because you know what?
I am the owner,
and I never get Tie Dyes
'cause you guys
all buy them up so fast.
It has been
the best day of my life.
Well, look at them.
Look at everybody's busy,
busy, busy,
pulling your orders.
So get out there and order,
order, order, order
more fresh stuff, yo.
Before LuLaRoe,
by all accounts,
Mark and DeAnne were
a semi-normal family.
They had a pretty modest
house for California.
After LuLaRoe,
they have balled out for sure.
They bought this extremely
lavish Wyoming ranch
that they host their
family on a lot,
and it's very
glamorous looking.
Mark has also used his wealth
to buy a lot of luxury cars.
One of them broke
the land speed record.
The Stidhams flaunted that
they were becoming wealthy
because that is kind of
part of the company model,
right?
Like, you want
to show how successful
you're being because
that will inspire other
people to try it as well.
We are in...
Gucci, shopping.
Look at these girls
and look how cute.
This is what we do.
DeAnne was what
these women thought
they could become if they
just had enough money.
The millionaire mindset
or a thought of
how can I become
and strive
with the opportunities
that are right
in front of me.
Family is very important
to the Stidhams,
so DeAnne hired basically
all of her children
in one capacity or another.
We want to introduce
you to our family,
which also happens to be
a core part
of the home office team.
Mark and I thought about
the people that we wanted most
to be involved were our kids.
We knew they could help us.
I remember
my parents just saying,
"We want to present
the opportunity
to our kids first."
They wanted us to be
a part of something that
they were seeing success
and they didn't
want it for themselves.
LuLaRoe really became
a very incestuous
when it came to how
they promoted people
and who was
running the company.
And I mean, the Stidhams
decided that they
were going to employ as,
I guess, as many family
members as they could.
And in my opinion,
it was also a way of them
controlling everything.
Because their family would
be totally loyal to them
and would do
what was necessary,
in order to keep
the business going,
according to the dictates
of its founders.
So as the business was
very small in the beginning,
my wife said, "I'd like
to have our kids involved."
They all had
different skill sets
and they were
the first executive team.
I think the values
of MLMs align
perfectly with
the way we think
about money in America
or the way we preach
about money in America.
Big things are happening.
They will continue to happen
by those that
are part of this company.
MLMs probably
wouldn't exist without
the prosperity gospel,
and what it
espouses is that Mormonism
in particular, being blessed
with money is like literally
being blessed by God,
like God favors you
if you are wealthy.
You want to know, if you're
good to your fellow man,
then...
then look around and see...
check your bank account.
If you have spent
your entire life
hearing the prosperity gospel
and hearing that you
can pull yourself
up by your bootstraps,
then when someone
comes along and says,
"Here, actually,
you can do it,
and you don't have to go
have any student debt."
You know, and you can
be the boss.
Then we're all kind
of primed for it
from birth here
in the United States.
Where there's a will,
there's a way.
And when you are ready
and you are determined,
you're gonna do
whatever it takes.
Remember that I will persist
until I succeed.
I wasn't even a year in
and I was attending almost
every training that I could
either fly or drive to.
By getting here, you prove
to yourself
that this was where you
needed to be
at the most important time
of your business.
They convinced me
to... to buy more,
buy more, sell more.
The bigger your business is,
the more you're gonna sell
because more people
will come to you
because you have more stuff
in your pictures,
and, you know, they
encourage that.
What they, LuLaRoe, would tell
you to do,
and especially the leaders,
is to put the money back in
to buy more inventory
and to grow your inventory.
So that's exactly what I did.
As much as I could,
um, use to buy more clothing
and add more styles,
and sizes and colors,
I would, I would put it
all back in.
I had somebody
underneath of me who, um...
sold $12,000 in one month.
And then she said to me,
"But I spent $12,000."
And I said to her,
"Well, you had to spend
money to make money."
"Order more inventory
and you'll do better."
It was just kind
of always a blanket.
What can I do to make
my business better?
Like, if you stood in line
to talk to DeAnne
and she would...
like, her first question,
probably back to you
probably would have been,
"Well, how much inventory
have you ordered this month?"
Remember, you ought to
be placing orders
every single day, do not wait
for things to be restocked.
You order what is available
to you every day.
Every dollar that we made,
they would tell us to reinvest
it back into more clothes.
Order consistently
to replenish
the sales that you're having.
Always felt more pressure
to buy more merchandise.
They always told us,
"The more you have,
the more you sell."
The more you buy,
the more you sell.
Like, it's not ethical.
Look at your inventory,
analyze what you're selling,
analyze what season is coming,
what you intend to sell
and order consistently
to sell consistently
so that your business
will consistently grow.
They're making money off
every single box you order.
That's why they're telling you
to order more boxes.
And you know what?
Maybe that was part
of their plan for sending you,
you know, a box full of half
of it is unsellable crap
because they know
they're gonna just tell you,
"Oh, you couldn't sell
half of it, order more."
So size medium Julia.
You can layer it, you can
put a Lindsay over it,
you can put a Shirley over it,
you can put a Joy over it.
I was just consumed
and obsessed with selling,
that was for sure. I just got
the endorphins as soon as
I had a sale.
Heart pink and a gold
and it's kind of like
an Aztec look to it.
So you have these pretty
triangles.
Here's my sales for the day.
I got to beat it tomorrow,
and I was just competing,
I guess, with myself and just,
"Hey, you know, I sold
1,000 today.
Let's do 1,500 tomorrow."
You have black, would be
super cute wearing it
with black leggings
and wearing this as a tunic.
I wanted to hit those top
rankings, you know,
to show that I was a success.
Super pretty.
Someone can just rock
this dress.
They train you to think
this way.
They're so good at it.
Every single week.
You know, with the webinar
and all of the trainings,
and they're encouraging,
you know, go to the trainings.
This is where it's at.
This is where the excitement
is created,
all of us coming together
and creating bigger,
better businesses together.
It just went from like,
nice and calm
to very much high-paced job
that I had to keep up in.
'Cause if you don't keep up,
you fail.
263, large royal blue.
1483, small black lace.
Polka dots.
Like 16-hour days.
I would wake up and I had
all these orders
that I saw immediately,
as soon as I got up,
before I went to the bathroom,
I would go pull orders.
We were like 24/7,
all the time.
What's the next thing
we can do?
I never felt like I could
take a break.
I just had to keep going.
Day one, working
for LuLaRoe was...
I would say, hit
the ground running.
As a professional designer,
I understand that I'm not
designing for myself,
I'm designing for the company,
and what they wanted was...
loud, busy, eye-catching.
Our main direction was just
make it pop.
When you're working
in production, there's always
this balance
of quality and quantity,
and with LuLaRoe,
it was like...
So we were given the task
by, Patrick, the head
of design and production,
to design
a thousand prints,
in one day between
me and three other designers.
It would be open
and existing print,
change of color, save it.
Put stripes over it, save it.
Put the stripes
in the background, save it.
Open another pattern,
put it over
the existing pattern
to make this unholy mash up
of two patterns.
You know, does it look good?
No. Save it.
It was a stressful
environment.
By the end of the day,
Patrick would have
a thousand patterns
to choose from,
and how many actually
made it to production,
I have no idea.
The evidence.
Oh, boy.
They stopped producing
the inventory
that I joined for.
I don't want print
overlay over print overlay.
The yuck colors,
the oranges, the weird shades
of mustard, stripes,
ugly flowers.
A jaguar, a bear.
None of them appearing
from the crotch.
So, that's good.
Uh, lot of shapes.
A pattern layered on top
of a pattern.
God! There's just so many
of them.
Here she is.
We're like, "Okay."
There were some
questionable prints.
You know, they put the...
the designer, Patrick.
They put DeAnne, Mark
on a pair of leggings,
like we had actual clothes
with their faces on it.
Uh, it was just strange.
This one, I designed
the ghost.
Owl eyes, peacock feathers,
tribal, ethnic.
I don't know.
We get the boxes.
We open it up.
And it was like,
"What the hell is this?"
All of the color vomit
you could put on fabric
encapsulated in these
brown boxes.
We were horrified.
No one in the fucking world
wants to wear leggings
that feature a bee
crawling up your cooch.
Oh, my God!
That bee is gonna sting
your big pink pearl.
No.
Blake is my 22-year-old son.
And he signed up
to sell LuLaRoe
under me and...
I wish I could have talked him
out of it.
His onboarding package
was horrendous.
The worst I'd ever seen.
Okay, any other...
anything else we can show?
We have just so much,
- so much.
- Here's your number...
number 17.
And so this is
number 30 right here.
It's pretty green one.
I just remember trying
to pattern mix
and put this with like
a striped shirt
and just thinking,
"This is the ugliest
thing I've ever seen,
but I've gotta sell it."
I think it's,
I think it's gorgeous.
And this one, which is going
to be the gray sleeves
with a really pretty
dark blue background
with pinks, purples, corals.
When I saw that box,
I actually called home office
and said,
"Do you understand what you
just sent my recruit"?
I wasn't trying to make
it my son. I'm like,
"Do you understand
his onboarding package?
Like, I've been in here
for three years.
I couldn't sell that."
Gray with... tigers.
Like, with black tigers
on them.
Number 1404.
This is an extra small.
I always remember her saying,
"This isn't good stuff.
We've gotta get it returned."
I have this one which is
so gorgeous black background,
there's really
gorgeous flowers
on there, golden flowers.
And I just remember
thinking,
"I've got to do it.
I've gotta push it.
I can do this."
And then, I remember
my first live,
I sold a pair,
and I've sold my very
first shirt,
and I remember just
looking to her
and being like,
"Yes, I did it,
I can do this."
And then I'm pretty sure
I sold one other piece
that live.
And then from there,
I would do lives
and not sell anything.
And then from there, about
six or eight months later,
I just kind of tapered off
and they went into a box
and I never sold them again.
You can't go overnight,
you know, making
clothing for a few
thousand people,
to making boxes
full of clothing
for 80,000 people.
You have to cut
corners somewhere.
It was madness over here.
They ship, receive
everything here.
That's where they would park
right there, all the Mercedes,
all their flashy cars.
I was working at LuLaRoe
from March of 2016
to January of 2017.
For what amount
we were gonna
do on a day, I was like
15 million, 12 million
in a day.
Okay, walking,
walking, walking.
This is what it looks like.
Leggings, leggings
and leggings.
More leggings.
It's like, get busy.
Everybody, start selling.
We can go see where they
have their moldy
clothes at.
The warehouse was full.
It was packed to the brim.
And somebody decided to put...
start putting clothes outside.
One night, like it started
to drizzle,
and the next day, sunny.
And then as time went on,
nobody really noticed
like the molding yet.
And yeah, starting to get into
the... to get shipped out.
Thousands.
Yeah, it's a lot of clothes.
I'm sorry.
Y'all just taking on the tour
of the LuLaRoe, uh...
All right,
we're taking off, man.
Why is he so angry?
When people describe
MLMs to you, they'll draw you
a pyramid,
and at the bottom
of the pyramid,
like the visible base,
um, you see just more
retailers, right?
Like that's a line
of retailers.
But I think there's
an invisible face
that gets left out of all
of those graphics,
and that's made up
of all the people
who are making the products
that all the retailers
are selling.
The people
at the very bottom
of the LuLaRoe
pyramid are not white
Christian stay-at-home moms.
Um, they're the people
making the leggings.
And let me show you
what I got,
because it's a piece of crap.
She's fighting mad.
She is just one of thousands
of women complaining
about the super soft leggings
they purchased,
only to discover
they have holes.
They're ripping, um, they're
wearing them for a few hours,
they're wearing them
for a few minutes
and finding holes
and large, substantial tears.
Christina Hinks
used to sell the leggings.
She showed me a pair
that an angry customer
returned to her.
I remember like my third,
third or fourth order,
getting the ever-coveted black.
Solid black leggings.
And I was like, "Well, shit,
I'm gonna keep
one of these for me,"
you know.
The day that I wore them,
I fell asleep on my couch.
I was woken up a few hours
later by the baby crying,
and I got up
and my husband's cackling.
Cackling.
"What's funny?"
He's like,
"Christina, your ass
looks like Swiss cheese."
Went into the bathroom,
took my pants off,
and you could put
your whole hand
through the holes
in my left butt cheek.
And I said, "Okay,
it must be a fluke."
So, I pulled the second
pair out
and I put them on.
Same thing.
I was pissed.
That's when I started digging.
That's when I started
reaching out to people.
MommyGyver was a blog
that I created to sort
of empower women
to do their own things,
like MacGyver,
who could turn anything
into anything.
So I had started
writing MommyGyver
around, um,
May and June
of the... of 2016-ish.
And I really started
writing about LuLaRoe.
I think the first post
I made was in December.
When I first started writing,
nobody wanted to cover it.
It wasn't a big enough
dumpster fire
for them to see the fire
from way high up.
And I felt obligated.
I felt like I had
to say something
because if I didn't,
who would?
All of these, these women
were sending me messages.
This particular consultant
was baited to onboard
with the understanding
that it would only take
her 20 hours a week
to make full-time pay.
She states that, um,
she learned very quickly
it's not a part-time job,
and even exceeded
full-time hours,
as was my experience.
As I started digging through
and as I started going
higher up and higher up
and into their close circles,
I was finding
leaders telling people
how to get other women
to buy in.
Know most people don't have
$5,000, $10,000
at their disposal,
but that's okay.
They can take that
credit card with $5,000
or $10,000 maximum
and they can max it out.
My sponsor initially had
suggested to me maybe
that I try, um, crowd funding.
In the end, to come up
with a last little bit, um,
we ended up
not paying some bills.
At one point, there was
a document given to me
where it was created
by a top consultant,
and it was how to come up
with the money.
Um, ask you friends
and family for a loan.
Borrow from your
children's college fund.
You can get a loan.
You can get...
Um, use credit cards,
you can use, um,
money from family.
You can sell stuff
that you already own.
Um, so there's lots of ways
that you can raise that money.
I started hearing that women
were... were, following me
and they were waiting
for the next article
to come out.
As I started getting
more popular in my blog,
I was getting death threats.
People were showing
up on my doorstep.
I was getting hate mail.
I was not expecting
MommyGyver to become
as famous/infamous as it was.
So are you guys
blocking the trolls?
That would be awesome.
Um, so make sure
that you do because
it would make me so happy.
There were retailers
on every corner, you know.
I mean,
it was really highly doubtful
that we would all succeed.
My next door neighbor
was a retailer
in our apartment.
I was here.
She was here.
And it was crazy, we all both
had our LuLaRoe rooms.
Everywhere you turn,
there was somebody,
I mean, you go to the mall,
you run into somebody
selling LuLaRoe,
wearing it
or something like that.
I made about 60 grand
in that first,
within that first year.
And I just took that money
and just threw
it back in there.
This dress
right here cost me.
I paid $30 for this, $30.
I'm lucky to get
probably $10 for it now.
And at certain point,
I was spending more than
I was bringing in.
I have boxes
in that corner right there,
and I have these pink bags
full of LuLaRoe.
This is all left.
This is all what I have left.
I really had enough inventory.
I really did,
but I bought more things.
That's what gets
you more in trouble.
I was telling
somebody recently.
If you wanna... what I paid,
we're talking
at least 20 grand.
Wow!
-$20,000 right here.
Wow.
- 20,000, 25,000 right here.
Sales just started
to drop like almost
half each month.
So, let's say June,
I did 16,000.
The next month
would have been,
you know, 12,000,
then 10,000,
then 8,000, then 4,000.
And by January 2018
I only sold
a thousand dollars.
And I just felt I needed
to have new inventory.
What I had was not selling.
I can only create so many
outfits with what I had.
So I actually took out loans
to buy more inventory.
My house was
more LuLaRoe
than it was honestly house.
Inventory all over
the front room
and the sitting room
and the dining room.
Everywhere.
There's stuff
that goes on in our brains
that is totally natural.
They are defense mechanisms.
They keep us alive.
We all have this, um,
cognitive bias
called loss aversion,
which basically means
that we feel losses
a lot more deeply
and more strongly
than we feel gains.
There's a lot of tricks
we play on ourselves
to like, not feel
like a loser.
There's another thing
called honoring sunk costs,
and that is throwing
good money after bad.
So, the more money
you put into your MLM,
the more you're losing,
the more you're thinking,
"It's an investment."
"I know I'm already
$10,000 in debt
and my husband doesn't know,
and our garage
is full of leggings,
and I can't quit now.
You know, I can't just
walk away
with that kind of debt.
I have to keep trying."
With LuLaRoe,
there's no safety net.
There's nothing
to save you when your,
when your business goes wrong,
because you aren't a business.
You're...
you're a retailer
for another company.
And if they fail,
they'll get protected.
But you are ass out.
Oh, my gosh,
there's so many large.
1446, white with the black.
I was in a jam.
I couldn't pay
any of my bills.
We were behind
on the house payment,
plus we had 11 kids.
So, it... it was just had
become desperation.
I pretty much hit rock bottom
and said I can't.
I went live with my closet
because I had so much,
so much,
and I still hadn't told
my customers yet.
And I just held up this dress
and I was like, "All right,
this is a sweater Carly,
it's super rare,
it's a unicorn."
Um, and then
I just start crying.
Once the tears started,
I couldn't get them to stop.
And I just told them,
you know, "This is it."
I already knew
I was gonna have to file
for bankruptcy.
There is no way.
I knew I owed
so much in taxes.
This is where I go
to make my monthly
bankruptcy payment,
715 basically.
I'm in a five-year bankruptcy,
so overall I'll be paying
a little over $40,000
with all the fees
and everything.
The lawyer fees and all.
I'll be honest
with you,
I thought about suicide
when all this was happening,
and just...
just to get out of that
after hitting rock bottom, so.
I, um,
have crazy anxiety now
that I didn't have before.
I felt like a failure.
I put myself in debt,
and I had no way
to pay it off.
Still tens of thousands
in debt
to this day that I still
haven't managed to pay off.
So you know the story
of Red Riding Hood,
how she went
through the forest
to visit her grandmother
and the wolf had eaten
her grandmother.
And the whole time
she's like, "Wow.
Grandma, you're acting
kind of weird.
Grandma, your nose
is a little different.
Holy crap, grandma,
you're eating me.
You're not really grandma,
you're a wolf."
That's what LuLaRoe was.
It was innocuous,
genuine, real,
love, emotion, comfort.
"Just kidding.
We're gonna eat you alive."
What happens to people
in MLMs,
and I've done interventions
to get people out
of multi-level marketing
schemes
is they get hurt,
and they could be bankrupted,
their marriage could end,
they become estranged
from family and old friends.
People can be devastated.
I mean, how do you get people
to buy into something
that is not in their own
best interest?
And the answer
is you manipulate them
in a kind of cult-like manner.
When I decided
it was no longer for me,
everyone that was above me
stopped talking to me.
I didn't want my upline
to be mad that I was leaving
because I know it would
affect their bonus checks.
It was hard for me to let go.
Um, it was hard for me
to admit failure.
I've talked to ex-MLM sources
who described
the process of leaving
as psychological warfare,
who found that the moment
that they expressed
that they didn't wanna
be involved
with this group anymore,
they were dropped like trash.
That's the thing
that lets you know
this is a destructive,
cultish group,
when leaving comes
with these major consequences.
I was never
making any money.
I stuck it out as long
as I could, and fall of 18,
that was it.
I just kind of dropped off
the LuLaRoe world.
Said, "I don't want
to do this anymore."
And it's lonely
when that happens to you,
because you don't have
anything else in your life
except for LuLaRoe,
and now you have
to rebuild it all over again.
LuLaRoe convinced us
that we were in something,
you know, super popular
and we were super important,
and you just kind of
fell into acting like it
and believing it.
And that's why I look back
on it feeling so cultish.
You are not selling clothes.
You are giving people freedom,
you are giving people life,
you are giving people hope,
you are giving
people confidence.
Is LuLaRoe a cult?
I would have to say,
I just can't think
of anything else
that makes people
quite that dedicated.
Think about
all the great things.
the positive things,
not the negative things.
I would be up until
four o'clock in the morning,
almost every night.
My kids saw way less of me
after I started.
I don't think I ever slept.
There's no
work-life balance.
You know, you're putting
all of your finances into it.
You've alienated
your friends and family.
I just can't think
of anything else
to call it.
When I left,
I was a mess.
I was a hot mess.
I was in hook,
line and sinker.
I believed all of it,
and I don't think
that they went into it
to create it to be a cult.
But from my experience,
it was.
Especially when I went to leave.
That was a struggle.
You quickly learned
who your friends were
and who they weren't.
They had no need
for me anymore.
Looking back on it now, I'm...
I'm shocked that I
drank that much Kool-Aid.
You're basically, like, marked
as a suppressive person
and you're hurting
their business by leaving
and by telling your truth.
So I just shut up and I left
and I refused to talk
about it until now.
I literally didn't know
what to do with myself,
because it was my identity.
The mentality in there
is always positive,
nothing negative,
and you're
in a LuLaRoe family.
So you have your LuLa mom,
your LuLa grandma,
your LuLa babies.
Everything is Lula
In LuLaRoe.
MLMs are scammy,
but they are not
just your average scam.
They have so much in common
psychologically with the groups
that we would traditionally
think of as cults.
You know, they encourage you
to recruit others.
They shut down
questioning and dissent.
They gaslight you
into thinking
that if you don't succeed
in this organization,
it is your fault.
If you don't make
your quota for the month,
well, girl, it's because you
didn't think positive enough.
You didn't envision
the Cadillac.
Therefore,
there is something
wrong with you.
You need to stick
it out another month
to really prove yourself
as the boss babe
we thought you were.
I just felt like a failure
and I didn't wanna
go to my mom
and after she gave me
that money from her
retirement fund,
like I didn't want
to go to her
and be like, "Mom,
I failed."
So, I just, I was in denial
a long time,
and I just
really just had
to face the truth.
It's really hard to see
yourself as a victim.
To say you were victimized
is to admit a weakness,
and a weakness feels painful.
Plus, if you admit
that you were victimized,
then you also have
to, in an MLM,
admit that you
victimized others,
which is even harder.
I just felt
extremely guilty
for the people that I,
you know, had join.
So, I just, I always think
about that, I always
wonder like, how do they
think of me,
like I had such highs
and then I had such lows.
And I think about that now,
like, what do they
think of me now
or did they think I was being
deceitful at the time.
So, while
a LuLaRoe recruit
might be a suburban mom
with highlights
wearing bulldog leggings
rather than
a new religious member
in a white robe
with a shaved head
on a commune,
the methods of manipulation
that they're under
are quite similar.
We were supposed to dress
a certain way all the time.
If it was too big,
we would tie a knot in it,
mix our patterns,
then we all wore it,
and we all wore
the same thing,
acted the same way.
So like
being on stage
and looking out
into the audience.
Um, everybody was twins.
I'm not going to lie, like
everybody had that Joy on.
How am I remembering
all these names?
It's like the cardigan,
the long.
And then everyone
was rocking leggings.
Oh, my gosh. Wow!
What a morning.
I can't imagine
what that must
have been like for DeAnne,
to look out and see everybody
that you've convinced
to be a certain way.
What that would feel like?
I've always just
kind of always wondered
what did she really think.
They need
that culture of conformity
where you're only hearing
the MLM rhetoric,
that toxic positivity
from your upline,
where you're only
hearing the mantras
and the faux inspiration
from the people at the top,
it creates the sense that
you're a part of something
bigger than yourself.
And I want to tell you
there is a sense of belonging.
I think there is a specific
group of people
that they're targeting
and it's middle-aged
white women in Middle America.
But they probably
do have sprinklings of,
you know, a Latina,
a black woman,
uh, you know, an Asian
just to, you know, bring some
diversity, some seasoning.
But, um, they use
a lot of black vernacular
in order to, um,
to look relatable.
Hey, girls. Hey!
Hey, girl, hey. Hello, hello,
everyone, welcome.
- Hey!
- Which is fine.
That's fine if you wanna use
black vernacular.
I'm not the vernacular police,
but it's not reflected
in their downline.
It's not reflected
on their stages
when they hold
these major events.
I have a problem
with it because
they're using
the Black vernacular
to profit,
but we're not profiting
off of it because
we're only there
for seasoning
so that they can tell,
the world,
"Yes, we're diverse."
Okay.
- Is that it?
Yes.
That really struck me
when I would sell my product,
um, Black people
would never...
I would... that would shut,
they would shut the door
in my face, yeah.
I promise you, I promise you.
And I have neighbors, people,
church, family, friends.
My daughter said the clothing
wasn't their style.
I guess they didn't like
the clothing.
I would say
95% of these women were white.
I have only seen a few people
of color ever
who were a part of LuLaRoe,
and all the main figures
who are very popular
and high up in LuLaRoe were
always very homogeneous.
Mark and DeAnne were
projecting a certain image,
an image of a white couple.
When you have a group
than has that kind
of leadership
that represents a...
a kind of prototype,
they encourage you to want
to be just like the leaders.
What's up, y'all?
We're here.
This is 2016,
New York convention.
It's getting live,
it's getting lit.
There's a bunch of ladies
in leggings and dresses
and leggings and dresses.
Did I mention
that they're in leggings?
Being Black at LuLaRoe
was great.
I was the unicorn Of LuLaRoe,
you best believe.
I rode that train,
I mean, I tooted my horn
and everything because
I mean, yeah, they...
It wasn't diverse at all.
I mean, in a serious,
on a serious side, like...
I don't know if I could
say like...
I may have could have gotten
taken advantage of...
...a few times,
like I definitely
endured some...
some racism I'm not,
I'm not going to lie.
But again, for me...
I'll put up with it.
I'm where I wanted to be...
I'm living my dream, you know,
and I've dealt with it
in my life.
You know, this is,
it's nothing new.
It's going to be everywhere
you go.
Like, there's always
somebody that hates you.
I was so grateful
for the opportunity just
to be there.
They incorporated me
in their family.
They let me come
to the cookouts.
I was in.
And I'm just like,
"I'm this nobody from Concord,
like, I mean..."
I was thinking, "Yeah, I want
to do this for the rest
of my life."
♪ Know yourself
Find your groove ♪
♪ Nothing is impossible ♪
♪ You are unstoppable ♪
♪ Happy days they come
and go ♪
Sing it.
♪ Always gonna have
that LuLaRoe♪
There was always a lot of hype,
fun activities,
ran by Sam Schultz.
Sam Schultz is DeAnne's
direct nephew.
Sam was right at the top
of LuLaRoe
and was really the LuLaRoe
hype man.
It was actually Sam Schultz
who came and approached me
at that beach.
He was the reason
why I was there.
Elijah! Elijah! Elijah!
I related to Sam,
like he was kind of my idol.
He was my big brother.
Ha-ha!
- Yo, what up, y'all?
- Look, it's a Monday.
- Back to work.
- Hey!
I would do
anything for Sam.
I felt in debt to him.
The first time
I met Sam Shultz was
at a LuLaRoe training,
and they will ask you
what your "why" is.
Can you guys see me okay?
Let's see, I felt like
this is like
an interrogation light.
He's very,
very good
at getting close to you
and listening to your story.
What's up, everyone?
It feels nice to have somebody
kind of ask you those.
Why do you...
Why do you do
what you do?
I told my why.
My husband had passed
in December of 2012.
There were
times shortly
after Scott passed
that I really probably
didn't deserve to have my son.
Which might not be
the best thing
for any mom to ever say.
Just self-medicated,
slept a lot.
It was bad.
And I told him that story,
and I think right
then and there, right then,
I was the target.
Because he knew the guilt
that I carried from the years
immediately after
my husband passed.
He chose close people
and groomed them for a while,
so he would get away with it.
So we wouldn't turn on him.
I called him my best friend
'cause I did think
he was my best friend.
And so did my son.
He loved him.
When you are brought up
in a household
that literally worships
the church of MLM,
all you know is how
to worship the church of MLM.
Sam kind of
encouraged us to,
"All right, come on,
let's do our own thing.
It's... we're going to start
our own thing."
I trusted him, you know.
And I quit, I quit LuLaRoe.
I did.
I was naive.
I learned that Sam
was in and out
of various schemes,
plots, get rich quick ideas,
whatever you want
to call them.
The Utah County musician,
who makes a living
organizing concerts
and once owned the popular
Sammy's Cafe,
is now facing
26 felonies tonight.
In all charging
documents say Schultz
recruited
at least 13 investors,
who collectively gave Schultz
$323,000.
There was a medicinal
marijuana farm.
You know, he wanted
more money from me
for these fake investment
opportunities.
In total,
Sam managed to get from me
almost $100,000,
and the majority of that
money was money left
by my late husband,
allocated to Peirson.
People will say
to me with
the current business,
"Oh, my gosh,
you worked so hard.
You worked, I can't believe
you do all this by yourself."
They don't know
the real reason
why I do all of it by myself
is because in my head,
every time the Airstream
door opens,
I'm constantly trying
to make up for what I lost.
Me, like so many others
of his victims, were plucked
right out of that company.
But you know what?
The company won't
take any responsibility
for it.
2017 was the big year
where they got
a ton of lawsuits
filed against them
and the backlash against them
really started.
I think there was really
power in numbers,
and once people all started
getting together and talking
about this stuff,
you know, I think
more lawsuits were filed.
I think people started
reaching out to the media.
And I think ultimately,
it started giving
the case attention.
Three Sacramento women
are suing
a popular clothing company
called LuLaRoe for $1 billion.
The attorney claims
the company
has cheated
thousands of women.
I'm a fourth generation
steamfitter of Local UA342.
I'm known
in the LuLaRoe Defective
Defectors' Support Group
as Heather Blithely.
My legal name, however,
is Heather Blevins.
I try to keep my online
social media presence
and my real life self
kind of separate.
I don't know
why I wanted to help so bad.
I really don't.
It just wasn't fair,
and no one was listening.
And everyone was telling us
we were wrong
for trying to help
and we were wrong for caring
and we just knew...
that it was real.
I think that
the Facebook group
is one of the reasons
why I have always known
this is a story
that's worth reporting
because people were
so incredibly passionate
about it.
I wasn't really sure
how to go about
telling you guys.
And just
really want
to see
justice in some form
or another.
When I first joined
LuLaRoe Defective,
it was pretty small
and I volunteered.
As consultants started
mass leaving LuLaRoe,
there wasn't any place
for us to say,
"Here's what really happened
behind the scenes."
So, it's like a domino effect,
right?
You get one person
who just is not happy
and they decide to say
something and then
it's like, boom.
The... the door gets
kicked down.
It's like, me too, me too.
This happened to me too.
The membership grew
pretty steadily,
um, from a few hundred
to a couple of thousand,
and at the height
of the group,
there were 75,000 members.
Heather is
one of my good friends now,
and she's a damn good
detective as well.
I can say that.
It was brought
to our attention by some
of the members
how a lot of their
onboarding packages
had ads that advertised
full-time pay
for part-time work.
$60,000 to $75,000 a year,
working 20 hours a week.
There was
a trend of burning your
onboarding package.
When people would cancel,
they were just so excited
to get out
that they would burn
their onboarding package,
and I realized that
evidence is being lost.
And so I went and got
a post office box
and asked the group for
their onboarding packages.
We encouraged everyone,
"File a complaint with
your state's
attorney general,"
and all we could
do is hope that
someone was going to pay
attention and someone
was going to take interest.
Finally, I got a message
from the investigators
of the Washington State
Attorney General's Office,
and she was asking if I had
any information about
which consultants
in Washington were impacted.
One thing I sent to them
was the brochure
that came
in the onboarding package
that said you could make
full-time work
for part-time pay.
Oh, and the video of Jordan
and Lindsay Wheeler,
who's a top consultant.
We need to get away
from being
a pyramid scheme, okay?
What it is is if you
sign up Sally,
you have, you have no reason
to help Sally
sell the product in her room.
Right? You can just keep
promoting her to buy, to buy,
to buy, to buy.
- You could even...
And they were
explaining
a pretty big policy change.
I'm not panicked
at all, right?
If you're doing
the right things,
there's no issue.
When the LuLaRoe
first started,
if you had people under you,
you weren't making
a percentage of the clothing
they sold.
You're making a percentage
of the clothing they bought.
So for example,
I'm in LuLaRoe.
I have a girl under me,
let's say.
If she buys ten shirts
and she can only sell two,
it doesn't really
matter to me.
I'm making commission
off all ten shirts.
And then eventually
LuLaRoe changed
their structure for bonuses,
where instead I was gonna
make only money
of the shirts she sold.
So instead of making money
for ten shirts, I was looking
at making money for two.
All of the sudden,
people's, um,
income was dropping
precipitously.
I mean, we've been talking
about it forever.
If you've come
to a leadership.
Yeah, this
is not new.
Yeah, this is not new.
This is something that
we've been talking about.
Lindsay, what do you say
to people when
they say we are a pyramid
scheme?
Quick answer.
We're not a pyramid scheme.
My husband thought we were
at first.
He told me I was gonna
share a cell with
Bernie Madoff
'cause he was convinced
that there was no way
that I could make this
kind of money doing
something legally.
That's my favorite piece
of evidence that
I've ever seen.
And again, that was sent
to me by a consultant.
You've
probably seen their brightly
colored tops and leggings
on your social media feed.
But tonight, the company
LuLaRoe facing
another lawsuit.
The Washington State
Attorney General says LuLaRoe
made claims of high profits
and tricked people
into joining a pyramid scheme.
So, what makes LuLaRoe
a pyramid scheme,
according to the Attorney
General's office?
Well, the monthly bonuses,
which were reportedly
seven to 12 times higher
than the actual
merchandise sales.
Do you ever
encourage retailers to share
how much they made,
um, in a particular
bonus check?
No. 121.
So, exhibit 121.
So I'm gonna
start playing at...
at the beginning
and play for a little bit.
I am from Maryland.
My... my last check
was $250,000,
and I do about
12,000 to 13,000 in sales
every month.
I'm in Salt Lake City...
Riverton, Utah,
and our last check
was 307,000.
I... I can't even say it.
It, like, blows my mind.
So, uh, correct me
if I'm wrong,
but everyone in that video
is making more
in bonus checks than
they are in sales, correct?
At that time, yes.
Why were
they making more
on bonus checks than sales?
I don't know. Maybe they...
maybe they helped
a lot of people
to help them make money.
When we heard
about the outcome
of the Washington State case,
we were all definitely elated.
We were super excited
that the consultants
got money back.
It really, I think,
gave us hope
that, um, what we were doing
was counting for something.
We weren't just screaming
into the void.
People were listening.
It was actually
creating change, um,
and some positive outcomes,
and we really hope
that it'll continue
through the rest
of the states.
The FTC needs to strengthen
its regulations
against, uh, multi-level
marketing companies.
Pyramid schemes
are already illegal,
um, the FTC, um, website
has all that information.
Uh, I think the FTC
really needs to step up
and expand that to all MLMs.
In the beginning
of doing a research
around MLMs,
I didn't understand
that 99% of people
made nothing or lost money.
And that's a lot, that's like
kind of a low figure.
They think maybe it's 99.9.
One, two, three.
Whoo!
In a successful
multi-level marketing scheme,
you need a lot of failure
because you're making money
off of the recruits
and you're making money
off of their, um, desperation,
which often manifests
as more investment
in the company.
LuLaRoe isn't
built for you to have
your own freedom
and to have
your own empowerment.
It is meant to build
the people at the top.
It's meant to make the people
at the top richer.
Capitalism is the root
of all evil.
It does surprise me
that LuLaRoe is still
in existence
because I didn't really think
that they would be able
to fight off
all of the litigation
against them
without having to file
for bankruptcy.
I think
that LuLaRoe still exists
because Mark
and DeAnne Stidham
want to continue making money
from this business,
and what their business
is all about is selling dreams
as opposed
to selling a product.
And... and there are people
that still want to believe
in the American dream
and the dream of LuLaRoe.
We just got here
to Cancun.
This is so worth
the hard work.
I can't wait to get together
with you
when you get here to Cancun.
And those of you
that are not here, get busy,
and know that we love giving.
I can't
believe it, I can't believe
like this is still going on.
It's like none of this
had ever happened,
and the cognitive
dissonance there
is just like, it's crazy.
This is the one
where I had my son with me.
It's like... I took Brooks.
it was so awesome.
- What, he's like a baby?
- Yeah, I was nursing.
And I was able to bring him.
- Yeah.
- Do you know what I wonder?
I would love to know,
and there's no way
to actually prove this,
but I would love to know,
like how many babies were born
- because of LuLaRoe.
- How many times have you seen
fund-raisers for like
IVF treatments?
And all of us
are like, oh...
I ended up
in Cancun this weekend
because LuLaRoe
is doing a incentive trip,
is what we call it
a Dream Trip
and, um, leaders, high sellers
are here,
they would come together
once a year,
just coming together
to be with my people.
But Brianna, you started
six years ago.
- Yeah, almost.
- Yeah.
So, I worked full-time
at the hospital.
I was in nursing school,
and I was doing LuLaRoe,
like all at once.
And so online just
worked really well for me.
And then when I graduated
nursing school,
I was like full-time LuLaRoe,
full-time at the hospital.
And then eventually
LuLaRoe took over
and I quit at the hospital
and haven't looked back.
Did you buy
before you sold?
I did. I bought,
I bought a lot before I sold.
Like a lot, a lot, a lot.
I loved it.
I mean, it was just...
It made me feel good,
and then the community
that I've built
since then has been amazing.
Everybody's looking
for this bad story,
but it's not the bad story
that's really there.
It's the empowerment
that we are bringing.
It's the joy
that we're creating
in people's lives
and this opportunity
that people have had to grow.
And the people that are here
are because of choices
that they've made
in their business.
And some people have left.
And they can find reasons
as to why.
And there could be reasons
that they want to use
that maybe are
against LuLaRoe.
It could be reasons on media
and things that they followed.
But no matter what,
it all boils down
to a personal choice
and how you choose
to run your business.
I am here because
of the choices that I've made.
Your... your customers
become your friends,
like it's not just...
- Oh, she's like my bestie now,
it's wild.
- It's not,
it's not like going
into Target.
Like, my customers would be
like, "Hey, will this fit me?"
Because I know their size.
- She really does.
- You build that friendship.
People would come up,
"Is that LuLa?"
And I'm like, "Yeah, it is."
- Well, and then you bond
with that person.
- Yeah.
'Cause they know what LuLa is,
- it's like this amazing bond.
- Absolutely.
It gave me the confidence
and then I started getting
into working out
and then I started...
I actually managed to lose
like 60 pounds
That's awesome.
We are around and thriving.
And it's... again it's
a people's perception
and choice.
If they chose
to stop following LuLaRoe,
then in their life,
we don't exist anymore,
but we are still here.
I really, really hate
when MLM participants
are portrayed as suckers.
There's nothing unusual
about someone
who would like
to run their own business
and have more time
with their families.
That is what the
American dream is,
and we've all been
pitched that since birth.
People tend to think
that folks wind up in groups
like LuLaRoe
because of "brainwashing."
They were brainwashed.
They were mind-controlled.
That would never happen to me.
We all are susceptible
to these methods
of manipulation.
LuLaRoe used the tools
of psychological
and emotional manipulation
to make money.
As long as there are people
in this country
who are locked out
of the dignified labor market
and made a promise
that the American dream
is still available to them,
the MLM industry will thrive.
I did join a couple
of other MLMs
after leaving LuLaRoe
just because I was
still trying to bring
a little bit of income
into my family life,
and none of those
panned out either.
After LuLaRoe,
I really finally got the idea
that this was not in any way
going to help me,
and that these types
of companies
were just predatory.
Yeah, that's starting
to look like a good...
It's ready to go,
cookie dough.
- See.
- Ooh.
You are my mother.
You hear the rhyme
you just did.
It's ready to go,
cookie dough.
- Aw!
- Mmm-hmm.
We could start us a jingle.
Well, the American dream
is for me
was, I promise you, just
to be financially stable
and own my own business.
And LuLaRoe could have worked,
could have been that for me.
However, I... maybe I'll...
I'll take all blame, though.
I just didn't have
that fight to... to, um...
to make it happen.
There you go. Voila!
But I... I would like
to give it one more shot,
and it can be lucrative.
If LuLaRoe came to me tomorrow
and asked me,
"Hey, you wanna perform
on a cruise like you did?"
Heck yes, please.
Like, let's go, win.
Like, yeah, no, I...
in a heartbeat.
- You never stop.
- No.
- Never stops, never.
- I can't.
Never, never stops. It's okay.
- Oh.
- Check who that is.
That is just in time.
I get asked all the time,
after my experience
with LuLaRoe,
"Why in the world
would you do another
direct sales company?"
And the answer is,
I honestly feel
it's apples and oranges.
Here's my nail collection.
I have like the
entire collection almost.
I'm missing two.
If you look
at the Better Bureau Business,
the BBB rating,
I think LuLaRoe had an F.
And my new companies
Plunder, Red Aspen,
they have an A.
I think that says something.
So this is my
old LuLaRoe group.
I struggle
with this MLM
because I do like MLMs.
I love a lot
of different MLMs,
and I like to support
other women
and their businesses,
of course.
So, I would like to say
that I'm not for them,
but my nails come from them.
My candles come from them.
You know what I mean?
Like, I feel like
there's a purpose for it.
Um...
And I feel like
they've been around
for decades and decades.
My advice
to anybody going
into an MLM
or even considering it.
I don't care
if it's nail strips,
protein shakes, vitamins,
what else is out there,
make-up, um, hair products.
I don't care what it is.
Say no. Run as far as you can,
as fast as you can.
I don't think
the takeaway
from the LulaRoe's story is
that it's wrong to have hope.
It's good to have hope.
The American dream
preys on hope.
And so until we make
the American dream
less all-consuming,
that hope will lead people
to harm.
So, it's the American dream
that has to change,
not our capacity to hope
that has to change.
I'm not surprised
at all
that LuLaRoe still exists.
This is just what the people
who start MLMs do.
And if it wasn't LuLaRoe
that was sticking around,
Mark and DeAnne
would go start another MLM.
We're aware
of the negativity,
but guess what?
It is a minute amount
compared to all
of the amazing positive things
that are happening.
Forget about using
the truth as your defense.
Use kindness as your defense.
That is the culture
of LuLaRoe.
This is just the way
we do business here
to make people think
that they're pursuing
their own success
while they're actually
making someone else rich.
It's just greed,
pure American greed.
Each and every
one of you are a part
of the American dream
because you are entrepreneurs
and you own your own business,
and I will tell you,
some days are not so good.
Guess what?
So many days are so amazing.
LuLaRoe.