Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
This one, Mommy.
This is what I want
for Christmas.
Put that away.
I'll come back.
Okay.
So you know what,
I think this little guy
needs to take a nap.
What's your name?
Charlotte.
Charlotte,
so should I tell Santa
that this is what
you really want for Christmas?
You know Santa?
Can you keep a secret?
Good, because I'm really
not supposed to tell anyone,
but Santa is actually
a personal friend of mine.
He is?
He is,
and, you know, he calls me
every time this year
asking me
what all the good girls
and the good boys
want for Christmas.
So, have you been good
this year?
Because I kinda
have to report back to him.
I've been good.
You have?
That's wonderful.
Santa's going to be
so happy to hear that.
Can I?
-Thank you.
-There you go.
You're wonderful with kids.
You must have some of your own.
Not yet,
but hopefully soon.
Henry, My fiancé, and I
we own this shop together,
and he loves kids.
If it were up to him,
we'd have a baker's dozen.
And how do you feel
about that?
It's definitely negotiable.
This sweater is so beautiful.
You know, Nicole made that.
Well, if you happen to have
one in my size,
make sure Santa puts one
under the tree for me.
Thank you.
That is very kind of you to say,
but, really,
it's just more of a hobby.
Well, let me know
if you ever decide
to make sweaters for people.
I own a store, Unique Styles.
I know my customers
would love your work.
Here's my card.
Thank you,
Something to think about.
See you tomorrow.
See ya.
Come on, Charlotte, time to go.
Bye, Charlotte.
-Bye!
-See ya.
What do you think,
Jack Frost?
You think I could make a living
selling my designs?
-Hmm?
Yeah, it's a crazy idea.
Hey there, my future wife.
Hello, future husband.
How'd we do today?
Uh, good. Busy.
We even sold the giraffe.
-Which one?
-Tall guy.
Gonna miss that big guy.
Oh, he's going to a good home.
Uh, you got our sweaters?
Yes.
Just finished them today.
Ah-hah.
Oh, they're beautiful.
You do realize
that we're going
to an ugly sweater party,
though, right?
Yeah, that is why
I made the proportions
from the eyes to the bill
completely off, you see?
-Yeah, no--
-Kinda ugly, right?
Yeah, I see that.
They're... hideous.
You know, this could actually
be the year
that we win this thing.
Yeah, that's not
going to happen.
You know Susan's won,
like, four years in a row.
Yeah,
but she has no idea
who she's dealing with.
Huh?
Wow, I like the way you think.
I like the way you kiss.
Mm, we're not wearing those.
Okay.
There she is.
Why are we stopping
at the house?
I left my gloves here.
I love our house.
It's perfect.
I can't wait
to raise our family here.
Oh, it's gonna be perfect
once I finish
all the renovations.
Mm...
Can we go inside?
Not today.
I just took out
all the flooring.
Aw...
Oh, just think, Nic.
This time next year
we're gonna be in our house
having Christmas dinner
with all our friends.
You promise?
I promise.
Oh, wait.
Oh.
Huh?
Aw...
The first of many memories
we're going to make here.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, hey.
Seriously, Susan,
why bother having people
over to your house
if you're going to make
your friends do all the work.
I'm not following.
-Not following?
-Nope.
You realize I made
a glazed ham, roast turkey,
rack of lamb,
and Beef Wellington
for your party.
Remind me, what exactly
is your contribution?
My fabulous personality.
That's what keeps 'em
coming back for more, sweetie.
-Right, I forgot.
-You're crazy.
Oh...
How is the renovation going?
It's going really good.
I mean, slowly but surely,
but I can't wait
for you to see it.
It's going to be amazing.
Hey...
Hi!
So, what do you think
of your sister's
Christmas sweaters?
I want one.
I'll trade you yours
for Phil's.
Uh, ooh, no.
-Not a chance.
-Yeah, no.
Attention, everyone!
For crying out loud,
Susan, lose the bullhorn!
Lose the bullhorn?
Please! Yes!
Okay, all right.
Well, friends,
it is time to give out
the grand prize
for the best Christmas outfit.
This cashmere throw
from Ooh La La Gift Emporium
goes to....
me!
It's not fair.
You've won
five years in a row now.
Have some jingle juice.
You'll be hearing jingle bells
in no time.
Ah, cheers.
Cheers.
Ooh, we are out of ice.
Tom, we've run out of ice.
What do you want me
to do, Susan?
You could break off
some icicles?
Uh, no, look, I could just
go to the market
and get some bags.
No need.
Tom, wake the kids.
We need those icicles.
Susan, do not wake up the kids.
Henry can go.
He doesn't mind.
Really, I do not mind.
-You sure?
-Yeah.
All right then.
Okay, thank you.
Hurry back.
-I love you.
-Love you.
Thank you.
Next year,
I'm gonna put my foot down.
I'm telling Susan
I am not bringing any more food.
I'm going to tell her
to order a few pizzas.
We can all throw in a few bucks,
call it a day.
What do you think, Nic?
Nic?
Where is Henry?
He should have been back by now.
I'm sure he's fine.
I tried calling him.
It went straight to voicemail.
I'm sure he'll be walking
through that door any minute.
Hello?
Hey, Tom.
How you doing, Nic?
I'm good.
Thanks for coming.
I know this time of year
could be hard for you.
I'm good, Tom, really.
I'm okay.
You sure you're ready
to let go of the house?
Yep.
Yup, I'm ready.
I'm ready to sell.
Okay, well, like I said,
my company is more than happy
to list it for you.
You think I can get
what Henry and I paid for it?
Not till the work's complete.
I just don't want you
to take a hit on the house, Nic.
Let's get someone in here
that can do the work,
and then think about selling.
Is that okay?
Mm-hmm,
and what about the store?
Any interested buyers?
I've got a couple showings
lined up.
So let's just...
give it a little time,
and I promise you
we will sell the toy store
and this house.
Great.
Thank you, Tom.
You got it.
I'm curious.
About what?
Well, after
you sell everything,
this house, the store,
what's next for you?
Oh, you know me, Tom.
I always figure something out.
Right.
I'm gonna go check it out.
All right.
Go for it.
Hey.
Got you a gingerbread latte.
Oh, thank you, Nic.
How's it going today?
Good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, busy.
Any calls?
Yes, Mrs. Barnes called.
Said she was looking for
a plastic rocketship
for her grandson.
Oh, I think we've got one
in the back.
Oh, and Pops called.
Twice.
He needs a new razor.
Gail dropped one off
at his house,
but he said
it's a lady's razor,
and it doesn't work,
and then he said
because Gail messed up,
he now has a mustache, so...
He grew a mustache
in two hours?
That's what he said.
You want me
to stop by the pharmacy
and pick him up a new one?
No, it's all right.
I've got to head over there
to make him lunch later anyways.
Okay.
Oh, hey, hey, uh...
how did it go with Tom?
Did he say
he could sell the house?
Yeah.
He, uh, just wants me
to finish the remodel first,
but, um,
I just have no idea
how I'm going to find
someone to do it.
You know what?
I happen to know a guy.
Yeah, he's an old friend.
He's a carpenter.
I think he could help you out.
-Oh...
-Want me to call him?
Yes.
Teddy, please.
That would be amazing.
Thank you.
Ooh, hello.
Merry, merry!
Hello.
Did you get my message
about tonight?
What about tonight?
A bunch of us are going to see
"It's a Wonderful Life"
at the Majestic, 8:00.
Please say you'll come.
I can't.
I have things to do.
I need to...
organize the back.
Nicole, you need
to get out more.
Have some fun.
I have fun.
Reorganizing the stock room
is not fun.
It is for me.
Gary Jankowski is coming
to movie night tonight.
Who?
Gary Jankowski.
The orthodontist?
Remember
I told you about him?
The single doctor?
Right... Barry.
Gary!
And he is just the sweetest.
I'm sure he is,
but tonight is no good for me.
You know, I have
a lot of stuff to do.
-Mm.
-A lot.
A lot of... a lot of stuff.
Mm-hmm.
Fine, be a party pooper,
but you're definitely
coming Tuesday, right?
Tuesday?
It's my ugly sweater party,
and, um...
I just thought it would be great
for you to be with all of us...
and you do not want to miss
what I am wearing this year.
Okay?
Biggest fashion disaster
this town has ever seen.
Please say you'll come.
Will Gary Jankowski be there?
As a matter of fact,
he has a dental convention,
so no.
Okay then, I will come.
Yes!
Hint...
my sweater requires an outlet
and an extension cord.
Intrigued?
Always.
Goodbye.
Bye!
Really?
Chips? Donuts?
Soda?
A frozen pizza, Pops?
Come on.
You know,
I promised Mom and Dad
when they moved away
that I would take care of you.
So, take care of me
and heat up that pizza.
Not a chance.
I'm making you a salad.
So, how you doing, Pops?
You feeling good?
I'd feel a lot better
if the Badgers
could get a rebound--
Oh, come on, you--
I miss going to games
with you and Henry.
The three of us went
to a lot of games together
last season.
He'd wear that big foam
Badger hat,
and nobody could see past him.
I miss him.
Yeah, those games
were a lot of fun.
You don't have to be brave
with me, honey.
It's okay to show
what you're feeling.
I miss him, too, Pops.
It will get better.
I promise.
How did you get through it
when Grandma died.
Well...
after your Grandma died,
for a year,
every single day,
I wrote her a letter.
I would pour my heart out,
I would tell her
how much I missed her,
I would tell her about my day,
what was good about my day,
what was bad,
and it helped to heal my heart.
Letters.
That is so beautiful.
Yeah, but these days,
you kids don't write letters.
Everybody's just texting.
Did you keep
any of those letters?
Yeah, some...
They're in the closet,
on the top shelf, I think.
Can I take some to read?
Well, of course.
About my lunch,
there is a frozen burrito there.
Uh-uh.
I just can't win.
Nope,
not if I have anything
to do with it.
Hey...
Can I come over?
I made you some tea.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Mm, thanks for letting me
come over.
Sometimes, it's just too hard
to be in my apartment
with all those memories,
alone.
You're my best friend.
You're family.
My home is your home.
You know, I've been thinking,
and I've been thinking
that I'm mad at you.
I am mad at you
because that night,
the night that Henry died...
you told me he was going
to walk through the door
any minute.
I know I did, but...
you know what happened
was a terrible accident.
It was no one's fault.
I'm so scared, Alan.
I know, sweetie.
I know.
What are these?
These are letters
that my Pops wrote to my Grandma
when she died.
Oh.
He said that writing them
helped him to not feel so sad.
Aw...
Can I see?
Yeah, sure.
"My dearest Margaret,
Today, I found the pin
we bought in Italy.
The cameo you loved to wear.
I sat on our bed
holding it...
and cried."
"Until then,
I've been
holding it all together,
but just how much I miss you
finally came flooding out.
Forever and always,
Your John."
It's beautiful.
I know.
Okay, we need cookies.
-I've decided.
-Yes, please.
Okay.
Hey, it's your favorite sis.
Another casserole
is on its way.
Be on the lookout.
That day at the house,
you said it would be
the first of many memories.
I didn't think
it would be the last.
One pretty pony tea set.
I hope your daughter
enjoys it, Angela.
I'm sure she will.
Hey, Nicole,
I heard a rumor
that you're selling the store.
Please tell me that's not true.
It is.
You know, ever since
I first met Henry in college,
it was always his dream
to have a toy store.
I swear, the proudest moment
of that man's life
was when we first
opened the doors
to Village Toys.
I remember that day.
You know, we were
each other's partners
I ran the business side,
and he was all about
the fun and the whimsy.
Henry was so amazing
at getting every kid
that walked through that door
to go to faraway places
with their imagination.
I miss that.
I think we all miss that.
You know, a year ago,
I never would have thought
I'd sell this place,
but then I realized, you know,
this was Henry's passion.
This was Henry's dream.
Without him,
this store doesn't really
make much sense
for me anymore.
I get it.
Sometimes, life shows you
a fork in the road.
You just never know
where life's going to take you.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Marry Christmas, Nicole.
Merry Christmas.
Higher, Billy!
The lights need to be
in the garland!
I got it, Mrs. Ward.
Well, hello, Nicole.
Hi, Helen.
I can't remember the last time
I laid eyes on you.
It's been a while.
You're planning
on fixing up the house
so you put it on the market?
That's the plan.
Oh, and Billy?
The Rudolph is looking
a little tarnished.
Yes, Mrs. Ward.
You know I'm on the committee
for our neighborhood
Victorian Christmas display.
Well, it all looks
so wonderful, Helen.
This year,
I'm the reindeer captain.
Good heavens! Walter!
Walter, darling!
-Come to Mama!
Oh, no!
Is it always like this
around here?
I'm sorry?
Dogs in Christmas sweaters.
I must have saw 12
on my ride over here,
Santa and reindeer
on every single lawn
on the block.
Speaking of which,
where's yours?
Um...
Oh, Teddy told me
that this neighborhood
went all out for the holidays.
This is more than
I could have ever imagined.
Yes, everyone around here
does seem to have
Christmas fever.
Apparently so.
You must be Joe Roberts.
Teddy's friend, the carpenter?
Nicole, right?
Yes.
Thank you for meeting me here.
Yeah, yeah.
Beautiful house.
Teddy said
that you needed some work.
You were thinking
about selling it?
Yes, uh... you want to take
a look around?
Sure.
Should I follow you in?
Oh, um...
You know what,
why don't you go ahead?
I need to make a phone call,
and after you've had a chance
to look around,
then we can talk...
out here...
about how to proceed.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure, whatever you want.
Okay, thank you.
You okay?
Yes.
I'm fine.
Um, what do you think
about the work
that needs to be done?
Well, I can do it.
I just need to purchase
some moldings and wood, and--
Great.
My checkbook's at the store.
Meet me there?
So, does this mean I'm hired?
Yes.
Okay, then.
I guess I'm hired.
Hi.
Here's the estimate
from the lumber yard.
Looks good.
I just need to find
my checkbook.
So do you want
to pick out the wood
for the living room mantel?
No.
You can decide.
I really don't need to be
a part of those decisions.
Okay.
Uh, I'll give you my work cell.
Anything you think of,
anything you need to run by me,
you can just give me a call.
You know what,
that won't be necessary.
Um, I'm really just
fixing it up to sell.
So if you have any questions,
you can reach out
to my realtor, Tom Young.
He's got an office
on First Street.
Tom Young.
Got it.
Where is my checkbook?
Uh...
Oh!
Right here.
Yo-ho-ho!
Well, I can see now
why you and Teddy are friends.
Okay, so I just got back
from taking Pops to the barbers,
and get this,
he wanted sideburns.
What?
I tell you, Nicole,
something's up with him.
He's gone completely nutty.
Well, I think
it's all the sugar he eats,
personally.
Uh...
Oh!
Thanks.
Sorry.
Was I... interrupting something?
Oh, no, no, no.
Um, sorry.
Joe this is my sister, Gail.
Gail, this is Joe.
Ahoy.
Ahoy...
I just hired Joe to do
the remodel on my house.
You're remodeling Tudor Road?
Yeah.
Tom said I should
before we put it up for sale.
You're ready to sell the house?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think it's time.
It's been almost a year
since he died.
So, I heard
you might be going
to Susan's party tonight.
Yes, I said I might.
Um...
I understand.
But you should go.
You should go.
Go have fun.
I mean, Susan said
her outfit's going to be
even crazier than ever.
Oh, Teddy and I picked out
some pretty solid sweaters
to wear to the party.
You're going
to Susan and Tom's party?
Yeah, Teddy invited me.
He said Susan said
everyone was welcome.
That sounds like Susan.
Yeah.
Well, I'd better
get back to the house.
Uh, nice to meet you, Gail.
Same.
So, if you change your mind,
and feel like coming
to the party tonight...
We can go together
and we don't have to stay
very long.
Okay.
Maybe.
-Okay.
I'll check in with you later.
Great.
Nice guy.
Did you bring
the fruitcake, Phil?
No one likes fruitcake, Gail.
I told Susan
we were bringing fruitcake.
I think we still have one
from last year
in the trunk of the car.
Think anyone
will know the difference?
With a fruitcake?
Take my hand.
I got you, Nic.
I got you.
Attention, everyone!
It is time to give out the prize
for the best sweater!
Our second place winner
this year is...
Alan!
You are the lucky winner
of this lovely
holiday-scented candle.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a minute.
I think I gave you this
for Christmas last year.
Ooh...
I was hoping my regifting
would go unnoticed this year.
Yeah, well, I noticed.
Well...
and now our grand prize
is this cheese board
that is from
Village Trinkets and Treasures
goes to....
Hmm... me!
I mean, come on.
It's not fun
if you win every year, Susan.
Don't get your tinsel
in a tangle.
Oh, what do you know,
it's already personalized.
Ooh...
how did that get there?
Oh, thank you.
-Cheers.
Wow, your friends are fun.
They are quite a bunch.
Are the holidays
always like this?
Yeah, every Christmas.
You should see
Alan's gift exchange.
It's pretty cut-throat.
-Cut-throat?
-Oh, yeah.
Attention, everyone,
Alan is demanding a recount,
and to be perfectly clear,
I strongly object,
based on the uniqueness
and creativity of my sweater.
Honey, I think your sweater
just blew a fuse.
Too loud in there?
Yeah, and too hot.
It's like she has the heat up
to 90 degrees.
Man, this neighborhood
is something else.
Yeah, I guess it is.
Did you grow up here?
Been here my whole life,
except for the four years
I went to college.
It must be nice,
actually really
being from somewhere.
I was an army brat,
so we moved around all the time.
Every year it was a new town,
a new school,
Christmas in a different house.
When I was a kid,
I was just wanted, you know,
some stability in my life,
a house I could call my own.
You never had
a house of your own?
Oh, dozens, actually.
Well, yeah,
when I was little,
I used to carve
all sorts of little houses.
You know, ones with big roofs
and white picket fences,
porches, high ceilings.
I guess I thought
that if I built it,
then maybe it would
become a reality,
that someday
I would build a home for real.
So, have you built
your dream home yet?
Oh, no, not yet.
Why not?
I guess I'm just still looking
for the right place
to build the foundation.
Hmm.
But until then,
you know, I'm happy
doing that for other people.
Huh.
So I guess I hired
the right guy for the job then.
I guess you did.
Mm-hmm.
I'm going to get going.
-Goodnight.
Hey, are you walking home?
Yeah.
Me too.
This direction?
Uh, yeah.
Ah.
Crazy idea here,
but I mean, since we're both
walking the same way,
maybe we can
walk home together?
Okay.
Cool.
So, what was
your childhood dream?
I guess to own my own business
and sell my knits.
That's an amazingly practical
grown-up dream.
Well, I guess
there was another one.
I mean, it's not really
a dream.
I was just a little kid,
and it's kind of silly.
Come on, tell me,
I want to know.
All right, so, there's
this really big pine tree,
and it sits just in the middle
of this meadow
outside of town,
all by itself,
and I always thought
it looked like
the loneliest tree in the world.
So this one Christmas,
I gathered up
all the remaining ornaments
and decorations I could find,
and I rode my bike
out there
with the intention
of decorating it,
but a little pink bike
on an icy road
only gets you so far.
Maybe, but you had a dream.
That's all that matters, right?
Well, this is me, so...
-Night.
Hey.
You should go
decorate that tree.
That is a crazy idea.
Sometimes, those are
the best kind.
I'm pretty sure
that nothing will ever compare
to the pain of losing you.
I wake up every day
and I ask myself,
how can I possibly
move forward in this life
without you?
Who am I now that you're gone?
Who am I
stepping into the unknown?
You haven't read
'Twas the Night
Before Christmas?
Well, you need to read this,
and before you know it,
visions of sugar plums
will be dancing in your head.
Hi.
Here. Just, uh,
excuse me for one moment.
Hey, what's going on?
You look like
you've just seen a ghost.
I texted Henry.
What?
You texted Henry?
Like Pops did
with the letters,
and someone texted--
Just look.
Read it.
"I'm so sorry.
This is not
who you think it is.
I got a new phone,
and this is the number
I was given.
I also have experienced
a great loss in my life."
"I understand
what you're going through."
Someone has Henry's number.
Well, yeah, I see that.
Well, maybe you should
look past that.
Look what this person
is saying to you.
They understand
what you're going through.
They get it.
Well, what should I do?
Well, I don't know, Nic.
Something tells me
Henry had a hand in this.
Henry?
What do you mean?
Well, maybe
it's a sign from Henry.
A sign?
What kind of sign?
Maybe the person
that sent you that text
is like an angel that Henry sent
to watch over you.
Just think about it.
What are the odds
that someone who has
gone through a loss like you
would end up
with Henry's number?
There you go, Nicole.
One turkey on rye.
Hold the mayo for Pops.
Can I throw in a donut for him?
Absolutely not.
-Morning.
I was just about
to head over to the house.
Morning coffee first?
I need to satisfy
my sweet tooth.
Ooh, you've come
to the right place.
What can I get you?
Uh, let me have
a piece of the fruitcake...
No... No,
I am gonna go with
a slice of
the gingerbread spice cake.
All right, Mike, no,
uh... rum cake?
No good?
Everything's good.
No, no, of course, it is.
It's just
it's his first time here,
so he has to get
the peppermint-bark cupcake.
Cupcake for breakfast?
You haven't lived
until you've had Mike's
peppermint-bark cupcake.
All right, Mike,
we're going with
one of those, please.
All right.
The moment of truth.
Come on, Mike!
What?
This is not fair!
This is amazing!
-This is amazing!
Aw...
It's good seeing you
laughing again, Nicole.
Um, I should...
I should get going.
All right.
Okay, goodbye.
Goodbye, Nicole.
-Okay. Bye.
-See you.
Bye!
May I have a large coffee,
please, Mike?
Sure, comin' right up.
No donut?
Not today, Pops.
Hey, Pops, can I
ask you something?
After Grandma died,
did you ever
reach out to anyone
to talk about the things
you were feeling?
Well, of course.
Even people you didn't know?
Sometimes, that's easier.
I'll let you in
on a little secret, honey.
After your Grandma died,
every day,
I would go
to the community center
for a swim, remember?
Mm-hmm.
Well, the truth is,
for a whole year,
I never stepped foot
in the pool.
What?
Yeah.
There was a young girl
who worked there.
She was maybe 20
when her mother passed away.
I think she recognized
my broken heart.
She...
I could talk to her
about all the grief
that I was carrying around.
She was somebody who understood
exactly what I was feeling.
Well, you could have
talked to me.
Oh, honey.
Sometimes, those
that are closest to us,
bless their hearts,
try too hard to help us heal,
you know what I mean?
Yeah, like Gail's casseroles.
So you never went swimming?
Well, a year later,
I went back to the pool.
I was in the deep end,
but I felt so uneasy.
I was gripping
the side of the pool.
I was scared,
and that girl, she was there,
and she said,
"Just let go."
And did you?
Yes.
Sometimes, you have to let go
in order to move forward.
I'm trying, Pops.
I'm really trying.
I know you are.
It's just hard.
You'll get there.
Oh...
My mitten.
You dropped it at the bakery.
Thank you.
You didn't have
to bring this out here.
Snow is in the forecast,
and you look like a girl
who's thrown a snowball
once or twice in her life.
That's a lot of gifts.
Yeah, they're for the kids
at the children's hospital.
That's gonna make
a lot of kids happy.
Teddy said
you're closing up shop.
February.
And then what?
You know...
I don't know.
Since my fiancé died a year ago,
it's strange.
I feel like
I'm on this journey,
but I don't really know
where the journey's taking me.
Hmm...
Well...
I think there's only
one way to find out.
Pick a card...
What?
Go on.
Let Genie Joe The Amazing
see what the future
holds for you.
Genie Joe The Amazing?
That's what
all my friends call me.
Please, Madame!
Let the audience see
what the card you've picked is!
The audience?
What?
Oh!
The audience...
Ah!
The future is bright!
You know what?
I think we actually
should hear from the audience.
Uh...
Well...
what do you think
about Nicole's future,
Lord Fluff 'n' Stuff?
Of course, her future's
looking bright, Joe!
Lord Fluff 'n' Stuff?
Okay, just stop!
Everybody thinks
your future's looking good.
Okay.
Yeah.
-Okay, well...
Well, I should get back
to the house.
I'm putting in
your new floors today.
Oh.
See you around, Nicole.
Yeah.
See ya.
Nicole...
Uh-oh.
Nicole The Amazing.
Oh... wow.
"The future is bright."
I was thinking
about your loss.
Three years ago,
I lost my brother.
He just turned 29.
We were two brothers,
the best of friends,
but I've learned
sometimes
things that break apart
can come together stronger.
Sometimes, those broken places
will let in the light.
Let the light in, huh?
Hi!
Hi. Mike wanted me
to drop these off for you,
Great.
You want to come in?
Sure.
Cool, come on in.
Uh, you know what,
since I have you here,
would you mind
helping me move my couch?
Sure.
Thank you.
Sorry.
I'm just trying to, like,
trying to go this way.
Okay.
-Okay?
-All right.
One, two, three--
-Whoa!
-Oh, no!
The peppermint bark cupcakes!
I think they're still good?
-Oh, I don't...
You know, are you hungry?
I'm always hungry.
I am, too.
Um, I have just the thing.
My sister loves to cook.
She brings me another one
of these massive casseroles
every week.
Mm...
You have to try
the broccoli cheddar.
Oh, I'm still working
on the carnitas and peppers.
Mm...
How many have we had so far?
I think, like, 10? 15?
I don't know.
I still have so many
in the freezer.
Wow, I think you're going
to have enough meals
to last you till New Year's.
I think I'm set for meals
until next Christmas.
Oh...
Oh, you gotta try this.
So good?
The mac and cheese is amazing.
Here.
-Yeah?
-Mm!
That is so good.
You know, I think my furniture
is actually
back where I started.
-Oh.
-Mm.
Well...
You know, when things
aren't going my way,
and I need
a change in direction,
I'll just go to the movies.
To the movies?
Yeah.
I'll just sit alone in the dark
and have a good cry.
You cry at the movies?
Yeah.
At everything,
even the previews.
You know the dancing box
of raisinets
and the singing soda
that remind you to get snacks
from the concession stand?
Yeah.
Gets me every time.
Really?
Well, maybe I should
give that a try,
instead of rearranging
my furniture next time.
I highly recommend it.
Oh, there's an early delivery
over at the house.
I should get going.
Gotta check it out.
Okay.
So, thank you for everything.
I appreciate it.
Thanks for stopping by.
Have a good night.
You too.
See you, Nicole.
See ya.
Thanks for your kind words.
I want you to know
I'm sorry for your loss.
"For months,
the grief just overwhelmed me,
but lately,
something has changed in me."
"What changed?"
"I realized that
while my grief may never end,
if I can take
one step forward every day,
my grief will not be a place
where I stay very long."
"Remember,
fight for your dreams,
because I promise you,
it's those dreams
that will light
your darkest hours."
Hey, I hope it's okay,
I thought I could work
a little later tonight.
Can I have that, please?
What?
That.
Oh. Oh, this?
Oh, I just thought it was
something I could get rid of.
I'll just put it back for you--
No, no, no, no, it's okay,
I can just take it.
I'm sorry, I should have
left it where it was.
It's okay, really.
Um... just keep doing
what you're doing.
I'm sure it's great.
Do you want to come inside
and have a look around?
Uh... I'm good.
I should get going.
I'm sure it's great.
Really, just great.
Thank you.
I'm very grateful
for everything you're doing.
Need some help?
Let me take a look--
No, it's okay.
Um, it's getting late.
I'll just deal with it
in the morning.
Then let me give you
a ride home.
It's fine, it's not very far.
I'm just going to walk.
Then let me walk with you.
You've already
walked me home once.
Then let me
walk you home twice.
I just have to
put some tools away
and lock up.
Sure.
I guess that's fine then.
Check out these reindeers.
They're so shiny.
I wonder what kind of polish
they use.
Well, did you see
the carolers next door?
Whoa.
Everywhere you look,
it's like the spirit
of Christmas is all around.
I can't decide
which house I like best.
Hmm...
You know,
when I was a little girl,
every year,
my dad used to take me and Gail
for a walk around the town.
We would walk for hours.
He wanted us to see
how each house in the town
was decorated,
and Gail and I would pretend
we were judges in the Olympics,
and we'd give
each house a score.
Okay...
Okay, so what kind of score
would you give that house?
Oh, well, this is
the Watson house.
Every year a 6.5.
Only a 6.5?
Yeah, I mean, crooked antlers
on the reindeer.
Oh, and then
rusted Santa sleigh,
you gotta take off two points,
and then Rudolph
with a tennis ball for a nose?
I mean, that's gotta be
like a 1.5 deduction.
-At least?
-Wow...
Okay.
Hmm, what about this house?
This is the Fraleys' house,
and I give it a 9.0.
Really?
A 9.0 for that?
Well, actually,
it's only really that high
because one year,
Mr. Fraley heard Gail and I
give it a 5,
and he actually complained
to our parents,
and I do not
want a repeat of that.
No.
No, you do not.
Okay...
What about this house?
Come on.
No Blitzen.
Blitzen?
Blitzen, my favorite reindeer.
No Blitzen, no perfect score.
Tough critic.
Mm, me?
You should see
Gail's scores.
Are you hungry?
Don't tell me you've never
had breakfast for dinner.
I can't say I have.
So do you make a habit out of
eating breakfast for dinner?
Oh, yeah.
And dinner for breakfast.
Ooh. Okay.
So, breakfast for dinner,
dinner for breakfast?
Mm-hmm.
Every Christmas morning,
my brother and I used
to wake up at 4:00 a.m.
and make spaghetti and meatballs
for breakfast.
It used to drive my mom nuts.
Wow.
So what about Fourth of July?
We'd celebrate on the fifth.
Mm. And Thanksgiving?
I mean, dare I ask--
was there turkey involved?
Why on Earth would
we do something like that?
Right.
Has anyone ever told you
you are a very unusual man,
Joe Roberts?
Only every other day
of the week.
Hey, I can make you my famous
spaghetti and meatballs
for breakfast one morning.
At 4:00 a.m.?
-I don't think so.
-Okay.
But thank you.
Then I can
cook you dinner sometime.
Need anything else, folks?
Uh, no. Thanks.
I think we're good.
Yeah.
Hey!
You work at
the toy store, right?
I do.
You know,
a couple of years ago,
I bought my daughter
this stuffed pelican
at your store.
You knitted
the cutest sweater for it--
it had candy canes all over it.
Any chance you can
make one for me?
Oh... um,
it's really just a hobby.
Oh, well,
if you change your mind,
let me know.
I showed that little sweater
to the girls at my book club,
and they all went nuts
for it.
I think you'd get
a lot of orders.
Thank you.
So...
"So"?
Your dream
of selling your designs,
having your own business--
you said someday
that could happen.
Yeah, maybe. Someday.
My father used to say,
"Someday
isn't a day of the week."
Go ahead. Try 'em.
Okay.
Here it goes.
What do you think?
Mm! Those are very good.
Nice. What kind of score
are you giving those pancakes?
Mm...
a 9.5.
"Nine-point" whatever!
Those are a 10!
Nope. Not enough butter.
-Come on.
-You gotta have the butter.
Ten! Nine!
Eight! Seven! Six!
Five! Four! Three!
Two! One!
I'm finding it
very hard this time of year,
to feel
all of the holiday joy
everyone around me
is feeling.
"Don't pack
your holiday memories away.
Cherish them.
Embrace them.
Let them into your heart."
He's not here.
He's gone to "Feel the Vibe".
What?
He's at "Feel the Vibe"?
I don't know what,
but something's up
with that man.
Well, thank you, Rose. See ya.
Bye.
To another holiday
ugly gift exchange
with great friends.
Cheers!
-Cheers!
All right, let's get into this.
What do we have here?
Uh...
what is this?
A wine-glass holder
for the shower.
Hey, Susan, this has your name
written all over it.
I love it.
I need one just like that.
Thank you.
Uh, Phil, your turn.
I'm gonna go ahead and steal
Alan's "sleepy kitty" chia pet.
Really?
-Hand it over!
-Really? Grr!
Oh!
Fine. Then I am gonna
steal it from Tom.
But I really like
these fuzzy reindeer slippers.
They're not even
your size, so.
Fine.
All right. I...
I'm gonna trade with Gail
for her Christmas
dashboard figurine set.
And what do I get?
Big, pink...
-sequined...
-...pillows.
It's a matching set.
Uh, Joe, did you pick?
Oh, yes, and I am very happy
with my "scared Santa" ornament,
so, hands off, everyone.
Well, one gift left--
Nicole, your turn.
Okay. Which one is it?
I'll try this one.
Here we go.
Oh, that is so beautiful.
Oh, I love that.
Where can I get one?
Well, you can't.
Why?
It's just a little something
I made last night.
It's nothing special.
"Nothing special"?
I change my mind.
I want to steal the sign
for my wine-holder.
-What?
-Yeah!
-It'll look great in my store.
-No!
It's not even
your turn, Susan.
Fine.
Thank you.
I love
my shower wine-holder.
-Hey.
-Oh, hey.
You know, I really like
the sign that you made.
I really like
that sweater you're wearing.
-Oh.
-Did you make that?
I did.
It's nothing special.
It is special, Nicole.
It's very special.
Thank you.
Tell you what--
instead of paying me
to renovate your house,
how about you
just make me two of those
famous Nicole Graham sweaters,
and we'll call it a day?
You know,
I'm glad I met you, Joe.
Does this mean
we're becoming friends?
I think we are.
So what do you think
the chances are
that Phil turns over
that chia pet to me?
Ooh, not
a snowball's chance in--
Attention, everyone!
Alan has sat on my wine-holder
and broke it.
I am demanding that he hand over
the reindeer slippers. Okay?
Are we all in agreement?
Welcome
to our friend group, Joe.
-All in favor, say "aye".
Hey, you need a ride?
Um... no, no, no.
I don't mind walking.
Thanks.
Oh, come on.
It just started to snow.
Get in.
Okay.
Do you know this one?
Because I do not,
and I am going to sing it.
"I was
thinking about you today.
How are you doing?"
Pretty good.
Lately, I think I've found
some joy in my life.
For the first time
in a long time,
I actually forgot
about feeling sad.
-"Just remember--
a joyful heart will always
chase away any sorrow."
What flavor is my mask again?
Eggnog. I'm gonna be selling it
in my store for the holidays.
Mm. It's so good.
Oh, don't eat it!
Why? It tastes so good.
I can't help it.
Let it soak in.
It's gonna do wonders
for your pores.
Mm. I'm so glad
we're doing this.
Me too.
This last year
has been so hard.
Mm. Really missed you, Nicole.
It's not been the same
without you.
I think Joe Roberts has been
a really good thing
for your life.
What does that mean?
Oh. Um...
Just that he's, you know...
a good guy
to have around.
What? Wait. No, no, no.
W-What is this look?
This--
This?
Nothing.
Okay, good, because
Joe and I are just friends.
That's all.
I bet.
We are!
You can even ask him!
-Uh-huh.
-And you know what?
I am in no way ready
to start dating yet, okay?
Especially not with
that podiatrist, or whoever,
that you're trying
to fix me up with.
-Orthodontist--
-Okay.
And Gary Jankowski is-- whoo!
...everything.
Uh, ahem.
So is Joe Roberts.
That's right.
Stop it, Gail.
You're being annoying.
-Oh!
What?
I... can dish it out,
too, Nicole.
Oh!
Ladies! Ladies, come on!
Let's keep it
together here, okay?
You know what, Susan?
-You're annoying, too!
-Oh!
How-- oh!
You're a horrible,
horrible sister.
The Queen Bees!
-Yes!
-We're back.
Gail! This looks amazing.
-Thank you.
-Mm!
I will take a...
candy-cane cookie.
Thank you.
Mm. Mm, so good.
I think these cookies
are better than Mike's.
Hey, I heard that.
But your cupcakes
are the best.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I meant to tell you,
I think I'm gonna be done
with the work on your house
by Christmas.
Oh. Sounds good.
I hope you like what I did.
If you ever want to come
take a look...
Yeah. Anyway.
There's this job
over in Rock Springs
that I might start
on the fifth, so.
What about your shelves?
What about my shelves?
The shelves in her apartment.
They're...
basically falling apart.
Falling apart.
-Yeah.
-Uh--
Sure. I can take a look,
push the Rock Springs job
a week or two.
We'd love that.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, he is definitely
good to have around.
You know?
Fix a couple of things.
Beautiful. Thank you.
I don't have
too many left, Nicole,
but I got some good ones
back here--
perfect for you.
Uh, let's see--
we have Fraser fir, pine,
spruce, Balsam fir...
oh, and, uh, that one there,
that's a beauty.
Uh, that's a Douglas fir.
Smell that.
It smells like Christmas.
Oh!
And this one here
is the Noble fir.
It's the perfect holiday tree.
The needles are actually
soft to the touch.
Go ahead. Touch it.
It feels like Christmas.
I want this one.
Okay.
It's a beauty.
I wanted to thank you
for helping me with my grief.
I know you understand
what I'm going through.
"Grief comes and goes.
It shows up
at unexpected times."
Talking to you made me feel
I'm not alone.
It brings me feelings
of comfort and peace
when I need it most.
"I was thinking,
maybe we should meet."
Meet?
Hey, Helen.
Nicole! Hi.
Hi. I was just picking up
some lunch for Pops.
I think he's over
the turkey sandwiches now.
He's been so picky lately.
Yes, I now how that is.
Think he'll go for
tuna on wheat?
Pops?
Yeah.
I'm heading over there now,
to bring him some lunch.
Oh! Um...
Oh, I was just about
to pick him up lunch,
like I usually do,
but if you're going--
I got this, Nicole.
I promise,
I'll take good care of him.
I know you will, Helen.
Oh! Um, no pickles.
-Pickles?
-Yeah.
Ah. Okay.
Oh! And nothing on sourdough.
What about avocado?
Avocado on a sandwich?
Who thinks of
these crazy ideas?
Good luck.
Pops?
-Yeah?
-Hi!
Oh, hi.
I just wanted to drop this off.
Oh, honey. Honey.
Come in, come in.
Are you wearing cologne?
Yes, I am.
I see.
Sit down. Sit down.
-Pops...
-Yep?
How do you move on
from the love of your life?
Oh... uh.
Well...
Margaret was my first love,
and...
the love doesn't go anyplace.
It just finds a new place,
deep in your heart.
I haven't given up
on love, Nicole.
I might've been a little late,
but I came to realize,
if you're given
a second chance at love,
you'd better grab it
with both hands.
I really like her, Pops.
Me too.
Okay!
What? No! You have to wait
till Christmas morning.
At my age?
Why wait?
Oh, honey.
I love this.
I'm so glad you like it.
Oh, I love it
when you make me things.
I still have the gloves
you made for me
when you were a little girl.
Oh, Pops.
Those had seven fingers.
You can throw those away now.
Oh, no.
They're easier to put on.
-Okay, here.
Here.
What's this?
-My gift to you.
-Oh...
Well, I want to wait until
Christmas morning to open mine.
Why?
Okay, fine.
Maybe just a quick peek.
Grandma's pin?
Yeah.
Oh, Pops, I can't take this.
I want you to have it.
I will cherish it forever.
That's why
I'm giving it to you.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas, honey.
Merry Christmas.
-Hi!
-Hi.
So I made you your favorite--
mac and cheese.
Just fire up the oven to 350,
put on another pair of sweats,
and you'll be good to go.
Thank you.
Whoa!
Goodbye, sweats.
Yeah, I got this
from Susan's shop.
I'm meeting someone tonight.
Let me guess.
Are you meeting Joe?
No. Not Joe.
It's actually
someone you don't know.
Well, I don't really
know them, either.
It's just someone
who's been helping me through
some things, you know?
Helping me through my grief
and some stuff
that I've been carrying around.
I don't--
It's hard to explain.
This is a good thing.
It's a very good thing.
I'm so happy for you
that there's someone out there
that you can
share your feelings with.
These past 12 months,
there hasn't been
a single minute of the day
that I haven't had a knot
in my stomach.
I'm so worried about you, Nic.
Hey. I'm gonna be okay.
All right?
So don't worry about me anymore.
Really.
I'm going to be okay.
Yeah.
Oh.
Careful, you don't want
to smudge your lipstick
before you meet
your mystery man.
Gail. Don't even go there.
Oh, I'm going there!
Have fun!
Oh, Nicole.
You're leaving?
Uh, yeah.
I'm meeting someone.
Oh.
Anyway, I just thought
I'd come by
and take a look
at those shelves,
but if you're busy,
I can come back another time?
Sounds good.
'Night.
Yeah, goodnight.
What was that?
A goodnight kiss?
A "goodnight kiss"
with a question mark?
Uh, what?
Because that felt like
a kiss without a question mark.
I'm sorry I thought,
since we're friends now,
that I would--
You would, what?
Just turn a question mark
into an exclamation point?
Y...eah?
W-W-Wait.
Where are you going?
To meet a friend.
And he is just a friend.
No question mark.
Yeah, that's-- that's great
that you have so many friends.
And I suggest that you should
go meet a friend as well.
Well, it just so happens,
I am meeting a friend--
exclamation point.
-Good.
-Yeah.
I didn't mean to do that.
You didn't mean that,
question mark?
Because, to me, that felt
like two exclamation--
Ugh.
Say hi to your friend for me!
My friend?
Uh, "friend"--
quotation marks.
"Something's come up.
I can't meet you.
I'm so sorry."
So, wait--
you got Henry's old number?
Wow.
That's a small world, huh?
Well... you know,
I think you should tell her.
You know me, Teddy.
I can't.
Why? She'll understand.
I like her, Ted.
You know,
in the beginning,
she was someone
who was grieving
and I was someone there
with a shoulder to lean on.
Became friends,
and, through texting,
we found out that grief shared,
it was grief lessened.
But, Ted, I swear,
when I went to the restaurant
last night,
I had-- I had no clue
it was her,
and at first, I was really happy
that it was her.
When I saw her sitting there...
she just looked so beautiful,
waiting for the man
who helped put all
her broken pieces back together,
but I-I couldn't
walk through that door.
I couldn't take another step
and tell her it was me.
Why not?
How could she ever
trust me again?
If she knew
that I was the one she was
pouring her heart out to,
I was the one
that was encouraging her
to move on from Henry...
The last thing
I'd ever want to do,
after everything
she's been through,
is cause her any more pain.
How could she ever believe
that I didn't know?
Yeah.
So what are you gonna do?
Give her that for me, please.
Wait.
So he just didn't show up?
No.
I waited and waited,
and then I got a text saying
that he couldn't come.
Well, so you'll make
another plan.
Ah, I don't know.
I mean, it was hard enough
to get myself to go
in the first place.
Nic. Hey, hey, there you are.
Uh, so, listen.
Joe wanted me
to give you this.
Oh.
Nicole,
I took another job out of town.
Sorry, I can't do your shelves.
Merry Christmas. Joe.
Hey. I just wanted to clear
the rest of this stuff out
before I took off.
Thanks.
Well, anyway, I'm sorry I--
I gotta go,
but you know,
other job.
Sure. I understand.
But before you go,
will you show me the house?
You want to go in?
Yeah.
I'm ready to do that now.
What do you think?
It's perfect.
Well, I--
I'd better get going.
Merry Christmas, Nic.
Merry Christmas, Joe.
Joe?
Wait. Um...
I just would very much
like to have you in my life.
Sure, Nic.
Sure.
Hey, Teddy. It's Nicole.
Uh, Joe left his phone
at my house today
and I don't think I'll be
seeing him anytime soon,
so I was wondering if
you could get it to him.
I will leave it in an envelope
at the shop for you.
All right.
Thanks, Teddy. Bye.
What? Mm.
I was disappointed
I didn't get to meet you
the other night.
I was gonna tell you
how thankful I am to you,
so I guess I'll do that now.
Thank you for letting me
lean on you.
I will always be grateful.
I know it was you.
Just sign here
and it's all yours.
Wow!
I am so happy for you.
Thank you.
I mean, it's always been
a dream of mine
to own a toy store.
But what about you?
What's next?
"Nic's Knits."
Are you opening
an online store?
Yeah. I figured, why not?
You remember Kim,
from Unique Styles?
Well, I gave her
a bunch of my designs
and she sold out of them
in 10 days.
It made me realize that, yeah,
maybe I could turn this
into a business.
And I also realized
you don't have to see
the full staircase
to take the first step.
I'm so proud of you, Nic.
You know, you've always
been my role model.
-Me?
-Yeah.
This last year,
everything you've been through--
you never let it defeat you.
It made me realize
what true strength is.
Thank you, Teddy.
Whew.
You knew, didn't you?
Knew what?
About Joe.
Texting me.
Look, I told him to tell you,
Nic.
I-I did.
He's not a bad guy.
He didn't even know it was you
until he showed up
at that restaurant
and saw you sitting there.
That's just the thing.
He could've walked right in
and told me then.
But, instead, he let
the guy who helped me
through my grief
just leave me there,
feeling alone and confused.
I've known Joe a long time,
and he's someone
who knows about loss,
knows how fragile people are,
and he just--
he didn't want to hurt you.
But he did.
By not telling me the truth,
he hurt me.
But Nicole,
just ask yourself this--
did he help you?
Because, the way I see it...
...you're a new person now.
You're filled with life
and joy again,
so he must've said
something right.
Hey.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
Of all the people in the world
who could've gotten
Henry's number,
what are the odds
that it would be you?
I mean, if that's not
a Christmas miracle,
I don't know what is.
I wanted to tell you.
But you didn't.
I never meant to hurt you.
I would never hurt you.
I-I can't figure you out, Joe.
Which guy are you?
The one who turns his back
and leaves,
or the one
who was the only person
who seemed to understand
everything I was going through?
I am that guy, Nic.
And I am-- I meant
every single thing I wrote.
I just wanted you to move past
your grief,
to live your best life
and...
I want to live that best life
with you.
I...
We can start over.
We can't.
Why not?
Because I don't know
if I can trust you.
Finally! You're here.
Hi. Is he here?
I told you,
he called and said
he's not coming.
Okay.
I know that you're really upset
about everything that happened
with Joe,
but do you think
you could just put it aside,
just for one day?
Maybe try to forget
about everything besides?
Today is my annual
Christmas Scavenger Hunt,
and you know what that means?
It's all about being
with people who love you
and it's about
having some fun. Okay?
-Okay.
-Gonna have some fun?
-Yes.
-Okay!
Where is everyone?
In the backyard.
The backyard?
Well, it's a scavenger hunt.
Where else would they be?
Susan, it's 25 degrees outside.
I made cocoa!
I can't believe
you're making us go outside.
Come on!
It's so cold out!
A bit of a nip in the air--
quite frankly,
I find it invigorating.
Can we please go inside?
Uh, no, we still haven't found
"the wrapped present."
Uh, Nicole, can you help Alan
find the wrapped present?
I would rather go inside
and wait for the cheese board.
That's against the rules.
Please, help Alan
find the present.
-Go ahead.
She's so bossy.
And you're just
realizing this now?
Wanna talk about it?
Not really.
You know, he should've told me
when he found out
that I was the one
he was sending those texts to.
And just because
he didn't tell you,
does that make those words
any less beautiful?
The way I see it,
we're all just stumbling
through this life,
trying to figure things out.
We fall down,
then we get back up again.
Everyone makes mistakes, Nic.
Don't let that be the reason
you give up on somebody.
Oh! There it is.
Ah!
Here we go.
Got it!
Open it.
It's in the rules.
Okay.
It's my house.
It looks exactly like my house.
Joe made it for you.
Said that, seeing as
you're selling your house,
you should at least
have something
to always remember it.
Teddy, where is he?
You're here.
You did all of this?
I thought the lights could
maybe help sell the house.
I'm not selling the house.
No?
No.
Because of you,
I am gonna wake up
every Christmas morning
in the beautiful house
that you built.
Because of you,
I found someone
to lean on
when I couldn't heal myself.
Nicole, I'm sorry,
I should've told you when I--
when I first realized--
-No.
I spent the last year of my life
only thinking
about what happened.
Playing it over and over
in my head,
again and again.
I was stuck,
but then you came into my life
and you showed me
how to push forward...
...how to move past
what happened before,
and focus on
what's happening right here,
right now.
And...
what exactly is happening
right now?
Wait.
Wait, uh...
So what score would you
give that kiss?
Mm. Say a 9.5.
Only a 9.5?
Well, kiss me again.
Let's make it a 10.