Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
NETFLIX PRESENTS
MARCH 2020
SUBJECT: SALARY ADJUSTMENT
DAUGHTER
BITCH
KEEP YOUR DISTANCE
EMERGENCY
BENTOS
"The most affectionate principle
by my mother."
Sometimes the rain comes
And raindrops cover the ground
Searching under umbrellas
For that someone who looks most like you
Oh, this really is
A senseless game
Sometimes the rain comes
And raindrops cover the ground
Maybe when the rain stops
I can see you again
Maybe the rain should continue
Falling forever
Clouded eyes
Clouded rains
Streaming across my face
Are tears, are rain
Standing in the street
I've made my decision
But I don't know if the rain
Can awaken you
FATHER
2020 ADVANCED SUBJECTS TEST
SUBTITLE TRANSLATION BY: