Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[tires screeching]
[crash]
[electric buzzing]
[heartbeat thumping]
[gasping]
[chattering on TV]
[heartbeat continues]
Welcome back
to the world of the living.
[TV chattering continues]
[indistinct PA announcement]
So?
[echoing]
Good morning, Tessa.
I'm Dr. Sarkisian.
You've been in
a very bad car accident.
You ruptured your heart
due to trauma,
which we were forced
to repair surgically.
Tessa?
[laughter, chattering on TV]
[seagulls squawking]
[ship horn blows
in distance]
[dishes clattering]
Morning.
I made pancakes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna go shoot photos.
Oh, it's so cold outside.
Yeah, I just don't want
to miss the morning light.
Well, maybe when you're
back, we could do a little
research for colleges.
All right. Bye.
["Teenage Headache Dreams"
playing]
She hides behind
that camera.
She's not taken
a single picture of us.
You're too pretty.
You'd break her lens.
Hey, I told you.
You've gotta let her
come to you.
It's been a year.
Signing a piece of paper
doesn't make us her parents.
Actually it does.
[shutter clicks]
You open, Sherman?
I am for you, Tessa.
Um, I think I'm
a little short.
That's no crime.
I'm only 5'6".
Enjoy the show.
[instrumental music
playing on screen]
[people shouting]
[alarm ringing]
[Zorg speaking French]
Sherman, where are
the subtitles?
You watch. I'll translate.
[speaking French]
"It's the first time
we've met in daylight."
[speaking French]
"But you're very early."
I think I'm just gonna go
tell the theater owner.
I mean, there's nothing he
can do about it. They
obviously sent him the wrong
print.
I can get my money back.
I've seen this film before.
I don't think you want
to miss it.
Does it have a happy ending?
No. Definitely not.
Okay. Then I'll say.
[speaking French]
"You gonna eat
all that chili by yourself?
In this heat, you're mad."
[Zorg speaking French]
"I eat chili no matter
how hot it is, Betty."
[both speaking French]
"Those bastards." "What?"
"Never mind. Kiss me."
[Betty speaking French]
"Those bastards.
How could they do this to
you?"
[continues translating,
indistinct]
I'm sorry.
How long was I doing that?
I lost feeling
about an hour ago,
so I'm not sure.
Why didn't you
say something?
Um, the movie is
a bit of a downer, so...
It's a love story.
[sniffles]
I mean,
not all love stories
are downers.
All the good ones are.
Romeo and Juliet,
Anna Karenina,
The English Patient.
Mm-hmm.
I think it's the ending
of a relationship,
that's what makes
a love story so memorable.
What about
Pride and Prejudice?
Jane Eyre?
Those both have
happy endings.
That's only because
the writer chose to end
their love stories
prematurely.
Wow. That is
a really interesting way
of not admitting
you're wrong.
[laughing]
Come on! Okay. Picture this.
Picture that Leonardo
DiCaprio didn't die at the
end of Titanic.
Do I have to? Oof.
You have to.
Jack Dawson is a jobless,
penniless gambler,
who possessed, at best,
marginal artistic talent.
He saved Rose's life.
Right, of course.
But he also love-bombed her
and stole her away
from her fiancé.
And poor Rose was
just so hypnotized
by that steamy car sex,
that she really thought
that he'd give her a life
of passionate adventure?
Please, come on.
That's a life of abject
poverty and dehumanizing
infidelity.
Titanic 2.
If you thought part one
was a disaster...
Oh, my gosh.
[clears throat]
I--
[Sherman] Time to go!
Jesus, this guy is getting
a one-star review, for sure.
So, um, how did you get
so good at speaking French?
My dad is
a foreign languages
professor.
So by the time I was 12,
he had me fluent in French,
Spanish, and Italian.
Oh! Oh, my gosh.
If I could just read
Dante's Inferno
in the original Italian,
my life would be
complete, I think.
I get that a lot.
Really?
No. No, I've never
gotten that before.
That's some pretty old gear
you got there.
You don't shoot digital?
No, I don't.
I get a much higher
dynamic range on film.
Plus, I'm also
kind of addicted to the
smell of the developing
chemicals.
The fumes make me
a little delirious.
[laughs]
Kind of like what your eyes
are doing to me right now.
Ooh.
That...
[both chuckle]
That was really cheesy.
No, no.
It was... It was...
a little cheesy, yeah.
It sounded perfect
in my head.
Oh, okay. Then let me
imagine that for a sec,
okay.
Okay.
Still bad?
It's worse, actually.
Somehow, I don't know.
[door opens]
[exhales]
Um, I should probably...
Yeah, me too.
Um, thank you for letting me
whisper in your ear
for three hours.
You are welcome.
Skylar.
What?
My name is...
It's Skylar.
I'm Tessa.
Maybe I'll see you here
again sometime.
Yeah, I'd like that.
[sighs]
Oh! My jacket.
[seagulls squawking]
[shutter clicking]
[clock ticking]
[ticking slows, distorts]
Sky. You're alive!
[heartbeat thumping]
Come on. I want
to show you something.
[lights humming]
Sky!
Bad dream.
You called out his name.
It's called a visitation
dream. We see lots of 'em
around here.
It's all part
of the grieving process.
I know. It just felt
like Skylar was really here.
Doris would love
to hear about that.
Who's Doris?
A patient writing a book
on the afterlife.
Okay.
The other day,
she offered to read my aura.
I politely declined.
What is that?
Your belongings
from the crash.
They closed
the accident report already?
Well, neither driver
had drugs or alcohol
in their system.
That's usually
the end of it.
They never even
interviewed me.
You said you didn't remember
anything about the accident?
I don't.
Maybe that's for the best.
[Dr. Sarkisian]
I'm very encouraged, Tessa.
The scan shows
your right ventricle
is functioning quite well,
despite the tear.
Finally, some good news.
It is more than good.
Ninety-nine out of 100
with this same injury
die on my table.
I did die.
Only for a short time.
I could see Skylar.
Like, he was in this...
this crazy white light.
What is that?
Was she, you know,
hallucinating?
When the body undergoes
severe trauma...
[heartbeat thumping]
...the hypothalamus
can flood the brain
with pain relieving endorphins.
[Vickie]
So when can we take her
home?
[Dr. Sarkisian] End of the
week. Tessa needs to be
extremely careful these next
few months.
Any chest pains
or shortness of breath,
you call 911 immediately.
Understand?
[shower running]
[heartbeat thumping]
[crying]
[crying continues]
[knocking on door]
Jazz? Just give me a second.
Jazz?
[electrical crackling]
[phone chimes, buzzes]
[Skylar]
You watch, I'll translate.
[indistinct PA announcement]
Hi, excuse me.
Are you Doris?
[exhales] I am going to take
a wild guess here.
Room B424,
girl with the broken heart?
[laughing] Relax.
I'm not psychic.
Jasmine told me you might
come looking for me.
Oh.
My condolences.
Thank you.
Are your hands injured?
Excuse me?
From the accident.
Did you hurt
your hands at all?
No, why?
Ta-da! Huh?
Oh, come on. Come on.
[chuckles]
So, what is your book about?
It's about ADC's.
After Death Communication.
Okay, so you believe that
dead people can contact us?
Along with billions
of other people
from faiths
that span the globe.
Sometimes, the departed,
they call out
to us in voice.
And other times, we can
smell their cologne or
perfume in the air.
No matter how they
communicate, the message is
the same.
"I'm still here.
And your grief,
like a beacon,
calls me to your side."
And when the separation
has been traumatic,
like with you
and your boyfriend,
there's often
unfinished business.
Like regrets or something?
Like things left undone
or unsaid.
[door opens]
[Vickie] Tessa.
We signed you out.
It's time to go.
He's in the in-between.
But he won't be there for
long, a few weeks at most.
And when he moves on...
he's gone for good.
I gotta go.
Oh, wait, wait.
Here, take this.
It's my first book.
It's a good place
to start.
That's okay.
He's reaching out to you.
Reach back.
It's too late for that.
[teacher]
Tessa, you're up.
[clears throat]
Um, this is a photo that
I took back in February.
Is that how you spend
your free time,
taking pictures of trees?
Well, it's actually
not a tree, asshole.
[class laughs]
It's a cell phone tower,
disguised as a tree.
It is an allegory
for the artificiality
of modern life.
[school bell rings]
It's a lovely photo, Tessa.
Your technical skills have
taken huge leaps this year.
Oh, thank you.
I know you're
still a junior,
but I think you have a good
shot of getting into the
Rhode Island School of
Design.
I'd be happy to write you
a letter of recommendation.
Thank you. I just--
My work's not ready
for that yet.
Oh? What do you feel
is missing?
Just like a point of view.
You know, something to say
that's my own.
Well, maybe it's time
for your subject matter
to evolve.
After all,
there is something notably
missing from all your
photos.
Yeah, I know. Color.
No. People.
You know, Tessa, before
an artist can find her
voice,
she has to find
a subject she loves.
Who or what
do you love, Tessa?
["Closer" playing]
[Skylar]
I should probably...
Yeah, me too.
Hey, okay.
What do you think?
Red?
Noisy colors
are trendy.
I don't know. I feel like
you're kind of taking
advantage of your dad's
niceness.
Of course, I am.
My dad is putty when
I get straight A's.
Hey, yo, Tess!
Hi, Cortez.
Hey, uh, do you have
plans this weekend?
As it happens, I actually
work as Tessa's full-time
scheduler,
so I can say, with
absolute authority, that
she does not have any plans
this weekend.
What are you saying?
What are you doing?
Well, the final crew meet
of the season is this
Saturday.
I was kind of wondering
if you 'd come out
and take some photos.
Uh, sorry. I don't really do
sports photography.
But if you glue
a selfie stick to your
forehead, it might be the
same thing.
Will Judd be there?
Well, wherever I go,
my rowing partner goes,
so...
Then we'll be there.
"We" will be there?
I'll be there as your photo
assistant, remember?
I'm her photo assistant.
Well, the first race
starts at30.
In the morning?
He didn't mean morning,
did he?
[Tessa]
Yup, he did.
[spectators cheering]
Do you think Judd
can see me from here?
Hey!
You are fired.
Give me this.
Assistanting is
not my thing. My bad.
You were the one
who dragged me out here.
So behave, please.
[announcer]
Racers, starting positions.
Ready your marks.
Row!
[air horn blows]
[rowers grunting]
[heartbeat thumping]
[air horn blowing]
[spectators cheering]
Whoo! Whoo!
Yeah!
[both laughing]
Yes!
Whoo!
[Shannon]
You never said he was hot.
Yes, I did.
No, you said he was cute.
Emojis are cute.
That guy is like melting
my sunglasses, Tess.
I think I'm gonna go.
Are you crazy?
You've been obsessed
about this guy for like
months, and you're just
gonna ditch?
I don't know what
to say to him.
"Hold me."
He just won the race.
Congratulate him.
Okay.
Can I put this on my Story?
If you wanna die.
Tessa! Hey-- Oh!
Oh, my God! Sorry.
Whoa, whoa!
My legs are always
Jell-O after races.
I can't believe
that you're a...
A jock?
A jock, yeah!
Jocks don't speak
Spanish, French and Italian.
Hey, this one does.
Well, they definitely
don't read
Jane Austin and
Emily Bronteë.
I have a thing
for happy endings.
Skylar!
Oh, shit. Here we go. Um...
That is what I
call a finish.
Thanks, Mom.
Um...
Movie theater girl.
Her name is Tessa.
How did you...
The blue eyes.
Skylar went on and on
about them.
Wow, Mom! Does anyone see
a deep, dark hole
I can crawl into?
[Leigh] You know,
he spent weeks searching
for you on the Internet.
Mom...
[Leigh] And he couldn't find
a thing about you.
Well, that is by design.
[phone ringing]
Told you.
She's analog. Like me.
[sighs] Your father
is driving me crazy.
Talk to him, Mom.
Tell him-- Tell him I won.
No. You can talk to him
yourself later. Are you
going to be heading back to
Edison tonight?
No, I'm gonna be staying
at Grandpa Mike's. Um...
But first, I was gonna see
if Tessa maybe wanted to
go...
Chill out and hang?
[softly] Oh, my God.
Movie theater
girl would love
to chill out and hang.
[Leigh chuckles]
All right. Bye.
Thanks.
[footsteps departing]
Thank you, Mom.
That's my mom.
She does, uh, parties.
[laughs]
[horn honks]
I can put the top up
if you want.
[laughing] No, it's okay.
It feels really good.
[sighs] You look amazing.
Say it in French.
[speaking French]
You too.
Um...
You don't have
a girlfriend, do you?
No. Not since
the eighth grade. Why?
This kinda looks like you.
[laughs] No. That is, uh...
That's my mom and dad
when they were teenagers.
Oh!
Yeah, this is actually
the same Jeep that my
grandpa
bought my mom
for her 18th birthday.
You can actually see it
behind them in the photo.
Oh, yeah! They're so cute.
They look so in love.
Yeah, they were.
"They were"?
Are. They are.
My dad's just
living and teaching in
Oregon right now.
That's pretty far.
Are they, like, taking
a break or something?
No.
They're gonna be fine.
They talk almost
every day, so...
Some music.
Whoa!
If you wanna
take a look.
[gasps] What?
Yeah, it's my mom's entire
high school playlist.
New Order. Cake. Bush.
Echo and the Bunnymen.
Your mom's like
my new bestie.
Your dad made
her a mix tape?
Yes, he did.
Can I play it?
It's the other way.
[both chuckle]
It's okay. I won't tell
the '80s police.
Shut up.
I have spent every summer
of my life down here
with my grandfather.
How have I never
heard of this place?
Well, that's my favorite
part about taking photos.
It's like you just
stumble and wander
and find places like this.
Right. But what...
what drew you
to this spot specifically?
The view.
That view.
[seagulls squawking]
It was called
The Empyrean.
It was a honeymooners'
resort back in the '60s.
It's so surreal.
It's unbelievable.
You've gone in there?
Unarmed?
I'll do anything
for a great photo.
"Empyrean"?
That's where Dante
meets God, right?
Highest of all heavens.
A place of pure love.
Look at it. If that's
not a metaphor for love,
then I don't know what is.
Can I see your photos?
They're not on my phone.
I don't shoot digital,
remember?
Well, how do people
see your work?
I don't show it,
unless I have to for class.
How come?
'Cause I'm not
good enough yet.
I find that
seriously difficult
to believe.
Okay, so if you won't
show me your photos,
maybe you can
give me a tour.
Of The Empyrean?
Yeah, show it to me.
I wanna see it, you know,
through your eyes.
["Never Tear Us Apart"
playing]
[both laughing]
[tennis ball thwacking]
[both grunting]
[piano keys playing]
Do you know how to waltz?
No.
Okay, just step back
this way.
Okay.
And then
your back foot forward.
And then it's like
one, two, three.
Straighten your leg.
One, two, three.
Okay.
And then you have to
put your chin up
and then lead.
Like you don't want
to pay any attention
to the other person.
Don't slip.
[both laughing]
You know it's true
Worlds collided
We're shining through
Do you want to see
what it's like to be
inside of a camera?
Yeah.
Okay. Close the door.
It works just like
a camera lens.
I kind of made it myself.
Whoa.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
[playing harmonica]
I mean,
it's pretty good, right?
Ooh, I mean, it's obvious
you just haven't been
playing that long.
Just three years.
Oh.
Should have heard me
back then.
[both laughing]
Can you hear them?
Hear who?
The ghosts of
newlyweds past.
No. What are they saying?
Well, the groom,
he's saying...
[in deep voice]
Come on, honey.
You've been in the bathroom
for two hours now.
It's time to come to bed.
You're my wife.
What does the bride say?
Well, the bride
is saying, um...
But you haven't even
kissed me yet.
Okay.
You want me to walk you
to your door
so your parents don't think
I'm a... taxidermist?
What?
Or like someone--
a serial killer?
That's okay.
Um, they're not
my parents, actually.
I, uh... I'm just
a genetic stranger
that lives under their roof.
"A genetic stranger"?
Yeah, it's, uh...
It's a long story.
For another time.
When can I see you again?
Um, well, when are you
back in Avalon?
End of the month.
And how long are you
gonna be here for?
The whole summer.
I'm staying with my grandpa
until I leave for Brown.
You're going to Brown? What?
I just kissed
an Ivy League bro?
[gasps]
[laughs]
Your street cred ruined?
Only if you tell me
that you're also a
lifeguard.
Yeah.
Are you serious?
Mm-hmm.
About three summers now
at Washington Avenue Beach.
No! Why?
Good night.
[heartbeat thumping]
[sniffles]
[continues crying softly]
Do I need to kick
this guy's ass?
No, she's just scared.
Why?
Because she likes him.
[shutter clicks]
[Vickie] Tessa?
[footsteps approaching]
Shannon's waiting.
Okay, I'm coming.
Hey, what's that?
That is four
A's, one A-minus.
Don't want to talk about it.
I'm gonna tint the windows,
so no one knows it's me
inside.
Geez, stop whining.
It's a car.
So did you call
the phone company?
Yeah.
And?
You were right. They just
said that Skylar probably
sent the photo before the
accident
and then it got stuck
in the server or something.
But that doesn't explain
why my phone just turned on
after it was completely
trashed.
Can you explain that?
I can't. No.
[sighs]
Hey.
It's totally normal
to read into things.
My mom did the same thing
after her sister died.
Every rainbow was a sign.
Every butterfly
was a message from heaven.
[door opens]
Meet my computer on wheels.
[Shannon] Shit.
Sorry. You put it
on my Spotify.
It's okay.
[music stops]
Hey.
Talk to me, Tess.
I can't believe he's gone.
It's like I close my eyes
and I see us meeting
for the first time.
And I remember every word
that he said to me.
I remember every expression
on his face.
And then I open my eyes
and it's like...
Did I, like, just dream
our entire relationship up?
Did I dream him up?
Hey. I was there.
He wasn't a dream, okay?
Your head's just
a little scrambled.
That happens when
two tons of metal comes
crashing into you.
I don't even remember
the last thing I said to
him.
Come on.
I'm serious.
We were fighting
that last week, remember?
Hey.
You guys had an epic summer.
One that you will
never forget.
Yeah.
Damn, I won't forget it,
and I was just
a jealous bystander.
[laughing]
Oh, my God.
It's my first day back,
and I look like a total
mess.
Yeah. You do.
[laughing]
You do, yeah.
[school bell ringing]
[phone chimes]
I heard about
what happened, Tessa.
I'm terribly sorry.
If you were my daughter,
I'd tell you to use it.
Use it?
The pain, the emptiness.
Channel it,
through your camera.
Some of the greatest works
of art were produced
by intense grief.
Okay.
Tessa.
RISD portfolio day
is right around the corner.
Thank you.
[seagulls squawking]
["Perfect Day" playing]
[Mel] So that's it?
You're just giving up
your photography?
It sure looks like it.
This is the same crap
your mom used to pull.
She'd become obsessed
with things.
Baking, yoga, pottery.
One day, lose interest,
move on to the next.
That's why she could never
get any traction in life.
Are you done?
You think Skylar
would have wanted this?
I don't know.
Why don't you go ask him?
[sighs]
[Skylar] It's okay.
I won't tell the '80s
police.
[Tessa] Shut up. [laughs]
[heartbeat thumping]
I'm still here, Tess.
Sky?
[seagulls squawking]
[footsteps approaching]
[Vickie] Tess?
I'm sleeping.
I just did a double shift.
You were asleep when I left.
Did you even eat anything?
I'm not hungry.
Can you please
just let me sleep?
[sighs]
[harmonica music
playing, faint]
No. No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no...
[gasps]
No, no, no. No, no...
No.
[heartbeat thumping]
[electrical crackling]
[heartbeat continues]
Hi.
[indistinct PA announcement]
Tessa?
Uh, I gotta talk to Doris.
Hang on a second.
Let me-- Wait, Tessa.
What--
Her family took her home
this morning.
There was nothing
more we could do.
Are you okay, honey?
Um, I just haven't--
I haven't eaten today.
Um--
You know what,
let me check you out.
Why do you need to talk
to Doris so bad?
It's just--
It's about what
she was telling me before.
It's about the afterlife.
Maybe that old coot
isn't so crazy after all.
What do you mean?
Your heartbeat is fast,
but it sounds healthy.
Wait, what do you--
What were you saying?
What do you mean?
Doris told me you'd
come looking for her.
She even left you something.
Her book.
Tessa, I have seen a lot
of dying and grieving
in my time here.
Looking back
never helped anyone.
There's either life
or there's death.
There's no place in-between.
I'm gonna find him.
[Doris on video]
What does the in-between
look like?
Well, we as living beings
can never imagine it.
We have no reference.
It would be like trying
to describe a sunset
to a blind man.
Technological advances
have made ghost-hunting
a legitimate field.
My friend Darlene,
she let me borrow her
full-spectrum digital
camera.
This baby can pick up light
well beyond the human eye,
with infrared night vision--
[Shannon and Tessa laughing]
[thunder rumbling]
Well, happy Fourth of July.
I don't know. I actually
kind of like this weather.
Don't call me.
So, you think this means
the fireworks are canceled?
I think so, yeah.
Yeah.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
Skylar, Tess says
you're going to Brown.
Congrats!
Thank you.
What are you gonna study?
Probably Latin.
That'll come in handy.
You never know
when you're gonna meet
the Pope or something.
Or need to conduct
an exorcism.
Nice. That's nice.
I don't know. I just don't
want to have any regrets,
you know?
I wanna live a bunch
of different lives.
What's the point of speaking
all these languages
if I'm not gonna travel
the world and use them,
you know?
Let's go.
We are going to watch
the fireworks on TV.
Are your parents home?
Do you want
to talk about it?
Not really.
Okay.
My mom filed
for divorce today.
I'm really sorry.
You know,
I know this doesn't
help right now, but...
just because
they're splitting up
that doesn't mean that
they don't care
about each other.
It means they've given up.
I don't think that's fair.
Fair to who? You or them?
[sighs] When you're
rowing a race and you get
to the last 20 meters,
your entire body
is telling you to stop.
Your muscles are on fire.
Your lungs are screaming at
you.
Everything inside you
wants to quit,
make the pain go away.
But if you want to win,
that's exactly
when you dig deeper
and you row harder.
You really don't like
to let things go, do you?
You noticed?
[laughs]
[fireworks boom]
[whistling, booming]
[sighs]
You're just starting
to make me believe
in happy endings.
Oh, no! The photo! No.
Oh, oh...
What?
It's totally ruined.
Now you see why I don't
let anyone up here.
I am pretty amazed
that you've let me
into your inner sanctum.
Yeah, well,
if you tell anyone,
I'll poison you.
Oh, you don't have to...
Hmm?
You don't have to look
through that.
No, no, no. Okay.
Yeah.
It's cool.
I like this one.
That's, um--
That's a cell phone tower.
Yeah.
It's an allegory
for something--
technology co-opting
our natural environment.
Really?
Really.
I know you hate compliments,
but this work is incredible.
I'm serious. It's like
you can see things
that no one else can.
That just shows
how much you know
about photography.
[laughs]
I mean, I think
you can sell this stuff.
Maybe on Etsy.
There is something
that's missing
from like all
of your photos.
Yeah, I know.
It's color.
No. You.
I just don't really think
the world needs another
selfie.
Oh, come on. What is wrong
with stepping in front of
the camera every once in
awhile.
I believe that a
photographer should point
her lens outward,
toward the world.
Yeah?
Yeah, so you can try
and understand it.
What about trying
to understand yourself?
If you had my past,
you wouldn't ask that
question.
You ever gonna
tell me about it?
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Come on.
I'll walk you home.
I never met my real father.
He ran off before I was
born.
And my mom...
The kind way to describe her
would be flaky.
Wow.
Instead of
counting sheep
to go to sleep
when I was a kid,
I would count her fiancés.
And Mel was
one of them?
Yeah, he was
the last one.
Her final victim before
she ghosted us for good.
And that's when
he took you in?
Well, he tried,
but the court,
they just didn't really
look too kindly on
a middle-aged bachelor
wanting to adopt
a young girl.
So then where did you go?
Ah, Family Services.
Foster care.
Oh.
You know how you said
that I notice things
that no one else does?
Mm-hmm.
When you live with strangers
who can hurt you,
and I bounced around a lot,
you have to really just
observe everything.
When you're a foster kid,
you learn the hard way to...
Never put your guard down?
Yeah.
Anyway, about a year ago,
Mel and Vickie got married
and then the court
let them take me in.
So that's why you call
yourself a genetic stranger?
[buzzing, clicking]
I did that.
[scoffs]
["One Day" playing]
[Vickie] Good God.
How early is it?
Super early.
A little splash
of almond milk, right?
Uh, yeah.
I like your necklace.
Yeah? Shannon
lent it to me.
You know, if you ever
want to borrow anything from
me, clothes or makeup,
jewelry...
All righty.
I'll see you later, Vick.
See ya.
[shutter clicks]
When a rower dies,
this is what heaven looks
like.
For me, heaven is
Paris in the rain.
Like cobblestone streets.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Is everything
in black and white?
Get out of my head.
You ever been? To Paris?
Someday.
Avec moi?
I guess I could use
a translator.
My parents had
their honeymoon there.
So I've been saving up
to send them
for their 25th anniversary.
What if they
don't want to go?
I mean, who doesn't want
to go to Paris?
Yeah, but what if they don't
want to go with each other?
It's not a crime
to fall out of love,
you know.
Tessa.
Hmm?
Love never dies.
What?
You just sound like someone
who's never been hurt by
life.
You putting me on notice?
[laughs] No.
Um, what the hell is that?
This...
is a rowboat.
I'm assuming you want me
to get in that?
You are getting
in this with me.
No.
We spent four hours
in your dark room
doing what you love to do.
Let me show you
what I love to do.
[birds squawking,
chittering]
[Tessa] Hands under your...
Thumbs there.
[Skylar] Thumbs here.
And then it's gonna go
simple like that.
You press it down.
Okay.
And then you tilt it
and then you pull it.
Hmm.
And then you're
pressing down,
tilt it,
and then pull it.
Okay, I'm gonna try
and go forward again.
All right.
Don't help me.
I won't.
I won't. You've got this.
You've got this.
[exhales sharply]
[Tessa] Oh, my God!
This is awful.
[Skylar laughs]
Oh, I'm tired now.
You're flying!
[Skylar playing harmonica]
I love you, Tessa.
[stammers softly]
We should probably
head back, yeah?
[slow pop music playing]
[moans softly]
[students chattering]
Hey.
"The in-between"?
That's just what
Doris calls it,
but every culture
has its own version of it.
So, it's where we go
after we die.
Not me. I'm going
to Jamaica.
I'm serious, Shannon.
It's like a waiting room
for our souls.
Okay, so you think Skylar
is reaching out to you
from this waiting room?
They were color photos,
Shannon. I don't...
I don't shoot in color.
I don't even own
the chemicals to develop it.
But you can't show me
the photos?
No, I told you.
The fixer didn't work.
I don't know why.
But maybe spirits
can't be captured on film
or something. I don't know.
All right.
Tess, I want
to believe you,
I swear,
but messages
from the other side?
I just think he wants
the same thing I want.
To see me one last time
so that we can actually
say goodbye to each other.
You loved him,
and he knew that.
What more is there to say?
[teacher]
Two-minute warning.
Please take your seats
and set your phones
to silent mode.
Dude, we need
to focus, okay?
You're not even
listening to me.
Yes, I am!
I just don't think
this is about color photos
or waiting rooms
or the in-between.
Then what is it about?
A girl who won't let go.
Just think about it.
Okay?
[door close]
[sighs]
[laughs]
Sorry.
[ringtone:
"Never Tear Us Apart"]
Cell phone use is prohibited
during the test!
[ringtone spreads to
all cell phones,
overlapping]
[students murmuring]
Didn't I tell you
the drive would be worth it?
This negative's made of
glass. It's coated in
collodion,
then dipped in silver
nitrate, which is crazy.
Because after that,
you only ave a few minutes
to take the photo
or the chemicals
completely dry up.
Hmm. That's exactly
what I was gonna say.
It's only ten grand.
It's a little
out of my budget.
But I can offer you
a gluten-free cracker
with rotting cheese on it.
You're so generous.
it's crazy.
Sorry. Am I interrupting?
No. Julian, hi.
We were just talking about
how much we love the photo.
Oh, yeah.
It's wonderful, isn't it?
I just love how
he prioritizes
mood and atmosphere
over subject.
That is a very sophisticated
insight for a girl your age.
Julian, meet my very
sophisticated girlfriend.
Hi, I'm Tessa.
Nice to meet you.
Congratulations on this.
This is great.
Oh, thank you.
Okay, kids, follow me.
I wanna show you something.
Doesn't it look amazing
all lit up like this?
Like it belongs here?
It does belong here.
Tessa, you have
an extraordinary eye.
I don't understand.
It's for sale
for $1,000.
Yeah, and we already have
two serious inquiries.
[heartbeat thumping]
Uh, this photo
is not for sale.
This was a gift to Skylar.
Can't you print
another one?
I really just don't want
anyone looking at it.
Can we please take it down?
Are you serious?
Take it down.
Hey, it's okay.
I'll take it down.
Thank you.
[heartbeat continues]
[no audible dialogue]
[train whistle blows]
That's exactly why
I brought you here,
to prove
that your photos are great,
even Julian thinks so.
I don't want this photo
hanging on the wall
of some random stranger.
This is my photo.
That means I get to decide
who I share it with
and I shared it with you.
You're right.
I'm sorry. I should have
asked you first.
I just wanted you to see
how amazing you are.
And that you can
get into RISD.
Who said anything
about RISD?
Shannon said your art
teacher thought you could
get in.
I'm gonna kill her.
It is the best art college
in the country.
And it's in Providence,
which is in the same city
as Brown.
Which if you get in,
we could be together.
I--
For real.
Without a ticking clock.
Even if I could
get into RISD,
which I totally doubt,
I cannot afford that.
You're going to
get into RISD.
No.
And you could just
get a scholarship.
Skylar, Jesus,
just give it up.
This is--
You can't fix everything.
What?
Your parents' marriage
and me.
Some things are
just beyond repair.
Is that why you
won't say you love me?
Because you're...
beyond repair.
Okay.
That's...
[machinery rattling]
[chattering on screen]
[phone chimes]
[knocking on door]
[pop music
playing on stereo]
[footsteps approaching]
Hey,00. I'm here
like you asked. What's up?
I would like to take
your portrait.
Uh... can I change first?
No, you don't have to.
You can just put that on.
What's that?
It was my mom's.
This really brings me
back to college.
I had a boyfriend
who was an art major.
Made me pose for him.
So... Mel isn't the first
person that you've been in
love with.
Gosh, no.
I've loved a few men.
Maybe even one woman.
Did you love any of them
more than they loved you?
Oh, probably.
Didn't that scare you?
Knowing that someone
could you hurt you more
than you could hurt them?
Yeah. Maybe at first.
But then I think I realized
if you protect yourself
from the lows,
you just end up missing
all the highs too.
You love Skylar. Don't you?
I think I'm screwing it up.
Yeah. If it's not
opening old wounds,
it's probably not true love.
I just don't
know what to do.
How do I get Skylar
to understand that...
I love him. [chuckles]
You start by saying it.
You need to hear
the words, Tessa.
You mean, he needs
to hear the words.
No. You need to hear
yourself say them.
Out loud.
So the world knows
your feelings count.
That you count.
Vickie, I'm sorry.
For how I've treated you.
Hey Google, dim the lights.
Yes!
Oh, man.
No smoke machine?
Shh!
We begin this invocation
by asking the
Archangel Michael
to protect us against
any malevolent spirits
that may be seeking a
gateway into this earthbound
sphere.
You wrote this?
You're interrupting
my invocation.
I'm sorry!
It's just-- This is crazy.
Did you read all of
these books in two days?
Bitch, yes!
You know speed reading
is my super power.
Enjoy Your Own Funeral.
Yeah. That happens
to be a classic
of the paranormal
metaphysical genre.
Now hush.
Okay.
[pop music playing]
We seek to communicate
only with the disembodies
spirit formerly known as
Skylar Adams.
No other spirits, please.
Okay.
A Ouija board?
Please, Tess.
This is a planchette.
There's a pencil tip
attached to the bottom.
We ask questions
and Skylar communicates
by moving our hands.
Just like he did in the gym.
Here. Fingers right there.
Okay.
Close your eyes.
[gasps]
Oh, my God, it moved.
Sorry that was me. My bad.
It's called scrying.
The deceased use the mirror
as a gateway to the world
of the living.
All you have to do is
stare into the mirror
in a trance-like state.
That's it.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Can we cover up
Gambino and Drake?
They're like really
distracting me.
Instrumental
Trans-Communication.
The spirit uses the TV
monitor as a bridge to our
world.
What is this? Okay.
Here you go.
Blocks out the gamma rays.
Do you see anything?
No. Do you?
No.
[sighs]
[both sigh]
Maybe I should have
read more books.
No. No, you've been awesome.
[phone chimes]
[sighs] Oh, man.
It's just Vickie.
Needs the car.
She has a shift.
Okay. I'll walk you out.
Okay.
[faint, high
-pitched humming]
[electric warbling]
[voice murmuring]
Hello?
[murmuring continues]
[GPS] Your route
is being calculated.
Proceed for four miles
to the entrance to
Highway 85 South.
It's a map.
[door opens, closes]
["Closer" playing]
Tessa? Tessa!
Sorry! I've gotta do this.
Tessa!
[tires screeching]
[GPS] Head southwest
to I-95 South,
and proceed for 106 miles.
Continue straight
for six miles.
[GPS] Take the next right,
and in 100 feet,
your destination
will be on your right.
[GPS] You have arrived
at your destination.
[heartbeat thumping]
I told you he
wasn't gone yet.
[laughs] Doris!
[chuckles] Come. Sit.
You know,
I love coming out here at
night
to watch the shooting stars.
My angels are
calling me home.
Skylar knows
the end is near.
You don't have much time.
He's been communicating
with you?
Well, I'm much closer
to his world than you are.
[chuckles]
What does he want?
My help.
To bring
the two of you together.
Can you?
Please.
In ancient folklore,
the souls of the departed
returned to places
where they experienced
their greatest moments of
love.
That's where they were able
to cross the life-death
barrier.
Now, perhaps if
you and Skylar went back
to where you felt
the most love,
the window between worlds
might open?
Okay.
But be careful.
If you do manage
to cross the barrier...
there may be no way back.
[hip-hop music playing
over speakers]
[teenagers laughing,
chattering]
Tess?
What's up?
This is not how I wanted
my summer to go.
Oh, no, what do you mean?
What's wrong?
They're so cute together,
it's stupid.
Who's cute?
Oh. Is that Judd?
[Shannon] That's Judd.
Oh...
My vagina is weeping.
They are cute,
but I'm so sorry.
That's terrible.
Oh, my God!
What?
Billy Hodges
came to my party?
Ciao, Billy.
Hey.
[sighs] It's
just three words.
Hi.
Can we go somewhere
to talk for a second, alone?
Sure.
[both chuckle]
Yo, brutha!Hey.
[Cortez]
I just heard the good news.
What news?
Um...
Oregon State!
Nothing's official yet.
Oh, bullshit, bro.
No, I just talked
to the new coach. He said
it's as good as done.
Come on.
Um...Okay.
Tess? Tess? Tessa?
Tess, I was gonna
tell you, I swear.
When?
When were you gonna tell me?
After I got into RISD?
No, of course not.
I just didn't want to give
you another reason to back
out.
What about our plan?
The same city?
No more ticking clock?
You weren't even gonna
send in an application.
I applied last week.
Well, thank you for waiting
until the last possible
moment to tell me.
[sighs]
The truth is, Tess,
my dad's not...
He's not doing that well.
He's really lonely in Oregon
and I feel like I should
stay with him for awhile.
Oregon is on the other side
of the country.
How were we ever
gonna see each other?
It'll be hard.
I'm not switching schools
permanently. I'm not!
And if you get into RISD,
and you will,
I'll be in Providence
before you are.
What happens if you start
to like Oregon? What happens
if your team starts to win?
Tess, my dad
needs me right now.
He's my family. I don't--
[exhales]
You don't understand
about family because--
Because I don't have one.
That is not what
I meant to say.
I knew this was
gonna happen.
I get close to people
and they disappear on me.
This is just what
happens to me.
Tess.
No.
You're just gonna push me
away like you do everyone?
The summer is over, Skylar.
And so are we.
[horn honking]
Hey.
Your ghost-hunting assistant
has arrived.
Here you go.
Direct from Daddy's closet.
Yeah, this is full spectrum,
motion sensor, night vision.
Perfect. Thank you.
Who gave you all the swag?
Ah, Vickie's credit card.
Whoa! Tessa's a
bad, bad girl.
Bye.
Hey, if there are nudes
of my mom on that camera,
I do not want to know.
[whispers]
Shh. I'm gonna tell you.
[seagulls squawking]
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
[faint, high-pitched hum]
[gasping]
[police radio chatter]
[officer]
Central, standby.
You Tessa Benson?
I can't believe
you tracked my phone.
The day you stole
Vickie's credit card
was the day you gave up
your right to privacy.
What were you doing
at the hotel so late?
I was taking photos.
I told you that.
What, are you trying to put
yourself back in the
hospital?
I don't understand this.
Things were so much better
this summer.
We started to feel
like a family.
Do you not understand?
Geez, I wonder what happened
at the end of the summer
that might change my mood.
You know what I've been
through? What Vickie's been
through?
Stop.
Love hurts.
You learn to live with it.
Fuck off, Mel.
Hey, no! You don't get
to talk to him like that.
Not after everything
he's done for you.
There's no...
Tessa!
[ultrasound warbling]
She's ruptured the repair.
Is it any wonder? The way
she's been running around
all crazy.
You can see right here.
There's a fair amount of
blood accumulated around her
heart.
Will she be all right?
Not until we
drain the chamber
and reinforce
the original suture.
We're gonna schedule you
for an OR first thing
in the morning.
No, no, I-- I'm not--
You gotta let me go.
You need to let me go.
Tessa! 50 milligrams now.
[Tessa] Jasmine, no!
Don't, please!
Tessa, if I let you go home,
you won't make it
through the night.
You don't understand.
Get some rest now, honey.
I never got to tell...
tell him.
Tell him what?
That...
They can never, ever
tear us apart.
["Never Tear Us Apart"
playing]
[song continues on ringtone]
Tess?
[groans] Shan, is that you?
Are you okay?
You-- You sound medicated.
I'm at the hospital.
What happened?
I saw him, Shan.
No way.
At the hotel.
I couldn't touch him,
but he was there.
I just have one place left
that I have to go.
The lake.
Where he told you
he loved you.
I just don't really have
much time left.
Okay, stay put. I'm coming.
Whoa.
Now what?
I don't know.
[electrical crackling]
Room 22.
I'll take him.
[chiming]
Oh. Ooh, two more.
[chiming continues]
Witching hour.
I'll take odds,
you take evens.
Yeah.
[elevator dings]
Whoa.
Let's go.
I could get used to this.
[elevator dings]
[security guard]
Hey! What are you doing?
Go, go, go.
Come on.
Oh, God.
Whoa. What the hell?
[tires squealing]
The lake is that way.
You've gotta turn around.
I know. I know!
It's the wrong way!
Please turn around.
I can't.
Let go.
What?
Let go!
[horns honking]
[both screaming]
[both panting]
I want a dead boyfriend too.
[door opens, closes]
What are you doing here?
Skylar says he's called you
and left you a ton of
messages.
So?
So? You're ghosting
your soul mate?
Shannon, my past is always
just gonna get in the way.
Remember last year,
you'd spotted
that condemned bridge
and just had to get a photo.
You had to jump
into the water,
even though it was
freezing cold.
You know what
I was thinking,
when I saw you down there
swimming against the current
to get your photo,
"Imagine if Tess could
be like this for her life,
and not just for her art."
He's leaving tonight, Tess.
Lock up for me.
[tires screeching]
[thunder rumbling]
This is where
the accident happened.
Do you know why
he brought you here?
No.
I don't know.
But I'm gonna find out.
Tess?
Tess!
Oh, my God.
I need help!
[line ringing]
[dispatcher]
911, what's your emergency?
[Shannon]
My friend just passed out.
She has a heart condition.
I'm at the corner
of 6th and Channel,
please send somebody!
[Tessa] Skylar!
Tess.
You forgot your hat.
[chuckles]
I'm so sorry, Sky.
I'm sorry. I'm...
[sighs] I should have
talked to you before
making any decisions.
No. You shouldn't have to
explain loving your family.
If I hadn't spent my whole
life just pushing everyone
away, I would have
understood that.
No, come on, Tess.
I love you.
[chuckles]
I said it.
Would you mind
if I said it again?
I love you.
[horn honking]
[Tessa screams]
[Skylar] Hey.
[gasps]
It's you.
It's me.
Oh, my God.
[siren wailing in distance]
I love you.
I know.
You told me.
I love you.
So that's why
you brought me here?
So that I'd know?
Yeah. No regrets.
So, is this...
Is this it?
We're still in Avalon.
Not exactly.
It's like everything
you see is a memory,
a dream that we have,
to project it onto the
world.
It's kinda cool.
Come on. I'll show you.
Okay.
[paramedics,
Shannon chattering]
[speaking French]
[doctors, nurses chattering]
I came out here
the first day I met you.
My parents had just told me
about the separation.
Felt like it was
the worst day of my life.
And then I met you.
And it was probably
the best day of my life.
Mine too.
[Dr. Sarkisian]
There's nothing more we can
do. She has a decision to
make.
She has to want to live.
Come back, Tess.
Come back, Tess...
[crying]
Hey.
What's wrong?
I've spent my whole life
learning how not to get
hurt.
And that's no way to live.
But... But even with
all the hurt that I feel
right now...
I don't regret a thing.
Because I love you.
And knowing that I'm capable
of feeling this way,
makes life worth living.
I don't want
to say goodbye.
You don't have to.
Love never dies.
[sighs]
I'm gonna miss you.
[sobbing]
Go give us
a happy ending, yeah?
Hey.
No more dying, okay?
[chuckles]
Oh, my God.
It smells so good.
Sit down. There's plenty.
I can't. I gotta go.
Good luck, Tessa.
Love you.
Go get 'em.
All right, bye.
See you later!
Ever since I was
a little girl,
people always told me that
I see things
that no one else does.
It wasn't just that
my camera was a way for me
to express myself.
It was the means by which
I captured the unseen.
It was only recently
that I discovered something
that I had been blind to.
A ghost.
All of us,
each and every one of us,
are haunted by ghosts.
The ghosts of
childhood trauma.
unfulfilled dreams.
The ghosts of lost love.
Like so many people,
I believed that,
if I just ignored
these ghosts,
they would
eventually go away.
This turned out
to be a mistake.
Just like all of
our worst fears,
these invisible spirits
gain strength in darkness.
If we run from them,
they run faster.
If we push them away,
they just push back harder.
What are we supposed to do?
It has taken...
great personal loss
for me to discover the
answer to this question.
We must attend
to our ghosts.
We must welcome them
into our lives
as though they are part of
us, because they are part of
us.
It's only when we
acknowledge their presence
will they make room for new
possibilities.
In the end,
I've learned that our ghosts
are part of who we are,
part of who we hope to be.
These hauntings
stay inside us,
tethered to our
hearts forever.
In life.
In death.
And... everywhere
in-between.