Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[cheery music]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
♪
- Hmm.
It is T-minus two days
before Christmas, Daddy,
and my family's coming home,
coming together
to celebrate you
on our favorite holiday.
♪ Five golden rings
♪ Four calling birds,
three French hens ♪
♪ Two turtle doves
♪ And a partridge
in a pear tree ♪
[chuckles]
♪
Mama's special recipe.
[sighs]
[solemn music]
♪
Lord, give me
your strength today.
Bless me with your patience
to deal with my family,
for they know not
what they do.
Lord, I can't believe Daddy's
not with us this Christmas.
Please send your loving angels
to be with this family
as we get through
this first one without him.
Protect us and guide us
as only you can.
In your precious name we pray.
Amen.
[bells chiming]
James.
Come on, now, I have cooked,
cleaned, and prayed,
and you're still not down?
Do you hear me?
Our children will be here
any minute!
Don't let me come up there
and get your ass!
Lord, forgive my mouth today.
I told you, I'm gonna need
as much patience as I can get.
James Mabry, I have never
known you to be this late,
fussing around like that.
What's wrong with you?
- Not getting it right,
Baneatta.
- The getting ready on time
to greet your family,
or your sermon?
- [chuckles]
Oh, man.
- Honey, you have been speaking
to this congregation
seven months now,
and you get better and clearer
and more powerful
every weekend.
- But this is Christmas.
And your daddy's
Christmas Eve sermons--
- They were something.
People would come from all over
to hear his sermons.
Hmm.
- You know, first time,
first Christmas I heard him,
I thought God
had given up on me.
But I heard him that night,
and I realized I had
just stopped listening.
- He was something.
- Yeah.
- But you're special
in your own way.
Daddy knew it; that's why
he gave you the church.
- [chuckles]
- And I know it too.
Mm.
- You have your title yet?
- No. No.
That's part of the problem.
How am I--
how am I supposed to top,
"While they're at home,
waiting on Santa,
we're in here...."
both:
"Praising Jesus!"
- [laughs]
Oh, see? See?
It's a classic. Man.
- It is.
- Mm.
- But you'll find your own.
- Yeah.
Your sister here yet?
- Would the house be so quiet
if she was?
- I can't be worried
about you two
strangling each other
out in the parking lot.
- Well, you need
to talk to her...
- Wait, Miss.
- Not me.
- My point is, Miss Baneatta,
I need you to promise me
you're gonna walk
into that church
with a positive attitude.
None of us need a repeat
of the funeral.
[mischievous music]
Mm-hmm. Baneatta.
- I promise.
- Good.
- To do my best.
- Lord, have mercy.
All right.
Your best is a start.
Now...
Can I have one more kiss
before I get ready?
- After you brush your teeth.
- Oh, Lord.
Ooh, what-what-what's that?
Whoa, I got that booty.
I got that booty.
I touched your booty.
[phone ringing]
[both laugh]
- Hello?
- This is Louis Lee,
your father Bernard's attorney.
- Oh, uh, hello.
Good morning, Mr. Lee.
I thought we had already
handled everything
with Daddy's will.
He left us this house, his car.
Was there more?
- Well, yes.
There was one more part
your father instructed us
to wait to execute
until the holiday.
I'm calling to let you know
that he left
an additional inheritance
for the entire family.
But only if--
now, you hear me--
the entire family
comes together for Christmas.
He chose that day for a reason.
[heartfelt music]
- It was his favorite holiday.
Wherever we were,
whatever was going on
in our lives,
we'd always come together.
- This should be easy, then.
- Great.
Um, our entire family's
coming today for Christmas.
- I'll need to see for myself.
- Of course.
Come by tomorrow afternoon
before church service.
Do you have the address?
- I do.
- Good. We'll be here.
- I sure hope so.
- Like I said, we will be here.
- Until then.
[doorbell rings]
- Oh, Lord.
- Um.
Excuse me, is this the--
the Jenkins home?
- Sure is.
- Are you Baneatta Jenkins?
- Yes.
- Uh, this is for you.
- Oh. Thank you.
May I ask who it's from?
- It's from me.
- Oh, do I know you?
- I'm sorry.
I just--I--
been envisioning this moment
for so long,
and I thought
it was gonna be easier--
would be in my mind.
- Okay.
- You're as beautiful
as I imagined you would be.
- I don't understand.
- I'm your sister.
- Oh, you have me confused
with someone else.
- No, Bernard was--
he was my daddy too.
I--I didn't know him.
I mean, not--
not like I imagine you do.
My mother kept who he was
a secret from me,
but when the cancer--
it, um, came for her quickly.
And it was just the two of us.
And at the end of the day,she--
she just didn't want me to--
to be left alone in this world.
So she told me who he was.
Who you all were.
The only family I have left.
And I know this must be
a shock for you,
all those years past,
all the years that
we could have known each other,
but I'm here to--
to get to know him
and all of you
on his favorite holiday.
'Cause I mean, what's the point
of being alone anymore
when I have family?
Right?
Anyway, um,
I'm staying downtown
at a hotel across the street
from the Fox Theatre, but...
I was really hoping to be
a part of the
Jenkins family Christmas.
- Well, you were hoping wrong.
This is a family affair,
and I do not know you.
You are not welcome here.
You need to go back
to where you came from.
- Tell that to Louis Lee.
- What did you say?
- The lawyer. Daddy's lawyer.
He called me, too, Baneatta.
He said that Daddy--
that our daddy--
left us something behind--
an inheritance.
And the only way
we could claim it
is if the entire family
were together at Christmas.
The entire family.
All his children.
Which I just explained
includes me.
Look, I just drove in
from Raleigh
to find my family.
- I'm sorry I couldn't
have been more help.
- [muffled]
Who was that?
- James, put some pants on.
This is not one
of your Zoom calls.
- But I--
[inquisitive music]
All right, be like that.
♪
- No need to let a good bottle
of wine to go waste.
[doorbell rings]
[laughs]
Oh, my baby.
- Hey, Ma.
[chuckles]
- Hello, Kenneth.
- It is, like,
two days until Christmas.
How you holding up?
- I was all right
till a couple of minutes ago.
- Oh, no. What's--what's wrong?
- Well, no one informed me
we were gonna have guests,
and you know how much
I like to prepare everything.
- Kenny, you told me
your mom invited me.
- Hey, remember,
I told you about my friend...
- Logan.
- Well, he's here now, so.
Come on, Luke.
- It's, uh, it's actually Lo--
- That's what I said.
- Hey, so, I know that nobody
will ever make it
as good as you,
but I attempted
to make your famous eggnog.
- Oh.
You really did.
[Kenny chuckles]
Try.
Why is it so runny?
my special ingredient--alcohol.
- Boy, why do you need
liquid courage
so early in the day?
- Yeah, why do you?
- I'm--look, I'm just trying
to do my part
to, like, spread
Christmas joy around here.
- Mm.
- Right.
- Larry, get your bag
and take it down there
to the basement.
[tense music]
- It's, uh, it's--
- Thank you, honey.
- Hey, Mom, is, uh, Dad around?
- You know him, always late.
- Okay, I just, uh,
I really need to talk to him
about something
before we trim the tree, so.
- So this is
the fifth ring of Hell.
Got it.
[doorbell rings]
- Oh, my favorite is here.
Don't you tell your brother
I said that,
but between us girls,
you know it's true.
[laughs]
Now where's
my favorite son-in-law?
Where's my Michael?
- He couldn't make it, Mom.
- Yeah, right.
Like he would miss a holiday.
Where's my Michael?
Where you hiding him,
in the car?
- I'm serious, Mom.
He had to work.
- Since when is work
more important than family?
- [coughing]
Ma! Ma, I thought you quit.
- LaTrice, mind your business.
- I'm just saying.
- You know what? Say less.
And put down that damn phone.
You need to pick up
a book and read.
- I am reading.
- What?
- Snapchat.
And TikTok is very educational.
- [chuckles]
Very funny. Very funny.
Now, listen, we're almost
at your auntie's house.
Mm. Oof.
Your Aunt Baneatta's bound
to say something slick
this weekend.
I don't need an excuse
to slap nobody.
I am trying to be
a better Christian.
Now how do the puppies look?
Are the puppies doing okay?
[both laughing]
Now there's the smile
I've been missing!
[cheery music]
♪
- No!
No! No! No! No! No!
Frosty!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
[car horn honks]
- [laughs]
We have arrived!
- Ma! Ma!
- Beverly is here!
- Oh!
- Get out the car, girl.
Get out the car. Hey!
[car horn honks]
- Go on.
Go help your Aunt Beverly.
I'll hold back your mother.
- [muttering]
- Let it go. Let it go.
- [laughing]
Okay.
- What's up, fam?
- Hey.
- [laughs]
Who's the white boy?
- Oh, LaTrice, this is--
- Don't get too excited
just to see me,
even though
I drove to see you 87 hours.
- You call that driving?
- Listen, you think
I rented a car
to come up
to a Christmas service?
Hell, no.
Beverly came to Atlanta
to find herself a man!
Where they at?
- Well, I don't know
about all of that.
- Oh, look at you.
- Who is that, and why's she
dressed like a Christmas tree?
- Oh, that is crazy Aunt Bev
from Tampa.
Sorry.
- Oh, no, you're right.
She's batshit.
- She kind of looks fierce.
all:
Sort of.
hanging from a thread
of life on your car?
- Oh, uh, it used to be a tree.
- You begged me
to bring the tree
because you and Daddy used
to pick it from the tree farm,
and here you are bringing
this mess today, of all days.
I knew I should have bought
an artificial tree myself.
One thing you need
to accomplish.
- Hi, Auntie! Hey, Auntie!
Hi! [laughs]
- Hi, baby.
You look cute.
- [gasps] Oh!
Thank you! I know.
[laughs]
- Hi, sister! Hi, sister!
Hi--uh, sister.
- Uh, LaTrice, come with me.
Let's try to find a place
to hide away from the adults.
- Thank you.
- You got on
with your cousin now,
and don't open up your mouth
and say too much.
You behave yourself!
- Okay, Ma! Dang!
[tense music]
- Hi.
- Hey.
- So, uh, who wants
to pick out a tree?
Should be a few left for
last-minute Christmas shoppers.
I'll--I'll get the truck.
- Why do you do that?
- Do what?
- Embarrass me.
- You embarrass yourself,
showing up at this house
with your jingle bells out.
- It is not my fault that God
has given me all this glory.
- Oh, don't put God in this.
- You know, is this
how it's gonna be?
Our first Christmas
without Daddy,
and all I want
is a hug from my sister.
I mean, what does that say?
[heartfelt music]
[laughs]Okay.
[both laugh]
I've arrived.
- All right. Come on inside.
I'm tired already.
- I know.
I know I can be a bit much.
And I'll fix the tree--
the thing--
the little--the little man,
whatever is name is--Frosty--
whatever is name is.
Okay. Okay.
- Of course it is!
- No.
- There he is!
My handsome nephew!
- Oh!
- Give your
favorite auntie a hug.
Hug my handsome nephew.
- Hey, Aunt Bev!
Merry Christmas!
It is so good to see you.
- Ooh, it's good to be seen.
Merry Christmas, baby.
And ooh, and who is this
beautiful white man?
- This here is--
- Kenneth, we'll
discuss this later.
I need help with the ham.
- Oh, wait, wait, stop, wait.
Hold on just a minute.
Sit down.
- What's wrong?
- I need you to give me
your honest advice.
Now, you tell Auntie--
tell her the truth--
how do I look?
[curious music]
♪
Okay, somebody say something.
- Uh. Uh.
- Well, uh, what--what exactly
were you going for?
- Oh, a husband.
Yeah, Deacon Scott
was giving me the googly eyes
at Daddy's funeral,
so I thought I would bless him
with a different view
this time.
The look I'm going for is, um,
engage-able, uh, uh, flexible.
- Uh-huh.
- Uh.
- Oh, oh, oh, not too thotty.
Not too thotty.
- Okay.
- But definitely exotic.
Roar.
[sultry music]
♪
all:
Yes!
- There is definitely a version
of that in there somewhere.
- Ooh, okay!
Ooh, I like him, Kenny.
Big ol' tall glass of vanilla.
Ah!
Baneatta, where'd you go, girl?
- She's insane.
- She's so funny.
- Yeah, I know.
- You're not coming.
I will tell them
when the time is right.
Michael.
Michael, I am not the one
that cheated!
Don't do this.
Michael, you owe me.
[sentimental music]
♪
[knock at door]
- You okay in there, cuz?
Need anything?
- I'm all good.
I'm just freshening up.
- Cool.
- Get yourself together,
Simone.
Get yourself together.
You're not doing this.
Not here.
Not now.
- Did you see these?
- Teach you--
- Pretty.
- Kenny, kids, come help me
with this tree.
- Oh, yeah. We got it.
[festive music]
Oh, man.
- LaTrice, help your auntie
fix this tree.
- Okay.
- All right,
you got it, muscles?
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, yay.
Oh, this is so wonderful.
What you got?
- Is this gonna fit?
- Yeah.
Oh, Baneatta.
Baneatta, you kept her!
- Of course I did.
Where else would she be?
- Do you remember?
- Remember what?
- You tell it.
- No, you tell it.
[laughs]
Okay, we'll tell it together.
- Standing up?
- It's story time.
- Okay.
- We'll both tell it.
- Look at these two.
- A long time ago,
when we were little girls...
- Okay, not that long ago.
- Child.
- Okay, a little long ago.
Go ahead.
[both laugh]
- Are you ready for this?
both:
Yes.
- Ah!
- Good job!
both: Yay!
- All right! Ah!
- Good job!
- [laughs]
Yes. All right.
Gather round, kids.
Looks like we are all set.
And now, we pray.
Lord, thank you
for another Christmas Eve
with my two sweet girls.
And thank you for granting us
another opportunity
to celebrate the birth of your
only begotten son, Jesus.
Let tomorrow be filled
with love and joy,
songs and laughter, and gifts.
Lord, we never take
these holidays for granted.
We cherish each
and every single one in love.
And now,
for all these blessings,
we give you the praise
and the honor.
Happy Birthday, Jesus.
both:
all:
Amen.
- Now, it is time for my
favorite song in the world.
You know it.
We're all gonna sing along.
Let me warm up
just a little bit.
♪ Do-re-mi-fa-so-la
- Daddy!
- [laughs]
- Okay. Fine.
Here we go.
♪ Joy to the world,
the Lord is come ♪
♪ Let Earth receive her king
all: ♪ Let every heart
prepare him room ♪
♪ And heaven and nature sing,
and heaven and nature sing ♪
♪ And heaven and heaven...
- That was my favorite
Christmas memory with Daddy.
- When she wasn't ruining it
with her voice,
you know what I'm saying?
[laughter]
Okay.
- So who is this white boy?
[sentimental music]
♪
- I'm gonna get
some more eggnog.
- Logan, come and join us?
- Thank you.
- Take these.
- Hey, Dad, can I talk to you
for a second in private?
It's kind of important.
I need to get some church
business done first, all right?
- Oh, yeah. Sure, Pop.
- Oh, grab one of those.
Yeah, take one of those.
That's cool.
Like actual earrings.
They're so hard to get out.
- These are--
[LaTrice laughs]
LaTrice.
["Deck the Halls" playing]
- Hey. Hey.
Why aren't you singing?
You love this song.
- I'd hate to let the gay out
in front of your whole family.
- You two all right back there?
- Yep.
Just filled with energetic
Christmas spirit.
- Hey. Logan!
[phone ringing]
[heartfelt music]
♪
Logan.
- Oh, so you do know my name.
Because your mom,
she's called me
everything in the books
but Logan.
Larry. Lando. Lantois.
I think at one point
she even called me Loofa.
- [chuckles]
- It's not funny.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- You know, I'm gonna
get a hotel room
to spend Christmas in alone.
- What? No! Please.
Look, do not let my mother
ruin the first Christmas alone
without my grandfather.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I'm so tired of hiding you.
But...
Can you please do this for me?
♪
♪ Deck the halls
with boughs of jolly ♪
- It's holly.
- ♪ Holly
♪ Fa la la la la, la la la la
♪ 'Tis the season to be jolly
♪ Don we now our gay apparel
♪ Fa la la, la la la,
la la la ♪
♪ I don't know
the rest of this song ♪
- [laughs]
Okay.
But you gotta
promise me something.
- What?
- That you stop shrinking
when you see your mother.
- Yo, what are you
talking about?
- The moment she walks
into a room, you freeze up.
Your--your entire demeanor
changes.
- That is not true.
- Prove me wrong.
- Deal.
Come on. Let's go back.
Yeah? All right, come on.
Would you get this?
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
All right, we'll do this.
- Something--
something feels off.
- What is it, sweetie?
- Mm, something's missing, Ma.
- Don't get me started.
Your room is exactly
as you left it,
but the living room
is mine now.
You all left us here
to take care of Daddy,
so don't come telling me
you miss something.
- I went to college, Mom.
I'm not apologizing for that.
- And for the record,
I tried to stay here
and help you with Daddy.
- Oh, Beverly.
- But you didn't want me
helping with Daddy.
- Hush up that noise.
- Suddenly there's no room
for me in this house.
- Now, not this again!
- It's Santa.
- All I'm saying is,
he better come through
with my presents this year.
He was a little light
last year.
- No, he's right.
It's Black Santa.
You know, the one
that stands there at the front
and greets us every day
when we come in?
- [laughs]
- That old thing?
I left his broke ass
in the garage.
- Oh, come on.
He was our favorite!
- He doesn't fit in
with the décor.
- Uh, what decor?
- This is not decor.
- Yeah, we would know.
- White boy's right.
There's no colorful lights.
- Yeah, other than
those bland beige ones.
- Cold and cheerless,
just like you, Baneatta.
- Oh, forgive me for trying
to elevate this family a little
by not being so tacky.
- Oh, God.
- Mama, come on.
You left all the things
that make this home
feel like home in the garage.
- You people love to complain.
But where were you when I was
unpacking all these boxes
without Daddy, alone?
Huh? I can't hear you.
Oh, right,
doing your own thing,
living your own lives,
expecting me to keep up
the mausoleum.
- There she goes.
- Uh, come on, guys, let's--
let's go in the garage
and find Black Santa.
- Yeah.
Good idea.
I'll be right with you.
Hold on.
Mm. Mm. Mm. Mm-hmm. Mm.
I'll be there in a minute.
This is good.
- Whoa. Oh, there it is.
Oh.
[sentimental music]
♪
- Remember this?
- Yes.
Sitting in the back seat
on a Sunday after church.
- [laughs]
Reparations?
- LaTrice, shut up.
Hey, Logan, what are you doing?
- Uh, your granddaddy
would be rolling in his grave
if he saw these smudges.
- Hey, don't--don't say that
in front of my Mama.
I've heard enough
from her today.
Man.
- He was really
something special.
Did Kenny tell you
that he met us in New York?
Yeah, he drove us
to Long Island.
I was so scared of meeting him.
You know, the patriarch.
But he welcomed me in
with open arms.
And he loved this car.
So it's the least I can do.
- I never knew that.
- All right, well,
if you're gonna clean,
you might as well lean.
- You know?
- Found him!
Fam, maybe auntie was right.
He is creepy.
[Kenny laughs]
- Yeah, she's not wrong.
- [chuckles]
- There you all are.
- Hey.
- Wait.
There's more stuff back here.
Check it out.
- What is it, my love?
- They're from Granddaddy.
- Wow!
- How?
- Mom, he, um,
he knew he was dying,
and so he got these
for us anyway.
- He wanted us to unwrap
something from him
on his favorite holiday.
Get these presents
under the tree now.
Once we get
some s'mores started,
freshen up our drinks,
we'll have a real night before
Christmas Eve celebration.
[upbeat music]
♪
- Ma.
- Ho-ho-ho, that's good.
- Ma!
- What? What?
Come on, listen.
Everybody needs to loosen up.
Shh.
♪
Come on, let me get
into the festive spirit.
Hold on.[laughs]
Ho-ho-ho.
Mmm. Mmm-mmm-mmm. Mmm.
Some more.
This is gonna make it a very
Merry Christmas for everybody.
[laughs]
Oh, yes. Oh, mmm-mmm-mmm.
What's Santa bringing me?
Everything.[laughs]
Mmm. Mmm-mmm-mmm.
[laughter]
Oh! Oh, oh!
[chuckles]
Ah, you know, honestly,
I don't see why it's so hard
to find a man in this climate.
Simone, tell me
some of your secrets.
- I ain't got nothing to tell.
- I mean, I would be thirsty
if I just let anybody
roll up on me,
but I am looking for quality
like Daddy.
Now that's the kind
of man I want.
Mm, mm.
- Man like that's hard to find.
- Why don't y'all hush up
already, talking about men,
talking about things
you don't even understand.
"Daddy" this and "Daddy" that.
Enough about Daddy.
Daddy was a man.
[solemn music]
That's it.
- Baneatta, what's gotten
into you?
- Yes.
He was a wonderful man.
A great husband,
a loving father,
a leader in our community.
But Daddy...
♪
I'm--I'm tired.
I'm just gonna go to bed.
- Oh, come.
Come on.
Come on. Come, come on.
- And where you
staying tonight?
You know the rules!
Family only in this house,
and he ain't family.
- Mama.
- Hey, don't say that.
- Why don't we sing Daddy's
favorite Christmas song?
Oh, it's tradition.
And you know what,
I'll even pretend like
I'm enjoying myself, come on.
- Maybe some traditions
need to be put to rest.
- Stop. Stop. Hey. Logan.
Logan!
- Please don't follow me.
I don't want to talk
to you right now.
♪
[sentimental music]
That isn't gonna work
on me this time.
- Look at me and tell me
you want to sleep down here
all by yourself tonight.
Come on.
Let's just sneak back up
to my room tonight.
- Sneak?
Kenny, you're a grown-ass man.
- What?
- [sighs]
You know, I--I--
I think it's way past
your bedtime.
- What--what are you
talking about?
- Maybe you should
sneak back upstairs
before your mama
catches you down here.
- Logan.
- Kenny, good night!
- Good night.
- [sighs]
♪
- Why are you so upset?
Talk to me.
Whatever it is,
we can handle it.
Together, always.
[apprehensive music]
- Earlier today,
a woman came by the house.
She said...
She's Daddy's daughter.
I have an illegitimate sister,
supposedly.
I don't know what to believe.
She said she's from Raleigh.
Daddy did go there a lot.
Don't just sit there, James.
Say something.
- I know.
- What do you mean you know?
- When your daddy died,
he confided in me.
- He did what?
- I think when your daddy
was dying,
it finally dawned on him
what he had done, Baneatta.
[sentimental music]
He wanted to unite the family
and bring everyone together,
but he died
before we could
make that happen.
- And you didn't think
to tell your wife?
- I was going to tell you.
- When?
- My love--
- No, no, don't you
"my love" me, James Mabry.
- You were so shaken up
when he died.
I didn't want to add
any more grief to your plate.
I wanted to tell you.
But you were hurting.
Baneatta, you--
you really haven't--
- Haven't what?
- Haven't been yourself
since your daddy died.
♪
- Since you kept this
a secret from me,
you're gonna go on keeping it.
This stays between us.
- Baneatta, baby, no.
No, that is not the way.
We have to unburden ourselves
of this truth and deal with it.
We can't live in a lie.
You know the truth now.
And this is what
your daddy wanted.
- I don't care what he wanted.
- If you live this way,
sooner or later,
God might find a way
to push you
into dealing with the truth,
and you might not
like it, Baneatta.
- You want me to ruin
my daddy's name on Christmas?
You're taking up the mantle
of this church.
I don't understand why today,
of all days,
you want to do this,
tarnish his legacy,
our family name.
The humiliation--
can you imagine?
Ha.
Don't look at me like that.
- I didn't expect this vanity
and cowardice from you.
- No, you take that back.
- Your daddy wasn't perfect,
but at least he knew.
- James.
- You call yourself
a good Christian,
but look at all the discord
you sow in your own home.
You won't open up your heart
to this woman,
your sister--your sister,
who has done nothing to you,
and who is alone.
And your other sister, Beverly,
the one--the one
you do recognize,
all you do is fight with her,
belittle her,
and make her feel small.
And your own children.
- No.
- Your own children. You--
- Do not bring them into this.
- You are so controlling.
Your own son--he's in love.
He's in love, Baneatta.
And he's still afraid
to tell his mama.
How does that sit right
with you?
We're all human.
Baneatta, we're all human.
And even though your daddy
made a mistake--
a big mistake, I admit it--
it's up to you to decide
how you are going to deal
with his legacy.
So you think on that.
What kind of family
do you want?
[pensive music]
♪
[twangy guitar music]
singers:
♪ Noel
♪
- ♪ The first Noel
♪ The angels did say
♪ Was to certain
poor shepherds ♪
♪ In fields as they lay
singers:
♪ Noel
- ♪ In fields where they lay
♪ Keeping their sheep
♪ On a cold winter's night
♪ That was so deep
singers:
♪ Noel
- ♪ He was born the king
of Israel ♪
singers:
♪ Noel
- ♪ Noel, Noel
♪ Noel, Noel
♪ Noel
singers: ♪ Noel
- ♪ Noel
["Up On the Housetop" playing]
♪
- ♪ Up on the housetop
reindeer pause ♪
♪ Out jumps
good ol' Santa Claus ♪
♪ Down through the chimney
with lots of toys ♪
♪ All for the little ones'
Christmas joys ♪
[music warbles out]
[cheery music]
♪
[doorbell rings]
- Merry Christmas Eve to you.
I take it that you're Mr. Lee.
- That's right.
It's a beautiful day
to celebrate Jesus.
- It sure is.
Please, come inside.
- I'm afraid all that
won't be necessary.
- But the family is all here
and eager
to hear what Daddy left us.
- Unfortunately, you and I
both know that's not true.
And as it stands, you'd be
forfeiting your inheritance.
Those are the rules of the law.
My hands are tied.
However, I heard you cook
a mighty fine Christmas lunch,
and if you were to invite me
back over tomorrow
before the terms expire,
you could gather the missing
pieces of your family,
and we can try this again.
It's up to you.
[sentimental music]
- We would be delighted
to have you join us
for Christmas lunch tomorrow.
You'll love my ham.
- Looking forward to it.
Good day.
- Um. Oh, who was that?
- Who was who?
- That man.
- Beverly, is that all
you ever think about?
- Well, if I'm being honest...[laughs]
- Where's the rest
of your outfit?
- It's a dress.
Besides, this is the kind
of outfit you wear
to snatch a man.
Where did he go?
Oh, oh, oh, okay.
- All right, and blow.
Blow, baby.
[groans]
- Yes! Come on!
Aunt Bev, you know
you forgot your pants, right?
- I did not forget my pants.
I'm so sick of everybody
in this family
talking about my outfits.
No, I'm not wearing pants.
You lucky I'm wearing panties.
Get on my nerves.
Getting on my nerves.
- Is she mad?
- Ma, I told you!
[laughter]
- Oh, my God.
- [clapping]
so we better get moving.
Uh!
[laughs]
Did you bring anything suitable
for outside
a Las Vegas nightclub?
- Just give me a few minutes.
I'm trying to put
something together.
- Been up here all day.
What's this?
- Oh.
LaTrice must have packed that.
- Oh, it's gorgeous.
- You would say that.
- What do you mean by that?
- 'Cause you gave it to me.
- Clearly, you haven't worn it.
- It's just not me.
- Try it on.
- It's not--
- Go on. Try it.
- [sighs]
Okay.
Mm.
[inquisitive music]
♪
- Deacon Scott has been
asking about you.
- Oh, has he now?
[laughs]
- Hear he's on his own
this Christmas.
- I don't feel safe.
- What?
- What have you done
with my sister?
- I just think you deserve
a good man in your life.
See? Gorgeous. Classy.
Any man would be lucky
to have you.
- [sighs]
You know what, this is scary.
I liked you better
when you were a bitch.
- Oh!
[both laugh]
- This is a new day.
I am ready for James'
Christmas Eve service.
Let's get kicking.
[chuckles]
- You know what,
having you as a sister
ain't so bad after all.
All right.
Help me find some shoes.
Let's see,
I've got something in--
Hey.
What's the matter?
- Fine. Everything's fine.
- Baneatta.
- Beverly.
That man at the door you saw...
- Yeah?
- I have to tell you something.
- Okay, what is it?
- Hey, Mom.
- Kenny, I'm talking
to your auntie right now.
- Right.
- Can it wait?
- But, um, Logan is--
- What about him?
- I really care about him.
I mean, I--I more than care
about him.
I--
- Whatever you do
behind closed doors
in your house
is your business.
This is my house.
There are rules, right?
- Mama.
- Right?
- Right.
- Good.
So put on that cute Christmas
sweater I bought for you.
- Okay.
- Some people never change.
- What is that
supposed to mean?
[solemn music]
- You'll figure it out.
- Beverly.
♪
- Oof.
She really got you down, huh?
It's only fun to pick at you
when I know you'll fight back.
- No, I'm tired, sis.
Y'all win.
- Y'all? What did I do?
- No, don't--don't--
don't act innocent, okay?
None of y'all can stand
to see me happy.
- Oh, come on. That's not fair.
- No, no, no, Ma is one thing,
but you not defending me,
that's the same thing.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
When you got that earring,
who stopped Mama
from ripping your ear out?
- You did.
- That's right.
- Mm-hmm.
- And when Mariah Carey came
and played downtown
at the arena,
who took you
after getting tickets?
And I don't even
like that mess.
- You did.
- I'm sorry, say that again?
- Mm-hmm.
So don't be accusing me
of not supporting you.
I love you, Kenny.
- Then I don't get it.
Why don't you like Logan?
- Okay, first of all,
I have been really nice to him.
And second of all,
if you really want to know,
I just don't understand why
all your guys have to be white.
You have never brought home
anyone that looks like us,
and I've always wondered
about that.
Why can't you find happiness
within your own race?
- All right, for the record,
I have dated Black guys.
Just not long enough
for you to meet.
And I don't know,
I think growing up gay
and Black and suppressed,
you learn to idolize the things
that you can see
from inside of your closet,
and the other Black boys,
they can't see each other
from inside of their closet.
So...
I don't know, our first crushes
are the things
that are paraded
in front of our faces,
and that is happy, self-loving,
free-spirited white boys.
I don't know,
without even realizing it,
the world conditioned my taste.
- Whoa. That's something.
- Okay, but that doesn't mean
that I don't love myself
or the men
that I share skin with,
so let's just
cut that notion today.
Okay?
I'm not with Logan
because he's white.
I am with Logan
because nobody
makes me happier.
[heartfelt music]
Can't you--can you find
a way to be happy for me,
just this once?
- Yeah.
[both chuckle]
- Thank you.
And since we're
on the topic of men,
am I supposed to keep
pretending
that I don't notice
that Michael's not here?
I--I promise,
I won't say anything.
- A couple of weeks
after Grandaddy's funeral, I--
I came home from work
and I found Michael...
Banging his new client Melissa
in our bed.
It happened after my promotion.
I started making
more money than him, and...
It seemed like
everything that I did
that made me successful
made him
feel smaller and smaller,
until he couldn't
take it anymore.
I couldn't process it.
That he could do that to me...
When I was taking care of us,
when I wanted us to win.
- God, I'm so sorry.
Simone.
- He took all of the good parts
of me with him.
- No.
No, that's not--
that's not true, Simone.
No, he didn't. Listen to me.
You deserve somebody who
treats you like a queen, okay?
Somebody who brings you
absolute joy.
- Like Logan brings you.
- Yes.
Yes, yes.
Like Logan brings me.
Come on.
God, if--if you're struggling,
you gotta call me.
Okay? 'Cause I'm your brother.
'Cause we cannot end up
like Ma and Aunt Bev.
- No.
- No, no, no, we can't.
- We cannot. Okay?
- No, we can't.
[both laugh]
- All right, so let's just
be better for each other.
Okay?
- Let's.
- Okay.
Okay.
- I love you.
- Give me some of that pie.
- Deacon Scott just called me.
We have a plumbing leak
at the church.
Sounds bad. We gotta go. Now.
- What? Oh, my God.
- Mmm, that's good.
- I know,
it's really great, right?
Okay.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- How bad?
- You remember that time
Miss Ella threw up
during Thanksgiving service?
- Don't remind me.
- Yeah, well,
it's worse than that.
Come on.
- Y'all, stay here.
- Oh, wow, what's going on?
- Are we gonna be able
to have service, Mama?
- Hey, Miss J.
- Have a cookie, Deacon Scott.
- [laughs]
Yes, ma'am.
You know, truth be told,
this be a--
this be an early treat for me,
since I won't be getting
much of a,
you know, Christmas lunch.
You know, uh, just me
at the house, you know, no--
you know,
microwave turkey meal,
something like that, by myself.
- What are you talking about?
Surely you'll be celebrating
with your people.
- No, no, ma'am, they, uh,
they all gone up to Chicago.
You know, I was aiming
to go with them,
but, uh, got a little busy
around here,
so, you know, here I am.
- I insist you come
by the house tomorrow.
- No, no, I couldn't do that.
- Oh, nonsense.
My Daddy treated you
like a son.
Don't you forget it.
You're family.
- Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am.
- Hello. Deacon Scott.
[both laugh]
- Hey. Beverly.
Hello.
[both laugh]
I mean, hello. Yeah.
- Yes. Yes.
- Yeah.
Yeah. How you doing?
- I'm doing just fine,
just fine, just fine.
- Look at you.
Too blessed to be stressed.
- Ooh!
- Too anointed
to be disappointed.
- Ooh, say what, now?
[quirky music]
- All right.
Sure is nice to have you
back in town for the holiday.
- Oh, well, I'm only here
for a few days.
- Yeah.
All right.
Let me ask you something.
Are you--are you a camera?
- Say what now?
- 'Cause every time
I see you,
I smile.
- Oh, that's sweet.
- Yes.
Yes, it's very,
very, very sweet.
- Yeah.
Well, hey, I'ma, um,
I'ma let y'all go ahead
and get out there.
I need to get on back in here
- Yeah, okay.
- All right.
- You better come
by the house tomorrow.
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'll be
by the house tomorrow.
[chuckles]Yeah.
- Yes. Yes.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- See you tomorrow.
- Uh-huh.
Hey, hey--
[imitates camera snapping]
- [laughs]
Oh. Heh-heh.
Oh, God.
I don't remember him
being so extra.
- Oh, he is a good man,
and Daddy loved him.
Isn't that what you said
you wanted?
- You always think you know
what's best for me,
but I don't think he's good
for me anymore, mm-mm.
- As much time as you spend
in the mirror,
I'm surprised you haven't
figured something out.
- What?
- You are not
getting any younger.
Time is ticking.
That is a good man.
- Mama, people are starting
to get restless.
- Where are they going?
- Oh, not all these
God-fearing Christians
looking for an excuse
to go home.
- Like you can talk.
[inquisitive music]
- You know what?
I have an idea.
- I don't have time
to entertain your ideas.
They always make things worse.
- No, no, no, no, Baneatta,
you gotta trust me on this.
It's gonna be so good.
Merry Christmas, everybody.
Merry Christmas.
You know, it's been a long time
since my sister and I
have sung.
- Oh, absolutely not.
[scoffs]
- I will let you sing lead.
- Well, if you insist.
- [laughs]
Okay. There she goes.
Okay. All right.
So--thank you, sir.
All right. All right.
You're a little high.
[both vocalizing]
Ah. Okay.
- ♪ Why don't you
all:
♪ Go, tell it on the mountain
♪ Over the hills
and everywhere ♪
♪ Go, tell it on the mountain
♪ That Jesus Christ is born
- ♪ Over the hills
all: ♪ Over the hills
and everywhere ♪
- ♪ Go to tell it
all: ♪ Go
♪ Tell it on the mountain
- ♪ That Jesus
all:
♪ That Jesus Christ is born
- ♪ Go and tell it
all:
♪ Go, tell it on the mountain
- ♪ Over the hills
all: ♪ Over the hills
and everywhere ♪
- ♪ Go and tell it
all:
♪ Go, tell it on the mountain
- ♪ That Jesus
all:
♪ That Jesus Christ is born
- ♪ He is born
all:
♪ That Jesus Christ is born
- ♪ He is born
all:
♪ That Jesus Christ is
♪ Born
- Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
[laughs]
[cheers and applause]
[indistinct]
Hallelujah!
Hallelujah![laughs]
Whoo, that was good.
- All right.
- Pass the collection plate,quick.
- Jesus is scolding you
right now.
- Jesus--Jesus knows my heart.
- Jesus can save you.
- Saint, everyone, everyone,
I have some
really terrible news.
There's no way
to have a sermon.
[crowd murmuring]
There's a pipe that's busted,
and it's just not safe.
I am so sorry.
Thank you, everyone.
Um, Merry Christmas.
- I need my Christmas Eve
sermon.
- And you shall have it.
Just give us a few minutes.
[inquisitive music]
They need you, James.
- We don't have a church.
- You have a congregation,
and that is all that you need.
People willing to gather
and hear the good word
of the Lord.
These people, our people,
they care, they're here,
and they are ready.
It's a beautiful night.
Daddy used to love
to walk up these steps
every Sunday morning.
It's a sign. I know it.
You'll stand on these steps
and use that mighty voice
that God gave you,
and people will listen.
You'll be wonderful.
I know you will.
- You're right.
- [chuckles]
- You're right, Baneatta.
But it's so dark.
What are we gonna do?
- Bev, girls, come with me.
- Deacon Scott, get my robe.
[heartwarming music]
♪
Y'all can't see it
from my angle,
but you are a most beautiful
congregation this evening.
You look like fireflies
shining your light back on me.
Now, I'm gonna
be honest with you.
I'm gonna be honest with you,
I haven't slept much
this past week.
Becoming your new pastor
has been my complete honor.
But--but--but stepping--
- Okay.
- I say--I say stepping...
- All right.
- Into Bernard's shoes...
all: Yes.
- Has terrified me.
- Uh-oh.
- You're all right, Pastor.
- You see,
over the past two weeks,
I've been racking my brain.
You hear me, folk?
I say, saints,
I've been racking my brain
trying to figure out--
figure out
what the sermon title gonna be.
I was more worried about me
than I was
feeding this congregation
with the mighty word
from the Lord.
[crowd cheers]
So--so the sermon title
this year--
the take-home title this year
is...
[laughs]
- Come on.
- "Ain't No Christmas
Without Christ."
I say hallelujah!
- He is heating up now.
- I say there ain't
no Christmas without Christ.
Say that to one another.
all: There ain't no Christmas
without Christ.
- Hallelujah!
all:
Yeah!
Well, well, well, church.
Church, I--I think our service
has come to its close.
I pray your spirits
are as full as mine is.
But before we depart
the house of the Lord,
I must offer these steps
to anyone
who might want to bring
Christ into their life.
Know that it is never too late.
He is always there for you.
- That's right.
- Yes, he is.
- Might there be anyone?
No one? Well.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I might have--
I might have spoken too soon.
Come on up here, ma'am.
It's never too late
to usher God into your life.
Give this brave soul
a hand, please.
- Amen.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
- Give us your name.
Tell us a little bit
about yourself.
- Hello, everyone.
all: Hello.
- Merry Christmas.
all: Merry Christmas.
- Hey, who is that, Mama?
- I, um--well, when I heard
about this service,
my spirit got real excited.
- Yes.
- And I've, um,
I've driven quite a ways
to be here.
And I almost didn't come, but--
but my heart told me
it was the right thing to do.
- Praise God.
- So I did.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm Brianna.
Brianna Jenkins.
I'm--
I'm Bernard's other daughter.
[crowd gasps]
- Oh, hell no!
- Lord, have mercy. Praise God!
Oh, Lord.
- I didn't mean to cause
the family any--
any harm or anything.
I just wanted to come here
to see my family,
to be with them.
I mean, 'cause it's been--
it's been
a longtime dream of mine.
But when I went to my sister
Baneatta's house earlier
to tell her who I was,
she turned me away.
So I had no other choice
but to come here.
[crowd murmuring]
[tense music]
- Kenny, what is happening
right now?
- Uh, you know as much as I do.
- Say something.
- Listen here, now.
I don't know
what you trying to pull,
but you better stop right now.
- Everyone--
- No!
- Everyone settle down.
- This is the Lord's house.
All are welcome.
This is the Lord's house.
- No way!
- All are welcome.
- Baneatta, you gave
me no choice!
- Baneatta, stop!
- You tell her to stop!
She's the one trying
to ruin Daddy's name
the first Christmas
without him!
- Baneatta, stop!
- No! She is lying!
- I'm not lying!
And I know you know it!
Tell them, Baneatta!
James, please, tell her!
- No!
- Baneatta, it's the truth!
It's the truth!
all:
Whoa!
- Baneatta!
- Did you know about this?
- Do I look like
I knew about this?
- Did Grandma Rita
know about this?
- She couldn't have.
- I can't believe
you let that woman
speak at my Daddy's church
without my permission!
- And I can't believe you would
keep the truth
from the rest of the family!
Would you want someone
to do that to you?
Ignore you?
Erase you,
like you don't exist?
Her showing up at our church
was a final act of desperation.
She's in pain, Baneatta,
and you contributed to it.
I mean, I just preached
on being--
on being devoted
to one another in love,
honoring one another
above ourselves.
That same love
applies here, Baneatta!
Did you ever stop
and put yourself in her shoes?
[apprehensive music]
♪
You can be as mad at me
as you want to be,
but you better make this right,
Baneatta.
You better make this right.
- Don't look at me like that.
You don't know
what I'm going through.
- You're right, Mama, I don't.
But the thing is,
I thought you were better
than this.
- [chuckles]
Heavy is the head
that wears the crown, right?
The crown is heavy on the head.
The--
- Bev.
- The queen--you think
that you're the queen.
You know what
I'm talking about.
You know, you want
to be the queen,
but it's harder
than it looks, right?
- She's ruining Daddy's name.
- Oh, he did that on his own.
- Why would he do that to us?
- To us? To us?
You're taking this personal.
You're take--he--
I loved Daddy.
I did.
I loved him more than anyone.
More than anyone.
But you know the difference
between you and me?
- Please enlighten me.
- I loved him, and he knew
that I loved him
as he was, as a man.
As a man.
You've turned him
into a deity, into a god.
But he's just a man.
Imperfect, messy, crazy,
just like me,
which is why
I was his favorite.
- Ha! Girl.
- The man loved us, sis.
But he was just a man.
But the question is...
Question is,
can you love him now?
Now that you know that he's--
that he's just...
- Like us.
- Just like us. Just like us.
Exactly. Exactly.
You talk about your family
a lot, Baneatta.
But do you love us as we are?
Messy, broken,
learning to be better?
[sentimental music]
- Of course I do.
- Sometimes it doesn't
feel that way.
- I'm sorry.
- I know. I know.
I know.
And--and Brianna,
you're punishing her
for something she didn't do.
Hasn't she been alone
long enough?
- [groans]
- I was a monster!
Mm.
- You--you were.
- I can't show my face
to her again.
- Oh, you can.
- I can't.
- Why not?
- I don't know if I can
let her into my heart.
- You can, and you will.
I've known you my whole life.
You're my sister.
And you can be
a big ol' B sometimes,
but that's because
you want the best for us.
I get that. We get that.
We love you anyway.
You're a good sister, Baneatta.
You're a good sister.
- I am.
- You are.
But don't you tell anybody
I said that or I will deny it.
Tell you what,
I'll go with you.
Let's go fix this together.
As sisters.
- Sisters.
- Oh, it's right down here.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, okay, here we go.
Okay. We're here. Okay.
♪
- Sister!
- Can I help you?
- We'd like you to come
to Christmas lunch tomorrow.
I'd like you to come to lunch.
- That's it? No apology?
- Well, you know what,
apologizing
is not really
her strongest suit.
I mean, these are great steps,
you know, baby steps
all in the right direction.
Trust me, girl.
- An hour ago, you were trying
to attack me in front
of your whole congregation.
- I am so sorry about that.
- You know...
All I really wanted was family.
Sisters.
Be a part of something
bigger than me.
Or at least that's
what I thought I wanted.
And then I met you,
a Jenkins,
and I realized,
if that's what family is,
I don't want any part of it.
- Oh. Oh.
- Oh.
- Come on, let's go.
♪
I know.
[heartwarming music]
♪
- He lied about that too.
This is calm, Mom.
I'm trying my best here.
- Hi, Logan.
- Oh, my God.
Uh, Mom, I gotta go.
Yeah, I--I love you too. Bye.
- Are you not staying?
- I'd like to,
but Kenny loves his mom,
as he should, but she hates me.
So I don't know
how it could work.
- Aunt Baneatta is tough.
Why do you think
I was asking everybody,
"Who is this white boy?"
I was asking because
I wanted the family to see you,
acknowledge you, accept you.
It was never about your color.
It was about how much you meant
to my cousin Kenny.
- That's amazing.
I thought you hated me,
just like everybody else.
- No. No, I don't.
Um, we're basically family now,
but, like, get off me.
- Oh, yeah, sorry.
- Yeah.
- LaTrice, this has been
such a stressful day.
But you somehow just made it
a lot better.
- Hmm.
- Thank you.
- No sweat, white boy.
[chuckles]
- Let me get some
of this butter over here.
Yeah. This here.
I have--
I have not had no cornbread
like this.
I swear, I'm gonna
have to take a nap
and come back for some more.
- [chuckles]
- Mm-hmm.
- Y'all think I'm playing.
Y'all gonna have to roll me
out this house or let me die,
'cause let me tell you
something, this--
this right here?
This is heaven. Okay?
- You are so sweet, Deacon.
[laughs]
- Which one of these plates
is yours, Bev?
- Uh, I made
the Brussels sprouts.
- Oh, I should have known.
Yep.
Sweetest Brussels sprouts
I ever seen,
I'll tell you that.
Yeah.
- [laughs]
Oh, Deacon Scott,
you are too much.
You are really too much.
- That's what they usually
say about you.
- You met your match, Mama.
- Could you pass that ham,
Lenny?
- His name is Logan, Ma!
- Do not use that tone of voice
with me at my table, Simone.
- Yes, yeah, it's your house,
it's your rules, your table,
it's your everything.
But this is also
Grandaddy's house,
where everybody is welcome.
God, I, uh, I'm just happy
he's not here to see
what you turned it into.
- How dare you!
- Baneatta.
[tense music]
- Mm.
You know, yesterday,
an attorney came by the house
and told me that Daddy
left us an inheritance.
- What?
- Well, how much did Daddy
leave us?
- What did we get?
- Nothing.
You all get nothing. Nada.
All he wanted was for our whole
family to get together.
But look at this family.
What a mess.
- And you contributed
to a large part of it.
- And let's call it what it is.
You ran away that girl Brianna.
She's part of our family.
- And I am in pain,
and not once have you noticed,
because all you care about
is yourself.
- I can't believe I've been
working so hard
to make you happy,
when you don't care
about my happiness!
- Your image is more important
than our well-being.
- You're the judgiest bitch
I know.
- I love you, Ma, but you need
to look at yourself
in the mirror before you
come at us like that again.
- You think you are so perfect,
when you have been lying
to the entire family!
- You can be a bitch with us,
but you know who's not here?
Brianna, and that's all on you.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- Look at yourself
in the mirror,
just like you said,
and you know what?
it's your fault, sister.
It is your fault.
[all speaking at once]
- Silence!
You're right.
I have been taking it
all out on you.
I trusted Daddy.
And I'm just hurt.
If he could lie to me
like that, to us, then...
[solemn music]
Anyone can betray us.
And that's terrifying.
♪
I didn't know he could be
that kind of man.
I kept the secret,
and that was wrong of me.
I didn't want you to know
that he was that way.
I tried to protect us.
I know it doesn't make any
sense, but that's the truth.
- Mama, we're all hurting.
Can't you see?
The only way to survive
is to protect each other,
to trust each other.
You take care of our pain,
but we take care of yours too.
And you gotta let us in.
- You're right, my angel.
You are right.
But I don't know
how to do that.
- Look, and--and Granddaddy,
he made a mistake.
Yeah, he messed up.
But he's not that one mistake.
You've gotta remember that.
- The reality is, I feel ugly.
I don't care what Daddy
left behind, his inheritance.
What I care about is,
I hurt this innocent woman,
that I piled more pain
onto her life,
and she didn't deserve that.
I didn't know
I could be so cold.
- Listen to our son, Baneatta.
None of us have to be defined
my our mistakes.
None of us.
- Mama, I know you sharing that
was hard.
So I have something I want
to get off my chest as well.
- What is it, baby?
- Michael and I
are getting a divorce.
- What?
Oh, no.
- Our relationship has been
suffering for a while now.
But I didn't--
I didn't want to be alone.
And I didn't want
to disappoint you.
- Oh.
- No.
- So I tolerated it.
I know how much you love him.
But when Michael
cheated on me...
That was the line,
and he crossed it.
- Simone, I am so sorry, baby.
♪
- [clears throat]
Um, I, um--
Mama, I need
to tell you something.
I am in love with this man.
- Kenny--
- No, no, no, no. No.
I, um, I need you to hear me.
I love you.
I do.
But I also love him.
He is my family.
So you can either accept him--
you can--you can accept us--
Or I'm gonna leave
with him tonight.
And Mama...
I'm not coming back.
Unlike Brianna,
there are no do-overs here.
- Can you bring some hot sauce?
- I'm sorry, Kenny.
- It's fine.
- Ooh, I didn't see
any of this coming.
- Son, son,
you stay where you are.
- No, Daddy, I can't.
I meant what I said. Come on.
[sentimental music]
♪
What is that?
- Your Grandaddy's ring.
This is what you
came here to do, right?
To ask Logan to marry you.
- You knew?
- You didn't think I knew
why you wanted
to talk to your daddy?
Don't you know
mothers know everything?
- Including my name.
[laughter]
- Kenny.
Do you love him?
Kenny, do you love Logan?
- With all my heart.
- Then what are you
waiting for?
♪
[laughter]
- Logan...
Will you do me the honor
of becoming my husband?
- Yes.
[all cheering]
♪
- Oh, man. Welcome.
[all speaking at once]
[lively music]
♪
- We should sing.
We should sing.
- Ready?
- Yeah. Ready? Go.
- ♪ Jingle bells,
jingle bells ♪
both:
♪ Jingle all the way
all:
♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride
♪ In a one-horse open sleigh
- Hey!
- Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
[laughter]
- Stop.
- I told you that!
[doorbell rings]
- I'll get the door.
Brianna.
- Your husband's sermon
really got me thinking.
Truth is, crazy or not crazy,
I didn't come all this way
to leave empty-handed.
- I'm glad to hear that.
- I had years
to think about you.
And I only gave you a day
to take all this mess in.
- Daddy would have been proud
of you to be so forgiving.
It's a Christian value
I'm still trying to get right.
I appreciate your giving us
a second chance.
Join us?
- I thought you'd never ask.
- Well, come right on in.
Come on in. You're home now.
Give me your coat.
I'll take your coat. Hello.
[heartwarming music]
♪
- Family.
Beverly and I would like
to introduce Brianna,
our sister.
- Our sister.
- Welcome home.
- Thank you.
- Well come on.
Let's say hello. Here she is.
- Hi.
- Get over there.
- Come on.
- Nice to see you.
- Oh, wow.
- Hi, Auntie.
- Give her a hug.
- Come, come.
You know what?
Now that we are all
finally together...
- Yes.
- We need to pray.
We are going to pray.
Take a hand.
- Okay. Oh.
- Come on. Come on.
Lord, Lord, I dare say
this is one Christmas
we will never forget.
- Sure won't.
- And as messy as things got,
I truly believe
that we are right
where you would have us to be,
with new traditions
and new family members.
So keep us, keep us,
and let this year's celebration
of your son
be our first of many.
Heavenly Father--
take it, girl.
- Oh. And...
both:
Happy Birthday, Jesus.
- Amen! Amen!
all: Amen.
[laughter]
- Amen!
- And can I say one more thing?
- One thing.
- Daddy, thank you
for my two sisters.
- Aw.
- Baneatta.
- ♪ Home for the holidays
- ♪ Presents
and familiar faces ♪
- ♪ Home for the holidays
- ♪ Heart in hands
and saying our graces ♪
- ♪ Home for the holidays
- ♪ It feels good to be
[doorbell rings]
- We got more guests?
- Okay.
[laughter]
- Well.
It seems like you managed
a Christmas miracle
and gathered the whole family.
- I'm sorry to have brought you
all this way,
but your services
are not needed.
- I beg your pardon?
- We don't care for anything
you have to offer us.
We're good.
It took me a while,
but I finally realized
we have everything we need
and more.
- Everything.
- I'm glad to hear that.
'Cause there is no inheritance.
- Oh. Say what now?
- Okay, well, let me explain.
There was an inheritance,
a small amount of money.
However, the amount of money
left behind
wasn't enough to cover
the costs of my fees.
- I'm sorry,
that makes no sense.
- Your daddy just wanted
to bring his girls together,
and I was so happy to help.
[laughter]
- Wow.
- No. Bernard! Bernard!
[all speaking at once]
- But if I'm being honest,
you Jenkins turned out
to be a lot of work,
so actually, I'm here
to collect the rest of my bill.
Come on.
- Uh, this man is crazy.
- Uh, but, like I said before,
I heard the lunch here
is to die for,
so I'll settle
for some leftovers.
- Man, get on in
and have a seat.
Let me get you a drink.
- Well--well, I can help you
with that appetite.
- Oh, no.
- With the leftovers.
I know where the leftovers are.
I mean, he's cute
and everything,
but I am off men for now.
Right, LaTrice?
- Okay, family,
money or no money,
Daddy played us, but we won.
Because we still got
an inheritance this Christmas--
two new Jenkins.
- Two new Jenkins.
Ooh, I know Daddy's up there
just smiling at us right now.
Oh, yes.
- Oh, I love this song.
- Mm.
- ♪ Come to Bethlehem and see
♪ Him whose birth
the angels sing ♪
♪ Come adore on bended knee
♪ Christ the Lord,
the newborn king ♪
- ♪ Angels we have heard
on high ♪
- Okay!
- ♪ Sweetly singing
over the plains ♪
- ♪ And the mountains
in reply ♪
♪ Echoing their
joyous strains ♪
- ♪ Gloria
all:
♪ In excelsis deo
♪ Gloria
[upbeat rock music]
♪
- No way.
- Let's go. Whoo-hoo!
- Oh!
[laughter]
all:
Oh!
- Oh, Brianna, you are
definitely our sister.
I thought Beverly
was a bad driver,
but you may be worse.
- I think she is worse.
We love you, girl.
[all laugh]
♪