Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
ACEMAKER MOVIEWORKS presents
a LEEYANG FILM production
Executive producer JUNG Hyun-joo
Producer LEE Han-seung
Directed by LEE Kyu-man
The Policeman’s Lineage
Let go!
Son of a bitch!
Stay where you are.
Your head’s next.
Detective!
I’m coming down, please...
Here it is.
Who are you handing this to?
You just saw me come in.
Listen to this guy.
No security cams nearby.
So you came in here
by sheer chance?
Yes.
I’ll count to three.
One.
Two!
Hey, listen, this isn’t yours, right?
Right.
Sir, we should take him in.
Let go, we were staking out
for days for him.
This is next.
Is it yours or not?
It’s mine! That drug is mine!
Witness, please come forward.
As a Seocho Police
Major Crimes officer
you’ve investigated my client
with Det. Sohn Byung-sik,
and you were present at
the crime scene during his arrest.
Is this correct?
Was my client forcibly arrested?
Yes.
Defense rests.
There he comes.
Choi Min-jae!
Backstabbing bastard!
Easy, easy!
Don’t do this here,
take it easy.
I understand who you are,
I do, but I’m still dumbfounded.
You go on ahead.
It was a month-long stakeout,
stupid bastard...
- I’ll arrest him again...
- Shut your mouth.
Lay low and come back
when things die down.
Choi Min-jae.
You’re the only one just?
That’s what I’m saying!
Why are you so anal?
Stay outside for a while and go home.
All right.
Oh yeah, Choi.
Internal Affairs wants you.
Choi Min-jae?
We’re from the Metro.
This is Det. Hwang In-ho,
Internal Affairs section chief.
Major Crimes, Choi Min-jae, sir.
I called you here for a favor.
Yes, sir.
We’d like you to covertly
carry out an internal investigation.
Police Record: Park Kang-yoon
Go after a cop, you mean?
Is this an order?
It’s nothing like that,
the decision is yours.
Then I’d like to decline.
This is dishonorable.
It’s also outside of my duties.
My apologies,
I’ll head out.
A cop died because of
this incident.
Honor of the police
is on the line.
We must get to the bottom of it
before it gets out.
Ever heard of Investigation Unit’s
Park Kang-yoon?
He’s a major player at Metro.
His specialty is intel gathering.
From gangs, drugs to gambling,
he’s got informants at every level.
He’s simply unrivaled.
Heard about the Wonju
factory drug bust 3 years ago?
Yes, I remember.
Wasn’t it a joint op
between NIS and narcos...
It looked that way,
but Park did that alone.
New Drug Distribution Gang Arrested
It’s possible,
if he crossed the line.
Roundup of New Gang 21st Century Clan
We believe that Park is backed
by a special organization.
He’s given tens of thousands
of dollars to investigate,
which are all from unknown source.
So how does the death
of a cop fit into this?
We had a man in his unit
digging into him.
Sgt. Lee Myung-ju,
he was killed.
We believe that he instigated
Lee’s death after finding out,
and destroyed the evidence.
Which means, a cop had
another cop killed.
Why me, sir?
Why did you become a cop?
My...
father walked this path.
I wanted to follow...
That’s it, lineage.
Grandfather, Choi Eul-young,
father, Choi Dong-su, and you.
Three generations of cops.
A cop’s blood flows in you.
Your father passed away
in the line of duty, no?
Yes, sir.
Everyone knew the man
who dissolved the 3-Way clan.
Is that so?
But his on the job death
was never acknowledged?
No, sir.
Did you know there is
a secret report on him?
I’ll share it with you
after this detail.
He took a child hostage!
Min-jae, it’s your dad.
I heard he was a cop.
Jeon Yong-bae!
This is Choi Dong-su!
Let’s talk, okay?
Let your daughter go,
take me instead.
Good to see you.
This bitch tried to kill me
with poison...
Jeon, please don't do this.
Mister...
Please let me go,
someone’s taking my child...
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
No!
Dad! No!
This was your father's.
Internal Affairs
Hwang In-ho
Hello, this is Choi Min-jae.
Sir, it was an order
from the section chief...
What are you doing?
Put the mask back on.
I could be hunted down, sir.
Take him.
Detective, sir!
You don’t know
what they’ll do!
He exploits the media like this.
Customs Agent Killed
Colleague For Drugs
But there’s someone
who’s driving Park crazy.
Na Young-bin,
I’m sure you’ve heard of him.
CEO of Mirae Corp.
3 convictions for production
and distribution of illegal drugs
He comes from money,
studied overseas.
He doesn’t need to do this,
but he’s got the smarts.
From politics to media,
his connections are limitless.
Park arrested Na 3 times,
but Na got away every damn time.
No wonder Park’s pissed.
Here, the one handing over
the bag is Cha.
The one receiving it
is presumed to be Park,
but we only got this shot
from his back.
Why is Park protecting Cha?
Cha is a small fish
compared to Na,
and not as meticulous.
And he puts up with Park.
Which means,
with Na locked up,
Park can do whatever he wants,
with Cha as his front.
Cha has been expanding
to the Japanese market
when Na got out.
This is our chance to get Park.
Who’s the victim?
The customs agent whom
Park put in front of the media.
Son of a...
Which way?
Jesus!
Out of the way.
What are you doing?
Park, you’re amazing.
You used a man’s life
as a bait for your case.
Pardon?
What happened?
It must be Na Young-bin.
He was released recently,
and started cutting his tails.
Everything’s Na to you,
what about Cha?
I heard he’s flexing
his muscles overseas.
I was told that Cha’s clan
has been disbanded.
So you’re cleaning up the mess
out of pure sorrow?
Chief Han.
If it wasn’t for us, you wouldn’t
have known about Na’s return.
If you’re gonna eat
my crumbs, do it quietly.
Are you serious?
I’ve had it with you!
Come on!
It’s barely been a month
since Na got out.
Sort this out before
shit hits the fan, got it?
Of course, sir.
Bring me something
to lock him up for good!
Yes, sir.
I’ll give you 10 days.
Sir.
I’ve assigned you
to Park’s unit.
Remember, you can
never be exposed.
Det. Choi Min-jae?
Chief’s desk over there,
captain’s over here.
And this is yours.
Thank you.
Put your bag down and report in.
Yes, sir.
My name is Choi Min-jae.
Good to meet you all.
Here.
Investigation expenses,
absentee logs.
Good luck!
I’ll do my best, sir.
Good!
What’ll help you adapt
and endure here?
In the end, it’s men.
No matter how difficult things get,
the man beside you will help.
I’ll remember that, sir!
Wait, hold up.
We have to head out soon,
cuff this fat bastard up,
he might wake up later.
Don’t have a pair yet?
Not yet, sir.
This bastard’s a weirdo.
Wait!
Who’s this asshole?
Sing a song.
Like this?
Then just stand there.
Make sure to dance too,
don’t spoil the mood.
Go on.
Uh, all right.
I’ll do my best.
One, two, three, four!
Be careful of
those cherry lips
- Be careful of those...
- Stop, stop, stop!
- Good morning.
- Sir.
Salute.
You should continue.
You know those
passport counterfeiters?
They opened up a shop
in Ahyun district.
- Make note of it.
- Thank you, boss!
Damn...
Choi Min-jae,
you’re with me.
Pardon?
You’ll keep him around?
Hey, hey, hey!
- Stay with him.
- Okay...
Get changed first.
Come on.
Sir?
Drive, Cheongdam district.
Yes, sir.
Deputy Manager Choi.
Me, sir?
Wanna be ‘Supervisor’?
No, chief.
Don’t call me that,
call me ‘boss’.
Don’t sound like a cop
out here.
Yes, boss.
Okay, give me
a rundown of you.
Yes, boss.
Born in 1990, majored law,
graduated the academy in 2015,
worked in Major Crimes
before my transfer here.
My hobbies are judo, tennis,
currently single.
I knew your father.
My father?
We had a history.
I didn't know.
My boss is out at the moment...
Good to see you, Mr. Kwon.
You startled me...
Why did you suddenly...
Who is he?
You’ll get to know him.
I’m Kwon Ki-ahn.
Choi Min-jae,
deputy manager.
You’re a cutie
with terrible manners.
You got a bark in you.
Na didn’t contact you?
I cut all ties with him,
you know that.
I got coffee, have some.
What’s Na’s product?
Something new?
Don’t be like that,
I really don’t know.
Several men are dead,
including a customs agent.
My company thinks
it’s a big case.
If you don’t cooperate,
it’ll get difficult for you.
When I think about that asshole,
I feel like shit, that’s all...
I heard the business was bad,
you got into retail too?
What’s with you today,
you’re embarrassing me!
What’s got into you...
You’re under arrest
for illegal substance abuse.
Mr. Choi, could you step outside?
But chief...
Go outside.
I really don’t know anything
about some customs agent...
I only heard that he was
gathering potential investors.
Money?
He needs money?
I heard he bought an expensive
license to a new technique.
It’s expensive enough
to buy Major Leaguers.
I’m serious,
that’s all I heard.
Please believe me,
look at my eyes, please!
Okay, understood.
Are we gonna overlook
his needle marks?
We don’t go after small timers.
Kwon may be a junkie,
but he’s got good ears.
It’s better to use him
as an informant.
Did you receive the key?
She changed it to a keypad,
28487898.
Asshole.
Don’t be scared, I drank
a barrel when I got in.
Stay frosty.
So? Was it cool
accompanying the chief?
I’m not sure yet.
Where did you go?
A furniture shop in Cheongdam.
So you were there
when he met his informant?
Yes.
Kiddo, the thing about
informants is,
you don’t tell anyone
about them.
Not even your wife.
Do you know what I’m saying?
I’m so jealous!
Hazing is still a thing?
It’s a tradition, sir.
It’s been too long
since we got a new member.
All right, let’s drink.
Go!
- Go!
For Unit 3!
Go on, kiddo.
Here.
Grow some balls.
You still got a long way to go.
Pour!
Get over here.
You're driving.
Drink!
17:20, Cheongdam furniture shop.
A front for loan shark Kwon Ki-ahn.
Park let his substance abuse slide,
to presumably receive intel on Na.
Considering Park and Kwon’s relationship,
a partnership with Cha is feasible.
21:05, arrived at Banpo home.
Thanks.
Come here starting
tomorrow morning.
Okay, good night.
Good night.
170cm wide.
170...
125cm long.
125?
That’s the window measurement
without the frame.
Depending on his shoes,
there may be some discrepancies.
Between 184 and 185.
Between 184 and 185...
Height: 184.5cm
And his ear...
This is close to a 90% match.
It’s hard to be this close.
Yes, sir?
Where are you?
I’m almost there, sir.
Come up when you get here.
The passcode is my license plate.
Yes, sir.
- You’re here?
- Sir.
I’m gonna wash up,
so change into that.
Right.
- Size okay?
- Yes.
- You look good in it.
- Thank you.
Are we going
somewhere in this?
Isn’t it obvious?
To work.
Consider it your work uniform.
Grab these jackets
and a watch too.
But sir...
Too much?
My salary is hardly enough
to buy any of these...
It’s from the top,
so don’t worry.
The top?
Let’s call them
key players of this society.
Including a few Metro Police brass.
No need to feel nervous,
just focus on work.
Chief, could I change my tie?
Pick whatever you want!
Na Young-bin
Why do we need suits
to catch criminals?
Never faced the super rich?
They only deal with
top 1% of society.
You can’t go near them
in a jacket you wore earlier.
Why do we take that into account?
We have to meet them
to catch them.
They use money
to keep us far away.
Without a warrant,
you can’t even get close.
Consider it your uniform.
Yes, sir.
Mercedes was paid entirely in cash.
One-year lease and deposit
for luxury apartment paid in cash,
funding source unconfirmed.
Sir, you can’t park here,
move along please.
I’m an on-duty officer.
I’ve never seen
a police Mercedes, sir.
Pardon me.
He’s a cop.
Vehicle Restoration
A few days ago,
one of Cha’s cars
was totaled and brought in.
It’s true that Cha is
working with Yakuza.
He must be trying to
push out Na for good.
If there’s no game in town,
he will create one.
Send me this photo,
got the plate number too?
Sorry for everything
and thank you.
- Take care.
- See you.
No contact with Cha yet,
but the man in the photo
is presumed to be Park.
Na’s investigation is carried out alone.
So is the Sgt. Lee murder case,
and his team is left out of the loop.
A private safe was found in his study.
Contents unknown.
I’ll submit a separate report
in the future...
Could I take your...
Na was released recently.
So how much more
do you need?
$500,000 should do.
This year’s expense rose
quite sharply.
Is it because Na
causing problems?
He’s a poisonous fungus.
I know you’re doing your best.
And you’re right,
he’s a poisonous fungus.
He must be removed
before he spores.
Yes.
He jacked up the cover,
and raised the barrier.
I’ll use the money
for the informants,
and cut down my
investigation expenses.
No, you have a reputation
to maintain.
Sponsorship is there
to be spent on the field.
I’ll talk to the elders
and send it right away.
My apologies...
It’s quite all right.
So it is from higher ups...
But why’d a cop...
Chief Park Kang-yoon
Yes, chief.
Sorry to bother you on the weekend,
but I need your help.
Right away, sir.
Good to see you.
What you asked for.
It’s nice to see you so often.
If you miss the deadline,
get me a gun, okay?
Kidding.
Whenever you need money,
make sure to call me first.
- Drive.
- Yes, sir.
Oh yeah, I got a gift for you.
This has a discreet camera
and you can record the footage
on your phone,
the quality is incredible.
I gave it a spin,
it’s stunning!
You’ll feel like a spy,
James Bond!
Forget the gift,
put it on my tab.
Catch plenty of bad guys!
Salute!
Boss...
Should you borrow so much
from a loan shark?
Why? Scared that
you’ll get shit stained?
I can pay back quickly,
watch and learn.
But even so that much is...
Investigation Unit had a cop
named Sgt. Lee Myung-ju.
The murdered cop?
The perp who stabbed him
is supposedly inside.
Under Na’s roof, cool, huh?
Is that true?
It was an expensive intel.
If it’s wrong,
I’ll fuck up the informant.
Isn’t there a membership
to these events?
Guess how much.
$30,000 maybe?
Depending on credit
$200,000 to 600,000 annually.
A non-member cover
is $20,000 for a day.
We’re closed today.
I’m not here for the club,
I came to see Mr. Na.
It’s a private event.
If you do not have a warrant,
please move along.
Piss off.
Walk away while you can.
Here, cover fee.
I came to play poker,
he’s my bodyguard.
Chief Park is coming in.
Mid-30s, about your height,
he has a scar on his right ear.
I’ll be at the poker table.
Scan Na’s associates
and slip out to the back.
Text me if you find him.
I understand.
Mr. Na, it’s been a while.
As you can see,
the table’s full.
So I should just go?
But we’re friends.
I’ll wait.
I fold.
I fold too.
Fold.
Mr. Kim, leaving already?
Jesus Christ...
Terrible manners.
Sit if you’re gonna play poker
quietly and leave,
or piss off.
He’s heading up.
Oh my...
Mr. Na.
Too bad for you, Det. Park.
Jang, did you suck him dry?
Bring me some more chips.
$50,000
It was great today,
thank you.
No, this is expensive stuff...
I can’t wait any longer.
I’m sorry.
It’s all right.
... a scar on his right ear.
Found him.
Okay, thank you.
My, my.
Mr. Na, what are you
up to nowadays?
Give me a business card.
I don’t have stuff like that.
I’m officially unemployed.
I heard you started
a venture business.
I got bad credit,
no money whatsoever.
It sounds so awkward to
hear that you’re penniless.
Give me your phone number.
I’m told this is a cordial event.
No reason not to give me yours.
Happy?
Remember him?
National ID: Lee Man-seok
Lee Man-seok, you’re under arrest
for the murder of Lee Myung-ju.
What are you doing?
You’re guests here.
Touch me again, I’ll arrest you
for obstruction of justice.
Are you thugs or cops?
Hey, that’s enough.
Pull your men back.
Let them go.
He confessed.
Motive?
It looks to be a simple robbery.
No gang affiliation
and no known grudges.
An inspector was killed
in a simple robbery?
And the perp’s employer
is Na Young-bin?
Not feeling well?
Get someone else?
No, sir.
Get him to fess up
by Monday morning.
Understood, sir.
Det. Choi!
Good work.
So Intelligence Unit 2 chief
is providing the funds?
Yes, if the fund source
is internal,
I don’t know if it’s
a cause for concern.
And Sgt. Lee’s killer,
Chief Park caught him himself.
That’s more suspicious.
Why?
This is confirmed to be Park, right?
Yes.
Aside from the sponsorship,
prove that he took Cha’s dirty money.
Didn’t you say he borrowed
money from Kwon too?
We need irrefutable evidence,
rather than suspicion.
What you see isn’t everything.
It’s an intense speed boat race!
Of the 6 boats, #3 and #5
are leading the charge!
#3’s Bae and #5’s Kim,
they’re on their final lap!
#3! Come on!
#3 vs. #5! It’s close!
#3!
The gap with the pack is widening!
They turned the final corner,
#3’s Bae Hyemin
and #5’s Kim Jong-min!
They’re fast approaching
the finish line!
Come on! Catch up!
#3 and #5 are at the finish line!
Neck and neck race
ends with #5 on top!
Come on!
Please keep your ticket
until the final decision.
Boss, didn’t we finish first?
- #3.
- #3!
Yeah, Bae Hyemin!
We did it! We won!
I saw him finish first.
Can we have a feast tonight?
No can’t do,
gotta repay my debt first.
The gambling debt from Kwon?
Better me than gamblers here,
so the money is used
for the public good.
Over there.
Loan repaid in full.
No evidence of bribery
or conspiracy with Kwon.
No defraudation for
personal gain found.
No proper contact with Cha.
Chief!
Is this also part of
your sponsorship?
No, this is my treasure #1
with a 20-year loan.
I’m going to live here
when I retire.
I’ll float around
and fish for life.
It’s a bit small for that.
I’ll have less physical
and material baggage by then.
A sleeping bag, dishware,
a camping stove and booze.
Be careful.
Holy cow!
Cool, huh?
Whoa!
That’s what I’m talking about.
- Chief.
- Yeah?
You said you knew my father.
You really don’t remember?
What do you mean?
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Let me go!
That’s my dad!
No! Stop!
I never thought
you’d become a cop.
I was so proud of him
when as a kid.
But...
after those incidents...
I became suspicious of him...
And resented him
for letting it happen.
So I wanted to know
what being a cop entailed.
When I transferred to Bangbae
it was January.
An old drug addict froze to death
by the police station wall.
It was my father.
An addict and an ex-con.
He probably came looking for me.
I was so ashamed of him
that I held his funeral
without ever telling my colleagues.
I don’t know how he found out,
but he came to the funeral.
Sgt. Choi Dong-su.
That’s who your father was.
Just don’t become a cop.
Never.
Can I ask you
more about him?
Don’t rush it,
I’ll tell you little by little.
Nothing’s biting,
let’s call it a day.
Name:
Park Kang-yoon
Seoul Metro Police
Investigation Unit
Final Report
...no evidence of embezzlement,
or illegal slush fund for investigation...
Na Young-bin
These are videos of
Na’s investor meetings.
Cross reference it
with today’s attendees,
ID everyone you can.
Once verified, figure out
their relation to Na,
criminal records, financials,
recent business transactions,
and any notable figures
they’re in close contact with.
Most importantly,
get their numbers.
Report to me when you do.
Yes, sir.
I need to get my stuff,
stand by here.
Yes, sir.
Section Chief Hwang
Something wrong?
No, behind us...
It’s probably nothing.
Back it up.
You’re charged with violation
of code of conduct, get out.
Give us a tour of your home.
I heard you’re well off.
Why not.
Sir.
What’s going on?
I wrote in my report that
there aren’t any problems.
I’m the one who decide.
Don’t worry, I’ll make sure
you’re not exposed.
So?
Should we open it,
or will you?
Open it.
What the hell?
There are only contracts.
Okay, we’re done here,
take him away.
This way.
Who’s your source?
I’ve told you already.
I received sponsorship.
From whom?
Yeonnam Association?
Sir, can you take the heat?
I could never take heat
for that much money.
That money can’t be clean.
Is there such a thing
as clean money?
I have no problem stripping
your uniform immediately.
But one man behind bars
isn’t good enough.
I’m going to uproot
your entire organization.
Sure, do your thing.
Sponsorship? Right,
they really like to spurge.
But don’t you know they’ll
use you and toss you out.
You’re just a prop to them.
You’ll use that money
to catch criminals?
Those who ignore principles
and laws and accept dirty money
are corroding the entire
police organization.
You’re a disgrace to
all the honest cops.
Do you actually think
what you’re doing is just?
I don’t care what others think,
cops are only cops when
we catch perps and close cases.
I heard you let your
child’s killer walk free.
You fucking trash!
Listen.
Let’s just do our jobs.
I’ll stick to investigation,
and you pretend to be a cop,
and go after hard-working
police officers, got that?
You are a tumor.
You must be removed
with a scalpel.
Try it, if you can.
Sir, you got a phone call.
Let’s see how long
you remain on top.
- Back?
- Yes, sir.
What happened?
Uh, the thing is...
they ambushed us, so...
That’s all?
Yes...
Call me with updates.
Yes, captain.
Choi Min-jae.
If you were by his side,
you should’ve watched him.
Right...
It’ll be in the 2nd report.
Financial, call records, wiretaps,
we gotta be thorough, sir.
Laying down the charge
won’t be a problem.
We’re close to uncovering
the Yeonnam...
What exactly is the reason?!
My apologies, sir.
But this time we have to...
Choi Min-jae
Come to the diner,
contingency meeting
Ma’am, could you leave us?
Get the shutter.
What are you up to?
Did something happen?
Why do you think
we called you here?
Hur, stay out of this.
Come here.
Min-jae, let me ask you
a serious question.
We’re not 100% certain,
but there’s a rumor going around.
Are you the mole?
Why can’t you talk?!
Are you the mole
who backstabbed our chief?!
Asshole, is that true?
Search him.
One second...
Bastard...
Your fingers will break.
Let go!
I’ll break them!
What’s going on?
They worked us.
It looks like Internal Affairs
planted him.
Everyone out except Min-jae.
Let’s go.
What was the reason?
Promotion?
It’s nothing like that.
So? What are my charges?
I concluded my report
with no charges laid.
Let me ask you something.
Internal Affairs and
my orders contradict.
Who will you follow?
Listen, you’re in my team
and we are a unit.
So you just have to
follow my order.
Even if it breaks rules
and deemed illegal?
Going after perps can’t be illegal,
no matter the situation and method.
It’s about choosing
to become a real cop,
or a bureaucrat.
There will be a time
you’ll be forced to choose.
I’ll follow the call of the police.
This does not change
you and I.
But things will be difficult
at the office for a while.
My report won’t have any effect?
Chief paid Kwon back in full.
Or is there other charges
that I don’t know about?
Park’s charges...
Are you protecting that bastard?
Sir.
Did you know Park
served under your father?
I knew.
What about his mother,
who committed suicide?
Your father locked up Park’s
father for substance abuse,
and his mother killed herself
from the shock.
Did he tell you that?
Your father checked in on him
while he was in the system.
Maybe he felt responsible,
or sympathetic.
When Park became a cop,
he joined your father’s team.
Like a foster son.
As promised...
your father’s record.
Sgt. Choi Dong-su
Investigation Report
Joined Yeonnam, a Private
Organization Within the Police
Superintendent Seo Joong-ho
It was your father’s.
Ever heard of Yeonnam?
What is that?
It started when Yeonnam district
was established in Western Seoul.
There was a time when cops
took donations to investigate.
They didn’t even have
gas money to do their jobs.
Police agency was shit poor.
When they had to travel
without any money,
they were still expected
to perform.
Some cops gave up
and let criminals go,
while others spent their
own money to investigate.
That’s how Yeonnam got started.
They gathered sponsors,
donations and managed them,
it became an organization
operating in secrecy.
In other words, it’s illegal.
At first their work produced
results and praises.
But still water is bound to rot.
The donation pooled
to be spent on investigation
became allowances
and slush funds,
and they took bribes for
going easy on syndicates.
Stop it!
Later, it became hard to
discern cops from criminals.
Your father and Park
were prime examples.
In other words,
he created Park.
Breaking laws and acting
without oversight,
he learned them all
from your father.
That can’t be.
I hear your father
became a junkie too.
Dad!
- Dad!
- No!
Dad!
So many needle marks...
I’m sorry to say, it’s true.
Undercover methods back then
were very primitive.
The best cover was to
become an addict himself.
His killer was a Yeonnam affiliate,
until he became an addict.
If your father wasn’t murdered,
he’d have shared the same fate.
With enough support,
they want absolute obedience.
Before the media got
ahold of this story,
Yeonnam was covered up internally.
Then someone lit the fire
on Yeonnam again.
Park was the fire starter.
Is that why you sent me?
You calculated that
Park’d take me in
because I’m Choi Dong-su’s son?
Without digging into the soil,
one can’t uproot the weed.
I’m done with this,
do what you will.
Who do you think led
your father to his demise?
It’s Yeonnam.
Park is ripe for picking.
Na is no easy foe,
and the sponsorship alone
can’t lead to his arrest.
Next step is obvious.
Cha is his ace in the hole,
and he will use it soon.
Think carefully.
This is our last chance
to right the wrong.
Choi Min-jae, you’re a cop,
don’t forget that.
Prove that you’re
not like your father.
Get over here at once,
starting stakeout
Yeah, I understand.
Got it, good work.
Please!
I’ll pay you back
within this month!
If you got money to burn,
you gotta pay me back first.
If you spurge on everything,
when will you pay back?
You still managed to send
kids overseas to study.
Them, right?
No, not that,
please, I can’t!
I really can’t!
Please, don’t do this!
Will you look at that...
You made 2 calls
to Na each time.
Is it against the law
to call him?
Of course not.
Then why are you
doing this?
You have an illegal loan
business at gambling dens,
and opened up shops
to sell drugs to youths,
and facilitated sex trade,
those are illegal though.
This is abuse of
police authority!
Filthy piece of shit.
Did you bring a warrant?
You didn’t?
Listen up.
You said Na started a venture,
what exactly is that?
What? What are you
talking about?
- What the hell?!
- Hold on, asshole.
Hold still, you son of a bitch!
If you move,
you’ll lose your chin.
Can’t you let me
in on the secret?
Stay the fuck back.
That’s enough, chief.
If you get in my way,
it means you can die
by my hands, got that?
Yes, venture! You’re so right!
He’s starting a venture!
Let me tell you about it!
He’s producing drugs!
- Producing drugs?
- Drugs!
- Here?!
- In Ansan!
- You sure?!
- I’m sure!
Chief, it sounds legit.
What happened was,
I attended Na’s investor meeting.
What he said was fantastic.
It was a sexy proposition.
You may all know already,
you’ll take home
as much as you put in.
Whether intentional or not,
if you leak anything,
you and your family
will be in great danger.
All right.
Let’s start with samples.
The ingredients have been approved.
When they mix with
caffeine in coffee,
that’s when you get high,
it’s revolutionary.
Na bought the rights
to the mixing technique.
To regulate this psychotropic drug,
it’ll take at least 3 years.
Why?
It’s hard to tell whether
this powder alone is a drug.
When mixed with coffee,
there’s no odor at all.
That’s why he disguised it
as a coffee roaster.
It’s the perfect front.
If it’s distributed all over,
kids get high while
drinking coffee and hanging out.
Getting a warrant
is impossible.
It’s legal in a constitutional country.
Detective, I’ll stitch you up
in no time.
Yong, you’ll have to help us.
You’re a funny guy,
you want me to die?
Or rot away for 5 years.
You can’t handle the cover.
How much?
$2 million is my cut.
It’s not much compared to others,
but I got off the bandwagon.
I got no cash to spare.
So? Will you front the cover?
Yes.
Dad.
Just don’t become a cop.
What, man?
Shit, you’re so childish...
There are other ways
to catch a mole.
Goddammit...
So what then?
- Drop the case.
- What?
Wait, sir!
Authorized Personnel Only
What can you do with
a rejected warrant?
Who’s blocking this?
What are you implying?
You got no evidence,
it’s all based on a testimony.
It’d be strange
if a warrant was issued.
So who’s the one
blocking this warrant?
Jesus...
All right, then submit a report
on how you got this intel.
We got a lead...
about passport counterfeiters
leaving for the Philippines.
Why don’t you take on this case?
We got a quota to fill.
Let’s get the counterfeiters first.
Mole
Head to Namsan.
It’ll be tough this time.
Is something wrong?
We received an order.
Can’t I get a partial funding?
It’s not about the money,
but a problem of will.
Just like rejecting the warrant?
That’s the situation we’re in.
Is it because of
Chairman Kim’s son?
All households have
a problematic child.
No amount of scolding
will do the trick.
With some time,
he’ll pull out.
But it’ll stir trouble
if you ambush them now.
Look the other way on this,
you got bigger things to do.
No.
A new type of drug could
flood the country in no time.
If they hit hard and pull out,
there won’t be a next time.
Park Kang-yoon.
You’re being dramatic.
The decision has been made.
Chairman Kim is Yeonnam’s
biggest supporter.
Cheongdam furniture shop.
- To Kwon’s office?
- Yeah.
For operation fund?
I’ll use it to get in,
then return it.
By winning the speed boat race?
I can do far worse.
Drive.
Yo, where’s Kwon?
He’s abroad.
He took off running?
No, he travels abroad regularly...
You laugh?
Did you just laugh? Huh?
Are we some kind of thugs!
Is Cha the only option left?
Watch your mouth.
What about Yeonnam?
They won’t back you?
Yeonnam? Is that
what Hwang fed you?
Come on, chief.
One must find a rightful option,
why must you resort
to an illegal option?
Can we do our jobs without
getting our hands dirty?
Are you saying nothing is illegal
when going after criminals?
What exactly is the call
of the police you speak of?
Listen up.
Us cops are always
standing over the boundary.
We can’t be black nor white.
- Is that even possible?!
- It is!
So long as people
support our work,
we can stand above the gray zone.
At times, they will push us
towards the black.
That’s being a cop.
If you can’t do that,
just quit.
That’s just it!
This is precisely why my father
didn’t want me to be a cop!
Yeah? That’s weird.
He suggested that
I become one.
A cop who could
move the world.
So Na is finally going down.
Damn.
I couldn’t even shit properly
because of that bastard.
A few days ago,
my fortuneteller said
I’ll live a long life.
That’s fine and all,
but he said I’ll outlive Na.
So I asked him
how he knew that.
He said he saw Na’s fortune too.
Fucking hell.
What do you think I did?
What did you do?
I buried him!
What are the chances of him
seeing both me and Na?
I got the chills and thought
maybe he was trying to bury me.
Have you forgotten, asshole?
I’m a cop.
Why?
Gonna lock me up?
Go ahead.
I’ll have to get your loan back
from jail then, bro.
Don’t call me that.
Bring it.
I put a GPS tracker
on the bottom of the bag.
Choi, come with me.
Give this to him.
Fine, after this job,
leave my unit.
Go back to your team, good?
Oh my.
Good job putting together
$2 million.
Protect that money.
If we don’t recover this,
we’re all dead.
The rabbit is going in.
Copy, standing by.
Choi Min-jae.
I expect big things.
I had some money stashed away!
Perfect timing, huh?
$2 million!
Out?
Safe, just barely.
Safe!
Safe...
The rabbit is inside.
I’ll now activate the machine.
Raising both of your hands
will be our signal.
Signal us only after
the final product is out.
No mistakes.
Boss, cops are here!
Park Kang-yoon, that asshole...
Turn the machine off.
Pardon?
Turn it off.
Yes, right away.
Attention please.
It’s the police.
Easy, don’t worry.
You’ll now witness
your top dollars at work.
They’re simply imported
coffee ingredients, right?
- Yes.
- That’s right.
Cops don’t have a warrant.
No evidence either, right?
But why is the police coming?
All units, we got the signal.
Move in, move in!
Go.
Son of a...
Bring him.
Come on, Mr. Na!
Can’t I adjust my hair?!
Don’t move!
Everyone freeze!
Stay where you are!
Get back in! Now!
Don’t move!
Against the wall!
Stand against the wall!
Show me your warrant.
Na Young-bin,
you’re under arrest for
production of an illegal substance.
What illegal substance?
This isn’t drug...
Det. Ahn.
Chief, nothing came out yet.
Switch it on.
Yes, sir.
It’s got a passcode lock.
Where’s the code generator?
Who knows...
Where the hell is it?
You son of a bitch.
Don’t move!
I swallowed it, asshole!
Do Not Enter
Wait till I shit it out tomorrow!
Get back! Don’t move!
- Det. Ahn.
- Yes, sir.
Who are you?
Stab him!
That bastard saw my face,
stab him!
Chief Park
- Arrest him.
- Yes, sir.
Buddy.
You made that yourself,
don’t forget.
Come on out.
See you again.
Get over here.
Chief,
I don’t see Min-jae.
The entry was chaotic...
Hey, Choi Min-jae!
Min-jae!
You okay?
Are you all right?
Get up!
He’s conscious,
get the EMT!
Yes, sir!
Lee Myung-ju... Lee...
- Ear...
- What?
Chief!
Sir...
The rabbit is gone.
A drug producer disguising
narcotics as coffee was arrested.
Over $100 million in cash
was found on the scene,
and the police is focusing
on the source of this money.
Drug Org’s Connection to
Daeho Group Heir
I told Park not to stir trouble.
He wasted our business funding.
It’s likely he took money
from the Yakuza.
The Internal Affairs is digging
into us due to this incident.
Park Kang-yoon...
I don’t know how to thank you.
Not at all, sir.
We should’ve paid
more attention, my apologies.
Since this case is related
to the death of an officer,
the Internal Affairs is
keeping eyes on it.
Chairman, I’m sorry
to bring this up but...
I was thinking of sending him
to Europe somewhere...
Yes, I’ll make arrangements.
It’s time to dump Park.
Cha
Yes?
Yo, bro! Come by!
We gotta celebrate
Na’s grand exit!
I told you not to call me that.
It’s a cause for celebration.
Is it because of
the runaway money?
Yakuza is already talking
about gutting you,
I’m barely holding them back.
Bro, I got a proposition
that’ll wipe away your debt.
You won’t be able to refuse.
I heard you’re getting a medal.
You’re a made man.
Hardly.
This is what you asked for.
The knife wielder who was
charged with Sgt. Lee’s murder.
He had a scar when I arrested him,
but not in the photo.
The fucker who stabbed me
also that the scar.
And Sgt. Lee’s killer,
Chief Park caught him himself.
That’s more suspicious.
For operation fund?
I can do far worse.
If you get in my way,
it means you can die
by my hands, got that?
Hey, what are you doing?
Where will you go?
Yes?
Tick, tock, time’s running out.
I know.
I thought you couldn’t come out
because of a rat outside your place.
Who?
The kid you hung out with,
he’s guarding the door.
You should’ve called ahead.
How are you feeling?
Fine, sir.
That’s good.
The guy who stabbed me
at the factory...
had a scar on his earlobe.
And this is the perp we caught
at Na’s gambling joint.
This was taken only a month ago.
He doesn’t have the earlobe scar.
And he’s in final stage of cancer.
He recently received
a large deposit to his account.
So?
Sgt. Lee Myung-ju...
You killed him.
And to cover up the murder,
you created a fake,
and arrested him.
No?
If I tell you,
will you believe me?
What about the $2 million
you took from Cha?
I saw you taking it at the port.
That’s my debt to repay.
So how exactly will you do that?!
If you cannot pay back,
you do it with your life.
You sure you weren’t
in bed with Cha?
Are you bugged?
Hold still!
Go home.
You took out Na for Cha
to take over the turf, no?
Choi Min-jae.
Learn how to see
the world properly first.
No one in my unit joined me
to stuff their pockets.
No, speak for yourself!
A cop must stand
above the gray zone?
You’ve already fallen
in the black muddy water.
The world will not
stand with you this time.
Okay, I’m the evil.
But I will lock up those
who are worse than me,
only then I’ll quit this,
so mind your own business.
Got that?
No, you won’t be able to.
I’m going to stop you.
Don’t resent me,
you started this.
Who’s that?
Who are you?
Hey! Answer me!
Welcome!
A $2 million gig won’t be
a cake walk.
Go to these coordinates,
pay the money and get the stuff.
Now that you confirmed it,
I’ll take your phone.
They’ll cut the power,
and contact you with this.
Thanks to your intel,
coast guards and narcos
won’t come near here.
I got a present for you there.
What are you doing?
You know what’s inside.
Hey!
Stop!
That’s enough!
Give me the key.
He’s probably not your
illegitimate son,
why are you protecting him?
It’s obvious he’s buying
his time to backstab you.
I’m getting rid of him for you.
Give me the key!
What’s with you?
You’re in a bind because
you won’t clean up your shit...
Buddy.
Bud.
You got shit for brain?
This is the west sea.
By morning with the tide gone,
everyone will see that car.
And a body is found in the trunk,
whom I beat up and put in.
If I’m labelled a cop killer,
I won’t be able to work.
Maybe I’ll wrap it all up here.
Or pull him out.
All right.
You’re a prickly one.
Look at that bastard!
Uh, bro?
This is what it comes to?
Delivering drugs to
pay back your debt?
Chief, it’s not too late
to give this up.
Don’t be cute in front of me.
There’s so much money here,
how much are you bringing in?
If a police chief is delivering,
wouldn’t you try to
get as much as possible?
Choi Min-jae.
I’m giving this to you
so that you don’t get killed.
Until I give you an order,
stay here like a ghost.
Got it? No matter what.
Chief.
I can’t be responsible
if you get yourself killed.
Remember, stay down,
got that?
Boss,
should we check the money first?
Hey.
Fucking pay me.
Count properly.
Police! Police!
Why isn’t that bastard
coming back?
Go check it out.
Yes, boss.
Chief!
Stop!
You fucking bastard!
Nobody move!
Drop your weapons
and surrender!
This is the narcotics!
I say it again,
drop your weapons!
Where are you going?!
Goddammit!
What are you gonna
do with that?
You son of a bitch!
Dammit!
Get me Park Kang-yoon!
Park! Get him down here!
Can I help you?
When we arrest Na,
slip out with the bag.
And lay low until I call you.
Chief Park Kang-yoon
asked me to drop
this off here at 11 PM.
$2 million, not a single bill missing.
It’s exactly 11 PM.
Park, that bastard...
Police! I’m a cop!
Chief, chief!
Over here!
Get me a stretcher!
Chief, is this fun?
This is the sweetest moment.
I told you to stay down.
Chief!
Sir!
This kid’s not obedient,
go educate him properly.
All right, thanks.
- Take care of him.
- Yes, sir.
Who’s that?
Park Kang-yoon,
you’re under arrest.
There’s been some misunderstanding,
we’re wrapping up another case,
and making arrests here.
I understand, do your thing.
On what charges?
For fabricating a suspect for
the death of Sgt. Lee Myung-ju.
Wait a minute, sir.
You can explain this, right?
Lt. Park Kang-yoon,
you’re under arrest for
evidence tampering among others.
You have the right to
retain a lawyer,
blah blah blah,
you know the drill.
Got anything to say?
Take him away.
Wait a minute! Stop!
Chief!
This doesn’t make any sense!
Park was arrested for
suspect fabrication.
We switched Chairman Kim’s
slush fund account to his.
I made sure Internal Affairs
won’t dig in any further.
Did Chairman Kim’s son fly out?
Yes, sir.
It’s too bad about Park.
Visitation Request: Park Kang-yoon
Chief.
I...
should have consulted you first...
It’s okay.
You were right to be suspicious.
You didn’t order
the suspect fabrication.
I didn’t but I’ll become
the fall guy for it.
It’s my fault as well,
Na was too good of a prey.
That’s why I bit down.
You can’t always win.
You sometimes lose some.
And get backstabbed too.
I did more than enough.
No regrets either.
When I get out of here,
I’m done catching bad guys.
I’ll live my remaining days
fishing instead.
That’s good.
By the way,
about my boat,
I didn’t get to put it away
since I was rushed in here.
There was a storm recently.
Could you go check
if it’s doing okay?
Sure.
Plants send a signal
before roots rot.
Leaf tips turn yellow like this,
or they shed leaves.
Park was tossed out like that.
You know that he didn’t do it.
That’s not important.
It’s about whether or not
the root is rotting.
It’s up to you to decide
how you determine it.
Sgt. Choi Dong-su
Investigation Report
Suspect Profile: Jeon Yong-bae
- A new addition?
- Yes.
Welcome.
Didn’t you come with
Chief Park some time ago?
I’m the son of Sgt. Choi Dong-su,
whom you killed.
It’s Jeon Yong-bae,
Choi Dong-su’s son will come by.
- You worked for Park?
- Yes, I did.
So? What’s this about?
I would...
like to meet the man on top.
What are you talking about?
He’ll surely come if it’s
about my father’s case.
If there’s no way from inside,
I’ll have to find a way from outside.
That’d ruffle a lot of feathers, no?
Is that a threat?
No, sir.
It’s been a while.
Yes, sir.
You asked for me?
What’s this?
It’s a report on my father Choi Dong-su,
and former officer and his murderer
Testimony of Jeon Yong-bae
Jeon Yong-bae’s testimony.
It details activities of
Yeonnam-sponsored officers,
and injustice suffered by
field officers from those activities.
There are other testimonies
and evidence as well.
Testimony?
It’s still just hearsay.
You do not have any
irrefutable evidence.
It won’t get past arraignment.
Details of the report are
quite powerful,
and the media will latch on to it,
turning it into a scandal.
Yeonnam sent Kim Jung-gyun
to Europe.
I’ve secured evidence that
he contracted a hit man,
and figured out
his escape route as well.
You wanted to ask for a favor.
You’ve grown up well.
You’re fiercer than your father.
Siheung Penitentiary
Buddy!
What have you done?
I’m not sure.
Don’t you always go by the book?
Sure.
But I might do this
until I catch all the bad guys
worse than me.
Boss.
Should we head to
Hapjeong district first?
A new drug from Thailand
flooded the market there.
Okay, Deputy Manager Choi.
- Drive.
- Sure thing.
So I hear Kim fled to Europe.
You’ve been gathering intel
even in prison?
European business trip
sounds good?
Our bosses won’t sign off on it...
We’ll get that after we return.
CHO Jin-woong
CHOI Woo-shik
PARK Hee-soon
KWON Yul, PARK Myung-hoon