(light ethereal music)
(wine splashing)
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
(glasses clinking)
(alarm blaring)
(static buzzing)
(light dramatic music)
(glassware clinking)
(chains rattling)
(light eerie music)
- You know I'm
worried about you.
You barely eat, I hardly see you
when you aren't in
that room working.
- I'm fine, all right?
Look, I'm sorry if I've
come across distant
or whatnot lately, but
I feel like I'm really
getting somewhere
with this work.
I don't wanna stop, not now.
I am so close.
(Peter slurping)
(phone ringing)
- Dr. Linda Rowe.
Yes.
Right.
Okay, sure.
No problem.
See you there.
I gotta go.
Shouldn't take more
than a couple hours.
- I didn't realize
you were on call.
- [Linda] Don't wait up.
(door thudding)
(chair scraping)
(ominous music)
(suspenseful music)
(bell dinging)
(ominous music)
(light dramatic music)
(gun clicking)
(mutant growling)
(suspenseful music)
- Oh, Christ.
How did you get out?
(mutant growling)
No, come on now.
You see?
There's nothing to worry about.
No harm.
(mutant grunting)
Come on, remember your home.
(mutant squealing)
(Peter groaning)
(flesh squishing)
(Peter screaming)
(gunshot banging)
(fist thudding)
(flesh squishing)
(Peter groaning)
(mutant growling)
(mutant grumbling)
(Peter screaming)
(flesh squishing)
(Peter gasping)
(suspenseful music)
(mutant growling)
(dramatic music)
- You sure you don't
want me to help you out?
- I've got it, thank you.
- You know, Jenna, you
don't have to leave so soon.
I could, I could setup the
guest bedroom and we could-
- We can what?
Go back to being happy families?
- Things don't have to
be like this, Jenna.
- I'm sorry, all right, I am.
But I'm not sorry
for what I did.
- [Alan] All right,
stop, stop, just-
- Some people just aren't
destined for one another.
- Look, I agree, but without
giving something a proper go,
I mean we can't, we
can't really comment
that on our relationship.
- We did give it a go, Alan.
One hell of a go.
We just aren't right
for each other.
Look, I'm gonna load up the car.
I'll be back for the rest
of my stuff tomorrow.
(door thudding)
(gravel crunching)
(car doors slamming)
- You okay?
- What, oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't exactly get
much sleep last night.
- Yeah, I can see that.
Do you wanna go home?
You still have that
holiday you barely used.
- No, no, no, I could,
I could use the
distraction if I'm honest.
- The wife?
- Ex-wife.
I guess I should get
used to saying that.
- Is she really
backing out on you?
- Says we're not meant to be.
Which is probably
partially true,
but I don't know how she got
to that conclusion so fast
'cause everything was
fine until I found out.
And then, bam.
Her mind was all made up.
- Yeah, well, how
fine can you really be
if she was playing
those games, huh?
Anyway, this might distract you.
- Hello, Marsh.
They're waiting over there.
(light eerie music)
- Oh, Captain Norton.
This is zoologist Alan Marsh
and his assistant, Julie Larkin.
- We got body, male.
Wife arrived home early in
the morning and found him.
Claims she was at work.
Claims she doesn't
know what coulda
done this to her husband.
- What do you mean
what coulda done this?
- Well, we're not really
sure, but we don't think
this murder was committed
by another human.
- So, what are you
saying did this?
- We don't know.
That's what we're hoping
you can help us with.
McKenna, would you mind?
- Miss Larkin, Marsh,
hi, thanks for coming.
Sorry to throw you both
in the deep end like this,
but we need an opinion.
Come with me.
- Sure.
(suspenseful music)
- Jesus Christ.
- Chambers, take
Miss Larkin outside
for some fresh air, will you?
- What are you thinking
coulda done this?
- A bear?
A big wild cat?
Christ knows.
- A bear so close
to the city, no.
And this attack
happened indoors,
that would be very
outta character.
Big cats don't really
come near humans
unless they feel threatened, so.
Oh, God, no, this was
something completely different.
- Do you have any idea
what might've done this?
- I'll need to take some samples
if that's okay with you boys.
- Do what needs to be done.
McKenna'll stay with ya.
- Appreciate it.
(light dramatic music)
- You essentially listen.
- Uh huh.
- We'll do all the talking.
Just make a mental
note of anything
she says that might
spark a thought.
Has she seen any wild
animals in the area recently
or any idea what
might've done this.
All right?
- Yeah, I gotcha.
(sirens wailing)
(somber music)
- Dr. Linda Rowe, I'm
Captain Edwardo Norton.
This is Detective James McKenna.
And with us today, we also
have specialist zoologist,
Alan Marsh, who's helping
us with the investigation.
- Hi.
- Thank you for waiting here.
I wish we were meeting under
better circumstances, Dr. Rowe.
How are you holding up?
- Call me Linda.
- Okay, Linda, we're gonna
have to ask you some questions.
Are you ready and
comfortable to begin?
- Sure.
- I have written down
here you arrived home
in the early hours
of the morning.
- I'm a doctor, I was on call.
Usually I don't get called
out, but last night I was.
- That was lucky for you.
- Excuse him.
So, can you tell me what
happened when you arrived home.
- I got home, everything
seemed normal.
I walked in and I knew
something was off.
The lights had been left
on and he never did that.
He was a in bed by
midnight kinda guy,
and he wouldn't leave the
lights on while sleeping.
- Was there anything
strange outside
the house before you went in?
- Nothing.
That was what was so strange.
I froze.
(Linda sneezes)
I had to get them to check it
was actually him
because I couldn't
believe he's really gone.
(Linda crying)
(Linda sneezes)
Thank you.
- Marsh here is gonna
take some samples
from your clothing, Dr. Rowe.
You okay with that?
- Sure.
- Here's my card.
Don't be afraid to just call me
if you can think
of anything, okay?
(light dramatic music)
- What are you thinking?
- She's clearly in shock.
Whatever was in the
house she has no clue.
But she's clearly had
some kinda reaction to it.
- What do you mean?
- Well, she was
sneezing profusely.
And she hasn't washed since
discovering her husband,
so I'm guessing whatever it
was has rubbed off on her skin,
her hair, and most
likely her clothing.
So, I'll get the
swabs off to the lab
and let you boys know asap
exactly what's going on.
I'm assuming you're gonna
ask her for clothing too?
- We'll be taking swabs and
a lamination from the prints.
- I'm not sure everything
she's revealing
is the entire truth.
- Why do you say that?
- The files of her husband,
they was all tampered
with or gone missing.
She's hiding something.
(ominous music)
- These fucking heels.
(trash thudding)
(rats squeaking)
(suspenseful music)
(woman gasps)
Just a rat.
(eerie music)
(mutant growling)
(suspenseful music)
(trash bin rattling)
(heel snapping)
(woman groaning)
(mutant growling)
(mutant shrieking)
(woman coughing)
(woman gasping)
(mutant shrieking)
(woman groaning)
(metal clanking)
(mutant growling)
(suspenseful music)
(woman gasps)
(mutant grunting)
(flesh squishing)
(woman groaning)
(woman screaming)
(phone buzzing)
- Alan speaking.
- [Linda] Hi, it's
Linda, Dr. Rowe.
I hope you don't mind,
I got your number
from the officer or
Detective McKenna.
I found something that you
might wanna take a look at.
Do you mind coming over?
(Alan sighs)
(light switch clicking)
(door thudding)
- [Alan] God damn.
- I'm sorry for calling
so out of the blue.
I was just in this
big old house alone.
- Why didn't you ask the
officers to come with you?
- What, Captain Norton
and Detective McKenna?
Not exactly the
comforting type, are they?
- No, I suppose not.
- Anyway, when I came back
I started looking around
and I found these.
You know they think
I was in on it.
I can sense it.
The way they worded their
questions towards me.
I found these in the workspace.
I was never allowed
in here before.
I found them in
there stashed away.
- You know, you should
be showing these to
the cops, not me.
- I wanted a second opinion.
Before I take this further.
- This paper looks new.
So you seriously had no idea
what he was up to
here in his lab?
- I knew he was
trialing some drugs.
After he got made redundant,
he really believed in the work
he was doing and he didn't
wanna give up on it.
He had the money to
get by month-by-month
and it was something he
was so passionate about.
I thought, what
the hell, you know?
As long as we can pay the bills.
- These uh, these packets
here on the table,
he's mixing medicines.
Growth hormone, 19-Nor-5,
androstenedione, Dianabol,
and uranium isotopes.
- Sorry, I get the first part.
Uranium what?
- It's uranium-235.
- So, it's radioactive?
- You never asked him specifics?
(Linda sighs)
Geez.
- I let him tell me what
he wanted to tell me.
I knew he tested on
generics in here,
you know, mice, rats, rabbits.
He was trialing a
drug which hopefully
some of these papers can
shed some light onto.
- You didn't know your
husband so well, huh?
- You only know what
people will let you see.
(fire crackling)
(light dramatic music)
I should ask before pouring.
Gin?
- I'll take it straight.
This your mom?
- Yeah.
Yeah, that's my mom
a few years back.
- You know, you
got the same eyes.
- Thank you.
People used to say that.
- I'm sorry, I didn't realize.
- You know, she would
usually be the one
I would call in a
situation like this.
(Linda sighs)
Like this, I mean, whoever
is in a situation like this?
I picked up my phone earlier
and I looked who to call
and there was no one.
I couldn't think of a
single person to call.
(Linda chuckling)
How'd I get like this, huh?
- You know, your husband must've
had something else up there.
From the markings I saw, it
had to be something at least,
at least his size if not double.
- You think so?
I will work with you.
I wanna help if you'll let me.
I wanna find out what my
husband was working on
out there and I wanna
find out what killed him.
And then, I wanna take the
son of a bitch out myself.
I will work with you.
I will tell you what
you need to know
if you help me get to it.
- All right.
You got yourself a deal.
Off the record of course.
- I'll raise a toast to that.
Top up?
- You know, if I keep
drinking like this,
I won't be able to
drive myself home.
- I have a couch.
You're welcome to
crash if you need.
- Top it up.
Thank you.
- So, tell me, where's
the wedding ring?
- I'm sorry?
- Well, yesterday when I
met you at the station,
you had a ring on your finger.
Now, it's gone.
So, either you decided to
hide that fact when you got
the call to come over or
there's something else.
- Wow.
It's a bit of both.
- Explain.
- I'm...
I'm going through a bit of
a nasty divorce right now,
and I didn't really
want that on show
or to be the topic
of conversation.
- How'd you even know it
would be a potential topic?
- Is it not?
- Well, I invited you
over here to help out
on a case and to figure
out what's going on.
- Hm and (clinking) gin is
an essential part of that.
Isn't it?
- You're good.
You really think
that you'll find out
what did this to my husband?
- 100%.
Look, whatever is out
there, I'll find it.
(traffic humming)
- [Chambers] This
is Suzanne Wright.
She was found in the early
hours of the morning.
The neighbors called
it in when they heard
a commotion around
the back of the flat.
Our boys went in and they
found her body
completely mutilated.
- Uh, where is the location?
- A side street by the club.
- So, it's gaining confidence.
It's ventured into the city.
- It seems so, yeah.
The same abrasions we found on
the first victim, Peter Rowe.
Any results back yet on the
clothing from the first scene?
Do we have any ideas yet
what kind of animal this is?
- No, I don't have my
results back either,
but I mean from these abrasions,
it's apparent to be
some kinda rodent.
- A rodent?
- I mean, last night she did say
he was working on
mice and rats, but-
- Who?
- Linda Rowe, she
told me her husband
had been testing
something up in his lab
and was taking mice and
rats up there to test
whatever drug concoction
he was coming up with.
- What the hell were you doing
with Linda Rowe last night?
- She called me.
She didn't wanna be alone and
she wanted to help somehow.
- And how the hell did
she get your number?
- Sir, I just
thought it would be-
- You and I will talk later.
We can't have people helping
investigating this crime
getting involved with the
victim's bereaved wife.
It's not professional.
And if you screw this
up, I'll feed your balls
to those animals you
study in the goddamn zoo.
- Look, she didn't call you
'cause she didn't
think you'd listen.
And you know what, I
kinda see her point.
Now, look, I'm here
to help you out
and if you wanna keep me here,
I wouldn't start by throwing
around your little
empty threats.
As for my personal life,
none of your business.
- He made something
up in his lab?
- He made something for sure.
As for what, that's the problem.
Right now, everything is
kinda pointing towards
it being some kind
of mutated rodent,
but I don't even wanna say that.
I mean, (sighs).
I mean, it defies all logic,
it defies all evolution.
Right now, (stuttering),
I can't say exactly
what it is right now.
It's just-
- You're saying some
mutated creature
is walking these streets?
- Quite possibly.
- [Norton] Damn.
Were there reporters
at the crime scene?
- Press office is
dealing with it now, sir.
It's hitting the
news as we speak.
- Look, whatever this thing is,
it's clearly feeding
once a day minimum.
So, we gotta put the
city on lockdown.
Keep everybody safe
until we can find it.
- Lockdown?
Are you crazy?
You can't put the city
on lockdown for this.
We don't even know
what the hell this is.
Look, we think it's
killed two people,
but we have no forensic evidence
linking them together as of yet.
Hell, we have no evidence of
anything right now except some
half-assed theory of a potential
serial giant rat killer.
The press will have a field day.
The public needs to
be warned, officially.
Only Christ knows
what we can tell them.
(light dramatic music)
(keys jingling)
- [Julie] What is
it about this woman?
- I'm just gonna go warn her.
- Alan, I know you
better than that.
- Julie, that is all.
- Do you really think
it's a good idea
to be hitting on
a grieving widow?
(Alan scoffs)
- Look, there's a major
difference between me warning
somebody and taking them out
for a candlelit dinner, okay?
I'm gonna be two seconds.
(door creaking)
(ominous music)
Linda?
Linda, you home?
(eerie music)
(ceiling thudding)
(phone ringing)
- [Linda] Alan, hi, it's Linda.
I'm down at the station.
They said you went
to check in on me.
- Yeah, I'm in your house.
- [Linda] Oh, sorry, I
left a little while back.
I was asked to go
down to the station
for some further questioning.
- Yeah, I think there's
something in your house.
- [Linda] What?
(eerie music continues)
- Yeah, I think it's come back.
(suspenseful music)
(light dramatic music)
Fuck it.
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
(Alan groaning)
(mutant growling)
(flesh ripping)
(foot thudding)
(Alan groaning)
(Alan grunting)
(mutant groaning)
(flesh squishing)
(Alan groaning)
(suspenseful music)
(door slamming)
- [Linda] Alan!
(Alan panting)
- It's in there, it's in there.
Come on.
Come on, get in the car.
- So, you're saying the thing
that attacked you
was a giant rat?
- Look, I know how
this sounds, all right?
But that thing, it
was more mutated.
It was the size of a
frickin' bear, I...
God knows how it got that big.
- Whatever he was playing with,
concocting in his
little room, it got out.
- We got the results back.
(light dramatic music)
From Linda's clothing
and the first victim.
It's definitely rodent fur.
It must've rubbed off
from her husband's body
and that's why she
had that reaction.
- The biggest question is
why did it go back there?
- Maybe it associates
it with its home.
Which isn't necessarily
a bad thing.
I mean, at least we know it
isn't in the sewers of the city.
- And where do you
suppose this creature goes
when it's not at its home?
- God knows, where
do rats dwell?
Sewers, dark alleys, dumpsters?
- Something the city is full of.
- I need to update the
chief on this latest.
(Norton sighs)
Christ, this is all we need.
- Look, this is a rat.
One larger in size,
I'll grant you that,
but it's still a rat.
And it's a once in a
lifetime opportunity
to deal with
something like this.
I've never encountered
anything like this.
I wanna find out what Peter
Rowe was trying to achieve,
how it got this big.
We should treat this like
we would any other case;
we trap it and then we study it.
- What if you're wrong?
What if it becomes
uncontrollable and
more people die?
- Look, if we act fast,
this won't be a situation.
- 24 hours, that's all we have.
We track this fucker down,
we figure out how
to take it down,
we capture it and we end this.
And it's all yours.
A word, Alan, before I leave.
(Alan groaning)
What is going on?
- I'm sorry?
- Your little assistant told me,
so I know you're going
through a hard time at home.
But jumping onto
the next best thing
is not gonna resolve your
mental state, all right?
I warned you about getting
involved with the wife.
You need to be
focused right now.
I need your attention.
You're the expert that's gonna
help us capture this thing.
Now, I can get my firearms
officers to shoot it dead,
but you want it alive.
So, in that case,
buck yourself up and just
stay away from the wife.
- I told you, there's
nothing going on.
- Let her grieve.
(Alan sighs)
Understood?
She could still be a suspect.
- Yeah.
I hear ya.
- We'll see you first thing.
McKenna.
(eerie music)
- Sir?
- Come on, we're off.
- Hey.
Everything okay?
(Alan chuckling)
I'm sorry for turning up.
I just wanted to
check you were okay.
I heard about the attack.
- I'm fine, really, it's
just a few scratches.
- I was scared to
go back to the house
after they told me
that thing was there.
They told me I
should be cautious.
He can't stop us
from having a drink.
That's not affecting
anything, surely.
- I guess I should go by
what he says while I'm still
hired and assisting the case.
- So, how come you
went by my place today?
- Uh, I, uh, just wanted,
just wanted to
warn you, ya know?
There's a huge mutant
rat running around.
I just wanted to make sure
you were all right, you know?
- I appreciate that.
Thank you.
- So, you thought about where
you're gonna wait this out?
- I'll probably just
go back to the hotel
that I stayed in after Peter.
You know, when they were
examining the house.
- No siblings or-
- No siblings.
- Oh.
- There's an aunt of Peter's,
but she doesn't really
have the space for me.
And I need to kinda
stay close by for work.
- Ah, so um, so how
long you been a doctor?
- Coming up to my fifth year.
I'm a late starter.
I started off as a nurse
and then I studied
and became a doctor.
I wanted something fulfilling.
You know, and after my mom,
I wanted to figure out
something I could do
that could stop others from
going through what she did.
And you, a zoologist.
What exactly does that entail?
- Well, we specialize in
multiple areas of animal care.
Anything from animal welfare
to controlling
pests and diseases.
My team and I mainly
focus on drug development.
We make drugs to help animals,
whether it be by stopping
the spread of diseases
or from stopping them from
contracting it themselves.
I started the business when
I just got sick of working
for my old boss and then
hired Julie as my assistant,
and I just haven't
looked back since.
(Linda sighs)
- You know, if I keep drinking,
I won't be suitable to drive.
(light dramatic music)
So, I should probably quit while
I'm ahead and go
check into the hotel.
- It's looking like
it's gonna cost you.
- Okay.
- You don't look surprised.
- Well, do any cars pass
their inspections, huh?
(mechanic scoffs)
Hm, sorry, how long
is this gonna take?
'Cause I've got places to be.
- Right, I'll go finish it now.
- Great.
- There's the papers.
Copy machine is
ready when you are.
- [Woman] Mm.
(ominous music)
- Stuck up bitch.
(suspenseful music)
(metal clanking)
(woman sighs)
(suspenseful music)
(rats squeaking)
(dramatic music)
(mutant growling)
(light dramatic music)
- Hello?
Hey, mister.
(door slamming)
Look, I don't have time
to be waiting all day.
(dramatic music)
(woman groaning)
(suspenseful music)
(mutant growling)
(flesh squishing)
(woman screaming)
(mutant growling)
(metal bins clanking)
(woman panting)
(mutant growling)
(flesh squishing)
(woman screaming)
(hammer thudding)
(mutant screeching)
(mutant growling)
(flesh squishing)
(woman screaming)
(mutant roaring)
(phone ringing)
- Alan speaking.
All right, yeah.
I'm on my way, I'm on my way.
(Alan sighs)
When?
When did this happen?
- The late hours of the night.
Seemed she had someone
checking out her car.
The rat got up probably
from the sewers below,
attacked the workman
and then attacked her.
- Anyone else around?
- Yeah, it was pretty quiet.
Although it does look like
the creature had attempted
to get into some
of the other homes.
- Goddammit, stop calling
this thing a creature!
I told you it's a rat,
it's a frickin' rat!
All right?
And you shoulda
put warnings out!
The public don't even know
what's out there amongst them.
All right, if you
had put warnings out,
maybe people would've
stayed fucking indoors!
- It isn't that easy.
We have to weigh up the factors.
Scaring the public into feeling
they aren't safe is not the way.
It's last case scenario.
The public's response is
what we need to control
in order to get
ahold of this thing.
This is no different to
any other serial killings,
except it's not human.
- Yeah, you're doing
a great job so far.
- Whatever actions that
coulda taken place,
it got into the garage.
There really isn't much
to have prevented that.
The body count's rising.
Christ, this thing
could attack again.
We need to get someone else in.
- I'm not leaving this case.
- Look, it's out of our hands.
We need to get the FBI in.
So, we just wanna thank you for
all the work you've done so far.
- I'm so sorry, Alan.
Look, what you need
to do now is to focus
all of your energy onto finding
that thing and ending this.
You can't listen to them.
- I have no intention
of doing so.
Thank you.
Those guys have no idea
what they are dealing with.
They didn't see that thing.
They didn't look in its eyes.
They didn't see its face.
That thing is angry
and it is hungry.
Whatever your husband
created, it is pissed off.
We gotta trap it.
- What do you mean?
- It'll go back to the house.
It obviously sees it as
some kind of safe place,
so we go back there.
And when it returns,
we're ready.
- We wait it out?
- Exactly.
- Okay.
- All right, all right.
(light dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let it come out.
You just stay there.
- Sure.
(fist knocking)
(suspenseful music)
(Julie scoffs)
(Alan sighs)
- Firstly, what the
hell are you doing here?
Secondly, what is going on?
- All right, okay, all
right, just let me explain.
- Go on.
- They uh, they
brought the feds in.
Another girl was found
dead this morning.
- [Julie] Oh, Alan.
- Yeah, right now I just
kinda wanna focus on
getting this thing
over and down with
so it doesn't get out
and harm anyone else.
- Well, I don't think you need
to worry about that much longer.
- [Alan] What do you mean?
- Go and turn on the news.
(restaurant guests
talking over each other)
- Hey, honey.
- What time do you call this?
- Come on, can't we
make this a good night?
- What, you want me to put
on a smile and just act like
you being late all the
time isn't a big issue?
- This thing's still
loose in our city.
This is my job, all right?
I can't just drop it
when I feel like it.
- Drinks?
- Vodka straight, please.
- Sure.
- I guess I'll take the same.
(light swanky music)
(light dramatic music)
(rats squeaking)
(rats scampering)
(trash thudding)
(rats squeaking)
(suspenseful music)
- Oh, shit, pickin' up
the fuckin' trash now.
(trash rustling)
(eerie music)
(rats squeaking)
Vermin.
(liquid splashing)
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
(mutant growling)
(muffled rock music)
Jay!
(Tina screaming)
Help me!
Jay!
(mutant growling)
Help!
(Tina screaming)
(mutant grunting)
(flesh squishing)
(body thudding)
(Tina gasps)
(mutant screeching)
(silverware clanking)
(mutant growling)
(ominous music)
(Tina panting)
(Tina crying)
(Tina screaming)
(suspenseful music)
(head crunching)
(mutant growling)
(neck snapping)
(body thudding)
(light swanky music)
(mutant roaring)
(waitress groaning)
(bottles shattering)
(waitress panting)
(mutant groaning)
(claws thudding)
(plates shattering)
(mutant growling)
(foot thudding)
(chair crashing)
(waitress groaning)
(neck snapping)
(flesh squishing)
(man screaming)
(hand thudding)
(people screaming)
(mutant growling)
(woman screaming)
(neck snapping)
(flesh squishing)
(woman screaming)
(restaurant guests screaming)
(man grunting)
(bottles shattering)
(flesh squishing)
(man groaning)
(woman screaming)
- You brought a gun to
our anniversary dinner?
- Fuckin' right, now
get the fuck out!
(gunshots banging)
(blood squishing)
(suspenseful music)
(Norton screaming)
(flesh squishing)
(dramatic music)
- You really think that'll work?
- Sure, I mean, it's just
about keeping it inside.
- Say it reproduces.
I mean, what do we,
what do we do then?
- Well, I mean, the
average rat reproduces
every three weeks.
And this being a mutated rat,
I'd say it could vary anything
from months to weeks to days.
I'd like to say that
days is unlikely,
but I mean, look, the
faster we catch this thing,
the faster we can end this.
- Well, I'm gonna hit the sack.
Doesn't look like it's
coming back tonight.
- [Alan] Okay, I'll
stay up till sunrise.
Don't worry.
- Let me know if
you need anything.
- Sure, sweet dreams.
- Good night.
I've put some fresh linen
and towels upstairs for you.
- [Julie] Oh, thanks.
- [Alan] Ah, man.
- Everything all right?
- Ah, it's just, just
my back still stings
from the other night.
I shoulda got it checked out
earlier today, but (sighs).
- Let me take a look.
I can help.
- Any excuse to get
my shirt off, eh?
- You wish.
Come on, I am a doctor.
- Oh, I know.
- Show me.
(Alan groaning)
Looks like these bandages
haven't been changed.
You should be changing these
twice a day to avoid infection.
Have you been using antiseptic?
- No, I was just using
whatever the police doctor
gave me when they
first checked me over.
- Alan, that rat coulda been
carrying all kinds of diseases.
Can you please take
care of yourself better?
- Yes, ma'am.
(light music)
- This is gonna sting.
- God fuckin' dammit.
(Alan clears throat)
(Alan sighs)
Thank you for caring.
It feels like it's been a while
since someone actually
cared, you know?
- I could say the same.
- How do you mean?
- I don't believe that anyone
truly has the perfect marriage.
I mean, I get that people
have their hiccups.
You know, the ups and downs.
- Uh huh.
- That's all I'm gonna say.
- What, he didn't
make you feel loved?
- He was a busy guy.
- Oh, I know that story.
I think that's, that's where
I messed up with Jenna.
I just wasn't as much
as I shoulda been,
and when I was, I didn't...
I didn't give her the
attention she deserved.
- People lead busy lives.
It's easy to get caught up.
It's understandable.
- Yeah, but what's not
understandable is not seeing
what's right there
in front of you.
And not showing that
person day in and day out
how much they mean to you.
That's supposed to be
the easy part, right?
(light music)
(bugs chirping)
(fist knocking)
- Who's that?
- What?
- Who's at the door?
- Oh, shit.
Shit, I fell asleep.
You stay here.
I'll go check.
(Alan groaning)
(door creaking)
- Thought we'd find you here.
- What's going on?
- Have you seen the news?
- With all that we know now,
did the police leave
this too late to tell us?
Should we all have been
warned much sooner?
What we know is that
this so-called beast
has now taken the lives
of dozens of citizens.
But perhaps that coulda
been avoided if the public
had been made aware much sooner
that a beast was on
the loose in the city.
Police have confirmed
that the beast
is a wild and predatory animal,
possibly ranging between
five and six feet in height.
The advice is to stay
indoors until further news,
and avoid drainage
areas and sewers.
They're advising that
if you see the beast,
do not approach.
People are being told
to travel in groups
of at least two persons,
keeping to well lit streets
and avoiding evenings
and night times.
- We need your help.
- Of course.
- You already have an idea?
- What, us being
back in the house
wasn't enough of a clue for you?
It'll come back.
We just gotta wait it out.
- Well, how can you be so sure?
- Look, I can't be
sure of anything,
but I can damn well be
ready if it does come back.
- How the fuck are you
three gonna take it out?
- Look, you called us
for a reason, right?
So, unless you have a better
idea, this is the plan.
Now, you can stay and
help us or you can leave,
and go about whatever little
plan you've already got.
No one's forcing you to
stay here, all right?
It's your choice.
- Tell us what to do.
(bugs chirping)
(trunk creaking)
- We're gonna need something
to defend ourselves.
- You didn't bring a firearm?
I thought you wild
animal experts
all had that as
part of your job.
- Well, pick your poison.
- I'll stick with my gun.
My friend died last
night because he couldn't
defend himself
against that thing.
I'm carrying and I'll
use it if needed.
- Look, I'm, I'm sorry
about Captain Norton.
We're gonna get this
fucker, all right?
- Damn right.
(trunk slamming)
(mutant screeching)
- Okay, we need
to go back inside.
Come on, come on.
- This gas, it'll actually work?
I mean, you didn't
seem convinced earlier.
- Yeah, well, I didn't
really understand it earlier.
But as long as we keep it
in the house it should work.
(mutant shrieking)
(Linda sighs)
- Be ready.
- What's going on?
- It's coming.
- What are you
planning on doing?
Stay inside the house.
- I'm gonna lure it
back to the house.
Now, get back in the house
and just make sure
every door is locked.
- You need to be careful.
- I got this!
Go back in the house.
- Just in case.
- We are gassing
it, not shooting it.
- We're gonna do anything we
need to to fuckin' kill it.
(gun clicks)
It's jammed.
(mutant growling)
(ominous music)
- What was that?
(bugs chirping)
(suspenseful music)
- Where is it?
(mutant growling)
(Julie screaming)
(gunshot banging)
(McKenna groaning)
(McKenna gagging)
(foot thudding)
(Chambers grunting)
(Chambers panting)
(Chambers groaning)
(bat thudding)
(Julie grunting)
(Chambers screaming)
- Get Alan!
(claw thudding)
(mutant growling)
(dramatic music)
(Julie groaning)
(mutant growling)
(suspenseful music)
(Julie panting)
(mutant growling)
(mutant pounding)
(Chambers panting)
- [Alan] Open the door!
- Fuck, I can't open
it, it's fuckin' locked.
(Julie screaming)
Where's the key?
I need to go
upstairs and get her.
- You go, I'll find
another way in.
(light dramatic music)
(Alan panting)
Goddammit.
Linda, it's in the house.
- I know.
- So, you get outside
and wait there.
I'll get Julie and
then we'll gas it.
- Leave it to me.
I'm going to.
- What the hell?
- I'm sorry, Alan.
I've got to do it myself.
- No, what the hell is this?
- Just stay there.
(eerie music)
(mutant growling)
(Alan groaning)
- Marsh?
(glass shattering)
(Alan groaning)
Julie, you up here?
- Yes.
- Is it locked?
(gun clicking)
(suspenseful music)
(mutant growling)
(gunshot banging)
(dramatic music)
(Chambers whimpering)
(mutant growling)
(gunshot banging)
(Chambers panting)
(glass shattering)
(mutant growling)
(Chambers gasping)
Oh no, oh God.
(dramatic music)
(Chambers panting)
(fists thudding)
(mutant groaning)
(table smashing)
(Chambers groaning)
(Chambers panting)
(dramatic music)
(chemicals splashing)
(glass shattering)
(knife whooshing)
(gate creaking)
(Chambers panting)
(mutant growling)
(metal bars creaking)
(suspenseful music)
(light eerie music)
(Chambers panting)
(metal bars creaking)
(suspenseful music)
(mutant growling)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Chambers panting)
(dramatic music)
(Chambers gasping)
(mutant growling)
(Chambers screaming)
(flesh squishing)
(mutant growling)
(gunshot banging)
(ominous music)
(Chambers gasps)
(Linda panting)
(gunshots banging)
(light dramatic music)
- I'm sorry.
Sorry.
(Chambers screaming)
(stairs creaking)
(flesh squishing)
(eerie music)
(door rattling)
(Alan coughing)
(door thudding)
(dramatic music)
- Alan, are you okay?
(Alan groaning)
- Where is it?
- [Julie] It's locked
in the dining room.
- What, what the hell happened?
- I think it was Linda.
- What?
- I found these
documents upstairs.
I think she's been keeping
close to us to monitor us.
To stop us from killing the rat.
I don't think her husband
made this monster at all.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying, these
documents are Linda's.
I think she was experimenting
on the rat to help her mother,
and I think it escaped
and killed her husband,
and now she's trying
to cover her tracks.
Look.
- What the hell?
(light dramatic music)
- Why'd you have to go through
and find all the information?
- Linda, what in the
hell is going on?
- She suffered a horrible death.
The cancer spread so rapidly.
There was nothing we could do,
but sit back and watch her
suffer until her drying breath.
To prevent anyone else from
ever experiencing this again,
I tried to make something in
vain of what happened to her.
To honor her life.
A cure that could
prevent anyone else
from having to go through
what my mother had to.
I found an antidote
that reverses cells
from growing at such a pace.
The idea was the cells
would reduce in size,
become manageable, so
the patient could live
with the disease for
many, many years.
It went wrong.
In fact, what I made
had the opposite effect.
It made cells grow
at such a pace
that it enlarged the body
the way a steroid would.
The rat I was testing on
was growing at such a pace,
I documented it
over several weeks.
- What, that thing was in
this house for several weeks?
- One night it must've
escaped, and found Peter.
And it killed him.
If Peter hadn't died that night,
I believe I would've found
the answers I was looking for.
The reaction the rat
had was a positive one,
even though it didn't work for
the direction I wanted it to.
If I had more time I could've
studied how to reverse it
and make the cells
dissolve at a similar pace.
I was so close.
- And now, he's
gone and we've got
a mutated rat just
dying to tear us apart.
So, what the fuck is
your big idea, Linda?
What is your plan?
- I have to end this now.
This is all my fault.
I was only trying to
do the right thing.
I'm so sorry it got out of hand.
I did not mean for
any of this to happen.
- You were using
me for information.
- As we continued to
meet, the more we met,
the more I realized how
they were involving you.
- No, no, no, no, no, you
used me for information.
Why didn't you just
tell me what you did?
I coulda helped you.
- And risk going to jail
for what's happened?
You seemed to have a plan
how to capture the rat.
I had already tried and failed.
- What do you mean?
Wait, when I came here to
warn you and I got attacked,
you lead it here?
- It returned while I was gone.
I was too late to trap it.
I'm sorry for what
happened to you.
I felt so bad.
If I'd been here, I could've
just killed it myself.
- Just, just, just
lower your gun.
Let us, let us help you.
- No, I want you to get
out of the house, Alan.
Let me deal with this.
- You can't do this alone.
(suspenseful music)
Just, just, just let
us, let us help you.
- I started this,
now I gotta end it.
- All right, I get it, I
get why you did it, okay?
Just let us help you.
Give me the gun,
give me the gun.
- Just get outta
the house, Alan.
(suspenseful music)
This isn't safe.
(McKenna grunting)
(bat thudding)
(Linda groaning)
- What the hell was
this woman playing at?
- Julie, McKenna, get
outside, get Linda.
- What?
- Just go outside, I'll
meet you out there.
- I'm not leaving you.
- Look, I'm gonna
set this thing off.
You get Linda, find a window,
and no matter what happens,
just get out, all right?
Okay?
- Okay.
(door creaking)
(eerie music)
(mutant growling)
Linda, wake up, we've
gotta get out of here.
(Linda groaning)
- I have to kill it.
I gotta kill it.
Oh, (groaning).
(eerie music)
(flesh squishing)
(suspenseful music)
(gas hissing)
(dramatic music)
- Get out.
Get out!
- Linda, come on!
- Go!
(mutant growling)
(suspenseful music)
- Go, go, go, go!
Go!
- I'm going!
(intense dramatic music)
(Alan panting)
- Come on, come on, come on.
Let's go, let's go,
go, go, go, go, go, go.
(suspenseful music)
All right.
(house rumbling)
What the fuck was that?
(intense dramatic music)
Fuck.
- I thought we
killed that thing?
- It must've got into the
drug concoction in the lab.
(mutant growling)
- Jesus, it's still growing.
- We've gotta get out of here.
- Come on, run!
- Move!
- Come on!
- Get to the car.
- Come on.
(dramatic music)
- Come on, man, start
the fucking car!
(car engine sputtering)
McKenna, how about we just
start the fucking car?
- Get out, now!
- Open the door.
Open the door!
- We can't get out!
- Open the door then,
open the fucking door!
Open the door, come
on, open the door!
Open the door then!
(mutant growling)
Oh, God!
- McKenna, I can't-
- This way, come on.
Come on, open the door.
Open the fuckin' door.
(mutant growling)
Come on!
- Oh, I'm stuck!
- Come on, come on.
(suspenseful music)
(mutant roaring)
(metal crunching)
(Julie screaming)
(car crashing)
(gunshots banging)
(mutant roaring)
(McKenna screaming)
(gunshots banging)
(body crunching)
(Julie gasps)
(bones crunching)
(Julie panting)
(ominous music)
(mutant roaring)
(Julie screaming)
- Goddammit it!
(mutant growling)
(Julie screaming)
(Julie panting)
(suspenseful music)
(mutant roaring)
(electric zapping)
(mutant whimpering)
(mutant roaring)
(mutant bones crunching)
(mutant growling)
Look, whatever that
thing has taken,
it's just gonna get bigger and
it's just gonna keep mutating
and there's only so
much his body can take.
Just watch.
(suspenseful music)
(mutant bones crunching)
(mutant groaning)
(mutant flesh squishing)
(explosion booming)
(blood splashing)
(Julie screaming)
(Julie crying)
(Alan panting)
(both coughing)
(light dramatic music)
(Alan spitting)
- Do you know how far we
are from civilization?
- You do not wanna know.
- Hey, I'm really
sorry about Linda.
(mutants growling)
- Ah, fuck, of
course there's more.
(dramatic rock music)
(light ethereal music)
(wine splashing)
(glasses clinking)
(alarm blaring)
(static buzzing)