Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
- [Michael] This morning, the
ACLU filed a federal lawsuit
against the Department of
Justice and against the FBI,
challenging the designation
of a musical fan base
as a criminal gang.
It is a quintessential
civil liberties case,
challenging government
abuse and supporting
the right of people
to express themselves
without fear of
police persecution.
- Recognizing the
absurdity of the situation
and that there are
civil liberties
and constitutional
issues involved
that extend far
beyond this issue.
I'd like to introduce
the plaintiffs.
Joseph Bruce and Joey Utsler,
also known as the
Insane Clown Posse.
(eerie ambience)
(music box playing)
♪ Do you like clowns ♪
(crowd chanting)
♪ Do you like bloody,
bloody, bloodshed ♪
♪ Wicked clowns
come out to play ♪
♪ Ha Ha ♪
♪ PCP ♪
♪ Meth and
anti-depression pills ♪
♪ Shit but I wont stop ♪
♪ Last time on the spot ♪
♪ Choked a cop ♪
♪ Stopped and had
a Faygo soda pop ♪
♪ In the back of my trunk ♪
♪ Chuck the chainsaw ♪
♪ Usually chop wood,
but that ain't all ♪
♪ It's a bit strange, all
up in your mid range ♪
♪ Cut a hole in your
head til I hit brains ♪
♪ Left a cop in a
pile while maybe ♪
♪ It's the night of
the chainsaw baby ♪
♪ Cut 'em up Chuck, somebody ♪
♪ Cut 'em up Chuck, get bloody ♪
♪ Cut 'em up Chuck, go nutty ♪
♪ Cut 'em up Chuck, cut
'em up Chuck, cut 'em up ♪
♪ You can't calm me down,
you can't calm me down ♪
- Clown motherfucking
love, Juggalos!
- I'm Violent J from
Insane Clown Posse.
Joe Bruce, my real name.
- I'm Shaggy 2 Dope.
AKA Joseph Utsler,
my government name.
- And I am an entertainer
extraordinaire.
- I'm a rapper.
- A musician.
- Artist.
- Actor.
- Wrestler.
- Pro wrestler.
- Father of three, married.
- I'm a Bruce brother.
- I'm an honorary
Bruce brother, I think.
- He's the third Bruce brother.
It goes way back to
when we were children.
- Yeah.
- [Stern] We're sitting
here with two big stars.
Insane Clown Posse.
Let's take a phone call.
- [Caller] You guys
are fucking horrible.
- [Caller] Let's have
a serious conversation.
When are you guys gonna
fucking kill yourselves?
- We've made USA
Today's worst album
of the year, like twice.
We made GQ's worst
artists of all time.
Page after page after page.
This is the worst music
you've ever heard.
What is this shit?
What is this garbage?
Just totally dissing.
We used to just look
and look and look
for one positive review.
Couldn't find it.
♪ Water, fire, air and dirt ♪
♪ Fucking magnets,
how do they work ♪
- What the hell was that?
- [Comical Voice] Yeah,
even clowns think they suck.
- People hate what
they don't understand.
And there's a lot to not
understand about ICP, you know?
Just the face paint alone.
Alternative music didn't
want nothing to do with us.
Hip hop didn't want
nothing to do with it.
Without a home, a home
began to form itself
and began to dig its own
niche out in society.
- Explaining Juggalos
is such a hard thing.
- You probably maybe
come from a broken home
and you dealing with
with depression.
You know what I mean?
Probably dealing with
depression like we do.
- Trouble, you know,
trouble in their life.
Stuff like that, you know?
I think that's why it's
such a good clique,
such a good thing because we're
Juggalos ourself, you know?
- What does it mean
to be a Juggalo?
Most people say family.
- You're just walking
around with your shirt
or your charm or something.
And you see someone
else and boom,
you've just made a new friend.
- Like the family
thing is really real.
We all have each
other's back, it's nuts.
- You're making it sound
like the Manson family, bro.
- Being yourself.
Being who the fuck you are
and not giving a fuck
what anyone thinks.
If it hurts your
feelings, I'm sorry
that your parents
raised a pussy.
- We exist because
other people judged us
and kind of made us outcasts.
We all band together under that.
- I've been a Juggalo since I
came out of my mom's vagina.
♪ What is a Juggalo? ♪
- [Shaggy] We
embrace the hate now
because what are we
going to do, fight it?
- [Violent J] It just made us
cooler to the Juggalos, man.
That's what's going on
in the outside world.
Inside with the
Juggalos, it was a party.
We were getting massive love.
- Clown love, baby!
Clown love! Clown love!
- Dude, it was off the hook.
It was so fucking fresh.
- [Violent J] That's what
we're hearing every day.
Meanwhile, we pick up a
paper that talks about
who could listen
to this garbage.
Which one do we believe?
We just went with the fam.
♪ What is a Juggalo ♪
- My husband has been
serving a life sentence
since he was 19.
So I got his mugshot.
Hi.
- [Shaggy] Hey.
- This is John.
He's been a Juggalo since
he was nine years old.
- Oh he's on the
phone? [Woman] Yeah.
- What up, man?
- [John] What's up, man.
- [Shaggy] Shit, just out
here baking our ass off.
What's good with you, man?
- [John] I love you guys.
You guys have got me through
so many dark times in my life.
You don't even know.
- [Shaggy] Are you locked up?
- [Woman] For life.
- Oh shit, for life?
- [John] Yeah, there's
thousands of Juggalos
in prison too,
bumping your shit.
- Well maybe you guys could
start up a Juggalo gang
in there, man.
And kick some ass.
- Or perhaps not.
- Baby.
- [Violent J] Want
us to sign the face?
- Yeah. They're signing
your face, baby.
- [Shaggy] I'm gonna
do another tattoo.
- [Woman] He's giving
you another tattoo
on your forehead.
- [John] That's crazy.
- [Violent J] We have this
beautiful relationship
with these people
and we fucking love
the Juggalos, man.
They want our music as a
soundtrack to their life.
So why not provide?
- [Radio Reporter] Music
fans or gang members?
- [British Reporter]
The government says
they're dangerous.
- [Male TV Reporter] These
142 pages document cases of
brutal murders, assaults
across the country.
They all have one
word in common.
Juggalo.
- [Female TV Reporter]
A Juggalo is a follower
of a rap group called
the Insane Clown Posse,
known for its violent lyrics.
- [Female TV Reporter]
There's about a million fans
and a percentage may
be involved in crime.
- [Older Female Reporter]
The FBI has classified
Juggalos as a gang.
- [British Radio Reporter]
Juggalos say they're a family.
- Family, family,
family, family!
♪ And I'd walk home
feeling like a samurai ♪
♪ I'd walk in the house
and see my mama cry ♪
♪ I'd ask why, she
points to my drunk pops ♪
♪ He tried to hit her
again, but that shit stops ♪
♪ I kick him in his throat,
you hear his neck break ♪
- We both come from poor,
broken families, broken homes.
- Our real dad bailed
when I was two.
We had to go through
his replacement,
which was even worse.
- The older I get, the more
I realize how fucked up
my childhood was, but
I definitely think
it helped made us
stronger people.
You know what I'm saying?
And I think it made us 10
billion times more hungry
when we starting out.
Not having nothing
when you grow up,
that'll shape you for the
rest of your fucking life,
whether you got money or not.
(My Heart Will Go On style song)
- [Linda] Yes, throughout the
whole house, isn't it, hun?
The nautical theme.
My name is Linda and
I'm Violent J's mother,
Joe Bruce.
And I'm a Juggalette.
I think I was probably
the first one.
- You were the first one, ma.
- [Linda] I was 19 years old
when I had my first baby.
That was Teresa. And then I
had Rob and then Joe's my baby,
the caboose.
We struggled.
We were poor, but we
never went to bed hungry
or anything like that.
But there wasn't a lot of
money for entertainment.
But as a mother, you always try.
- [Violent J] We were the
poorest in the neighborhood.
We got the food
stamps and all that.
But our imaginations were there.
Big time imaginations,
you know what I'm saying?
We had a club name.
We called ourselves The Floobs.
First thing we did was
make having nothing cool.
It's okay to have
mismatched shoes.
We had these rickety old bikes
and kids would make fun of us.
They were riding around with
Mongooses and Supergooses.
We'd have fucked up bikes.
They were pieced together
from like nine other bikes.
And we made it cool.
We were like, that's
the Floobmobile.
We turned it around
and we really did feel
like we were the shit.
Cause we were part
of the Floobs.
- [Shaggy] We
didn't feel left out
cause we were with each other.
Like them fucking
trench coat mafia kids
from the fucking
Columbine or whatever.
They're all crying about
they didn't have no
friends, whatever.
There was two of
those motherfuckers,
you know what I'm saying?
They have friends, they
had each other, you know?
- [Linda] They have a lot
of self-worth together.
Even maybe separately they
don't, but together they do.
Joe had a fire, is the
only thing I can call it.
When he wanted to do something,
you couldn't deny it.
He just had to, he had to do it.
- We always been the type
of kids that do whatever
we were into, you
know, we have to do it.
- And then he started going
really interested in wrestling.
I remember driving him
to Joe Louis Arena.
I didn't have the money.
And I knew that if I didn't
take him, he would've walked.
- I must've been 15 years
old, maybe 14 years old.
Out back is where
we all would get our
autographs from all the
wrestlers coming out.
And all of a sudden, I see
these two guys wrestling,
these two young kids.
And I'm like, holy shit, man.
They do it better
than the guys inside.
- [Linda] I remember
coming home from work and
there'd be footprints
on my ceiling.
And I was trying to figure
out how that happened.
They would super suplex each
other in the living room.
He'd be flipping them and
the guy would actually
walk on the ceiling.
They were in junior
high school and
they started their
own wrestling league,
National Allstar Wrestling.
- [Violent J] We had a ring
built in his mom's backyard.
Built out of railroad logs.
We'd wait till it would rain
and we'd be out
there in the rain
pounding it in the ground
because the ground
would be softer.
And then we use garden hose
to wrap around the
railroad rails.
- And we'd sell
it to the fullest.
To the kids in the neighborhood.
We ran it like a real
wrestling organization.
- We would advertise.
- Flyer the neighborhood.
- Flyer through the
neighborhood, house to house.
Come see N.A.W. kids wrestling.
We weren't waiting till
we grew up to wrestle.
We were like, we're
bringing wrestling to us.
- I got to make the hot dogs.
I had the hot dogs
going and chips.
It had free lunch.
When you came, you got a
hot dog and a bag of chips.
But they did it all themselves.
I don't know where a lot
of that talent came from,
but there was something
going on all the time.
When they started going to high
school, it was really hard.
Cause all of a sudden you
don't know where they are
or who their friends are
or what they're doing.
♪ You ask do we gangbang ♪
♪ Do we bang in a gang, mang ♪
♪ Do we bang bang ♪
♪ I'm a gang banger, man ♪
♪ I bang in a gang, mang ♪
♪ You can suck my wang, mang ♪
♪ Richie-boy, bitchy-boy ♪
♪ It's a Southwest thing ♪
- [Shaggy] That's the first
titty bar I ever went to
when I was 15.
- Oh, that's the Atlantis?
- No, no.
Atlantis I went
to when I was 14.
I put on a fake mustache.
- [Violent J] I could show
you the greatest place
to hide a dead body too.
- The Floobs ended up being
eventually the Inner City Posse,
which was their own gang.
- We were gonna
be some bad asses.
We were forming our own thing.
Even though, the fact of the
matter is, we didn't know shit.
- We were like gang-wannabe.
- [Violent J] We started tagging
ICP all over the neighborhood.
With rhinestone ICP hats on.
We were crazy for doing
what we were doing
because these were
real gangs here.
And we learned how to
get our ass kicked too.
- Yeah I learned how
to take a good beating.
- So we were walking
past these gang members
sitting on a porch
and they were just
giving us this mean eye.
So, boom, we just
march on through, man.
Like we're the Warriors.
Here we go, man.
And we give them
these mean mugs.
There must've been, I don't
know, 20 of them at the time.
And I was like, fuck
man, here we go.
Somebody says something.
I say, fuck you.
And fuck all you guys.
And we (imitates
heavy breathing).
All of a sudden,
man, the gang squad.
God couldn't have timed it
better for us to save our lives.
The gang squad pulls up
and Joe and I start walking.
We start walking
and these guys are booking
all around me, surrounded them.
And we're just
like, ah, ha ha ha.
So they get them.
We're at the corner.
Fuck, look at us.
You fucking asshole.
And fuck you.
- We were a fucking
miniature gang.
And so when this FBI
gang thing happened
25 years later, we
thought it was funny.
We laughed. We were like,
dang we're gang-bangers.
- Oh yeah, yeah, haha.
- Officially.
Dopeness.
They're saying Juggalos are
one of the 10 most
notorious real gangs.
So look at that
company right there.
- Bloods, Crips and MS-13 is
like, yeah, I'm in a gang.
♪ Straight outta Compton ♪
♪ Here's a crazy
brother named Ice Cube ♪
(heavy hip hop beats)
- [Violent J] Here
they are, man.
Greatest of all time,
the Beatles of rap.
The stuff that I was like,
I can't believe what they're
saying. Is that real, you know?
That's the shit I love man.
The stuff that scared me.
- When I was a kid, I had
that poster in my bedroom.
Vanessa Williams.
Look at at how fine she is, bro.
Fifteen years old,
this was on my wall.
And I don't know how many
times I nutted to it.
She ain't even naked.
My mom was a hippie.
So of course she
had the White Album,
that creepy-ass Queen record.
Everything from that,
the Blues Brothers.
There was always
music in my house.
Third, fourth grade or whatever.
That's when rap started
catching on a little bit.
Learned how to start
scratching, deejaying.
Herbie Hancock, he was the
first one to commercially
put a scratch on record.
And that was actually
the first scratch
I ever learned how to do.
- [Violent J] Endless
Michael Jackson.
I can't even find a bootleg,
a piece of video footage
or a song of Michael Jackson's
that I don't already know.
♪ Went R&B top ten hit ♪
♪ And we had T-Pain singing
all of our own shit ♪
♪ Fuck that, though,
yo, I'm a Juggalo ♪
♪ I'm a Jugga-lugga-lo
fo' sho' ♪
- Michael Jackson
is without a doubt
the biggest influence.
- You know you really
gotta dig somebody
to get a tattoo of them,
you know what I'm saying?
Oh!
- [Violent J] You take Michael
Jackson, mix him with NWA
and throw some
Pearl Jam in there.
(singing long notes)
And somehow out of
that weird concoction
is the Insane Clown Posse.
I mean, can't you
tell, listening to ICP?
We're huge Michael Jackson fans.
- Look at this horrible
picture they used.
He looks like the
fuckin' Toxic Avenger.
♪ Drop the motherfuckers
all the way to Delray ♪
- [Violent J] When we started
rapping, when we were kids,
this was gang ridden territory.
That's what we'd rap about.
And all of our friends
were like, yeah,
you know what I mean?
Make more shit about Southwest.
I was working at a gas station.
He was working at
a Coney island.
Every single fuckin' dime
went right into the pot.
My girlfriend's paycheck
That was plenty
to get us started.
We recorded our first EP.
And we were gangsters.
We were doing the gangster rap.
♪ Violent J servin'
ghetto hard street shit ♪
♪ You know it's potent when
the funky-ass beat hit ♪
♪ Rolling the dice and
we's hittin' point ♪
♪ ICP! ♪
♪ Out of Southwest Detroit ♪
♪ Running with a gang
of twenty street hoods ♪
- [Violent J] We had
our EP, Dog Beats,
in every record
store, everywhere.
- [Shaggy] We were given
a mission from God.
- They're not going to catch us,
we're on a mission from God.
- [Violent J] Went
to every record store
we could find in the phone book.
We used to go way out in the
middle of nowhere and steal
the phone books
from the Denny's.
- [Shaggy] Just so you
can look up record stores.
- Lot of people would put
them in their neighborhood
and that was it.
These aspiring
rappers, they sucked.
They had no heart,
man, no fuckin' drive.
♪ Inner City Posse's
got the Dog Beats ♪
♪ ICP we got the Dog Beats ♪
- [Violent J] With Dog
Beats, everywhere the
car could drive, we
had it on consignment.
- So many other local bands
in Detroit at the time
would lie to us.
- They would say, "How
many have you guys sold?"
And we'd say, oh man, "2,800".
And they would say, "Oh, you
guys got a ways to go, man.
We're at like 8,000."
- And then we
would be like, how?
- How?
- How are they doing it,
you know? They were lying.
But come to know
later they were lying,
but we would all of a
sudden have to meet 8,000.
So we would just go home and...
- [Shaggy] Must work harder.
- [Violent J] Must work harder.
- [Shaggy] All work.
- [Violent J] No
time for pleasure.
- No playing, no
♪ Bow wow wow yippy
yo yippy yay ♪
- Everywhere, flyers.
24 hours at Kinko's
all the time.
Our Kinko's hustle was
pretty immaculate, man.
They had these little blue
keys and it was a copy counter.
They had a resetter
right by the counter.
So we're like, yo we're
fucking stealing one of those.
Put like a 105 on the key,
but we really were
off like 2,000.
It was never hot chicks
up in there, but you know,
somebody would be banging a
broad, you know what I'm saying?
To get free color
copies in the back.
- [Kinko's Spokesperson] Kinkos.
Your branch shop is 24 hours
a day, seven days a week.
- [Rudy] I remember
one particular evening
before they went on stage.
Joe came along with some
clown wigs from Halloween.
I was like, this
is not gonna work.
My boys are rapping
about breaking into cars,
beating up guys, stealing,
fucking chicks.
And then here you come out with
a clown wig, you know, on stage.
And I remember the reaction of
the other artists backstage.
They're like, "The fuck
are these guys doing?"
- It's fun to paint your
face and hide behind that.
I can fuck up now, I'm a clown.
You already expect me
to do something stupid.
Cause I had clown paint on.
There's something
refreshing about that.
(audience cheering)
- [Rudy] And then the word
got around about these clowns.
These clowns, man,
with the wigs.
These guys were stealing shows.
They were coming in,
doing the fucking deal
and then leaving.
And everybody was
leaving with them.
♪ Hey, Faygo, say, Faygo, ♪
♪ What a way to go, Faygo ♪
♪ That precious
sauce, Juggalo Juice ♪
♪ Crack that fat boy,
let it go loose ♪
- [Violent J] Run-DMC had Adidas
and the Beastie Boys had
White Castle hamburgers.
- Let me get 800 cheeseburgers.
- [Violent J] So we had Faygo.
- [Shaggy] Lot of shit was just
natural shit that happened.
You know what I'm saying?
We had Faygo onstage.
Got excited, started
spraying it around and shit.
Kids fuckin' loved
that they were there.
We love fuckin' doing it. We
just did it more and more.
- [Violent J]
That's who we were.
We always had a two
liter, you know.
What the fuck, man?
We used to pass fuckin' two
liters like they were 40s.
- Straight up.
- And now I remember
this clearly.
I remember Joe saying
Insane Clown Posse.
The reaction from our crew was
(crickets)
Do you think?
♪ Gotta go, gotta get
before I get the wrap ♪
♪ Gotta chopped off head
chilling in my lap ♪
♪ Mr. Shrink, Mr.
Shrink, I'm sick ♪
♪ Lunatick-tick-tock,
it don't quit ♪
- [Rudy] We're watching the
crowds and there's like 75.
Then we're coming around
again and there's like 250.
We made fuckin' money.
Here's your money.
You got something.
I think it was 25
bucks or something,
but it was 25 bucks, dammit.
Who wants to go get a
fuckin' real job now?
- We thought we were rich, man.
- We were fuckin' getting paid.
We were driving new cars
because, well we
drove one new car
and that was for times we
needed to look impressive.
We had a Suzuki Sidekick
that way when we pulled
up to the in stores,
you know, we were fresh.
- [Shaggy] This right here
behind us is St. Andrews Hall.
Hey, who's playing here tonight?
Who?
- (Indistinct)
- Lights or something.
You know what I'm saying?
- Fudge?
- Did they say Fudge?
- The history in this building.
Nirvana, Pearl Jam, INXS.
- ICP.
♪ I'm running with a
Southwest street gang ♪
♪ And I never let my
Southwest meat hang ♪
♪ 'Cause you know
what ICP's all about ♪
♪ Take a brick off the street ♪
♪ And bust you in the mouth ♪
♪ Find the girl's daddy's rich ♪
♪ And his sweet little
angel's my sewer freak bitch ♪
- [Linda] It was just a real
thrill the first time I saw it,
when I went to the first
concert and I saw the Juggalos
in line going
around the building.
To me, I just
couldn't believe it.
I couldn't say, "get
a real job" anymore.
I wanted them to have the
Bruce Brothers Hobby Shop.
I keep asking, "is
that going to happen?"
And they said, "Well, maybe
someday it might happen."
- We had this wonderful
thing going on.
We're making money at it.
We're making a living.
We're able to raise our kids.
As far as albums we've sold,
if you combine them all,
I think it's something
around 10 million.
It might be as
much as 14 million.
- [Shaggy] Thirty years
later, we're still working.
Just like we always have.
We still put out
records, we still tour.
- [Violent J] We still move
merchandise all over the world.
You can't download a t-shirt.
You can't download
a pair of thongs.
(energetic hip hop beats)
It doesn't take a rocket
scientist to figure out
why we're still in business
and why this act became real.
Because it's destiny,
man, it's our destiny.
- [Video Narrator]
Psychopathic records presents
the infamous, world famous
Gathering of the Juggalos.
And this year's four day
long outdoor music festival
of freshness, flavor and
motherfucking freedom.
Fuck work.
Tell them your Juggalo
homies said they can
eat a dick up till they hiccup.
(whimsical music)
- [Shaggy] The Gathering is a
family reunion for Juggalos.
A weekend of pure bliss, fun
and nonstop flavor.
- Where did you get that?
- [Man Behind Camera] Get what?
- Get dick in your mouth!
- The reason why The
Gathering is so important
is because that is the
one week out of the year
where a Juggalo, who
is probably ostracized
in his or her community,
can unite with people
who are just like them.
- We're here this weekend
to fucking rage and party
and then clean up
after ourselves.
(epic orchestra crescendo)
- [Rob] It draws between five
and 10,000 people every year.
Juggalos that come
to the gathering,
they're the most diehard
Juggalos that there are.
- It took me 36
hours to get here.
- Traveling for about 55 hours.
- Dude, I quit both
my jobs to be here.
- I'm out on bond right now.
I'm not even supposed
to be here, real talk.
- I think if I died, my soul
would've made the journey.
I'd still be here.
- [Man Behind Camera] You
guys go to The Gathering?
(group exclaiming in unison)
- Ah hell no, man.
I heard them Juggalos are
like gang members and shit.
- They crazy!
- Yeah we don't
associate with that shit.
- These guys will
always be outcasts.
Juggalos will never be cool,
but that's the way
we like it though.
Hey brother, you okay?
- [Woman] Yeah.
- It was a woman.
My bad.
A lot of these women are
plus size, shall we say?
But they're walking around
in bikinis or topless.
And I love that because
it is such an affront
to the bullshit beauty standards
that we have in society.
If they were on a
normal beach somewhere,
everybody would be giving
them shit for that.
Here, no one cares.
- [Margee] Lots of
body pride here.
I have seen some women
who are so super proud
of their bodies and
that is very inspiring.
- [Jason] It doesn't
matter how you look.
It doesn't matter how
much money you make.
It doesn't matter what part
of the country you come from.
You come here,
you're just one of us.
It's just like in that old
movie, Freaks, you know.
One of us, one of us,
gooble, gobble, one of us.
We accept her, we accept her.
♪ One of us ♪
♪ We accept her, one of us ♪
♪ Gooble, gobble,
gooble, gobble ♪
♪ One of us, one of us ♪
- I think it's important
that people understand
that Juggalos are really
the last real subculture
left in America.
Because when you think about
all of the classic subcultures,
you think of punk, you
think of mods and rockers.
You think of goths.
Groups that were considered
a subculture at one time
have now been absorbed
by the mainstream.
In order for a group of people
to be considered a subculture,
the mainstream has to hate you.
You know, you can take
it back to England
in the seventies,
when you had the sex
pistols and you had
the Damned and all those
old school British punks.
They were not welcomed
with open arms.
The media and the government
wanted them shut down.
We live in an age where
all of those old previous
subcultures have ceased
to be subculture.
But Juggalos are
still a group that is
reviled and misunderstood.
And I think that those
are two of the attitudes
that are going to create any
subculture that has strength.
They're not going to like you,
and they're not going
to understand you.
- [Violent J] Why did the
FBI say Juggalos are a gang?
You know, you gotta ask the
fuckin' stupid-ass FBI that
because I don't
know why that is.
- [Shaggy] The FBI
never contacted us,
asked us what Juggalos
were about, anything.
- First I heard the report, I
thought it was just a rumor.
I think I asked
somebody to look it up
and it was a official.
Like official, like
a referee whistle.
It was like (whistle).
Hold up, you're
a gangster. What?
You're going to jail. What?
That's my first thought. What?
Are we going to jail?
Are we fuckin' get
locked up for this shit?
What does that make
us, gang leaders?
The thing is Juggalos
aren't a gang.
- Right.
- It kind of sickens me.
It's added so much to the
prejudice that we already had.
It was already the most
hated band in the world.
And if I wore a Insane
Clown Posse t-shirt
and I walked down the street,
some people would already treat
me like I'm less than them.
Now there's a government agency
telling everyone it's okay.
You can be prejudiced
against them.
They're criminal.
- If I get labeled a gang
member because of what the FBI
has labeled everybody, I could
lose my security clearance.
I could lose my job.
- I've had somebody make
the comment where I work,
"Oh, well, you're
a gang member."
I've never broken the law.
I've never been to
jail, at least, OK,
I worked in a jail,
but I've never been
to jail unwillingly.
♪ Say fuck the world ♪
♪ Fuck the world! ♪
♪ If I only could I'd
set the world on fire ♪
♪ Fuck 'em all ♪
- [Juggalo] I was
riding my bike.
I just had my backpack that
has a hatchet man on it.
The policeman pulled me over
and he started questioning me,
started searching me.
He asked me my gang
affiliation, what rank I was.
♪ Fuck all fifty
two states, oooh ♪
♪ And fuck you ♪
- The only probable cause that
they have is this right here.
- You can get stopped on
the street just for wearing
a Riddle Box sweatshirt
or sporting a Hatchetman
charm around your neck.
Cops can and they do stop you.
They will photograph you
and they'll take a picture
of your tattoo.
They'll put you on a gang
list just for wearing clothes.
- What the fuck is that?
You got like a mom taking
her 14 year old son,
to go to Hot Topic, to buy
an Insane Clown Posse shirt.
This kid's a gang member?
Somehow he's in the
same boat as MS-13?
Bullshit.
- Our daughter is
four years old.
So are they gonna consider
her a gang member?
- So I was trying to
reenlist in the military.
All the recruiters
pretty much like, hey,
ICP tattoos, no.
Gang affiliated, you know?
Cause it's a question on
there, are you affiliated
with any gang or have been?
- I got arrested
for a DUI and I got
separated into a gang unit.
Locked up with all
these gang members,
Nortes and Crips and Bloods.
I'm not going to
lie, it's terrifying.
♪ Fuck the police,
and the 5-0 too ♪
- [Male Juggalo] If police
look at your car and
they determine that's a Juggalo,
hundred percent, you're
getting pulled over.
- [Female Juggalo] They
start pulling stuff out.
We're like, this is gonna take
us hours to pack it again.
It took us four hours
to put it in there.
We get back on the
expressway and sure enough,
if we don't pass the same
cops and they have a Juggalo
pulled over and all their
stuff pulled out of their car.
- People were getting fucked
with on a major level.
- We did not understand
the magnitude of how it
would fuck up Juggalos.
- Didn't know the
repercussions of it, you know?
- And once we started
getting the reports,
the jokes stopped and
the freshness ended
and it just started sucking.
- [Crowd] Fuck the FBI!
Fuck the FBI!
- You know if this were to
happen to a band
that America liked,
the country would be
up in arms about this.
But it happened to the
Insane Clown Posse.
So it's a joke.
Stop and take us
out of the equation.
Look what they're saying.
- If the Juggalos qualify
as a criminal street gang,
many other groups of fans
could be similarly categorized.
For example, fans of
particular sports teams.
A lot of the gangs
use sports memorabilia
as their gang logo.
If you're in a gang neighborhood
wearing that particular
jersey or cap or whatnot,
law enforcement can use
that as probable cause
for stopping and searching.
- The gang label was misguided,
but it was also very
intentional because I feel like
America hates the poor.
- Right now I work
in a restaurant.
It's okay.
- Oh yeah, me? I work
at a hardware store.
I admit to doing that.
- I work at taco bell for now.
I mean, it's
something to get by.
- I do roofing for a living.
- Oh, I mow grass.
- [Female Juggalo]
99% Of my friends,
they're in the service
industry, fry cooks,
just on the bottom
chain of society.
So to see any unity between
these people is a major threat.
Like if they're going
to come after these kids
who put on face paint
and throw cheap soda,
I mean really, come on.
It's the most harmless thing.
If they're gonna
to come after that,
what are they going
to come after next?
(baby wailing)
- Yeah, we've been
together for 16 years now.
We've been married for seven.
- Eight.
- Eight, oh my goodness, yes.
- I love you, bye.
Love you.
- [Natalie] There he goes.
Bye babe.
Today I got ready for
work with you guys.
I drove to work.
I love what I do.
They have me on their pamphlets.
It was just like any
normal, typical day.
Except for, you know,
you guys watched me
out in the parking lot.
At the end of my workday after
I'd seen all my patients,
I received a phone call from
the head of human resources,
wanting to know what this
documentary was about.
So I told her it was about
music that we listen to
and how the music is associated
with being in a gang.
And they terminated me.
- It's like some
crazy communist shit.
I don't know what
a communist is,
but I know this feels
like some big, powerful,
scary government bullshit.
- There's no word to
describe how insane,
how crazy, how asinine it is.
I'm about to start
making words up.
And just think if
we just rolled over
and took it up the ass,
where would it stop?
If we don't do something
about it, who's next?
- Check this out, there's
some real shit here, man.
Real shit man, all right?
Fuckin' major news here.
Three letters, the FBI.
We're not just laying down
and taking it up the ass.
(crowd chanting)
Check it out, we're
taking the name Juggalo
the fuck back from
them motherfuckers,
you know what I'm saying?
We have the best
legal representation
money can buy.
There he is right here, Farris.
Give it up for our
attorney, ya'll.
- You all have a family
attorney now, all right?
We're gonna lay the
law down on the FBI
for the whole fam.
(crowd chanting)
- People always joke and ask
me if I'm going to show up
to court in face pain
or something like that.
If the opportunity presents
itself, maybe I will, but...
I focus on a lot of DUIs,
a lot of possession
of marijuana cases,
a lot of misdemeanor cases.
I see this big guy at an
ATM with his wife and kids
and figure out that
it's Violent J.
So I said, "You probably
don't meet too many Juggalos
that are lawyers."
And I was like, "Let
me give you my card.
If you ever need
anything, give me a call.
I'll do it for free."
And I figured I'd never
hear from them again, ever.
Violent J announced
that Juggalos could come
to this makeshift
office that I had made
at The Gathering and
fill out a statement
and I could interview
them and stuff like that.
There was a line out the
door and around the corner
at that trailer for
people making statements.
Story after story of people
that were doing nothing wrong,
but were being treated
like criminals.
We filed a Freedom of
Information Act request
to find out why the FBI
put them on the gang list.
What we got was
shocking and surprising.
Literally looked like Google
research of some news articles.
The majority of it
was random alarmist
local news articles off of
the internet saying that
there was some crime, whether
it's vandalism, assault,
stealing, larceny, and the
people happened to be Juggalos.
And that was what they
sent us as support for them
putting Juggalos
on the gang list.
Basically what the FBI said
is we're just reporting what
these local law enforcement
officers are telling us.
That was their other excuse.
From the outside looking in,
it might look like a gang.
It also looks a heck of a
lot like any other fan base.
It starts with Juggalos, but
it's a very slippery slope.
People who listen
to gangster rap.
Lil Wayne claims to be
related to the Bloods.
Maybe people going
to his concerts,
maybe some of them are Bloods.
Maybe they're all Bloods.
And then that's sort of where
this has snowballed into.
That's what's at stake.
Whether we live in a
free country or not.
Whether we live in an
America where everything's
gonna to be censored and
you're going to be afraid
to express who you are.
- [Juggalo In Group]
I swear to God.
- [Juggalo Interviewee]
The FBI, they might as well
be hating on fans of KISS.
Are they gang members? No.
Why the fuck does that
make us gang members?
It's a bunch of
discrimination bullshit
and there's no reason for it.
- You just find a
small group of people
that most people don't
give a crap about
and you box them in and you
say those people are bad.
Then you just make
everybody else say,
oh, well screw those
people, they're bad.
Well, if you box everybody
up enough and you make
all these small
individual bad groups,
then everybody's
bad and everybody's
fighting one another.
- If having bad taste
in music was a crime,
every Parrothead in the world
would be on the gang list.
(crowd whoop whooping)
- [Thomas] Here in Los Angeles,
MS-13 had a
notorious reputation,
kind of like Insane Clown Posse,
of being kind of
eerie and mysterious
because some of its members,
probably less than
1%, were Satanists.
I spent over 16 years
researching the MS-13 gang
on a daily basis.
I was hanging out with
active members of MS
from the wannabes to the OGs.
I would bring pizza or soda pop.
The problem was when I was
started getting paged at
two o'clock in the
morning, right?
I need a ride home, Thomas.
The FBI assessment of the
Juggalos as a non-traditional,
or hybrid gang, states
that many Juggalo subsets
exhibit gang-like behavior
and engage in criminal
activity and violence.
So what is a street gang?
The federal definition
is an association
of three or more individuals.
Who's members collectively
identify themselves
by adopting a group identity.
(crowds exclaiming)
Who's purpose is
in part to engage
in criminal activity and which
uses violence or intimidation
to further criminal enterprise.
- We're not a
criminal organization.
We're not even an organization.
We're not organized.
- [Gathering Attendee] Just
because I'm wearing this shirt
that's got the Hatchetman
on the back and everything.
It doesn't mean
I'm a gang banger.
It doesn't mean I'm going
to hurt you or kill you.
We're just one big family.
We look out for each other.
- We look out for each other.
Half of us ain't got parents.
Half of us ain't got
nobody to give us nothing.
- [Juggalo] It's just the
loyalty they bring to you.
That's what makes
a person family.
I'm family, she's family.
Hell, shit, all
of you are family.
Wanna come by later
and get fucked up?
We can get fucked up.
Don't matter, we're family.
- It means a lot,
we like family.
This is like a family.
It means a lot to me.
I love them, they love me.
- The Juggalo family
is the only people
that I can trust.
That I know if I need
something, they're there.
- There's no more gang
members in Juggalos
than there is anything else.
We sold 10 million
records, guaranteed.
10 million people, take
a comb through that?
Whatever you're looking
for is gonna be in there.
- [Shaggy] They say that
because some kid committed some,
even a horrific crime, that
happens to be a Juggalo,
that just means all Juggalos
are criminals and gang members?
It's crazy.
People that listen to
Mozart kill people.
I'm sure Jack the Ripper
loves some Mozart.
- [TV Reporter] Two
men calling themselves
Juggalos are arrested after
the body of 21 year old,
Michael Goucher is
found in the woods
stabbed more than 20 times.
- We've got multiple individuals
committing gang related crimes,
gang motivated crimes.
And they're using
the name Juggalo.
- The media spotlight
is on this thing.
The media blew it up.
It got everybody in an uproar.
- [Male TV Reporter] A Juggalo
is responsible for attacking
a man on a bike
with a meat cleaver.
- [Male TV Anchor] The
FBI cited a robbery and
a beating of a homeless man.
They also cited a Juggalo
who shot and wounded
a couple in Washington state.
- [Male News Reporter] The
two suspects involved actually
had their faces painted
like clowns at the time.
- [Female News Anchor]
Shops, restaurants and bars
under attack in one of
Portland's trendiest
neighborhoods.
- [Male TV Reporter]
A threatening message
laced with profanity.
A group called the Juggalo
family, taking responsibility.
- We're just doing
what we do, man.
We're doing it for the
Juggalos, you know?
Every business sells
to their clientele.
Well that's all we're doing.
- We're not going to
water down what we do.
If people like it, they like it.
If not, fuck 'em
anyhow, you know?
- [Bashir] A number of people
who have been associated with
acts of violence and murder
have had some kind of
connection to ICP and Juggalos.
They're no longer regarded as
innocent lovers of your music.
- I say bull(beep).
I say it's not true.
- Let me give you an example.
In February, 2006.
Individual attacks people
with a machete in a gay bar,
he kills a police
officer in traffic stop,
he call himself a Juggalo.
- [911 Caller]
Someone's been shot.
- [911 Operator]
Somebody's been shot?
- [911 Caller]
Someone's been shot,
you have to get here now.
(swell of orchestra music)
♪ Were so gallantly streaming ♪
♪ And the rocket's red glare ♪
♪ The bombs bursting in air ♪
♪ Gave proof through the night ♪
♪ That our flag
was still there ♪
♪ O say does that
star-spangled banner yet wave ♪
- [Lt. Schoenfeld] We are
here at the 29th annual
Utah Gang Conference.
This is our opportunity to
teach our community partners
about current gang trends
and give them the information
to use in their daily functions.
♪ Gang signs, up in the sky ♪
- What I do is I teach
basically hip hop music
and how it's gang involved.
If you have questions about
what some of this means,
there's a definition book.
And for the safety
of the presenter,
do not share any information
about the presenters.
- [Man Behind Camera]
Oh shit, turn it off.
- Take pictures, videos.
- [Lt. Schoenfeld] I think
that the focus of that
threat assessment
was on Salt Lake City
because we were seeing
heavy activity from our
Juggalo groups that made us
identify them as gang members.
From about 1996 until
kind of the mid 2000s,
we dealt with Juggalos out
on our west side a lot.
- [Nelson] There were some
problems between Juggalos
and members of other
gangs that became
relatively common for a
couple years in Salt Lake
to have people who affiliated
themselves with Juggalos
to be fighting with somebody
who was a member
of another gang.
In the summer of 2008,
there was a serious assault
involving two Juggalos
that I charged
as an attempted murder.
Two Juggalos attacked a young
man with a large hunting knife
and a battle axe that was
mounted onto a golf club.
Stabbed him multiple times,
took multiple swings at
his shoulder and neck area.
- We get a call of aggravated
assault in progress.
Initial information
given by our dispatch was
two male suspects, tan Nissan.
My partner finds
a Juggalo pendant.
It's a Hatchetman hanging
on the fence of the house.
I see this tan Nissan
approach me and I'm like,
no, this can't be true.
And I see the Hatchetman
on the back of the window.
And so I was like, you know
I got to pull this car over.
We're like face to face.
And I noticed as
I'm talking to him,
I could still see some dry
blood splatter on his face.
I end up doing a
search of the vehicle.
I pull out all these weapons,
lay them out on the
trunk of the car.
Daggers, hatchets.
There was just a whole
arsenal of weapons.
- [Nelson] The victim's
neck was just filleted open
from the axe.
It was one of the
more bloody and
disturbing crime
scenes I've ever seen.
I mean, it looks
like a slasher movie.
- [Det. Afatasi] We follow
a national definition.
Group of three or more people,
common name symbol identifier,
that engage in
criminal activity.
You know, Juggalos, they fit
under those three criterias.
It's fair to say that
some were gang members.
They're violent.
You know, the music is violent.
♪ I stab people, 4,
5 people everyday ♪
♪ I tried to see a shrink
to stop that shit ♪
♪ But it ain't no fucking way ♪
- [Interviewer] Did you
want to stab people?
- [Violent J] Sometimes.
Maybe in my subconscious
anger, but not in real life.
We're sitting here
in clown paint.
- How do you write a line
like, from Pluto to your anus,
we are underground famous?
- That's dope, man. Welcome
to the world of rap.
- What does it mean if you
call a song Imma Kill U?
- [Shaggy] It means
I'ma kill you.
But I mean how you take
that, I mean are you
like a grown retard
or something?
You're gonna go out and do it?
- [Violent J] Are you some
kinda murderer to begin with?
- This is what you say
in To Catch a Predator.
♪ I stab 'em in the neck
first, 'cause it hurts ♪
♪ Hit 'em where
the blood squirts ♪
♪ Carve his whole face
off and make him eat it ♪
♪ Chain him up by the foot
in my basement bleeding ♪
- We're entertainers
you know what I mean?
- So you don't really mean-
- No we'd be in
prison right now.
- We'd be in prison for life.
- I myself was molested as a
child, you know what I mean?
- Really?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- [Linda] I always wonder if
it would have been different.
You know you always think,
I wonder if I hadn't married
an asshole, if their lives
would have been different.
- This guy was like the worst
kind of human being ever.
You know what I mean?
He'd get super angry
at Duke, our dog
and he used to chase him around
the yard and like kick him.
For us, We just stayed out
of the house all the time.
One of the kind of
lingering damages
is I don't like to be
touched by guys at all.
I just snap.
You know.
- [Margee] My name is Margee
Kerr and I'm a sociologist
and I'm working on a book
about how and why we engage
with thrilling and
scary material.
And coming to The Gathering...
(passing motorist hollers)
I was reading about
how negative things
happen at The Gathering.
But Juggalos themselves
would state that
they loved each other.
It was all about family,
all about respect.
So I saw this huge discrepancy
between what the people
themselves were saying and
what outsiders were saying.
And for a sociologist,
that's like a huge red flag.
So I wanted to come
and see for myself.
I see a lot of parallels
between the motivations
behind hardcore kind of
gangster rap and ICP.
Both are speaking about
their experiences,
living in a lower
socioeconomic status,
being discriminated against,
having people judge them.
- You ever been broke?
You ever had a family member,
maybe alcoholic
or drug addicted,
that's impacting your life?
Somebody who's just struggling,
just trying to make it till the
next week or the next month.
- You're not one of
the popular kids.
You're not playing sports.
You're not in any of the clubs.
- Growing up, I was kind of
tortured, made fun of a lot.
My mom moved me from
school to school.
- I was raised in Philadelphia,
in the Catholic Church,
in the 80s and the 90s.
And what went down
there was fucked.
We're so angry and we're so
hurt because as children,
we were abused.
♪ Ticket, please, thanks,
walk trough the doors ♪
♪ Into the halls of
illusions, visit yours ♪
♪ And see what could
have and should have ♪
♪ And would have been real ♪
♪ But you had to fuck
up the whole deal ♪
- [Margee] I think
that for a lot of fans,
they probably are connecting
to the violent lyrics
because it may be
similar to the things
that they've
experienced themselves.
You know, it seems like
there are some people here
who've had some
pretty tough times,
and I think that they are
connecting to the music
just as any fan base
would connect to lyrics
that are going to speak to them.
- [Violent J] We make
music for people like us.
Broken homes, hard times,
dealing with painful
shit in their life.
It's real anger.
It's your opinion amplified.
♪ When they were kids, you'd
beat 'em and leave 'em home ♪
♪ And even whip 'em with
the cord on the telephone ♪
♪ And that reminds me, man,
hey, you've got a call ♪
♪ Watch your step to
hell, it's a long fall ♪
- [Linda] An ICP song
is like a three minute
Stephen King novel.
If you want to know what's in
the mind of a serial killer,
you're curious and
you want to go there,
but don't live there.
It's a different place to go.
It's make-believe
and it's very graphic.
♪ In the back of my truck,
Chuck the chainsaw ♪
♪ Usually chop wood,
but that ain't all ♪
♪ It's a bit strange all
up in your mid-range ♪
♪ Cut a hole in your
head 'til I hit brain ♪
- [Juggalette] It just
blows all of our minds
how somebody can
make a horror movie
and it's all graphic and gory
and that's okay and acceptable.
But we can't sing a song about
mass murder makes me happy.
That's catchy.
It's funny.
- In a way ICP's
music was so healing.
I didn't need to
stand up and rage out
because it's kind of like
the clowns did it for me.
They allowed me to
laugh at all that pain
and laugh through that pain.
- It allowed me to vent things,
get things off my chest.
- [Male ICP Fan]
All the other music,
no matter how cool the beat is,
when you listen to
what they're saying,
you're not really
relating to it.
These guys are
talking about, hey,
we're outcasts and
we don't give a shit.
(videogame gunfire)
- [Violent J] Come here, Rust.
Big 'ole Rusty dog.
- [Ruby] Did you
sing the Rusty song?
- Rusty dog.
What are you doing, Rusty dog?
I'll tell you how we met.
She was working at a Friday's.
- TGIFriday's in Minneapolis.
- And she was the girl
at the front that's like,
"Hi, can I seat you?"
And she sat us down, all set.
Put the tables together
and I was like, man,
I gotta step today.
- No, I didn't sit you down.
- Obsolete information.
- [Michelle] I have a
better memory than you.
- [Violent J] And
then I was like,
"What're you doing tonight?"
What made me super fresh was
I was leaning like this,
but I wasn't leaning
against nothing.
I was just leaning
against air like that.
And I was like,
"Why don't you come with
me to this concert?"
- I said, who, what concert?
- "What concert
are we going to?"
And I was like, "mine".
She came to the show,
jumped on the bus with me.
And then all you saw
was lights and exhaust
as we pulled out of town
together, never to come back.
- [Michelle] It's true, the
next day I went to Denver.
With him, it's true.
♪ In yo face! ♪
- We're not young
and wild no more.
It's not wilding
out, getting crazy.
♪ I pop out the box,
swing on a spring ♪
♪ Big Violent J with
the axe out, shing ♪
- [Shaggy] Violent J and Shaggy
2 Dope are derived from us.
Of course Joe and Joey
don't go out cutting necks
and chopping heads off
and dragging bodies around
from our car and shit.
♪ Smash thru the glass
as the fireworks blast ♪
♪ Shaggy the clown here
to murda some ass ♪
We're family men.
We both have a wife and
kids and families and shit.
I don't believe Shaggy
2 Dope or Violent J
really have families
cause they're
too busy murdering people.
♪ Step yo ass back before
the hatchet attacks ♪
♪ And ya catch a few
hacks from the axe ♪
- His music isn't for moms.
The only thing I'm
really familiar with
is in the beginning.
Because I've stopped
listening now to his music.
I used to listen
to it all the time.
It scared me because
I would wake up
with that tune in my mind.
♪ I be the strangler,
known coast to coast ♪
♪ And I turn any
thug into a ghost ♪
♪ In yo face ♪
Plus, I know Joe Bruce.
Violent J is a made up person.
You know, he's
different than my son.
Joe Bruce is very
emotional and loving.
Violent J is streetwise
and he's crude.
♪ I shook the hand of Satan
with a cross in my palm ♪
♪ Burnt all the flesh
all the way up his arm ♪
♪ I wasn't scared, I
was giddy to do it ♪
♪ Then I lopped his
head off and threw it ♪
♪ In yo face ♪
- The masses just
hear fuck, bitch,
I'll stab you,
dobeedo, you know?
But there's so much
more underlying.
- [Linda] One of the things
that I always thought was true
was when you have to
make a major decision,
your first instinct
on it is from God.
And then the rest of
your doubt is the devil
trying to talk you out of it.
And I was brought up knowing
that there's something
bigger than us.
You know, it's something more.
- [Violent J]
Juggalos, they hear it.
The messages in the lyrics.
Each album gives people a
chance to look at themselves
in different ways.
If our music sounds like
endless garbage to you,
you're not a Juggalo.
You're not meant to hear it.
- When somebody first
handed me an ICP CD,
I realized it was starting
to answer questions
I didn't know I had.
What is death?
What forever really means.
What's going on
in the afterlife?
- It tells you a way
to live your life.
You know, treat
people with respect.
Make sure that you live
your life right from wrong.
Don't judge people.
- [Violent J] I believe
it's the one and only
holy man, you know.
I believe it's
God talking to us.
- Señor Jesus.
- And we are meant to talk
to the Juggalos, you know?
♪ Where's God ♪
♪ Where's God when
shit goes down ♪
- [Linda] Joe told me we
are the transportation
to heaven or hell.
What you do with
it is up to you.
If you listen to the
message, it's there.
But if you just listen
to the gruesome, well,
that's up to you.
♪ This life is tricky,
mean and strange ♪
♪ You can only be sure
about one thing, change ♪
♪ For worse or for
better, maintain ♪
- [Rob] They're showing
you the horror of life.
They're showing you the comedy.
There's like all his
comedy in all their music.
And then there's
all this violence.
But then there's also
these touching songs
that are uplifting and
trying to guide you toward
living a righteous life.
♪ Truth is happiness
is in your own head ♪
♪ How you perceive shit
and believe it is ♪
It's like what a carnival
really aspires to be.
All these wonders,
all these horrors
and also an enlightenment.
And it's why they've
endured for so long.
People are still captivated
by what their message is.
- [Juggalo Fan] The
government can probably find
200 Juggalos, say these
are all gang members
and I can show you
20,000 than aren't.
- [Announcer] Let's give a fuck.
- These holidays, every
kid deserves some toys.
Let's get a fuck!
The kids deserve it, man!
The fucking kids!
- [Natalie] Juggalos
have coat drives
and they donate turkeys
during Thanksgiving.
♪ Do you notice and
recognize miracles ♪
- At home we do
canned food drives.
- [Male News Reporter] A group
of Insane Clown Posse fans
grab some brooms, shovels
and some trash bags
and hit the streets of
Buffalo to help clean up.
♪ Are you a believer
in miracles ♪
♪ Pure motherfucking
magic, right? ♪
- Custom made jerseys,
worn only once by
Violent J and Shaggy 2 Dope.
- $3,500!
- Remember this helps
out a fellow Juggalo
and he's gonna be getting
a lung transplant.
- At Hallowicked, which is
their Halloween concert,
If you bring in canned
food, they donate it
to the charities and
they'll give you a free CD.
They make sure you can only
bring in good canned food,
can't bring in like corn.
You gotta bring in like
SpaghettiOs and stuff.
- It's not a publicity
stunt, you know?
It's just something
that's right to do.
- Nobody ever wants to
talk about the good stuff.
The bad stuff is what sells, so.
- [Shawn] Have your chest out
like you're fuckin'
bad-ass, you ready to fight.
- [Zach] I can't do that.
- [Shawn] Think of like a
tough song in your head.
- [Jade] I get called
bad-ass every day at school.
- [Shawn] 'Cause you
are a bad-ass, ready?
- [Zach] I can't stop.
- [Jade] I have to do it again.
- [Shawn] Redo.
- [Jade] You can't
say, don't smile.
- [Shawn] OK, get your smile
out, get your smile out.
- [Zach] I smiled.
- [Shawn] My room is a
explosion of ICP.
I'm a collector of
ICP memorabilia.
I think even if I
didn't like the band,
I would like their merchandise.
It's just really cool.
The clowns are awesome.
Of course I've got my
Ringmaster blanket.
My Zippos.
This was in the backstage
for the wrestling area.
That's off of
Violent J's shower.
It's a very small town.
You do tend to get looks
when you dress
differently than most.
Like people you're
holding the door open for,
they give you just
the strangest.
What the?
They're like, "Oh that's
a nice Kokopelli."
You're like, "Dude, it's
not a Kokopelli, all right?"
My Hatchetman will stab
your Kokopelli, all right?
My name is Shawn Wolf,
AKA Sly Guy Smooth.
I've been a Juggalo
since I was 16.
I have raised my kids that way.
They know all about it.
Hi, Jade Bug.
- Hi.
- How was school?
That's my Jade Bug.
What are you 17 now?
- Yeah.
- [Shawn] By two years old,
she knew who Violent
J and Shaggy were.
We had a poster up, you're
like "Oh well who's that?"
"That's Violent J."
"And who's that?"
"That's Shaggy 2 Dope."
- I'm glad that he's into
the same music I am or else
we would be butting
heads a lot with
how loud we play our music.
- [Shawn] Zach's
birthday is today.
Same as Shaggy 2 Dope's.
And he just turned 15.
- My dad bought me
tickets and a VIP pass
to the ICP concert
tomorrow night.
Yes, I'm extremely excited.
I can't really express
excitement though.
I don't know, it's kind of
a weird thing that I have.
- [Shawn] How are you buddy?
- [Cody] Not bad,
how are you, Dad?
- [Shawn] Cody is my oldest
one, he just turned 18.
- How was school?
- Not bad.
- [Shawn] Me and Cody's mom had
like a one-time
deal after school.
I was only 15 at the
time and just stupid kid.
Young, dumb, full of come
kind of thing, you know?
And so she got knocked up.
I went over there one day and
she'd moved to California.
Just didn't tell me or nothing
like that, just took off.
When he was about seven,
she decided to put
him into a boys' home.
- Don't throw it too high.
- [Shawn] She just
abandoned him.
Didn't come back and try and
visit him or nothing like that.
And they actually started
trying to work with me
to get custody of him.
I want my kids.
I was raised without a dad
and I would never
do that to my kids.
Somewhere after about a year,
they finally sent
somebody out here
to come in, like inspect
your home and make sure
it's livable for him.
We invited this
lady into our house.
You see my living
room and stuff.
It has nothing to do with ICP.
It's totally family oriented.
Once I brought her into my
room and she saw, you know,
all of this and it was a bit
overwhelming for her, I think.
They flat out told me, no,
we're not going to give you
custody of your kid.
I mean, my heart just dropped
to the floor, you know?
And then they told me why.
I would portray possible
gang affiliations.
Man, it's just a straight
kick in the nuts.
You know, I really don't even
know how to describe that
besides flat out, you
put me on the ground
and beat the hell out of me.
I'd much rather have that than
someone denying me my kid.
- For most of my life, I
mainly felt like I was alone.
There was no one I could
talk to, not even therapists.
I've been in group homes
pretty much since I was six.
And my one shot at
getting out was him
and it was all just
vanished as soon as
they said that he
couldn't have it
all because of some ICP thing.
A group home is pretty much
where kids go who have been
labeled all these
labels like ADHD, PTSD.
Little kids to 18.
In a way it's kind of like
a leeway juvenile place.
Due to some of it, I don't
think I was able to mature
as quickly as a lot of other
people, such as my sister,
who's always been around a
family member or has always had
someone there whenever
she needed to talk.
- People are talking
about, well, why don't you
just get rid of the ICP stuff?
ICP is not the problem.
As it is now, he just turned 18.
I personally never
got custody of him.
- [Zach] Flip up a burger.
- As we come around,
we got our VIP Faygos.
And the vest that I'm wearing
is actually Violent
J's vest that he wore.
Hello?
Hey man. Yeah, I'm doing an
interview right now, man.
Let me call you back.
What?
So my friend Kyle just called
up and said that the ICP show
in Mesa just got canceled.
This is my kids' first ICP show.
That's crushing right now.
We have no idea why yet.
- [Woman On Phone]
Can I help you?
- Yeah, I'm actually calling
about the ICP show tomorrow.
I heard he got canceled.
Is that correct?
- [Woman On Phone] Yes,
it has been canceled.
We were only told that because
of the logistical issues.
We're not told why.
- All right, thank you much.
- Well that's not very fair.
- [Shawn] Maybe they
can use our tickets
for the Tuscon show.
Get ahold of the
promoter or something.
Fuzzy, I know, oh, I
can get a hold of Fuzzy.
- I have no idea who that is.
- [Female TV Host] What
specifically are your concerns
about a group like
this coming here?
- [Male Caller] Violence.
- [Female News Anchor] The
concert is called Shockfest
and one of the headlining bands
is the Insane Clown Posse,
which is known for its
fans, the 'Juggaloos'.
A group designated
as a gang by the FBI.
♪ Where can I go they
don't want me no mo' ♪
- People get most
of their information
about street gangs
from the media.
We're hardwired to pay
attention to threat.
And so the media uses that
to get audience share.
So they have an agenda to
find the most sensationalistic
stories to tell about
the street gangs.
- [Male News Announcer]
A look at the Juggalos
and the danger they
present to Northern Nevada.
- Come October 8th, 3,000
of them will be admitted
inside of these doors.
- According to one
city councilman,
violence is a concern.
- [Leonardo] We have
too much violence
in Fort Myers as it is.
Why do we want to add to it?
- [Female News Reporter]
In an email, he wrote,
I Googled Juggalos and
did not like what I saw.
- [Male TV Reporter] And
because this is a city facility,
the city council
could decide to cancel
the concert altogether.
- [Jason] We found a
spot in Kaiser, Missouri
for The Gathering.
The camp owners, they knew
exactly what the Juggalos were.
I didn't hold anything back.
And mind you, Kaiser is
where the Hell's Angels
have held their
national biker rally.
And it's like, OK so Hell's
Angels are welcome, no problem.
The media caught wind of it.
It was generating all this fear.
And so you have all
these people in Kaiser,
they're just reading
the headlines
and they see Juggalos, gang.
Those two words side by side.
The townsfolk were actually
calling the camp owners
and saying they were arming
themselves, getting ready
for the gang to come in.
(gunshots)
Like they thought Juggalos
were gonna come storming
in there and start destroying
like roaming the
streets at night
causing destruction
and havoc or something.
The campground owners pulled
the plug on the whole thing.
And we were left without
a Gathering grounds.
We were crushed.
We absolutely were crushed.
Since the Juggalos were
first labeled as a gang,
more and more The
Gathering suffered.
Like last year we
ended up losing a lot.
- We lost a great deal of money.
I believe something along
the lines of $700,000.
Then it was reported
on the news that
we couldn't pay all the vendors
and we were having
financial problems.
We're not a multi-billion
dollar company, you know?
- [Shaggy] That's not like
a Pepsi's money that lost.
That's not Dorito's.
There is no corporate
sponsor to The Gathering.
That's fresh out of his
pocket and my pocket.
- If The Gathering
tanks, we lose our ass.
- You don't know what's going
to happen at The Gathering.
Is it going to get raided?
Everybody's talking about it.
I don't believe it
will ever happen,
but I wouldn't want it to happen
and it very much could.
- Retailers dropping
our line of merchandise
because it's gang paraphernalia.
- We used to have such a
good working relationship
with Hot Topic.
And now, since the
gang thing came out,
they don't even carry us.
- [Shaggy] Dropped it.
- [Violent J] It's really
fuckin' up our business, man.
My daughter's only seven.
And I have to maintain
this till she's 18.
I had to be able to
take care of her.
It gets harder and harder
every year, you know?
We got to keep staying relevant.
Keep making the
right moves and plays
because we got a long way to go.
Like without this, I don't
know what I'd be doing.
You know?
- [Shawn] One time, man,
I'm standing there and
I'm like in the front row.
I got hit with a full
two liter of Faygo
on top of my head, dude.
Almost knocked me the hell out.
I wasn't paying attention.
That sucker came right down
on top of my head, dude.
I got messed up, but then I
got a full Faygo out of it.
Oh, It's All Over,
that's a great song.
Do you guys know
this song at all?
♪ It's all over ♪
♪ Here we go, in the air we go ♪
♪ Huh, walking along my path ♪
♪ The city has morphed
into a blood bath ♪
♪ Some are looting,
others shooting ♪
♪ The Devil's in the sky
and he's recruiting ♪
♪ Tornados twisting
through downtown ♪
♪ Throwing buses
and trucks around ♪
♪ Me, I climb the
roof of my house ♪
♪ Spread my arms out and sing ♪
♪ It's all over ♪
♪ Here we go, in the air we go ♪
- What's up, homie?
- [Shaggy] You all right?
- [Violent J] What's up, man?
- [Shawn] These are
my kids right here.
Their first show.
- [Jade] I'm kind of nervous.
- [Violent J] This shirt
had to be your dad's, right?
When a ninja comes up to us
and he chooses to tell
me about how the FBI
is fucking him up,
you feel like you can
save this kid somehow.
Or make things better.
That's hard to deal
with emotionally.
- Thank you, Chop.
That's fuckin' awesome, dude.
Thank you guys.
Have a good show.
- [Violent J] First
time seeing ICP?
- Oh man, my heart's
racing right now.
- Two whoops.
- You're giving us these?
- I brought them for you guys.
- This is awesome!
I have so much trouble
at meet and greets.
You know, I'm sweating under
the makeup the whole time.
What do you say to a
kid when he comes up
and peels his shirt
off and his whole back
is a big mural to your music?
- Glad the music could be
there for you, brother.
- Yeah, no doubt, man.
- What could you say
that's good enough?
It's just a lot, man.
- [Michelle] You
know you worry a lot.
You think about your family.
It just takes a toll
on your brain, babe.
- It gives me panic attacks.
I wouldn't want my worst enemy
to suffer from a panic attack.
You're sitting there
watching TV, all of a sudden
you're about to
get hit by a train
and you don't know what the
fuck is causing the fear.
When you come out of it,
you're just exhausted.
Let's talk about something else.
- Okay.
♪ Who loaned ya money,
homie, who owes ya cash ♪
♪ Who taught you how to
use a bong for the grass ♪
♪ I don't know much
but I gotta assume ♪
♪ When ya hit ya first neden ♪
♪ Ya homies was in
the other room ♪
♪ We talkin' about
homies, homies ♪
- [Michael] I like
The Allman Brothers
and Earth, Wind & Fire
and Stevie Wonder.
The closest thing
to rebellious music
growing up was, uh, Aerosmith.
I don't listen to
Aerosmith anymore.
- [Farris] We filed our first
lawsuit the summer of 2012.
That lawsuit was
just to give the FBI
a chance to explain themselves.
They didn't really have
a good explanation.
- [Male News Anchor]
Now the members of the
Insane Clown Posse
and several Juggalos
have partnered with the
ACLU to sue the FBI.
- This morning, the ACLU
filed a federal lawsuit
against the
Department of Justice
and against the FBI
challenging the designation
of a musical fan base
as a criminal gang.
- [Saura] One thing
that we should get clear
right from the start,
organized crime has nothing
to do with the Juggalo culture.
- Discrimination based
on the type of music
a person listens to
is flat out ridiculous
and un-American bull shit.
We are official
plaintiffs in a lawsuit
against the FBI officially.
We're going to war with the FBI.
- ICP is not defendants
and it feels good.
You know what I'm saying?
- It's like a fucking big-ass
cheer like (imitates cheer).
- The ACLU, they don't play.
And it's gotta be a real cause
for them to get involved.
- [Michael] The American
Civil Liberties Union
is the oldest and largest
organization in the country
dedicated to defending the
civil rights and civil liberties
of all people in this country.
We work on a wide,
wide variety of cases,
including freedom of
speech, freedom of religion,
police misconduct,
voting rights,
rights of people of
color, rights of women,
rights of LGBT persons.
We are here to ensure
that our country lives up
to its values of freedom
and democracy and liberty.
I didn't initially see this
as being in any way comparable
to the other civil
rights cases we had.
But the more I learned,
the more it reminded me
of many other of our cases.
And it wasn't just
about representing
a bunch of people who
painted their face.
There was serious
constitutional issues at stake.
Throughout history,
there has always been
a tendency for the government
to want to suppress
controversial speech.
And that could be
speech from the left,
speech from the right,
speech from non-conformists.
That's why we have the
First Amendment to serve
as a check on abuse
of government.
Because of the First Amendment,
people in this country
can listen to whatever
music they want.
They can express themselves
the way they wish
without fear of
police harassment.
They can worship
the way they wish.
There's the right to protest.
There's a free press to report.
- We need music that expresses
the times that we're happy.
We need music that expresses
at times that we're angry.
And ICP, they're doing
that for their fans.
And for me, it was Soundgarden
or Jane's Addiction
or Ice-T tea or NWA.
I mean that's the
time when I grew up.
But time and time again,
every 10, 15 years,
we find ourselves
in this situation.
♪ Fuck the police comin'
straight from the underground ♪
- [Male News Anchor] NWA
has taunted law enforcement
with its lyrics urging
violence against police.
- [Interviewer] FBI, how
did the FBI situation stuff?
- [Dr. Dre] There was one
guy that thought he would
write us a letter.
He's in Utah somewhere.
- I guess he figured if sent
us a letter, we'd be like,
oh, the FBI sent us a letter,
let's stop writing
records and doing this.
- [Saura] The FBI just seems
to find itself once again
investigating
musicians, fan bases.
Whether it's John Lennon,
the Deadheads or
KISS, they're wrong.
- [Michael] Certainly
fans of various groups
have been targeted
throughout history,
but I believe this
is unprecedented.
- If we get removed
from the gang list,
I think everything will
go back to the way it was.
I believe that.
(dark hip hop beats)
- [Violent J] The judge
looked at it and said,
this ain't even worth going
to court, and threw it out.
- [Female Reporter] The Detroit
based rap group known as
Insane Clown Posse
has been classified
as a gang by the feds.
And it's going to stay that way
according to a US
District Court judge.
♪ How many times will a
judge decide my fate? ♪
♪ Who is he, a bitch,
nothing great ♪
♪ He takes shits, and
fucks his old floppy wife ♪
♪ Plays with his balls
and judges my life ♪
- They claimed that we
didn't have standing
to bring the case.
And the major argument was
the harms we were alleging,
for example, people
being pulled over
by the Tennessee police,
those were harms inflicted
by third parties.
- Which is crazy because
they're doing that
because the fuckin'
FBI says we're a gang.
- [Michael] The FBI created
a gang list to inform
the actions of local
law enforcement.
It's obvious that local law
enforcement is going to react.
- It's a sad, scary,
scary fuckin' thing.
- The First Amendment
is a fundamental right
upon which many of our
other rights are based.
And if people in a free country
aren't able to
express themselves,
whether it's
politically or socially,
we do not live in a democracy.
Juggalos should not
be afraid to express
who they are in this country.
They have an absolute
right to do that
without fear of harassment.
- Insane Clown Posse, that name
induces laughter everywhere.
- It's like, all right,
yeah, everybody knows
we're getting fucked with.
Everybody knows the FBI
is in their fuckin' courts
giving us the the
shit end of the stick.
- One member of a
popular rap duo is facing
legal trouble for
a traffic stop.
- [Female TV Anchor] His
drug screen came back
looking like a pharmacy.
Pain meds, muscle relaxers from
hydrocodone to amphetamine.
- [TV Show Host] Shaggy 2
Dope attempted to drop kick
Fred Durst in the middle
of a Limp Bizkit show.
- [Female News Anchor] The
feds say both members of ICP
owe the IRS nearly $380,000.
♪ I have a headache,
my brain feels dead ♪
- You all right?
- Yeah, man.
♪ I'm trying to hold myself
together, impossible task ♪
♪ My only question,
how long will I last ♪
- [Female News Anchor]
79 criminal arrests
at the festival organized
by Insane Clown Posse.
- A police officer was fired
for identifying as a Juggalo.
- [Male News Reporter]
Suspects sporting t-shirts
with the Insane Clown
Posse are each charged
with two counts of rioting.
- [Female News Anchor] One
homeowner we spoke to called it
the concert from hell.
♪ I'm falling apart ♪
- [Rob] Now we've been through
a lot of shit over the years.
Motherfuckers have
been trying to stop us
since the inception of
Psychopathic Records
and the Juggalo family.
We got the FBI.
We got motherfuckers pulling
our fucking Gathering location
out from under us.
But will that fucking stop us?
- [Crowd] No!
- The FBI wants ICP dead.
Not only that, the FBI
wants you Juggalos dead.
But check this out right here.
We ain't never ever gonna die.
You motherfuckers!
Little bit louder!
Come on!
Here we go!
♪ Hey, yeah, yeah ♪
- [Crowd] Family,
family, family.
- Last night we
filed a 41 page brief
in the US Court of Appeals.
We're not asking
for a miracle here.
All we're asking is for the
judges to follow the law
and give the Juggalos
their day in court
so that justice may be served.
- We'll get our day in court
in front of the Sixth Circuit.
I'd like to think that we'll
have a strong shot there.
And we're up talking
about whether or not
the federal courts
have the authority to
decide in this case,
what the heck the
Constitution means.
- [Saura] By designating
the Juggalos as a gang
and calling each of
the appellants that,
by implication, a gang member,
you've branded
them as criminals.
- Doesn't the report
itself specifically say
that there's criminal
subsets of Juggalos?
The DOJ is not saying that
all Juggalos are gang members.
- That word subset does no work.
It is meaningless to
everybody involved here.
It's meaningless to the
law enforcement officers
who enforce the law and
that's what's most important.
It did nothing to save our
plaintiffs from suffering
law enforcement
and other actions.
So let me pause it,
I mean, is that-
- [Farris] That was awesome.
- [Female Team Member]
That was very good.
- [Farris] That was great, yeah.
That made me feel like this
is totally different than
your average person
on the gang list.
- In the morning, do I
actually remember to say that?
- [Michael] If we want
to get back in the game
and be able to prove that
the rights of Juggalos
across the country were
violated, we need to win today.
So this is a critical
moment in the case.
- [Saura] Good
morning, your Honors
and may it please this court,
the Department of
Justice's hybrid gang rule
burdens the rights of
over a million people
in the Department of
Justice's own words,
based on the actions of a few.
- [Judge] Are you
disputing that some people
that self-identify as Juggalos
have done what this
assessment says that they do?
- [Saura] We're not
challenging the finding
that maybe eight people
someplace in Idaho
are acting as a criminal street
gang and bearing the name
Juggalo for reasons that
are out of our control.
There is no data to support
that this group is engaged in
criminal activity
because they're not.
Their primary purpose
is to be music fans
and the vast majority
are law abiding people.
- [Judge] Thank you, counsel.
- May it please the
court, Lindsey Powell
for the federal defendants.
The 2011 report does not
state that all Juggalos
are gang members and no
legal consequences follow
from this report.
- [Judge] Not the be facetious,
but could you pass the
FBI background check
and be in your job if you
were a member of the Juggalos?
- [Lindsey] Um, I-
- [Judge] These third
parties told these folks
it was upon reliance
on this assessment
that they were taking the
actions that they were taking.
They say the police
officer came up to me
and I read your group is a
gang in the FBI assessment
and so I'm going to
detain you, search you,
whatever it is
they say they did.
It seems to me a little hard
for you to get around that.
- [Lindsey] It's simply
information being provided
for law enforcement entities
to use how they see fit.
- [Judge] Thank you, counsel.
Appreciate your arguments.
And the case will be submitted.
- [Michael] Saura
did an amazing job.
His arguments obviously
resonated with the
court of appeals
because we won unanimously.
♪ You know who
you fucking with ♪
♪ W-w-w-w-w-w-w-w-wicked
clowns ♪
♪ You know who
you fucking with ♪
♪ Wicked clowns, wicked clowns ♪
♪ Wicked clowns, wicked clowns
♪ ♪ Don't fuck with me ♪
♪ Wicked clowns, wicked clowns ♪
(calm music)
- [Dep. Moore] The county
itself is the second largest
county in the state.
However, we're still
considered a rural community.
Farm community.
Predominantly Republican.
Midwest USA.
This is the Licking County
Common Police Court House.
Most people would just call
it simply the court house.
I mean, we have the
world's largest basket.
(swelling orchestral music)
- [Steve] We have
everything from
the Grateful Dead
to Jimmy Buffet.
Lollapalooza was
here back in the day.
My wife and I have owned
it for the last 21 years.
And I saw that they
had lost their place
in Missouri, I think.
I'm all about giving
people second chances.
(uplifting hip hop)
- [Shaggy] What up?
What up, son?
- Whoop, whoop.
- [Violent J] The
overall vibe is great.
The comradery amongst each other
that can only be
described as euphoric.
We almost flipped this
bitch right there.
♪ On Juggalo Island ♪
♪ We can be one ♪
♪ Let our nuts
hang by the water ♪
♪ On Juggalo Island ♪
♪ We can have fun ♪
- [Kevin] This is our
13th fucking Gathering.
Whoop, whoop, (indistinct).
- [Dep. Moore] I know
that the community
raised some concerns
when they found out
they were coming here.
- [Steve] I got a lot of
pushback from the locals
and more pushback
from the state.
- Well, they do their
internet research
like everybody else does.
And you hear the stories
and we've assured them
that we'll be providing
deputies inside the venue.
There's no law on the
books that say it's a crime
to be a gang member.
- [Bandit Crew Member]
We do country shows.
We do the hippy shows.
And now this is the
first time we've had
the Juggalos out here.
And really, I think the hippies
are really the same thing.
It's just a little more tattoos,
a little more aggressive.
But other than that I've had a
good time out here with them.
It really shocked me because
everybody was telling us
it's gonna be all this and that.
- I want a picture, man.
Can I get a picture?
- Sure.
- Thank you, man.
- No problem, thank you.
- Thanks a lot.
- Thanks, buddy.
- Thank you, brother.
- No real issues.
Not on our end.
For the most part, fans
seem to want to take care
of themselves, offering
out to help each other.
- If you need more bread,
come back and see us, OK?
- Appreciate you.
- No problem, man.
Keep your homeys
hydrated too, all right?
Lot of Juggalos don't have much.
When they get
here, we feed them.
Hot dogs, we got water for them.
We've got about 800 or so
pounds of donated clothing
so far that people have brought.
We're just the part of the
family that likes to cook.
- [Preacher] May we christen
this space our new home.
A place where we never
have to feel alone.
A place of love,
music and peace.
A time when we can cherish
and stress the least.
That is not gonna
happen, anyway.
- [Man On Radio]
Hey Kevin or Alan.
There's a bunch of ATF guys
that tried to get in here.
They're just gonna basically
go throughout the grounds,
giving out everybody the bone.
- [Farris] Well, the ATF,
the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco
and Firearms are outside
the back entrance to
the Gathering of the
Juggalos right now
which is on private property.
What I'm also
concerned about is that
the ATF often
works with the FBI.
They can not come onto your
property without your consent,
without a search warrant
signed by a judge.
- You guys rented
the venue from me,
but I'm not gonna
give them consent.
But you're going to
explain everything?
- I'm going to explain
it all to them.
So if you're ready
to go out there.
All right, let's do it.
That's one of them right there?
Is that one of them
right there too?
I'm an attorney, I'd
like to speak to you.
You with the ATF?
Excuse me, sir.
I'm an attorney,
can I speak to you?
Are you with the ATF?
Are you a law enforcement agent?
Did he just flick us off?
We should point out,
very unprofessionally,
one of them flicked
us off on his way out
after refusing to speak to me.
- [Michael] After an initial win
in the Sixth Circuit
Court of Appeals,
the case went back
to the trial court
for another motion to dismiss by
the FBI and the
Department of Justice.
And this time we lost.
- Hold on, fuck you man.
- And we went back up to
the US Court of Appeals
and we lost there as well.
- Fuck you.
Wait a minute, what?
Fuck you.
- [Michael] The court held that
because local law enforcement
were not forced to
harass the Juggalos,
the FBI was not responsible
under the Administrative
Procedures Act.
- When it gets thrown
out of court repeatedly,
how else are you
going to stand up?
What do you do?
You protest.
- [Male Announcer] Thousands
of demonstrators assembled
in the nation's capital
for a mass protest.
- [Male Narrator] The Lincoln
Memorial is forever enshrined
as a megaphone for the voice
of the American people.
From anti-war protests
to million man marches.
- [Ickes] In this great
auditorium under the sky,
all of us are free.
- [Newsreel Announcer]
They came from Los Angeles
and San Francisco.
They came from
Cleveland, from Chicago.
Jackson, Mississippi,
from Birmingham, Alabama.
(crowd chanting)
♪ Smile, I'ma blow a
hole in your neck ♪
♪ And leave you standing there
looking stupid like Beck ♪
♪ Everybody jumps to
the Juggalo sound ♪
♪ Fuck outta here if you
ain't down with the clown ♪
♪ Everybody raised on
the East Side, rize ♪
the West Side, rize ♪
♪ Everybody raised on
the North Side, rize ♪
♪ South Side, rize ♪
♪ Everybody, rize ♪
♪ Everybody raised on
the East Side, rize ♪
the West Side, rize ♪
♪ Everybody raised on
the North Side, rize ♪
♪ South Side, rize ♪
♪ Everybody, rize ♪
- [Violent J] Discrimination.
Fuck that.
You're making history
and you know damn
well in your hearts,
we're the good guys here today.
I'm not gay, but I
would fuckin' march
for the right for two
gay people to marry
each other if they wanted.
In the eyes of Juggalos,
there's no such thing as a VIP.
We're all very important.
Let's march, motherfuckers!
♪ Calling the Juggalo a
gang banger, outrageous ♪
♪ Pulling ninjas over
whipping out gauges ♪
♪ And the judge slams
down the hammers ♪
♪ To the big house now
for you gang banger ♪
♪ If we let this be,
we'll be face to face ♪
♪ With one man as he
dictates the human race ♪
♪ Mr. FBI, Mr. Officer ♪
♪ Tell me why you want
me in coffin sir ♪
♪ Is it because we like to
hang out and be scrubs ♪
♪ Must be thugs out
here peddling drugs ♪
♪ Well let me tell ya,
all that meddling does ♪
♪ Is make us wanna leave
you embedded in slugs ♪
♪ Free speech motherfucker ♪
♪ You can hurt our name ♪
♪ You can't salt our game ♪
♪ Fuck you and your claim ♪
♪ We don't bang, we're family ♪
- [Violent J] I've got a
picture hanging in my studio,
holding my kid's
hands, marching.
That was like hands down,
probably the greatest
day of my life.
And there were people there
that aren't even Juggalos.
They were there because
they heard what was going on
and they knew it was bullshit.
- Straight up.
- And they were there
enough to march.
That was America, man.
- We asked the people
at the National Mall
since we have the day secured
and we have our stage set up,
could we perform there?
And they were like, sure,
as long as you don't swear
or throw any Faygo.
You know what I mean?
And we're like, we got you.
♪ Cut a motherfucking
chicken up, what ♪
♪ Who's going chicken huntin' ♪
♪ We's goin' chicken huntin' ♪
♪ Cut a motherfucking
chicken up, what ♪
- [Violent J] Be proud, we
made motherfucking history!
Juggalos!
- There was a lot of press
coverage for that march.
And strongly in our favor.
Everybody pretty much agrees.
Everybody's like yes,
that's definitely
some bullshit right there.
The government stating
your fans are a gang
is undoubtedly bullshit.
But so is your music, you know.
That hasn't changed,
but that's another march.
- [Shaggy] Even though
technically we're
still on the list,
now the normal person
that hears about ICP
being linked with gang stuff.
To them, it's almost
laughable now.
It's like, come on these
kids are not gang members.
- [Violent J] We stood
up as far as we could.
And we said we're not a gang.
In our eyes, we feel
like we won that shit.
- [Michael] I think the
best evidence of the success
of the case is the complaints
that we've been receiving
about harassment by local police
have dwindled to almost none.
To express their appreciation,
I even got an invitation
to Hallowicked.
They invited us onstage to
spray Faygo on the crowd.
I put a clown mask on and
actually went out and did it.
But I got out quickly cause
I was getting really sticky.
- [Saura] This is a case that
could go to the Supreme Court.
This is a case that
is important enough
to go to the Supreme Court.
- If the government can
target a group of people
based on their musical taste,
they can target
of group of people
based on any reason at all.
- I work for an
insurance company.
- I'm a carpenter.
- A college graduate.
- An IT guy.
- A Juris Doctorate graduate.
- I help train soldiers,
federal first responders,
Department of Homeland Security.
- I wanna grow up
to be a teacher.
- The FBI designation
was unprecedented.
And it's a bad precedent.
- I'm a veteran.
- I'm a soldier.
- I'm vice president of the
Desert Storm War Memorial.
- I'm a Juggalo, also a father.
- I'm a brother.
- And a husband.
- [Michael] The First
Amendment guarantees
the right to freedom
of speech that serves
as the foundation for
all the other freedoms
we have in this country.
- And I'm not a gang member.
- Definitely not gang members.
- I am not a gang member.
- [Michael] Without
these freedoms,
we are not the United
States of America.
- [Violent J] We
got one more for ya.
We going out with a
motherfucking bang.
And a pow.
And a boom.
Come along!
♪ With a bang, say
goodbye to everything ♪
♪ Your complete annihilation
is the reason he came ♪
♪ And a pow ♪
♪ He's wiping everything out ♪
♪ Turn your whole fucking
world into a mushroom cloud ♪
♪ And a boom ♪
♪ It's your inevitable doom ♪
♪ Nobody escapes and
everybody's consumed ♪
♪ Welcome to the Dark
Carnival Supershow ♪
♪ You're our specially
invited guests ♪
♪ And I'll tell you what fo' ♪
♪ Cuz you're the
evilest pedophiles,
rapists and abusers ♪
♪ All together we've got
fifty thousand of you losers ♪
♪ You're all about to
witness an incredible sight ♪
♪ Nobody's ever lived
to tell about it ♪
♪ And don't think you might ♪
♪ It's about to rain
flames, frames and brains ♪
♪ To be blown into pieces
is the reason you came ♪
♪ Racists, bigots, wife-beaters,
judges and cowards ♪
♪ All crowded together,
expecting a show
and some dollars ♪
♪ But instead the shit
you're gonna see ♪
♪ You'll fear it in Hell ♪
♪ It's a constant explosion,
see and feel it you shall ♪
♪ With a bang ♪
♪ Say goodbye to everything ♪
♪ Your complete annihilation
is the reason he came ♪
♪ And a pow ♪
♪ He's wiping everything out ♪
♪ Turn your whole fucking
world into a mushroom cloud ♪
♪ And a boom ♪
♪ It's your inevitable doom ♪
♪ Nobody escapes and
everybody's consumed ♪
♪ In the deserts of Nevada,
where nothing else matter ♪
♪ It's the perfect
place for you ♪
♪ And your intestines
to splatter ♪
♪ And while bang, pow, boom ♪
♪ Steady stomps you all out ♪
♪ You in the hail for
the nuclear fallout ♪
♪ With the snakes and
fakes, creepy sneaks ♪
♪ Hoods and crooks,
horny freaks ♪
♪ Shady ladies, Evil Ernies ♪
♪ Richie Richs and
Charley Cheaps ♪
♪ Bang, pow, boom, they
say the show is the bomb ♪
♪ I heard it's
straight up explosive ♪
♪ Some even call it napalm ♪
♪ Nobody battles back,
this ain't no kind of war ♪
♪ It's a one-way execution ♪
♪ Blow you straight to
hell through the floor ♪
♪ What the fuck you think you
here for, sound the alarm ♪
♪ Ladies and gentlemen,
eat shit and die ♪
♪ Let's bring him on ♪
♪ With a bang ♪
♪ Say goodbye to everything ♪
♪ Your complete annihilation
is the reason he came ♪
♪ And a pow ♪
♪ He's wiping everything out ♪
♪ Turn your whole fucking
world into a mushroom cloud ♪
♪ And a boom ♪
♪ It's your inevitable doom ♪
♪ Nobody escapes and
everybody's consumed ♪
♪ The air is thick with sick ♪
♪ From demented
brains and thoughts ♪
♪ But here they are
all together, every
one of them caught ♪
♪ This is a celebration, in
that the Carnival's cheering ♪
♪ It's not too often bang, pow,
boom, makes and appearance ♪
♪ And the winds in the sky
will carry away all the ash ♪
♪ But for now let us enjoy
the big back-splash ♪
♪ With a bang ♪
♪ Say goodbye to everything ♪
♪ Your complete annihilation
is the reason he came ♪
♪ And a pow ♪
♪ He's wiping everything out ♪
♪ Turn your whole fucking
world into a mushroom cloud ♪
♪ And a boom ♪
♪ It's your inevitable doom ♪
♪ Nobody escapes and
everybody's consumed ♪
♪ With a bang ♪
♪ Say goodbye to everything ♪
♪ Your complete annihilation
is the reason he came ♪
♪ And a pow ♪
♪ He's wiping everything out ♪
♪ Turn your whole fucking
world into a mushroom cloud ♪
♪ And a boom ♪
♪ It's your inevitable doom ♪
♪ Nobody escapes and
everybody's consumed ♪
- [Violent J] We fuckin'
love you, Juggalos!
Whoop, whoop!
- I appreciate you guys coming
in and videotaping this.
Hopefully there'll be
a little truth come out
and not just the dipshittery
that we're known for.