Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
The storm is raging!
The storm, the storm!
Visibility is nil.
Strike the sails.
Watch out, Jaber!
Come on, all together.
The ship is drifting.
Drifting!
Be careful, we're going to collide!
Veer to the right!
More to the right!
Thank God.
A long time ago,
back in the 7th century
Trade by sea between
the ports of the Arabian Peninsula
and the shores of the Indian Ocean
flourished.
Goods from the West have arrived!
Goods from the West!
Yemeni coffee!
Pistachios from Aleppo!
Damascene silk!
Arab merchants' decency earned the respect
of traders on different shores
and created an environment where
different cultures were accepted
During the Umayyad era
the plague spread in
the Arabian Peninsula and beyond.
The infection appeared on Arab merchants
on their way to Gem Island
So, they decided to die at sea
and spare the island their deadly disease.
The wives and children of the merchants
who fell victim to the plague
had to return to the Arabian Peninsula
The King of Gem Island gave them
a ship to return with their belongings.
In honour of their martyrs
Sohaila.
Sohaila!
Sorry, Sir.
It's OK, they are just kids
Pirates!
Gold! Gold! Gold!
Priceless loot is in our sights
Gold, Gold! Gold!
Light the fire of wrath.
Move forward, roar,
wreck everything, destroy.
Bring forward,
the treasure we crave.
Here is our toll, sir
Not bad, take
the women and their valuables.
Move, get down.
Rescue us, Al Hajjaj!
Excellent!
Is this all the gold?
All of it, my lord.
And the toll?
They had no money, so we
gotthe gold and the women.
Where are they?
Under guard, well protected.
Great!
Daher, the king of Sindhistan,
was a powerful man.
Welcome, priest of sacred Shouka.
You came just in time.
He made an alliance with the Med pirates
to rob merchant ships.
But this time, he took
the Arab women hostage.
The priest came to him with a prophecy
that upset him.
A prophecy?
Yes, my lord.
What does your prophecy say,
priest of destruction?
The prophecy says, my lord,
The Arabs will not rest until they save
their women and children.
Let them come to us,
And we will drown them in the sea.
And if they come by land
my elephants will crush them.
But the prophecy, my lord.
The great army of Daher
won't be affected by such nonsense.
Zaid.
Amr?
It looks like it will be an exciting race!
Why don't you join them?
Racing against Mohammed and Sobha!
I will surely lose.
The kid!
My son!
Mohammed lost the race.
I wish you had taken part.
What's your name, young knight?
Iyad, sir.
I didn't expect
you would lose a race.
But I won a third friend.
Iyad, Amr, Zaid.
You missed the prize!
This is a more precious prize.
Thank you, you are a true knight.
My lord!
My lord
- What do you have?
- The Med pirates kidnapped our women.
Bin Al Qasim, why did you bring us
to your uncle's house?
Al Hajjaj is holding a council
to rescue the women hostages.
- I want to know their plans.
- What does that have to do with us?
What does that have to do with us?
How can we know their plans?
It's war, then.
And we're ready.
We should send Mohammed Bin Haroun
with his army from the Chinese borders.
He is very close to Daher
They will send Mohamed Bin Haroun
from the Chinese borders.
Where is Bin Al Qasim?
- Bin Al Qasim is outside, my lord.
- Not now.
Pardon, my lord, the matter is urgent
and cannot be delayed.
- What do you want, Bin Al Qasim?
- I want to help rescue the hostages, sir
Do you know where they are?
Somewhere in Debal Bay,
the stronghold of the pirates.
and how did you find out?
I heard it from sailors
who travel there.
How old are you, my son?
He just turned fifteen, my lord.
And you want to save the women
kept at Debal Bay?
And teach the Med pirates a lesson.
They treat me like a child, Sobha.
My heart is longing,
My destiny is calling.
As if I were a stranger,
in my own land
I long for a land.
Where my dreams can
spread their wings and fly
like a speeding horse.
What you are asking me for
is difficult, my son
But not impossible.
You're the ruler of Basra, dad.
You can help me.
Al Hajjaj will send Bin Haroun
to deal with Daher.
Must the women and children
wait until Bin Haroun's army moves?
I'm planning a quicker operation
to rescue the hostages.
You're still too young, my son.
I have to do this,
even if no one believes that I can.
Even if life turns against me.
I'm longing for a land.
Where my dreams can spread their wings
and fly
like a speeding horse
Hit harder! Harder!
Come join us, Bin Al Qasim.
I have a more urgent matter,
Abul Aswad.
It's a clever and ambitious plan
We'll be discreet.
We need you with us, Abul Aswad.
We'll launch a quick raid
and rescue the hostages.
Unfortunately, I won't be here.
We need you with us.
We've been ordered to join
Bin Haroun's army.
Ibn Al Qasim,
Despair is not a trait of youth.
What shall we do, Abul Aswad?
Boys, Abul Riyah is the man
for your mission.
I'm Abul Riyah,
One day, I lost my leg.
That very same day
my passion erupted.
I grew wings
and flew to the horizon
He's Abul Riyah.
I'm Abul Riyah.
He's Abul Riyah,
One day, he lost his leg.
that very same day
his passion erupted.
I grew wings
and flew to the horizon
I sew sails as if
I would wear them.
The sun, humbly sets behind my door.
He sews sails as if
he would wear them.
The sun, humbly sets behind his door.
The sea is in my blood,
the wind is my blanket,
the wind I'm caressing
as if lips were kissing.
He's Abul Riyah, Abul Riyah,
One day, he lost his leg.
That very same day
his passion erupted.
I grew wings
and flew to the horizon
I'm Abul Riyah,
a fire of emotions.
I sleep like a baby
when storms rage manically.
He's Abul Riyah, a fire of emotions.
He sleeps like a baby
when storms rage manically.
I'm the brother of waves
and the twin of cheeriness.
Whenever waves rave
my heart is their slave
Yet I feel free and brave
He's Abul Riyah,
One day he lost his leg.
That very same day
his passion erupted.
I grew wings
and flew to the horizon
He is Abul Riyah.
It's him.
Abul Riyah
It's a dangerous quest,
Bin Al Qasim.
I want your advice, Abul Riyah,
you're the hero of the Battle of Masts,
an expert on the sea and its battles.
Oh yes, the sea...
Afrakoosh, Bardakoosh
Enough mumbling, priest of destruction,
tell me what you want.
Look and listen.
What do you want me to see, priest?
It's the knight.
It's written
that a man named Mohammed,
Grandson of Mohammed.
Keep your prophecy
to the layman, priest.
No harm my lord,
if we handle this matter with caution.
Exactly!
Let me deal with this.
I will send someone to find him
in the Arab army and bring him to you.
I can't take it anymore,
how can I sleep with all this snoring?
Curse the day I met you, Shamhoresh,
the worst day ever!
Wake up you animal
Bakhtoo, what's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Was I snoring?
Not at all! This is the best thing
in my life, it's your gift!
It's like having a drummer
playing in my head!
I can't control it, Bakhtoo.
I have a problem with my nose
Always the same story!
I told you to see a doctor!
Afrakoosh, Bardakoosh
King of the sculpted demon.
- Shamhoresh!
- What's going on?
What's happening?
Oh yee King of the sculpted demons.
Afrakoosh, Bardakoosh...
King of the demons who are sculpted
onto the walls of the temples
of the sacred Shouka.
Oh yee King of the sculpted demons.
Send me your two miserable jinn.
The powerful Shamhoresh.
And the sly Bakhtoo.
May they appear before me.
Our lord, the priest of destruction.
Update me on the
Chinese Wall mission, you wretches.
Everything is fine.
We did exactly what you asked.
Why were you late? And where is
your report on your mission?
Sorry, sir, we were on a vacation.
That was our agreement.
We couldn't even sleep.
Don't you complain about sleeping!
Acupuncture didn't work, my lord.
Frankly, he needs a miracle
for his nose.
Not now!
It is written that a man named Mohammed,
Grandson of Mohamed,
Will kill our ruler, our lord,
our protector,
His majesty King Daher the Great.
We must take action
as soon as possible.
We're trapped!
Good news, folks!
Good news!
Good news, Ibn Al Qasim!
Hello, Abul Riyah.
any news?
I found you a big merchant convoy
going to India.
Great!
But they said I have to go with you.
Did they really say that?
Do you think I put in all that effort
just to stay here?
I'm worried that you may find
the journey hard to endure.
Worry about yourself and your friends.
For me, the sea is my life.
And that's where I wish to die.
Bakhtoo, is this the Arab army?
No, Real Madrid football club!
Of course it is!
Oh my God! How will we find
the man we're after in this crowd?
And most of them must be
named "Mohamed"
Call "Mohamed",
and they'll all answer.
But we want Mohamed,
grandson of Mohamed.
- I have an idea!
- Your ideas are stupid.
- It's a great one.
- Your ideas are like your nose.
Just listen, give me a chance.
We possess two soldiers,
walk among them,
and we ask for Mohamed,
grandson of Mohamed.
As I said, it's a stupid idea
By the time we reach our target
he'll have found Daher and killed him.
You're right.
How will we solve this, Bakhtito?
Don't call me that!
Ok, chill out. Use your brain
and find us a way.
We need a smart plan.
Bakhtito will find it.
You said you don't like that nickname.
Only I can nickname myself,
and my departed mom could too.
I wish her good health.
Mohamed Bin Al Qasim embarked
with his friends and Abul Riyah,
On an unpredictable adventure.
This is the spot.
We're close.
- Where's Abul Riyah?
- There.
Merchant convoy coming!
Do you see that carriage?
Yes, I do.
There are two cooks hired to
work for the Arab soldiers.
- How do you know?
- Did you forget I'm a Jinni?
Oh, yes.
We'll possess them to disguise ourselves,
and enter the camp.
And we will cook and eat a lot!
You only care about your belly!
Get ready, when it's exactly below us,
we'll jump
One... two... three...
Possess the man not the horse dummy!
Just a kiss, don't be scared.
Oh wow, that was funny
They're close.
Bin Al Qasim!
Pirate ships are getting closer
Act as if you're ready to pay the toll.
At my signal, we'll spread out
as we agreed.
Let's face them!
They're ruthless!
Don't worry.
Come on, men.
Careful, be careful.
Pay attention, lads.
We prepared a party for them
they won't forget.
Raise the sign that we are ready
to pay the toll.
Search their ships thoroughly
for gold and women.
Like we did with the Med pirates?
Yes, idiot! Hurry, up!
Point each catapult towards
a different ship.
Abul Riyah, make sure
their aim is right.
Come on.
What's that?
A warship! you idiot
Get ready
Launch!
Raise the shields!
Watch it
Fire!
Run away!
They're running away!
Help!
Help! Save us!
What is it?
An old man calling for help.
It could be a trap!
Even you Amr!
Mind the fire!
Save the women
and the princess of Qossah!
Come on, hurry up!
- Come, my lady.
- My mistress is in there.
They call me Abu Haroun.
In our Emirate, ruled by King Daher,
there are many Arab merchants.
We have a mosque built by a merchant
in the era of Caliph Othman.
God bless his soul.
We fell hostage to the Zot pirates
while we were returning from a trip.
Weren't they the Med pirates
of King Daher?
No, sir. The Med pirates are busy
with the feast of their God Shouka.
It seems we got ourselves into
the wrong battle!
What a mess!
God sent you to save us.
Actually, we came to save
other people.
- The wives of the Arab merchants.
- Do you know where they are?
Yes, but you need a guide.
Abu Haroun!
Our princess wishes to...
Our princess wishes
to meet her savior.
The one who saved her.
Go, Bin Al Qasim.
The princess awaits you.
I'm glad you're safe.
Abu Haroun told me you're Bin Al Qasim.
Yes, and you?
- Lola Benny.
- Lola Benny?
- Does it sound odd to you?
- Somewhat.
It sounds like our "Lobna".
- Lobna?
- Yes.
Then call me that, if you want.
My princess.
How can I reward you?
I don't take rewards
for fulfilling my duties.
Then come to my father's palace.
It's very close.
I can't, but I will provide
you with guards,
Who will escort you to your palace.
What do you think, my lady?
He looks brave and handsome.
But he's a stranger, Amina.
singing: Oh mercy! Mercy...
calm down, calm down
Are you here?
Of course! Here I am in the flesh!
- The battle is raging out there.
- And the food is simmering here.
- I'm starving, you done?
- Not yet.
You deserve it.
Did you find our man?
It's pointless. The records say that
half the soldiers are named Mohamed.
But our man has a grandpa named Mohamed.
Everyone is Mohammed
Even their chief is Mohammed,
And his grandpa is Mohammed.
- That's him!
- You think?
It's crystal clear:
Mohammed grandson of Mohammed.
- So what do we do?
- Where's your brain power now?
Are you making fun of me because
for once, I liked your idea?
I think we should kidnap him
and take him to the priest.
- You never have a complete plan.
- OK, what shall we do?
We poison his food and get it over with.
What? No, Bakhtoo.
We don't kill. It's not how we work.
Ok, forget it, I have a brilliant idea.
Oh my!
Sorry, bro.
Tell me, what's your idea?
I found an herb on the mountain here.
It has an awesome effect.
A superb Indian herb.
What does it do?
It wastes a person.
You won't even recognize who you are.
When they take their lunch break,
we'll put this herb in their food.
And we put a lot of it, so when they
go back to battle,
they'll be spaced out!
The King of Qossah.
Hello.
Welcome. My daughter told me
everything.
To return the favor
We came to help you free your hostages.
The feast of the God Shouka
is after tomorrow.
Everyone will be busy
with the ceremonies.
Then it will be easy to enter
the hostages camp.
That is very smart.
Until that moment comes,
you will be my most welcomed guests.
We would be honored to stay.
Welcome to the prince
and his friends.
Come!
You look like an Indian prince.
Maybe you should think of staying here?
It seems we will all stay.
Your country is beautiful.
Find me a wife, Abou Haroun.
Hey guys, when are we
rescuing the hostages?
Tomorrow in the cover of night...
- What kind of ritual is this?
- They've been chanting since dawn.
What are those branches?
They're from the Salla tree,
which is sacred to them.
They burn it after sunset.
There's the hostage camp.
It's as quiet as a graveyard.
There are only a few guards,
most of them are celebrating.
Stupid! What are you doing?
If Daher finds out, he'll behead you.
And who's gonna tell him?
They're celebrating there,
and we're here guarding their women.
It won't take long, tomorrow
we will send them to Daher.
Then let's celebrate tonight
You're so evil.
Get us more drinks.
The night is still young.
What is that?
Go check it out.
I guess it was just a cat.
Watch out! There!
They've come to rescue us
Get us out of here!
Zaid stop. We came to rescue
the hostages, not to kill.
Come on, quickly.
Tell me, son, who is your leader?
We want to thank him.
Not now, my lady.
Let's move.
Amr!
Don't take it out.
The arrow pierced my heart.
Don't leave me here.
Throw my body into the sea.
You'll live, Amr.
You'll make it, with God's help.
I'm the cause of Amr's death.
No, it's Daher. It's he who ordered
the women to be kidnapped.
He's responsible for what happened.
Let me deal with Daher. Leave me here.
I'll find a way to avenge Amr's death.
Calm down! Thank God for saving
the hostages, before they got hurt.
No, Zaid, I don't want to lose
another friend.
Be sure, Daher will pay for his crimes.
Tomorrow we will delay our departure,
to carefully study his fortress.
It's true, whoever controls this
fortress, rules the whole Debal region.
And he who liberates Debal,
can free all of Sindh.
What are all these rocks?
They throw these rocks
from the fortress at invaders.
What are you thinking,
Bin Al Qasim?
How to break in.
Is this what we came for?
Mohamed, it seems impossible.
Especially if they throw
these huge rocks at us.
Except if...
Except if we use the same rocks
to break into the fortress.
Your idea is good and smart,
but it needs " a lady luck".
- A lady luck?
- Yes, a giant catapult is my lady luck.
And no one but Abul Riyah
can build it.
- Will you come back?
- Yes.
Let's go, Bin Al Qasim.
- I promise.
- Do you see that golden star?
You mean the polar star?
Whatever its name, it's witness
of your promise of return.
Whenever you look at it,
you will see me.
We're late, Bin Al Qasim!
Farewell.
One wave follows another,
saying: I want to catch it.
What are those birds?
Shimo, isn't that the temple?
Yes, that's it.
Seriously? Why does it look so small?
Bakhtoo, I can't see the opening
where we should enter. Do you see it?
- Isn't it that one?
- If you see it, then fine.
Let's go.
Our master, our lord, our chief...
Your grace.
We're very tired.
It's wonderful to see you.
We bring you great news.
Really great!
Stop it, you cretins!
Have pity on us, so the sacred
Shouka will have pity on you.
Damn you!
We're already damned!
And no one can set us free.
Get a grip, you wretches.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing, sir. We're just
enjoying our reckless youth.
What about Mohammed,
grandson of Mohammed?
He is wasted.
- Excuse me?
- We put drugs in his lunch.
And also in his men's lunch.
Like this one.
Then the army of our King Daher
tore them to pieces.
Including their leader Mohamed Bin Haroun
Bin Mohamed.
Are you satisfied?
Is he a young man?
Who?
Mohamed, grandson of... Mohammed.
Not at all, sir. He is an old man,
maybe seventy years old.
Then it's not him.
The prophecy says he is a young man,
Seventeen years old.
Then excuse me, I'll leave it to you
and your prophecy.
Just explain to me
How can a nation have
a seventeen-year-old leading an army?
That means a battalion commander
would be in kindergarten?
That's what the prophecy says,
Bakhtito.
I hate nicknames.
His majesty, King Daher.
Your prophecy came true, archpriest.
My men killed Mohammed Bin Haroun
and defeated his army.
Isn't he The Mohammed,
from your prophecy?
It must be him, majesty.
An urgent message from Debal, majesty.
What?
Some Arab sailors attacked
the hostage camp.
The hostages?
Yes, majesty, and their leader
is only sixteen years old.
Sixteen? And what is his name?
They say he's Mohamed Bin Al Qasim
Bin Mohammed.
It's him! Mohammed Bin Al Qasim.
In the incense, prophecies gleaming,
omens of a knight appearing,
Like a bird of prey.
Our defeated soldiers,
hanging from the claws of eagles.
A prophecy that will destroy the old
A fire which turns us into ruins.
A frightening prophecy gets louder,
it bursts like gunpowder.
Our glory plunging to hell!
Shouka, our powerful God,
Sacred apex of our worship.
May the invaders
be struck by thee,
swept up by the wind
you surely will send.
Nourish the land with their blood
like a river, oh god,
like a river.
Let the sky drop boulders,
then fire that smolders.
Let those who escape
your claws of destruction
beg your mercy
at their defeat.
At their defeat.
God is great.
Mohamed Bin Al Qasim came back
from his first mission
But he was so sad
for the loss of his beloved friend.
At the same time he was happy,
for he met the love of his life.
Do you love her, my son?
I've never had this feeling before.
I'm ashamed.
That's life, my son.
Separation and encounter,
life and death.
Two sides of the same coin.
Bakhtoo, will we really kill, like he
ordered us? Why are you stopping?
Listen, yesterday a fax arrived
at my office.
Saying that Mohamed Bin Al Qasim
is in love with the Princess of Qossah.
Lola Benny? I don't blame him.
Let's stop somewhere,
instead of hovering like this.
The fax said he will go back to her.
Oh, love! How I wish to try it
Focus on our job! When he returns
he will kill Daher, as the prophecy says.
- You think so?
- Do you doubt our priest?
Of course not.
But what shall we do?
We must prevent him from
returning back to Sind.
We have to find him
another sweetheart.
So he won't go back to Lola.
Let's go.
- Where to?
- To the land of the lovers...
My passion overflows,
- Overflow?
- What overflow?
After such a reception
I can die happy now.
- What about your bride?
- Where is she?
I mean, the giant catapult you said
you'd build.
Are we really going back?
With a careful plan and patience,
we can free the whole of Sindh.
Bin Al Qasim, I'm too old
for your dreams.
Look there!
- They'll declare him a hero.
- He deserves it.
What the heck are you saying?
Stop it, you'll punch a hole in my head.
Just think, if he becomes a hero,
Al Hajjaj will appoint him to free Sindh.
You're right.
We have to act quickly.
I've got an idea.
- Let's go!
- Where to?
To the house of Al Hajjaj.
You who come out of a bath,
with rosy cheeks like peaches...
Bakhtoo, what is that?
It's Ayat, daughter of Al Hajjaj.
Follow me.
Hold me.
- How does she concern us?
- She's at the marrying age.
We must convince her to marry
Mohamed Bin Al Qasim.
Shame on you!
It's you who's my shame!
Look, you possess the big maid,
and I, the thin one.
My God! She's violent.
Quickly, before the envious look
in their eyes is gone.
- What's going on?
- Nothing, I stumbled.
Why are you suddenly fat
and talking like a man?
It's just that...
You be silent.
Can't you hear, my lady?
- What?
- The music of the celebrations outside.
What celebrations?
Basra is celebrating
the return of its hero.
What hero?
Your beloved cousin,
Mohamed Bin Al Qasim.
What?
He rescued the Arab hostages
and brought them back from Sindh.
Give me one.
Sindh... Arab hostages...
Which hostages?
Come and watch.
look there!
I don't care.
How come?
I heard that Sohaila, daughter of
Abul Hakam, wants to marry him.
Who?
Sohaila, my lady.
The one you hate.
That skinny bamboo stick?
Yes, her. The one who's
not half as pretty as you.
Why don't you have a look?
A look at whom?
At the hero.
Look, he's coming.
It's my father, Al Hajjaj.
- She's also blind.
- We don't mean your father.
We mean that handsome
young man at his side.
Yes, I see him.
- Who is he?
- The groom.
Whose groom?
Could be yours!
Your cousin. You deserve him,
and he deserves you.
He could be your Romeo.
He would do everything for you.
His love for you
keeps him awake all night.
He could be Romeo and you are Juliet
But maybe...
Maybe what?
Maybe he won't like me.
The way you look
Awoke a feeling in my heart.
You! The most beautiful
woman I've seen.
I want him, mom!
- Mohamed?
- Yes, him.
I love him.
You?
Yes, Mom.
It's the first time you've said
something meaningful.
What are you saying?
Ayat is almost twenty
And no one has asked for her hand.
And no one is better for her
than Bin Al Qasim.
- Ayat?
- Yes, Ayat!
But I'm thinking of sending him to lead
an army to free the land of Sindh.
My daughter's husband will
never go to war.
But marriage is not on my mind.
You're old enough.
I'm not ready.
Al Hajjaj has appointed you as Ruler
of Shiraz, south of Fares.
- And the liberation of Sindh?
- That's all he told me, tonight.
What did you say?
He set a date for you to take the position
at the beginning of the month.
I open my hands.
And I see you.
And I travel without moving a step.
I open my hands.
And I see you.
And I travel without moving a step.
My soul always meets you
At the polar star.
I close my eyes for a few seconds.
My body stays in its place
And I see your soul coming to me
At the polar star,
You who dictated the encounter
of our longing souls.
Although distance makes us suffer
you decided we should meet
- I open my hands and see you.
- I close my eyes for a moment
and I travel without moving.
My body stays in its place.
Your soul always meets mine
at the polar star
My lord.
My prince.
- Fokha.
- What's wrong? You didn't even eat.
I've lost my appetite.
May God spare you sadness
and sorrow, my son.
Merciful God, you who hear us,
We can foresee our encounter.
God, when will you bring us
back together?
So that our hands will join,
under the polar star.
Oh, my goodness!
I feel for you, my son.
So you killed him?
Consider him dead.
What do you mean, you idiot?
We got him married.
Look, sir. Look
What is it?
A new invention called:
the magic mirror.
It replaces the old crystal ball.
It's the new model.
You can also use it when shaving.
Position it well, zoom in.
Watch Bin Al Qasim and his wife
in the land that he was appointed to.
Bin Al Qasim, come.
Zoom in, quickly.
Come, come...
I made you some yummy food
worthy of a king.
Do you like it?
I think that Bin Al Qasim
is out of our way now.
Excellent.
That's enough for now, get out
of my sight! And you, take a holiday.
Yes! Finally the time has come
for me to get married!
I will go to King Daher
to give him the news
I am sure he will be relieved.
But what shall I tell him?
Tell him he's dead.
The king won't go and check.
I'll tell him that he's dead.
- The surgery, my lord.
- Which surgery?
- For Shamhoresh's nose.
- Not now!
Leave
Never mind, my friend.
It looks like I'll have
to do your surgery.
I changed my mind, my nose is fine
After the success of Bin Al Qasim
in rescuing the hostages,
Arab merchants were
persecuted in the land of Sindh.
Women and children were killed.
Our money was stolen, Sir.
We have to do something.
What else shall I do?
I sent Abdallah Bin Nabhan
to Daher with an army.
He was killed and his army defeated.
Then I sent Bin Al Warqaa,
and he met the same fate.
What can I do?
I remember that Bin Al Qasim had
planned very carefully
To attack Daher by land and by sea.
He made a tour of the country, finding
the enemy's weak spots.
Then, call Bin Al Qasim.
This is the fourth marriage proposal
you've refused, my daughter.
All the princes of the realm and
neighboring realms have proposed to you,
but you refuse, giving no reason.
You know the reason, father.
The one you're waiting for, won't come.
He will.
Two years have passed
and we've had no news of him.
I know he will come and I'll meet him.
I feel it in my heart.
Bin Al Qasim!
Welcome back, man.
When did you arrive?
I came yesterday
and I am at your command.
What is this huge catapult?
It's the "Bride".
Abul Riyah designed it.
He bought Lebanese cedar wood.
Where's Abul Riyah?
I haven't seen him today!
An illness kept him from coming.
I'm sorry you can't come with us,
Abul Riyah.
I wish I could, my son.
But it seems illness
works in tandem with age.
They say you're more than
100 years old. Is that true?
The truth is that you will win,
Bin Al Qasim.
Don't exert yourself.
I see victory written
on your forehead, my son.
We'll miss you, Abul Riyah.
Give my greetings to Lobna
and her old father.
May God be with you, dear friend.
Go in peace, my boy.
Afrakoosh Bardakoosh
King of the sculpted demon.
Bakhtou Shamhourish
Have mercy on us, our lord!
Have mercy!
I'm a newlywed, my lord.
I haven't consummated my marriage!
Consider him dead?
Isn't that what you said, you
miserable wretched creatures?
What happened?
Mohamed Bin Al Qasim,
you disgrace to jinn!
What of him?
He's leading the Arab army
toward our land.
Through the wide desolate deserts,
defeating one city after another.
Why is it our fault?
He is about to sack Armail.
If you had killed him at the start,
this wouldn't have happened.
We can't foresee the future.
And I've just got married,
After 500 years of engagement.
Go and kill him.
We're not killers.
You know it too well. We may make lovers
fight or bring bad luck.
We can do black magic,
make a kid stumble...
I order you, in the name of
our sacred god Shouka,
and in the name of Bardakoosh,
the demon sculpted on my temple,
To go and never come back except
with news of Bin Al Qasim's death.
That's it,
I am fed up with this priest.
You said it. But what can we do?
We rebel.
As long as we stay under his influence,
we are his slaves.
You don't know how I feel.
My wife, her family and friends...
They're all wondering why
I ran away on my wedding day
But I'm a man!
Bakhtoo, they know we're not free.
Of course, you're a man.
You're the best man of all.
This is unfair!
The issue is that he ordered us
to kill Bin Al Qasim.
I will not only kill him,
I am ready to tear him to pieces.
- Did they really enter Armail?
- Yes, my princess.
After besieging it for three months.
- How is he?
- Very well.
Is his wife with him, Abu Haroun?
No, princess.
I checked myself.
Could he have forgotten
his promise to me?
That I will always be in his heart
and keep loving me
Love that
defies distance,
far away from me
Engulfed me with a yearning
I can't contain any more.
Is his heartbeat still eager?
Does he still long for a chance
To declare his love to me?
Just a glance of him
Would fill me with joy
Creating such strong feelings
I can't contain any more
Our next stop is here: Debal.
The great stronghold.
They're asleep.
Come on, let's possess them.
let's go
He who rules Debal,
controls the whole land of Sindh.
Our ground forces will proceed
on a path parallel to the shore.
We surround the city
and set up our giant catapult.
That will put them
between a rock and a hard place.
Finally the place is empty
and he's alone.
Let's finish our mission quickly
so I can get back to my bride.
Come on, follow me and be quiet.
He created man from clay,
like a potter,
And he created the jinn
from a smokeless flame of fire.
He's talking about us.
So, which of the favors of your Lord
would you deny?
I won't move from here,
pull yourself together Shamhoresh.
I can't.
Lord of the two sunrises
and Lord of the two sunsets.
So, which of the favors of your Lord
would you deny?
Did you hear?
God is great.
- Shamhoresh?
- Yes.
- Are you crying?
- His words moved me.
Close your ears and don't listen.
God is great.
We have to kill him
while he's kneeling.
No, why should we kill a man
who never hurt us?
He's an enemy of our master,
our patron.
- But he's not our enemy.
- But we are forced to do it.
We're not free.
Oh company of jinn and mankind,
if you are able to pass beyond
heaven and earth, then pass.
You will not pass,
unless God allows you.
So, which of the favors of your Lord
would you deny?
God is great.
Afrakoosh, Bardakoosh,
King of the demon sculpted
on the walls of the temple
of the sacred Shouka.
Come here before me,
I will not harm you.
Those two naughty jinn,
refuse to obey my orders.
Damn them!
Where are they?
I'm free!
The taste of life
is no longer bitter.
I'm free.
The taste of life
is no longer bitter.
No more black magic.
No more evil and bad deeds.
I'm never going back
to harming people with magic.
I'm free.
The taste of life
is no longer bitter.
How splendid is the taste of freedom!
I've desired it for so long.
The world seems like
a river flowing with sweets.
I feel as free as a bird
keeping my conscience clean
in the silky wings of a butterfly
flying right beside me.
I'm free.
The taste of life
is no longer bitter.
I'm free.
The taste of reality
is no longer bitter to me.
I'm free, Shamho.
Have a kiss.
Me too, Bakhtito.
I don't like nicknames.
You're still the same.
Fine, I'll let it go this time.
Oh man!
My lord!
Don't leave me with this confusion
and tell me
why didn't those two
insolent demons come?
Go back to your old tomes,
archpriest.
And find another way to keep
worshiping your sacred Shouka.
The God of cruelty and destruction!
I found it!
The magic formula!
His majesty, King Daher.
You lied to me, priest of destruction.
You told me he was dead.
And now I discover that
he's leading the Arab army!
Please, listen to me.
Speak priest!
No, my lord, I swear I fell victim
to my two demons' trickery, but...
More lies!
I'll go to him myself.
Are you going to fight, priest?
I'll kill him to prevent
the prophecy.
- What did you find Bin Wahb?
- We are close to the Debal stronghold.
I think we should camp in those woods
where there is water and pasture.
They will camp here.
So it seems.
I wish we could go to him, Abu Haroun.
Would you disobey the king?
I don't know Abu Haroun,
but my heart...
It's your father, the king.
I knew you were here, when I looked
for you and I couldn't find you.
You know, father...
What I know well, is that we have
an agreement with Daher.
And we have to abide by it.
But, father...
If you don't obey my orders
I will put you in jail. Let's go!
We'll act in complete secrecy.
The fleet has reached Debal's shores
Great. Our siege is now complete.
Let's offer them peace.
Daher is a cunning criminal.
He won't accept peace.
We have to try to avoid
the horrors of war.
How long will I stay imprisoned here?
Until he frees Debal.
If Bin Al Qasim is victorious
Daher and his men will flee
to the North.
Then our king will no longer be afraid
of Daher's wrath.
And I can see him?
Yes, my daughter.
Let's hope it will happen soon.
He's back, and who knows...
If he will come to see me.
He overcomes the distance
to come closer to me.
He speaks to me, with a gaze
that means the universe to me.
I am hostage to my own desire
and I can bear it no more.
The polar star is there and also here.
Didn't Abu Haroun say he'd bring her
when we reach Debal?
Yes he did.
Why didn't he keep his promise?
Maybe it's better like this.
I'll go and bring you some food.
- Have you seen the "bride"?
- What? Where is she?
Why are you shocked? I mean the
giant catapult we're standing on.
Damn you, Shamhoresh.
Abul Riyah built it, the one-legged man.
Do you remember him?
- Do you see what I see?
- Oh no it is him.
Will he fight?
After he lost control of us, it seems he
will try to prevent the prophecy himself.
Bin Al Qasim is in great danger.
Stop staring at me. Come!
- Where is he?
- There.
He's pretending to be a water seller,
that trickster.
Abul Aswad has besieged the harbor.
We're ready too. Send our messenger
to offer peace to the city.
Damn these two.
You know, brave men of Debal,
your city is fortified with walls
that can't be breached.
It is protected by Shouka,
the God of destruction.
And whoever tries to invade it
is doomed to disappear.
Glory to Shouka.
Glory to Shouka,
protector of Debal and Sindh.
Have courage and hold on
and we will defeat them,
as we did before.
Death to Arabs!
Death to the Arabs!
My lord, they've sent a messenger
with their peace terms.
Their terms? Do you hear this,
heroes of Debal?
There will be no peace and no negotiation
You've heard it yourself
No peace no negotiation.
What news of the priest of destruction?
- He doesn't get tired.
- Bakhtoo, I'm dead tired.
Bakhtoo.
Save me, Shamhoresh. If I die
in this body, I won't come back.
Don't be scared.
You know, Shamhoresh,
I've not consummated my marriage yet.
I wish I had a baby jinni
to carry my legacy if I die.
How do you think they will respond?
They may choose peace.
They're opening the gates.
Is that all Bin Al Qasim can do?
Two degrees up.
Up two more degrees.
It's our chance, Sobha, hurry!
Archers!
- Have you lost your mind Mohamed
- Then why are you following me?
I am not sure
but I won't leave you alone.
Attack!
- What are we doing sir?
- Just trust in God and in your leader.
Oh God! Oh God!
This isn't over
we're just starting
Bin Al Qasim entered the city with his
men, after Daher and his men fled north.
You've long been waiting for this.
Why don't you go to him?
I miss him so much,
but I'd rather die,
than beg to see him.
Who knows if he still remembers me?
Fokha?
Are you tired of longing for her,
my prince?
I've never stopped thinking of her.
If I were you, I would not wait.
I've counted the nights
waiting to see you.
I was so scared that
you would forget me.
I spared no effort
to come back to you.
I can't believe you're back.
Will you marry me?
Don't cry, my love.
Maybe they're tears of joy.
After my battle with Daher,
we will get married.
I worry for your safety from Daher
and his giant elephants.
Don't worry, my love.
I've planned for everything.
Will you allow me to help you?
In battle?
- Did you forget I'm a warrior?
- I'd be worried you'd get hurt in battle.
As long as we're together,
there's no fear.
Hurry up, men, we need to be done
before sunset.
Riders are coming from the woods.
What are you doing here?
We're digging a canal to collect
the seasonal rain.
Finish quickly and leave.
We'll ambush them here.
The main battalion
will hide behind the trees.
The advance guard will wait
for them by the river, here.
When the enemy army advances,
our knights will retreat.
luring them into this path,
where we will attack them
from all sides.
Advance!
After them!
I don't understand.
Do you understand any of this?
Mohammed Bin Al Qasim left Zaid alone.
What's happening?
They followed our men along the path.
It is time, attack!
Perfect!
Our plan has succeeded.
Get ready for a great victory.
Advance!
Our plan worked.
Hit them!
They've overcome our men!
Right flank.
Courage my men
Left flank.
- What is this?
- It's fire, my lord
Hold your positions.
Elephants are afraid of fire!
The fire comes from behind us. The
elephants will push the horses forward.
Advance!
They look terrifying, Bakhtoo.
Show no mercy.
Hit them hard
Why are they staying still?
Why don't they move forward?
Now!
Fire!
Advance!
Traitors!
Hold your positions
Don't leave me here.
Throw my body into the sea.
Zaid!
Watch out, Zaid!
What if I defeat you, Bin Al Qasim?
I'll let you go
you can flee with your men.
And your men?
Stay away from him.
- But, Bin Al Qasim!
- I said stay away from him.
Take him prisoner.
Sobha.
You did well.
Nothing is impossible...
Nothing is impossible!