♪ ♪
[ Y2flix.cc - Watch Movies and TV Shows Online for Free ]
DAVID:
I had the most amazing dream.
- [birds chirping]
- [rumbling]
[clock ticking]
RAMONA:
What was it?
[wind whistling]
DAVID:
The house was finally finished.
♪ ♪
The decorating was done.
The barn was full.
[ticking continues]
The yard was covered
in those flowers you love.
What are they called?
RAMONA:
Irises?
- DAVID [chuckles]: Yeah.
- Hmm?
DAVID:
Irises.
They were everywhere.
And we were having so much fun.
You, me and the kids.
Life was good.
RAMONA:
That's a nice dream.
DAVID: The only thing left
was the name.
RAMONA: Every farm
doesn't need a name, you know?
Mm. Mm-mm.
DAVID:
With all the work we've done...
...we're naming
this damn place.
[crackling]
So...
What name would you pick?
[Ramona chuckling over video]
DAVID:
Hmm?
For the perfect home?
RAMONA:
Mm...
I don't know.
[David sighs]
That's no fun.
It's quite fun
because I don't know.
The kids are supposed to say,
"I don't know."
RAMONA:
I-I can... I-I don't know.
[David chuckling]
[Ramona sighs heavily]
Hmm...
I had the most amazing dream.
[muffled knocking]
RAMONA:
What was it?
DAVID:
The house was finally finished.
TAYLOR [muffled]:
Hey, Mom?
DAVID: The, uh,
the decorating was done.
The barn was full.
TAYLOR [muffled]:
Mom.
The yard was covered
in those flowers you love.
What are they called?
RAMONA:
Irises.
- [chuckles]: Yeah.
- Hmm?
Iri--
Mom!
[groaning]
Power's out.
RAMONA:
[sighs] Shit.
So, um, are you gonna, like,
call the electric company
or something?
[groans]
- Can you hurry?
- Just...
let me wake up, Tay.
[Taylor sighs]
- RAMONA: Okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
[groaning]
[pained grunting]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[grunts]
[sighs] Give me strength.
Give me strength.
ANNIE:
"'Let me in.'
"'Not by the hair
on my chinny chin chin,'
"replied the little pig.
"'Then I'll huff and I'll puff
and I'll blow your house in.'
"But before he could,
"the little pig just opened
the door and let him inside.
"Because all the big, bad wolf
wanted to do
"was to be friends, and the
little pig wanted that, too.
"So, they painted watercolors,
"and they read books,
and they ate snacks.
"Then the little pig took
the big, bad wolf
"into the little pig's closet.
"And then
the big, bad wolf found
"the most colorful dresses
they could find,
"because the big, bad wolf
wanted to play dress-up.
- So..."
- Big, bad wolf plays dress-up?
Penguin doesn't like
the scary parts.
Just wanted to say
good morning.
[whispers]:
Good morning.
[crutches thumping]
♪ ♪
TAYLOR: All right,
come on, buddy. Come on.
Go, go, go, go, go.
All right, ready, boy? Okay?
Go get it.
[dog panting]
[chickens clucking
and squawking]
All right, buddy.
Hey, guys.
[clucking and squawking
continue]
Ready?
[dog sniffing]
[bottles rattling]
[Taylor sighs]
All right.
[gas hissing]
[knob clicking]
[sighs]
[groans quietly]
[floorboards creaking]
♪ ♪
[lighter clicks]
[pills rattling]
[sighs]
[sizzling]
Damn it.
[grunts]
[dishes clinking]
[crutches thumping]
[yelps]
[breathing heavily]
- [crutches thumping]
- [food sizzling]
Annie! Uh-- What are you doing?
- ANNIE: I wanted cheese.
- Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh.
I'll do it. I'll do it. Okay.
Tay, you got to watch her.
Here.
- [Ramona sighs]
- [quietly]: All right.
So, you want extra eggs?
Here you go.
[Ramona groans]
Thank you.
TAYLOR:
Yeah, did they, um...
Did they say how long
till the power comes back on?
Um...
I can't call 'em, Tay.
Mom, are you serious?
Can we not, please?
So, you can't play
your video games for a day.
Oh, my God.
If you hadn't broken
your phone,
maybe you could have
called them yourself.
[Taylor sighs]
What about the food
in the fridge?
It'll be fine
if we keep the door closed.
So, let's try not
to open it much.
[crunching]
Tay, what's...
What's in these?
What am I tasting?
Doritos?
What?
- I like it.
- I like it, too.
[laughing quietly]
[Ramona laughing]
[Annie and Taylor join in]
[laughing]
[Ramona clears her throat]
[dog gagging]
Oh, Charlie.
- What... Oh. -Gross.
- ANNIE: Charlie.
G-- Ugh.
- [Charlie groans] -TAYLOR: Ew.
- RAMONA: Charlie.
What is that?
[whining]
What'd you all feed him?
Food, Mom.
Why wasn't it dog food?
'Cause we don't have any.
All right.
I'll add it to the list.
Put him out on his chain.
I'm still eating.
Tay.
Now.
[sighs] Come, boy.
- Come on. -I'll help you, Mommy.
- Thank you.
- [door closes]
- [insects chirring]
Come here.
Hey, bud.
Charlie, Charlie. Come here.
Put it in the garbage.
[sniffles]
And wash your hands really well.
[cabinet door closes]
[grunts]
[sniffles]
[paper rustling]
[water rushing loudly]
[muffled rumbling]
- [rain falling]
- [windshield wipers pulsing]
♪ ♪
[horn blaring continuously
in distance]
[blaring horn grows louder]
- [horn honking]
- DAVID [muffled]: Watch out!
[metallic crashing]
[glass tinkling]
TAYLOR [muffled]:
Mom.
- Mom.
- Yeah.
[water continues running]
There's a woman in the yard.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[Charlie barking outside]
- Mommy?
- Uh-huh?
Who is that?
I don't know.
[Charlie continues barking]
ANNIE:
Where'd she come from?
I don't know that, either.
[barking continues]
TAYLOR:
What a creepy lady.
ANNIE:
Yeah.
Why is her face covered?
Uh, maybe to protect her
from the sun?
Mom, come on now.
I don't know.
She's probably disfigured
or something, or...
Maybe she's, uh, dead.
[gasps] Mama.
- RAMONA: Taylor, stop.
- What?
You're scaring your sister.
The lady ain't dead.
If she was,
she'd, you know, tip over.
No, she could be.
See, dead bodies get
all stiff and stuff.
We learned about it
in school, see.
One time, this guy died
and nobody knew about it.
And when they found his body
a few days later,
his arm was stuck out like this.
- Mama!
- RAMONA: Tay, stop.
TAYLOR [imitates ghost]:
Ooh...
Tay, knock it off! Please?
- She is not dead.
- [barking continues]
She's probably just...
...lost.
ANNIE:
Probably she just needs help.
Maybe we should call
the ambulance.
Well, that's a good idea,
Annie baby.
Yeah, that is
a really good idea, Annie.
Except we can't.
Remember?
[grunting]
[barking continues]
- TAYLOR: Why is she dressed
like that? -Yeah.
TAYLOR: It looks like
she's going to a funeral.
ANNIE:
Yeah.
[barking]
RAMONA:
Charlie!
- Stop!
- [barking continues]
ANNIE:
Mommy?
- I'm getting scared.
- Okay, come here.
There's nothing
to be scared of, okay?
Daddy would know what to do.
Uh...
All right. All right.
I'm gonna go out
and talk to her.
- You are?
- Yep.
- ANNIE: Really?
- Wh-Why you? You're injured.
- Tay?
- What?
Just stay inside
with your sister.
[grunts]
Everything will be fine.
- Okay?
- [barking continues]
Charlie!
Enough!
Stop.
Nonstop barking.
[barking]
[chickens clucking]
[sighs] Hey. Oh, no.
Annie. Annie, it's okay.
It's okay.
I know Mom hasn't really
been Mom lately, okay?
But I'm here.
All right?
[barking continues]
RAMONA [shouting]:
Can I help you?
Hello?!
How about I look after you,
and you look after Penguin here?
Okay?
[Taylor laughs quietly]
Ma'am?
Charlie! Stop!
♪ ♪
Can you even hear me?
I just want to help you.
Where'd she get that chair?
I don't know.
[woman muttering quietly]
Sorry?
WOMAN:
How did I...
...get here?
I don't know.
Was gonna ask you
the same thing.
Are you hurt?
WOMAN [distorted]:
What's your name?
Uh, Ramona.
What about you?
WOMAN [normal voice]:
Ramona what?
Mm...
Just Ramona's fine.
WOMAN:
I only ask 'cause I noticed
that ring on your finger.
[distorted]:
This your home?
Uh-huh.
Mm...
My husband... bought it
as a fixer-upper.
WOMAN: Looks like
he's still got a lot to fix.
Look, I'm just trying
to help you.
You seem confused, and...
...lost.
What you need?
Just tell me.
WOMAN [normal voice]:
Nothing.
I'm fine.
Well, um, if you're fine...
...can you get off
my property, please?
WOMAN: Ever wish someone else
would be strong for once?
And instead, you could just...
[echoing]:
disappear.
Ma'am...
my husband should be back
very soon.
You should probably go now.
Please.
WOMAN [echoing]:
Your husband's not coming home.
Excuse me?
WOMAN:
Your injured leg,
that busted-up truck over there.
Guess you were lucky.
[echoing]:
And he was not.
And who are you?
ANNIE:
Mommy!
Go back inside!
Go!
WOMAN:
Your children are such darlings.
[distorted]:
Ripe enough to eat.
Get off my property,
or I'm calling the police.
WOMAN [normal voice]:
Today is the day, Ramona.
[distorted]:
You called, and I came.
[singsongy]:
Today is the day.
[muffled rumbling]
♪ ♪
Where is she going?
- [barking]
- Charlie, hush!
- [barking continues]
- [grunting]
[grunting]
[keys jingling]
[ignition sputtering]
Come on.
- [ignition sputtering]
- [barking continues]
What is she doing?
I'm scared.
It's okay.
[barking]
[Charlie whining]
[panting]
RAMONA [whispering]:
Come on. Come on.
[ignition sputtering]
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
[sighs]
I'm going out there,
and I'm not going unarmed.
Wait till Mommy comes back.
- [crutches thump] -Jesus, Mom!
- What are you doing?
Nothing.
TAYLOR:
So?
Who is she? What does she want?
Nothing. She's just some woman.
Why'd you go to the Jeep?
Uh, I thought
we might need this,
just in case the power doesn't
come back on by tonight.
Mom.
Mom, come on. What did she say?
RAMONA: Oh, she didn't really
say anything.
Just thought I was
her nurse or something.
Her nurse?
Yeah, she said something
about being on medication.
Maybe even be off
her medication.
Either way...
she's very confused.
Okay, yeah,
but how did she get here?
Probably wandered off
from that nursing home
by the high school?
That's my guess.
But why is she dressed
like that?
Babe, I don't know.
But we should just
not mess with people
in that kind of a state, so...
best we don't go outside.
Ooh.
- Who wants ice cream?
- [Annie gasps]
- Me.
- Come on. Come help me.
- RAMONA: Vanilla?
- Yes.
- Yes what?
- Yes, please.
Okay. One for Annie,
two for Mommy,
and... Tay?
Tay, ice cream?
Okay.
Once the freezer door's open,
we got to eat all
the ice cream before it melts.
She tell you her name?
Mom?
- No.
- No?
Then how are we supposed
to ask the nursing home
if she's missing
if we don't know her name?
Tay, she was confused.
Maybe hurt. I don't know.
It wasn't easy getting answers
out of her, okay?
[sighs]
I think you should
get Dad's gun.
And if you don't, I will.
Go to your room.
No.
- Tay, go to your room.
- No!
Go!
[Ramona grunting]
Annie, baby.
If you don't eat up
the ice cream,
Mommy's gonna have
to eat it instead.
♪ ♪
[Ramona sighs]
As soon as the power
comes back on,
I'll call
and get her out of here.
In the meantime,
doors are all locked,
and we'll just keep
an eye out on her.
Okay?
- ANNIE: Mama?
- Hmm?
I think she's closer.
Annie, take it to your brother.
[Annie sighs]
♪ ♪
[wind whistling softly]
- [insects chirring]
- [wind whooshing softly]
[metallic creaking and groaning]
[Ramona sighs]
[Ramona groans quietly]
"Blue."
Mommy?
Uh-huh.
That's-that's good, baby.
[inhales sharply, groans]
That lady hasn't
gotten up once today, Mommy.
Not even to go to the bathroom.
RAMONA:
[chuckles] Nope.
♪ ♪
Mm.
"Purple."
Mommy, that correct?
Does that look correct to you?
The hump goes the other way
on the "R."
It goes to the right.
[groans] Wait. Ah, ah, ah.
Here, let me show you. Look.
Little "R."
Big "R."
RAMONA:
Mm.
[continues writing]
How come
you don't paint anymore?
Maybe I will,
when a beautiful picture
comes into Mommy's... head.
Erase it and try again.
♪ ♪
There. Is that correct?
Uh-huh. That looks good.
Uh, stay here with your brother.
Uh, I'll be right back.
[Ramona grunts]
[chimes tinkling softly]
[tinkling grows louder]
[insects chirring]
[lock clicking]
[grunts]
[whispering]:
Charlie.
Charlie, inside now.
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[chain rattling]
[strained grunting]
Shit.
[grunting]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
What happened?
Hmm?
Nothing.
ANNIE:
"Red."
Is that correct?
TAYLOR:
No.
No, no. It's-it's wrong, Annie.
Did the "R" backwards again.
He's right, honey. Try again.
[ball continues bouncing]
Taylor, can you not
do that, please?
Taylor!
Hey, Mom.
Why don't we just drive
to a neighbor's house?
So, that way,
we can use their phone
and we can call
the old folks' home,
and we can get
Missus Weirdo Funeral Lady
out of our yard even faster.
See? I'm a genius.
I can't drive like this,
and you know that.
Yeah, but I can.
- Mm-mm.
- Mom, come on.
Dad used to let me drive
the Jeep
up and down the driveway
all the time.
RAMONA:
Twice. He let you do it twice.
Okay, but it'll be like
ten minutes of driving, tops.
- No.
- Why?
Because one, I said so,
and two, you're not old enough.
Can you at least
just let me try?
I said no.
[inhales]
Fine.
[sighs] F-Fine.
I'll-I'll just walk.
Th-There's that one farm,
uh-- What's it called?
Um, The A-Aurora? Aurora Acres?
You know, I'll-- It's-it's
only a couple of miles away.
I'll-I'll walk there,
and then I'll ask them
if we can use their phone
- and-and get this lady...
- Taylor.
[slowly]:
You're not going anywhere.
[Taylor scoffs]
[quietly]:
Bitch.
Excuse me.
- What did you just say?
- Nothing.
RAMONA:
No, I heard it. You said...
TAYLOR: I said you were acting
like one of those.
Not that you were one.
[breathes deeply]
[ball continues bouncing]
♪ ♪
[ball bouncing louder]
[ball thuds]
[window slams shut]
Annie, the hump goes
to the right!
To the right!
Which way does it go?
- [softly]: Right.
- To the right.
How many times
does it take you to get it?
God. How many times
do I have to tell you?
Same thing with your brother:
"Stop throwing the ball."
Same thing with you:
The hump, it goes to the right.
What are you looking at?
[crayon drops]
Which way does the "R" go?
Which way does the hump go?
Then don't do it
the other way again.
Do you understand?
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
Mommy just got
a little upset, okay?
I'm sorry. Come here.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry. It's okay.
It's okay.
Mm-hmm.
Everything's gonna be okay, hmm?
[Annie screams]
Annie.
RAMONA:
[grunting] Shit.
- Annie.
- Ah.
Oh, my God. Here.
- What happened?
- Ow.
I was getting water,
- and I stepped on something.
- [Ramona grunts]
Oh, baby.
I got tweezers upstairs.
Let's go clean it out
and put a Band-Aid on it, okay?
- [Annie gasps softly]
- Get her down.
- Don't make me step in the
blood. -Okay. Don't-- Got you.
Stay on the ball
of your foot, okay?
ANNIE:
Okay. Ow.
Can you keep an eye
on her? Okay?
ANNIE:
Got a little blood on Penguin.
RAMONA:
Aw, it's okay.
It's just a little blood.
Just get upstairs, okay?
ANNIE:
Ow.
[insects chirring]
[crutches thumping]
ANNIE:
Ow, ow.
[Ramona grunting]
[whispering]:
Charlie.
Okay.
- [inhales sharply]
- Does that feel better?
Yeah, it feels better.
Annie, baby, um...
...I didn't mean
for this to happen.
It's okay. It was an accident.
Yeah.
It was an accident.
Accidents happen.
Like when Daddy crashed
and died.
[insects chirring]
[gasps softly]
♪ ♪
Mommy?
- Mm?
- Are we gonna stay here?
What do you mean?
In this house.
Now that Daddy's dead.
We still gonna live here?
I don't know, babe.
Do you want to live here?
Do you?
♪ ♪
I don't know.
If you don't want to, it's okay.
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
[clattering]
[breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
[ignition sputtering]
[sputtering stops]
- [creaking and clattering]
- [gasps]
[soft rustling]
- [wind blowing]
- [cover rustling]
[wind gusting]
[breath trembling]
[clattering]
- [grunting]
- [distorted shriek]
[gasps]
[Taylor grunts]
Damn it, Tay!
Get the f-- Get in the house!
Now!
♪ ♪
- [door opens]
- RAMONA: What the hell
- is the matter with you?
- [door slams shut]
I told you to stay
inside this house!
You know what else you told me?
That everything
was gonna be fine.
Oh, oh, "Everything's fine.
Everything's fine."
Well, guess what, Mom.
It isn't!
Tay.
But you already knew that,
didn't you?
- You knew the car didn't work.
- [sighs]
Who is this woman?!
Huh?!
What are you not telling us?!
And-and where's Charlie, huh?
He's dead, isn't he?
RAMONA:
Taylor, please.
TAYLOR:
See? No, she's been lying to us
all day about that woman
out there.
Right?
Admit it.
You know who this woman is.
Right?
I am just trying to protect you.
Oh, well, you're doing
a really good job at it.
See, I don't know why we should
listen to you, anyways.
I mean...
She's on crazy person pills,
you know.
Tay, I'm sorry. I'm...
No. No. I should have
done this hours ago.
RAMONA:
Tay. [grunts] Taylor.
Tay!
Tay, stop!
[lock clicks]
Taylor, I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
[doorknob rattles]
[pounding on door]
Taylor!
- [pounding on door]
- Taylor, open the door.
Taylor, don't you dare.
Taylor!
[Ramona cries out]
[whimpering]
[airy howling]
[panting, grunting]
[Ramona grunting]
[whimpering]
RAMONA:
Put it back!
Taylor! Taylor, come here.
- Taylor! Don't! Taylor!
- [door slams shut]
Taylor. Shit.
[cries out]
Taylor. Taylor!
- [lock clicks]
- [pounding on door]
Taylor!
- Tay, don't you go outside.
- Hey.
Hey, don't worry. Dad taught me
how to use this thing.
Just, um,
don't go outside, all right?
And-and don't let her out.
- [pounding on door]
- RAMONA: Taylor, stay inside!
Don't you go out there!
All right, listen up, lady.
You're trespassing, all right?
You got ten seconds
to get off my property
before I start shooting.
All right, legally,
I can do that, I think.
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Lady, I am not playing with you.
Five!
♪ ♪
Four!
Three!
Two!
♪ ♪
Annie, baby,
can you come help me?
Annie?
Annie, baby?
Your daddy never
take you hunting?
Shut up about my dad.
It wasn't him.
[insects chirring]
RAMONA:
Annie?
Mommy?
Annie, can you, can you get
that knob on the floor?
[wind whistling]
[chimes jingling]
[Taylor gasps]
[breath trembling]
Annie, I'm sorry.
I'm trying to do what's best
for you and your brother,
so I changed
the scary parts, honey.
You killed my dog, right?
You bitch.
You're confused.
Your mother's been lying to you.
About everything.
What do you mean?
That night,
when you lost your daddy,
your mama told it all...
[whispers]:
backwards.
[soft clattering]
Oh, God.
Oh, Annie. Thank you, honey.
Thank you. Thank you.
[sniffles] Okay.
Wh... What are you doing?
Annie, come here.
- Annie. [stammers]
- Annie.
Annie, come here, now.
Go to the living room.
Tay... give me that gun.
You lied to me.
You said that the roads
were wet,
that Dad just lost control
of the wheel.
But that was just another lie,
wasn't it?
Tay...
What really happened
that night, Mom?
- Please...
- Mom, I need to know.
Okay.
[sighs]
The night was going well,
at first.
We had a beautiful dinner.
And your dad, he...
...he knew something was wrong.
That... something was
on my mind.
So I told him the truth.
- [low crowd chatter]
- [piano playing gentle melody]
[David clears his throat]
All I'm saying is,
the kids are happy.
I'm happy.
So, I don't get to be happy?
You weren't happy in the city.
Always coming home,
crying, upset.
And all you'd ever tell me is,
"I'm suffocating."
At least I could work there.
Right?
You're fulfilled in the ways
that you want to be fulfilled.
I am not.
Everything about me is
giving over to everybody else.
I'm doing stuff for you.
I'm doing stuff for the kids.
I'm doing stuff for the farm.
I'm doing stuff
for the fucking chickens.
We can't make another shift.
We just did that.
Which you said
you were okay with.
you were happy with.
Which you said you were
looking forward to doing all...
[sighs]
We can't just keep moving
all the time.
Okay. So, how about I go?
[laughs softly]
Ramona.
This was a "we" decision.
Which is now a "we" issue
that we have to fix.
And we can't fix it
by you going away.
Well, maybe it's not fixable.
Check, please.
[David exhales]
We had a... this vision of a,
of a perfect life.
And I just...
I just couldn't live it.
- [insects chirring]
- [steady pulsing]
[soft whooshing]
[ball bouncing]
♪ ♪
[steady pulsing grows louder]
Charlie?
You're not happy.
Okay.
But if you want things
to get better,
you're gonna have to dig deeper.
[engine starts]
[rain falling]
[distant thunder rumbling]
♪ ♪
- [low whooshing]
- [glass snapping]
- [scraping]
[low whooshing]
- [rain falling]
- [windshield wipers thumping]
♪ ♪
[thunder rumbling]
- [horn blaring]
- Watch out!
- [tires screeching]
- [crashing]
[glass tinkling]
So, yes, I was driving
the car that night.
So I lied.
I lied to you.
[steady pulsing]
[low whooshing]
- [door creaking]
- [low clattering]
[gasps]
[low whooshing]
[screaming]
Annie, what happened?
Are you okay?
- [loud clattering]
- What's going on?
It's her.
Come on, baby! Come here!
[glass shattering]
Tay, come on.
Annie!
Go.
[clattering continues]
[whimpering]
We got to get somewhere dark.
Completely dark.
- TAYLOR: The attic!
- Go, Annie.
[clattering continues]
Go, Annie, go.
[train whistle howls]
RAMONA:
Go. Go!
[panicked chatter]
- [train chugging]
- [airy howling]
- [train whistle howls]
- Go.
Hurry, hurry, hurry. Come on.
- [airy howling]
- [chugging continues faster]
[rattling]
[grunting]
- RAMONA: Go, Annie.
- [grunts]
Go, honey! Go!
- Go! Go!
- [Annie grunting]
[low whooshing]
RAMONA:
[grunts] Tay!
[grunting]
TAYLOR:
Got you.
[both grunting]
[Ramona grunting]
[low whooshing]
- [Annie whimpering]
- Annie!
- [screaming]
- RAMONA: Hang on to her!
Go! Tay, get her!
- [screaming]
- Tay!
ANNIE:
Mommy!
[Ramona grunting]
TAYLOR [whispering]:
Come on. Come on, come on.
That's okay. That's okay.
Hey.
- Come here. Come here, honey.
- Got to get up now.
RAMONA:
She can't get in.
She can't get in now, okay?
We're safe.
♪ ♪
[rhythmic panting]
- [breathing shakily]
- [creaking]
[breathing rapidly]
RAMONA:
It's okay, honey.
She can't get in here.
It's okay.
- [clattering]
- [gasping]
[thumping]
[Ramona gasping]
[clattering]
- [thumping]
- [chandelier rattling]
- [debris falling]
- Move, Tay. Move.
[creaking]
[rattling]
[breathing heavily]
[thumping, debris falling]
[creaking]
[Ramona breathing heavily]
[low creaking]
[eerie roar]
RAMONA:
Taylor, move!
TAYLOR:
Oh, my God. Quickly.
[flashlight clicking]
[Ramona grunting]
TAYLOR:
Go. Quickly.
- [Ramona grunting]
- [clattering]
Stay here, Annie.
- [Ramona yells]
- [glass breaking]
[Ramona screams]
[airy shrieking]
Mom!
[Taylor grunts]
[rapid clicking]
[clicking stops]
[singsongy]:
Annie.
[breathing shakily]
[singsongy]:
Annie.
[breathing rapidly]
[steady pulsing]
[distorted]:
It's me, baby.
Don't be scared.
[faint, distorted screaming]
WOMAN:
I've come to bring you home.
[faint, distorted screaming
continues]
♪ ♪
No.
I won't hurt you.
- I would never...
- [whimpers]
ever hurt you.
Shh, shh.
Shh...
[pulsing stops]
[breathing shakily]
[Ramona whimpering]
[Taylor crying quietly]
ANNIE [muffled]:
Mommy?
- [Ramona gasps]
- [flashlight clicking]
RAMONA:
Annie?
[clicking continues]
Annie! Come on.
We need to find her.
[Ramona grunting]
[clicking continues]
Annie?
[heartbeat pulsing]
ANNIE [muffled]:
Mommy?
Annie?
[clicking continues]
[clicking stops]
RAMONA:
Stay here.
I'm gonna go by myself.
TAYLOR [echoing]:
Wait. [stammers]
Here, take this.
♪ ♪
ANNIE [muffled]:
Mommy?
[lighter clicking]
Annie?
ANNIE [muffled]:
Mommy?
RAMONA:
Annie?
I'm coming.
[whispering]:
Annie?
♪ ♪
[lighter click echoes]
I had the most amazing dream.
[birds chirping]
The house was finally finished.
The decorating was done.
The barn was full.
The yard was covered
with those flowers you love.
What are they called?
Irises.
Yeah. Irises.
They were everywhere.
We were having so much fun.
You, me, the kids.
Life was good.
That's a nice dream.
The only thing left
was the name. [chuckles]
RAMONA [voice breaking]:
Every farm doesn't need
to have a name, you know.
With all the work we've done,
I'm naming this damn place.
[Ramona chuckles]
What name would you pick, huh?
For the perfect home?
[crying]:
I don't know.
Baby, I really don't know.
- Aw.
- [sniffles]
Come on, it's okay.
[Ramona crying]
It's okay.
Oh, I've missed you.
[Ramona sighs]
♪ ♪
DAVID:
What's wrong?
Where are you going?
- [Ramona grunts]
- Where are you going?
[mutters quietly]
[Ramona grunting]
[grunting stops]
[gasps]
♪ ♪
[Charlie barking in distance]
[insects chirring]
RAMONA [in distance]:
Hello?
[Charlie continues barking]
Ma'am?
Can you hear me?
Just want to help you.
You lost?
[Charlie continues barking]
Are you in danger?
Ma'am!
RAMONA [as Woman]:
How did I get here?
[Charlie continues barking]
RAMONA:
Sorry?
RAMONA [as Woman]:
How did I...
get here?
RAMONA:
Um...
I-I don't know.
Was gonna ask you
the same thing.
I just want to help you
'cause you seem
confused and lost.
What do you need?
Just tell me.
[Ramona as Woman
breathing rapidly]
[whimpers]
[low whooshing]
[whimpering]
[low rumbling]
I'm drowning.
Today is the day.
Today is the day, Ramona!
♪ ♪
[Taylor breathes softly]
[steady pulsing]
[clattering]
- [Ramona grunting]
- [horn honking]
DAVID:
Watch out!
[horn blares]
Annie?
[breathing shakily]
♪ ♪
Don't be scared, baby.
It's me.
[breathing shakily]
I come to take you home.
No. No, no, no, no.
- I wouldn't hurt you.
- [low whooshing]
I would never...
- ever...
- [whimpers]
ever...
[steady pulsing]
...hurt you.
Annie. Annie.
Annie, Annie. Annie.
Annie, wake... Annie.
Annie, Annie.
♪ ♪
Annie?
Annie. Annie.
- Annie.
- [Annie gasps]
Hey. Hey. Hey, it's me.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Mom.
- We're okay.
♪ ♪
Take your sister
downstairs, Tay.
- But-but, Mom, we need to go.
No... -Hey.
Give me the gun.
Go, now.
- Go. -Come on, come on.
Annie, quickly.
Let's go.
[door closes]
This ends here.
This ends right now.
You leave and never come back.
Leave!
Leave us alone!
WOMAN: I can't tell you
how long I've waited
to see that gun in your hands.
RAMONA:
I will blow your head off.
WOMAN:
I believe you'll shoot.
Trust me, I do.
After all...
that's why I'm here.
To help you,
like you asked me to.
[quietly]:
Give me strength.
♪ ♪
WOMAN:
Every morning,
you pray for the strength...
to do what?
To go on.
No.
You threw away
all those bullets...
...except for one.
No.
I have children.
They need their mother.
They've needed their mother
for weeks.
But you've been
locked away in here.
Praying... for me.
I'm the corners of your mind.
RAMONA [quietly]:
I don't want this.
WOMAN:
The scary parts.
Today is the day.
♪ ♪
My kids...
Will they be okay?
[low whooshing]
[lighter clicking]
WOMAN:
Only if you set them free.
♪ ♪
[lighter clicks shut]
[weakly]:
I want to say goodbye first.
Of course.
RAMONA:
Annie? Taylor?
[breathlessly]:
Hey. I want you two to go.
Taylor, take your sister
and leave, huh?
You know how to get
to the neighbor's farm, right?
[grunting]
Aurora Acres, right?
- TAYLOR: Y-Yes, yes.
- Okay. Okay?
I want you to go straight there.
- Here, take this.
- But-but, Ma, what are you...
- Mom, what are you saying?
- Okay?
And you, take this.
Put this on.
Everything's gonna be all right.
You'll be...
you'll be better off.
ANNIE:
But I don't want to.
RAMONA:
Well, you have to, honey.
TAYLOR:
Mama. Mama, I don't understand.
We can all just leave together.
- We... All of us.
- Tay, no.
It'll be a lot better, okay?
Trust me.
So, go. Go on.
Go.
ANNIE:
Mommy, wait.
Annie. [sighs]
I don't want you to be alone.
Okay. Go. Go, go, go.
[sniffles]
Go, Tay.
Stop looking and go!
♪ ♪
[sniffling]
[grunts softly]
[crying quietly]
[low whooshing]
[Ramona grunts]
[whispers]:
Now.
[Ramona grunting softly]
[low whooshing]
[Ramona breathing shakily]
[Ramona grunting]
[crying]
[Woman shushing]
[Ramona whimpering]
WOMAN [whispering]:
Come on, Ramona.
Okay? It's okay.
[Woman shushing]
We don't have all day.
[Ramona grunts]
♪ ♪
[low whooshing]
[owl calling]
- [wind whistling softly]
- [insects chirping]
[owl calling]
[footsteps]
[door creaking]
TAYLOR:
Mom?
RAMONA:
Taylor? Annie?
- TAYLOR: Mom.
- ANNIE: Mama.
- Mama. -Mama.
- [Ramona grunts]
- ANNIE: Mama.
- RAMONA: Annie.
Guess what.
I changed the...
the scary parts.
You coming?
- TAYLOR: Hey, Mom?
- Yeah.
Is she gonna come back?
Well, not today.
But if she does, we'll be ready.
I'll be ready. [sniffles]
[Annie and Taylor chuckling]
♪ ♪
- [Taylor exclaims]
- ANNIE: Yes.
TAYLOR [chuckling]:
Oh, my God.
RAMONA: All right,
video games for everybody.
- ANNIE: Let's go.
- Come on.
- [Charlie barking]
- ANNIE: Hey, Charlie.
- Charlie is back home.
- Charlie. There you are.
- Charlie.
- I thought I lost you, buddy.
- ANNIE: Charlie.
- TAYLOR [laughs]: Oh, Charlie.
ANNIE:
Charlie, I love you so much.
[Taylor laughing]
RAMONA:
Come on, kids.
♪ ♪
DAVID:
I had the most amazing dream.
- [birds chirping]
- [rumbling]
RAMONA:
What was it?
♪ ♪
["Middle of This Storm" by
Ayanna Witter-Johnson playing]
♪ Each day ♪
♪ Before the sun will rise ♪
♪ I count my fears ♪
♪ Guilt now clings to me
so tight ♪
♪ Night after night ♪
♪ Shadows dance round my mind ♪
♪ Doubts grow strong ♪
♪ When I am all alone ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ And when all my thoughts
are racing ♪
♪ And when all I have
is falling down ♪
♪ Who will hold my hand? ♪
♪ Who will keep me standing ♪
♪ In the middle of this storm? ♪
♪ And when all I know
is changing ♪
♪ And when all I see
is burning down ♪
♪ Who will hold my hand? ♪
♪ Who will keep me standing ♪
♪ In the middle of this storm? ♪
♪ And when the sun begins
to set ♪
♪ I pray the wind
will take my tears ♪
♪ And let me rest ♪
♪ But every night ♪
♪ Shadows dance round my mind ♪
♪ Doubts grow strong ♪
♪ When I am all alone ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ And when all my thoughts
are racing ♪
♪ And when all I have
is falling down ♪
♪ Who will hold my hand? ♪
♪ Who will keep me standing ♪
♪ In the middle of this storm? ♪
♪ And when all I know
is changing ♪
♪ And when all I see
is burning down ♪
♪ Who will hold my hand? ♪
♪ Who will keep me standing ♪
♪ In the middle of this storm? ♪
[vocalizing]
[song ends]