Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
NETFLIX PRESENTS
MY FAMILY IN COLOUR
BY FERRARI & VENOSA
3°C, G. MARCONI INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL
SURROGATE MOTHERHOOD
Dario?
Can you stop being a moron or what?
Is this just for you?
You're such an idiot.
Shut up!
DADDY SIMONE,
COME AND GET US AS LATE AS POSSIBLE
AT LEAST TWO HOURS. GOT IT?
RECENT CALLS
INCOMING CALL
SIMONE, ANSWER!
SORRY, CAN'T TALK NOW.
I'M AT HOME!
AT HOME? SO WE AREN'T MEETING?
ACTUALLY, GIVE ME SOME SPACE.
I NEED SOME TIME!
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
ARE YOU MAD?
YOU REALIZE THIS AFTER TWO YEARS?
PLEASE, DARLING. TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON!
FORGIVE ME IF YOU CAN… I LOVE YOU!
WILL YOU GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE?
GUYS, I HAVE IMPORTANT NEWS.
LET'S MEET TOMORROW MORNING IN MY STUDIO
I'M HERE… BUT WHERE ARE YOU?
EMERGENCY ROOM