Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
♪ Don't you say my name
♪ And are you honest
♪ And are you free
♪ And do you trust
♪ You trust in me
♪ But can I believe you
♪ Do I even know how
♪ I wanna be
♪ Don't you
♪ Come around here
♪ I wanna be
♪ Just let me be free
- Good morning, and
welcome to Flesh First.
My name is Pam
Dillis, your host.
Next up, we'll see the
band in the studio.
But before we jump back
in, let's take a few calls.
1-555-62-
- All right, cut.
That was great, I
think we got it.
Thank you very much.
- How was that for you?
- It was good.
Joe.
Actually, can I have more vocal?
- Let's do it.
- Next up, we have
American duo, Boy Harsher,
with their brand new
single, "Machina",
featuring Ms. BOAN,
Mariana Saldana.
This song comes off
of their latest album,
"The Runner ".
So, without further ado, I
present to you, Mariana Saldana
and the-
♪ Machina
♪ I can't
♪ Spend the night with you
♪ Save the dance with you
♪ I can't
♪ End my night with you
♪ Feel your heart beat too
- Hello.
Where are you?
You don't have to do this.
I can help you.
Just come back.
♪ I can't
♪ End my night with you
♪ Feel your heart beat too
♪ I can't
♪ Spend the night with you
♪ Save the dance with you
♪ I can't
♪ End my night with you
♪ Feel your heart beat too
- Yeah, I love this synth.
It's kinda what
got me into music.
Before I knew what I was doing,
you could just like
hold down one key,
sweep the cutoff a little bit,
and it was just
like a whole track.
And yeah, then I was hooked.
Got some favorite ones in here.
I can show ya.
I got this guy right here.
♪ Here we go
Not that one.
That's a little
different than I thought.
Let's try this guy out.
Yeah, there we go.
Yeah.
I'd still be making this
stuff if no one was listening.
I can feel pretty
broken sometimes.
And there's something about
sticking your hands in these
sounds and controlling them.
It just makes me feel normal.
At least for a little while.
- Now that was very tender.
Lots of emotion.
Next up, we've got
a new one for you.
This one is called
"Give Me a Reason",
and you're hearing
it here first.
♪ When you come
♪ Will you call my name
♪ Come and tell me
♪ I'm the only one
♪ Afraid of the runner
♪ It draws herself clear
♪ Oh the runner
♪ What does she say
♪ When you come
♪ Will you call my name
♪ Wish I knew how
♪ To walk away
♪ Make it so easy
♪ But then you say
♪ Wish you knew how
♪ It has begun
♪ Wish I knew how
♪ I've come undone
♪ It feels like
♪ I'm coming on too strong
♪ The reason
- Hey.
Hey.
I know.
It's okay, baby.
Just come home.
It's going to be alright.
- Hey, Jae?
- Okay.
I guess that's just part of it.
Yeah.
And then.
Oh, cool.
Yeah, that looks really-
- Jae?
Knock, knock, hi.
- Okay, yeah.
I gotta go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey.
- I think
we're ready for you.
Are you feeling alright?
- Yeah, okay.
- Cool.
Let's just get this laid
in real quick, please.
Thank you.
32-33, take 4.
- Let's
talk about The Runner.
- Okay.
- A monster.
- She's reckless,
and out of control,
and it's pure evil.
There's a human side to her too.
And I hate to say it,
but I can kinda relate.
There's bad nights,
and things I regret,
and things I'd
like to take back.
- Do you see
yourself in The Runner?
♪ What's done is done
♪ My old friend
♪ Taking my way
♪ Taken to the end
♪ I'm coming to the end
♪ What's done is done
♪ My old friend
♪ Taking my way
♪ Taken to the end
♪ I'm coming to the end
♪ Feeling new
♪ Seeming used
♪ Birthday suit
♪ When they shoot
♪ Autonomy
♪ They're on the move
♪ They're onto me
♪ Like they're onto you
♪ Where do you see me
♪ Where they come
♪ When we run
♪ Autonomy
♪ They're on the move
♪ They're onto me
♪ Like they're onto you
♪ I saw fire on the runway
♪ Autonomy
♪ They're on the move
♪ They're onto me
♪ Like they're onto you
♪ When we run
♪ Feeling new
♪ Seeming used
♪ Birthday suit
♪ When they shoot
♪ Autonomy
♪ They're on the move
♪ They're onto me
♪ Like they're onto you