(film reel clattering)
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
(heart beating)
(indistinct chattering)
(sirens wailing)
(tense music)
(stretcher clattering)
(chattering on intercom)
(indistinct chattering)
(door opens)
(machinery beeping)
(Claire grunting)
(machinery beeping rapidly)
(tools clinking)
(baby crying)
(birds chirping)
(woman and man groaning)
(Claire sighs)
(clock ticking)
(soft piano music)
(Claire sighing)
(Claire sighs)
(finger taps)
(Claire scoffs)
(Claire sniffs)
(monitor clicking)
(coffee machine clacking)
(monitor beeps)
(baby cooing)
(soft piano music)
- Who's awake?
(chuckles) Who is so handsome?
(baby cooing)
Uh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Our daddy is still sleeping.
We don't wanna wake him up.
You know how grumpy he gets
if he wakes up ahead of time.
(chuckles) Oh, my little treasure.
(lips kissing)
(Claire chuckles)
(toy rattling)
(coffee machine buzzing)
(Claire sighs)
(coffee pouring)
(coffee machine clanks)
(pillows thud)
(footsteps shuffling)
(Eric clears throat)
- Babe.
I want you to meet someone.
See. Nothing.
She just sits there. Not a word.
(Monica sighs)
- Good afternoon, Claire.
My name is Monica.
- She's here to help, Claire.
- Tell me, is it more convenient for you
to come into my office?
Well, would you rather have sessions here?
Okay. Then I'm gonna come here.
Would you like that?
It's not necessary for
us to discuss anything
you don't want to talk about, you know?
I'll just come here and
spend time with you. Okay?
Great. And how about we start today?
- So you'll take us?
- Yes.
- Oh, thank you.
- It's fine.
- All right. Please.
- Claire, do you want
Eric to stay with us?
Eric, you have to leave.
- It's family therapy. Well
the whole family's here.
- You heard her wishes.
- No, I didn't.
I haven't heard a thing.
- That's not gonna work.
We won't get any positive results.
(Eric scoffs)
- Claire, why don't you talk to me?
Please. Why don't you talk to me?
- Eric, you-
- No, tell me,
No, I shouldn't!
- Eric!
This is Claire's time.
If you want a session, you
should schedule an appointment.
- Fine.
(footsteps thudding)
(door opens and slams)
- Quite a temper.
Is he abusing you?
So did you ask for me?
- No.
- I see.
- What's there?
- It's your case.
It's so big already?
- No, this one's your medical.
- May I?
- Do you wanna talk?
- I do.
- About this?
- No.
- About your mom?
- What about your husband?
- He just can't stand
the silent treatment.
(Monica chuckles)
(birds chirping)
(soft piano music)
(pen clicking)
(pen scratching)
(Claire sighs)
(bottle clattering)
(dial pad beeping)
(phone ringing)
- [Mary Voicemail] Hello.
This is Mary Clarks.
Please leave me a message after the tone
and I'll call you back
as soon as possible.
Oh, and if this is Claire, don't worry.
I'm fine. I'm probably just asleep.
(machine beeps)
- Mom, I know
what you're gonna say,
that I'm overreacting or something,
but anyways, I have a question.
Do you know how I can tell
if a hair is mine or not?
This is so stupid.
Ah, (chuckles) I don't even know how
to ask this question properly.
In conclusion, I will
only say that I found
someone else's hair in Eric's bag
and that he is cheating on me.
Mom, I know what you're going to say.
And please don't, okay?
I already caught him
lying to me several times.
(chuckles) What lies you ask?
Well, I will tell you.
First of all, he spends three
nights a week at the gym.
And second of all, he
keeps having these dinners
with clients which I'm
not even invited to.
No, of course he spends
every night in our bed
but still something is happening.
And I know it. I mean,
I can, I can feel it.
They say that a woman knows
when her man is betraying her.
Did you feel this way with Dad?
Well, why didn't you ever tell me?
Well, if you told me maybe I would...
(sighs) Yes, I don't know
what I would have done.
But who knows?
Maybe it would help.
Mom. Why didn't you...
(machine beeping)
(Claire sighing)
Oh my God.
(dial pad beeps)
(phone ringing)
- [Mary On Voicemail]
Hello. This is Mary Clarks.
Please leave me a message after the tone
and I'll call you back
as soon as possible.
Oh, and if this is Claire, don't worry.
I'm fine. I'm probably just asleep.
(machine beeps)
- You're right.
I just screwed myself up again. (chuckles)
I, the hair just seemed darker.
Call me when you wake up, please.
I, I had another bad dream.
(ominous music)
I ran and I ran
(footsteps pattering)
and my boy cried
(baby crying)
and he cried.
(footsteps pattering)
(Claire panting)
(baby crying)
And then the cries got louder
and I couldn't find him.
I lost him. I don't know where I put him.
And then I'm getting closer,
(Claire panting)
but he's nowhere to be found.
(phone clicks)
(message dings)
Babe.
(phone vibrates)
(phone vibrating)
(keyboard clattering)
(objects clattering)
(drawer opens)
(Claire sighs)
(dial pad clicking)
(phone vibrating)
(Claire sighs)
(soft jazz music)
- Are we celebrating something tonight?
How could I forget?
Oh, whoa, my God, look at you.
You look amazing.
(Claire laughing)
Wow. Let's take a look.
Hold on. Hold on.
(whistles) Whoo.
(Claire laughing)
What is going on?
Ah. Why don't we just
skip the main course?
We'll go right to the dessert.
- No, we should enjoy it fully.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- And how long have you been
enjoying it fully without me?
- (laughing) Sit.
- Okay. My God.
Whoo.
(sighs) I actually just
got done with dinner
but how much can you eat
when you're talking the whole time, right?
(Claire chuckles)
- Do not spoil the atmosphere.
(phone and keys bang)
(soft jazz music continues)
How was your day?
- Good. How was your day?
- (chuckling) Fantastic.
(Eric chuckles)
So let's have a drink.
- Let's drink.
(Claire gulping)
(glass clacks)
(Claire sighs)
What happened?
- (chuckles) Any ideas?
What day is today?
- Thursday.
- No, I mean, what day is today?
- Ah, it's March 26th.
(utensil clinks)
(Eric sighs)
- Is something wrong?
(Eric spits)
Look at me.
Look at me!
- What exactly are you celebrating?
- Why just me. We.
- No, I am not celebrating this with you.
(chair slams)
(keys jangling)
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
No, don't go, don't go, don't go, please!
Please, please, don't! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I didn't mean it!
(panting) I'll be better.
I'll be better.
- Okay.
(soft jazz music continues)
Do you wanna call Monica?
Okay, I'm gonna call Monica.
(dial pad clicking)
(Eric sighs)
What time is it?
- It's too early.
I'm just fixing your pillow.
- Mm.
(phone clicks)
(crickets chirping)
(footsteps thudding)
(pants unzip)
(Eric sighs)
(watch clicks)
(watch clattering)
(Eric sighs)
Are you asleep?
You could respond. You know?
I had a very difficult day.
- As every day.
- Well gotta pay the
bills somehow, don't we?
- I missed you.
(Eric sighs)
And you?
- (sighs) Of course I missed you.
(Eric chuckles)
(Eric sighs)
- How was your day?
- (sighs) Fine.
- Well, you said it was difficult.
- Yeah, like everyday.
- I want you.
(Eric chuckles)
- Mm.
I'm so tired, babe.
- Please?
I really want you.
- I'm all sweaty and smelly.
I should really take a
shower before we do this.
In the morning.
- A shower will only take a
couple of minutes. Come on.
(Eric chuckles)
- Let's just do it in the
morning. I'm so relaxed right now.
- (chuckles) Well I love you
and I don't care if
you're sweaty and smelly.
(Eric chuckling)
- Come on, babe. Tomorrow.
(Eric sighs)
- Well you're always in a hurry
to leave me in the mornings.
- Mm.
- You're always in a hurry to leave me.
- That's not fair.
Okay. I'm working for two here.
- (scoffs) What do you want from me?
You want me to go back to work?
- That would be nice. You know?
Your place is still your place.
- Did you contact them?
- (sighs) Your boss called me.
He just wanted to check up
and see how things were.
He wanted to see how
you were feeling. Okay?
- And?
- And I told him that you
were feeling, ah, better.
- (chuckles) Better?
So you think that I feel better?
- I don't know.
I'm just ready...
Just ready to go back to what?
- I don't know. I just thought
it would be nice for you
to get out of the house, you know,
and, and get your mind off of-
- So I should just forget about everything
as if nothing happened, right?
- I don't know.
Do as you see fit. Okay?
- No, no, you tell me.
You tell me what I need to do.
You know better!
- I wanna go to sleep. Okay?
And you're not understanding
what I'm saying.
So please just lie down.
(Claire scoffs)
- How can you be okay?
How can you be okay
when I'm suffocating?
How can you be so insensitive
that we can't even share a word about it?
- About what, Claire? Huh?
Because there is an unbearable amount
of its going on right now!
God, we need to live a normal life
and not in a fucking cemetery!
We need to live a normal life, Claire!
I love you and the only reason
I haven't grabbed my shit
and left is because of that.
- But?
- But what?
Huh? Say it.
But what? But what?
You went an entire month,
an entire month without talking to me
and not a fucking single word, Claire.
You didn't say anything.
And I thought, I thought
that was horrible.
I thought that was so bad.
But now look this? Look at this.
You're, you're, you're constantly talking,
even in your sleep.
And at work you're calling me
and you're calling me
every 15 minutes, Claire.
And if I don't answer right
away, you're texting me!
And if I don't answer that you call again.
And I don't know, I don't know how long
you can do this to me.
I don't know how long
you can do this to me
because I need some fucking peace!
Okay? I need some peace
in my own home, Claire.
Fuck!
I am not a clown.
Do I look like a fucking clown?
I am not a clown!
I am not some fucking
monkey that's gonna jump
when you say jump.
- I don't do that!
- It's either talk or fuck with you. huh?
You either wanna talk or you wanna fuck.
And it's not even good!
Look at me!
I'm fucking tired!
And I'm going to sleep
on the fucking couch!
(melancholy music)
(Claire sobbing)
(phone ringing)
- [Mary On Voicemail]
Hello. This is Mary Clarks.
Please leave me a message after the tone
and I'll call you back
as soon as possible.
Oh, and if this is Claire, don't worry.
I'm fine.
I'm probably just asleep.
(machine beeps)
- I told you
this is it.
Yes.
No. Please, please, Mom.
Tell me how can I save my marriage?
Well, what can you tell me?
You couldn't make it work with Dad.
You don't want me to be happy.
(Claire scoffs)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yeah, no, you're right.
You're right. You're right.
(sighs) A woman should always be a woman.
Yeah.
(chuckling) Who would ever want this?
(phone clicks)
(birds chirping)
(baby crying)
Hush, my love.
It's your mommy. Mommy remembers you.
Mommy loves you.
(baby cooing)
And Mommy loves your Daddy.
And there is no way that we can lose him.
(baby cooing)
(suspenseful music)
(shower spraying)
- I don't know why you
don't just go with me.
- And how exactly do you
think I'm gonna do that?
- Well, you would go upstairs
and get ready quickly
- Mm-hmm.
- And we'd go.
Preferably using your feet.
- Come on. You're out every evening.
- Well, you like this body, don't ya?
- (chuckles) Yes.
- Yes.
- Ah, seriously, I don't
know how you do it.
You here all day by yourself.
Come on. Let's train together.
- I have so much to do.
- Oh yeah? Like what?
- Why don't you just
take me out on a date?
- (laughing) We're married.
I don't have to do that anymore.
I'm kidding. Baby.
Baby, baby. Exactly, baby.
What about that?
- What about that?
(soft piano music)
- Nothing, I had a few bad days.
It's fine.
- Okay. Hey.
I love you.
- Really?
- I swear on my abs.
All six of them.
- Go.
- (sighs) You sure?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Go.
Hey, wait.
- Hey?
- Um, I read an article
that we can bring intimacy
back into our relationship
if you just carry me to bed every night.
(Eric laughing)
- Where did you hear that?
- Go.
- (chuckles) Okay, baby.
I'm gonna carry you. You
get ready. (chuckling)
(water spraying)
(suspenseful music)
(birds chirping)
- What do you see?
- It's obvious.
The woman.
- The woman?
- Free woman.
- Who is a free woman for you.
- Do you feel like a free woman, Monica?
- I could say that.
- But?
- There is no but.
- Oh. Then I envy you.
- Don't you feel free?
- I felt like that before.
(sighs) Years later, here I am,
scared,
hopeless,
useless.
- I wouldn't use those words.
- And what words would you use?
- Let's see, tired, confused, and, um...
- I only feel pity for myself.
You know I only have you?
I mean, there's only you for me.
I don't have anybody else.
God, I'm pathetic.
- You named the qualities
which as you believe
belong to you now, what about before?
- Oh, I was fearless.
Full of life.
In love.
- Do you love your husband?
- Of course I love my husband.
But I can't give my love to him alone.
- Who else?
- If I were free as before,
(soft piano music)
I wouldn't suppress my desires.
I wouldn't
ignore my impulses.
- It's not right.
- I don't care.
There's a connection between us.
I can feel it.
Why did you decide to take my case?
Why did you come here?
(both laughing)
(Monica moaning)
- And who else?
- Only you.
To show you how free I am.
(shower spraying)
- Claire?
- Oh.
Claire, do you hear me?
- Hmm?
(Monica groaning)
To show how free I am.
- You wanted to show me something.
- What?
- You left our conversation
and you mumbled about
wanting to show me something.
- Nevermind.
Why did you take my case?
- I took your case because
I wanted to be close to you.
I agreed to come here 'cause
I wanted us to be alone.
Because I wanted to help you.
- Not that.
- Because I knew I could help you.
- Why did you agree to come here?
- Because you refused
to come to my office.
- No, no.
(dishes clacking)
- Who else should you give your love to?
- Do you want a coffee?
- Claire, we're not done here.
- I wanna stop now.
- Who else should you give your love to?
- I'm tired. Okay?
- Who else, Claire.
This needs to be said.
- I want you to leave my house.
We're finished for today.
(Claire gasps)
- You know you can trust me, right?
- What are you doing here?
- Are you all right?
Come sit.
- You shouldn't be here.
Get out of here.
- Calm down.
- Get out or I'll call the police.
(suspenseful music)
- Oh, hey.
(Monica sighs)
How was today?
- We need to talk.
- Ah, okay. Yeah, let's
just, come on inside-
- No, listen.
Your wife is losing the
boundaries of reality.
(toothbrush scraping)
(water running)
No, you're not listening to me.
Do you think I'm joking?
- No, I don't think you're joking. Okay?
I just, I don't think
that this is critical.
You know, things just
started getting better.
- This is a problem.
And it's not going to get
solved by ignoring it.
If you don't see it, it
doesn't mean it doesn't exist.
You've completely stepped aside.
It's not right.
Why did you stop keeping the diary?
- Well that's why she has
the meetings with you.
- No, look, I can't keep
coming here anymore.
- Why?
- It only fuels
her disease.
She feels too comfortable at home.
You need to come to my office
and you must bring her in person.
In this setting, she
assumes that I'm her friend.
- Okay. So what's wrong with that?
She's creating a trusting relationship
with her therapist, right?
- I'm not her friend.
She's my patient.
(Eric sighs)
(hair dryer whirring)
- He's so cute.
He's literally the most
beautiful baby in the world.
Mom, how can he ignore him?
I don't understand.
You're right.
Parental instinct does
happen much later in men.
He just needs to spend
more time with the kid.
- [Eric] Babe, I'm home.
- Okay. I love you.
I gotta go. Bye.
(Eric sighs)
(footsteps thudding)
- Hey.
- What were you doing in there?
- Mm.
- Oh. Mm.
Mm.
Well someone's in a mood.
- You hungry?
- I ate already.
- Oh.
- I didn't know there was gonna be food.
- Well, then there's always gonna be food.
- Oh, okay.
- You go change.
- Okay.
- And I'm gonna bring
us some wine and cheese.
- Wine and cheese?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
Wow.
Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- Wine and cheese.
- Hey, you wanna watch something?
- Sure. Yeah, just something light.
- You know, I've been thinking for a while
that I don't need therapy anymore.
- Really?
- Yeah. I feel much better.
- What does Monica have to say about it?
- Who cares?
I feel great.
(soft piano music)
Besides, she's not gonna let me go.
It's probably just a money thing.
- Red?
(wine pouring)
- Of course.
- Since when?
- Um, (clears throat) it was on sale.
(wine pouring)
- That's my girl. (chuckles)
- Ooh, careful, careful.
(Eric clears throat)
- So...(chuckles)
I got a call from the funeral home.
They said they didn't
receive last month's check.
Did you, did you send it?
(wine spilling)
- Oh my God!
- Oh, goodness.
- I'm so clumsy.
I, oh, Jesus.
Uh, (chuckles) um, I probably just forgot.
Can you just do it for me?
- Claire, that's really
your responsibility.
- Please.
Just do it for me. Okay?
You know I'm not good with numbers.
(towel scratching)
- You're in financing. What do you mean?
Claire?
(towel scratching)
- Ow!
Ah, fuck.
(Claire scoffs and sighs)
- What did you say?
- Your mom was there.
She, she, she couldn't stay till the end
because she felt so bad.
- You're lying.
- Claire, and, and,
and soon she...
- No.
- Claire, your boss was there. Okay?
He showed up and he gave you time off
so you'd get ahold of yourself.
- Oh, fuck.
(Claire sighing)
(suspenseful music)
(door opens)
(keys jangling)
- Leave already. I'm all right.
(engine revving)
(lock clicks)
Oh God. (sobbing)
Oh God! Oh God!
Oh God, forgive me! (sobbing)
(somber music)
I didn't want that.
Oh my God. This was everything to me.
(sobbing)
I didn't, I didn't do it on purpose!
Oh my God!
(screaming)
He's wrong! He's wrong!
I didn't want it at first.
But I thought maybe it was just too early.
Oh God!
Oh my God, forgive me!
(sobbing hysterically)
Our father who art in heaven,
hallowed by thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
(whimpering)
Oh my God!
Give us this...
Give us this day our daily bread
And forgive us our
trespasses as we forgive...
As we forgive those who
trespass against us.
(sighs) Let's do something nicer.
- Hey, hey, you.
Come on. What are you doing?
You need to stop running
around the house and sit.
- I spend all day in this chair.
- Yeah, you look great in
it and you can have it.
- All right.
- Okay, all right.
- Hi.
- Look at you.
You're glowing.
How's my baby? Huh?
How's my little guy? You okay in there?
Mm. (laughing)
- He's gonna be able to reply soon.
- Yeah.
It's going to be a little
while before he can
understand what we're saying.
Oh, mama.
Hmm?
Pretty soon.
Ee, so close.
- You can't be scared.
- Ah, I can be scared.
(both laughing)
- I read an article yesterday.
- Mm-hmm.
- Actually, what do you think?
Where do birth pains score on the list?
- What?
- The list.
- Yeah.
- The score number two.
Guess what number one is?
- What?
- The pain you feel when your
limbs are severed by a bomb.
Mm-hmm.
- Oh my God.
- And I have to go through this.
- Yeah.
- Ah.
- Oh.
- Oh, what?
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Just kicking. Just kicking.
- Just kicking? He's kicking?
- Yeah, it tickles.
- Oh, he's excited for Daddy.
Kick again, buddy! Kick for Daddy!
Come on!
- (laughs) Stop screaming.
Let me, let me get on the floor.
- Okay.
- He kicks more
when I'm laying down.
- All right,
let's get you down.
Oh, my baby.
(Claire sighs)
Here we go, easy.
Let me get the dress.
- Oh my God. I am so ready.
- Mm.
- Ready, ready, ready.
- Oh.
- Ah, severed limbs or not.
- I got ya.
- I'm ready.
- Okay, okay, easy, easy.
Watch your head on the desk.
Give me this. You good?
- Okay, yeah, yeah.
- How are those feet?
- Good, okay.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay.
Stay. I'll go get a pillow, okay?
(Claire sighs)
(soft piano music)
Oh, here we are.
There we go.
- All right.
- Okay.
- There we go.
- Oh, that's it, that's the spot.
- So what did you do?
- Oh, what did I do? What?
- What did you do?
- What?
- Oh, no, I didn't do, I was, ah, nothing.
- Please?
- No.
That's my little secret.
You're not gonna know.
- I'll tell you if you want.
- Okay.
- I got you a T-shirt
that says, Best Dad Ever."
- (chuckles) Jeez.
- That you can wear when
you go walking with the boy.
- That's very sweet of you,
but a little bit too soon.
- Oh yeah.
Yeah. You're right.
Especially since you said you
wouldn't change any diapers.
- No. No.
I just think that there's
a person for that,
that we can pay that's more
qualified to deal with that...
- You're joking, right?
- Absolutely not. I will, I will-
- But you said, we agreed.
- No, mm-mm.
- No.
- I signed nothing.
- The dad has to take part.
- Okay. Okay.
I will change one diaper per week.
- No!
What if I have to go somewhere
and you have to be alone with the kid?
He's just gonna sit in a stinky diaper?
- Okay. Well, first of
all, where are you going?
And second, why are you leaving us?
- Well, maybe I have to do my nails.
Actually, yeah. I'm gonna do my nails.
- Oh, the nail, okay. Okay.
Easy-peasy. That takes an hour tops.
I can let him sit.
- Hands and feet.
- Okay.
- Plus the traffic.
And I'm gonna need a coffee.
- Oh.
- That's like
three to four hours at least.
- Okay. Fine.
I will change him while
you're gone for that one time.
- No, no, no!
(Eric chuckles)
- Fine, I will change all the diapers.
- You don't get it, do you?
You're gonna fall in love with
your son when you see him.
- I know.
- And his poops are gonna
smell like roses to you.
- (laughs) You're exaggerating.
No poop smells like roses.
- Look, I'm voluntarily
agreeing to go through this pain
so you can change half of the diapers.
- Ah, fun fact. That Pain?
Orgasms. Yeah.
When you're going to birth
all of the endorphins,
they, they act up and, and
those, those are orgasms,
but the contractions are,
are covering them up.
So you don't realize it.
You just feel pain.
So I mean, that's why the baby and the mom
like have such a good
connection after birth.
- Hmm.
- Yeah, I'm jealous
'cause I'm just gonna
to be in the hallway,
pacing back and forth,
waiting for this to all be over,
banging my head against the wall.
- What? The hallway?
- Yeah. Where else would I be?
- You're gonna be in the room with me.
- What?
- Yeah.
I need you to hold my hand.
Hold my leg.
- Seriously?
- Help me push.
- Oh God.
(Claire laughing)
(suspenseful music)
- Oh shit.
(Claire laughing)
- Oh, don't, don't. That's not funny.
I don't wanna, no.
Oh, don't do that. Oh.
- Come on, I wanna have sex
with my husband after that.
- I want you to have sex
with your husband after that.
- All right. Help me up.
- Are we having sex right now?
(Claire scoffs)
- I can't stay in one
position for too long.
Come on.
- Okay, yeah. Let's do this.
Here.
- Oh.
- Mm.
- Oh God, okay.
- Gotcha, I gotcha.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Here we go, yeah?
- Yep.
- All right.
(Claire sighs)
- You know, you're gonna fight me
for the right to change the diaper.
- (laughs) Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
- Well that's a fight
I am willing to lose.
(Claire chuckles)
Here we go.
- Do I look like a goddess?
- You, you kidding me? Yes,
of course, you look like-
- I feel like a goddess.
- You are the goddess.
Goddess of God's.
- That's why I like this dress.
- This, this dress is amazing.
All right. Ready?
Twirl, loop, hold.
I got ya, I got ya.
And dip.
- Oh God, oh God!
- Oh, you're so light.
- Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
- You're the lightest pregnant,
pregnancy baby ever.
(Claire laughing)
Here we go.
(Claire sighs)
Huh?
- Oh, baby.
- And feet.
- Okay.
- The feet, the feet,
the beautiful feet.
- Yeah, thank you.
- There we go.
- Oh baby.
- What?
- I wanna eat now.
- Oh, of course.
What would you like to eat?
- Hmm, I want ice cream.
- That is a good choice.
- Mm-hmm.
- I second that.
Ice cream coming up.
Mm-hmm.
- Oh wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Yes, Madame?
- And a sausage.
- Sausage?
- Do we have any ice cream
that tastes like sausage?
- No, but I will scoop out some ice cream
and instead of chocolate
chips, I'll put in sausage.
Deal?
- No, keep it separate.
- I hear and I obey.
Coming up.
(lips kiss)
(birds chirping)
(suspenseful music)
(monitor buzzing)
(baby crying)
(monitor beeping)
Baby, what are you doing?
- Oh, thank God you're here.
Can you help me? I can't figure this out.
- Honey.
- Hmm?
- What are you doing?
- Seriously, they're writing this
for some kind of genius or something.
I mean, I literally don't
understand any of it.
Can you help me?
- I, uh...
- Here, let me see. Right
there is this piece.
But this has three holes
and that has five holes.
- Claire, we, we, we put the
crib away several months ago.
Why did you bring it back out?
- (chuckles) You're joking.
- Claire, why did you bring it back out?
- Our baby's gonna be home
soon and we have to be ready.
Look, if you don't wanna help me,
I'll just handle it myself.
Okay?
(paper tears)
What did you do?
- We lost our kid.
- What did you say?
- I can't, I can't do this.
- Talk to her, please?
I can't do this. You just, you-
- What did you say, you bastard?
Have you already buried our child?
- Stop it!
We buried him together.
- What kind of father are you?
- We buried him together.
It was a small ceremony, Claire.
It was the smallest coffin
I've ever seen in my life.
- No.
- Your mom was there
and she, she didn't stay to the end
because she, she couldn't take it.
- You're lying.
- Yeah, and then soon she...
Claire, you were sitting right
next to me the whole time
and you didn't make a sound.
- No, you're lying.
- Your boss showed up.
Your boss was there and
he gave you some time off
so you could collect your things
and get ahold of yourself.
- No.
- Yes, yes!
I thanked people for coming!
- No, no, no.
There were some complications.
- No, there weren't any complications.
- And, and, and, and the doctor
needed to keep him for a checkup.
- No.
- And the hospital's
gonna call any moment, any moment.
And they're gonna give him back to us
and they're gonna call
and we have to be ready.
Okay? We're such silly heads.
We left everything to the
last minute. (chuckles)
- Why doesn't he have a name?
(somber piano music)
Hmm?
What is his name, Claire?
How old is he?
- Eight months.
- Eight months ago
we lost our kid, Claire.
It was March 26th, our due date.
We already headed to the hospital
but you wanted to run upstairs
and take a shower and you did.
And you know what? You tripped.
You tripped on the belt of your rope
and you fell on your belly, Claire.
You fell hard.
(Claire whimpering)
We didn't know what to do.
And so we rushed you to the hospital
but the surgeons couldn't
find a heartbeat.
They gave you a shot and you had the baby.
And he was dead.
- No.
- Our baby's dead.
- Mm-mm.
- No.
Why my baby? Oh, God!
Oh my boy, my boy. (sobbing)
I can't, I can't...
I, I, I can't...
- I pay you to do this!
So you fucking do it!
- You need to remind her every day. Okay?
Every day.
- Okay.
(heart beating)
(Claire gasping)
(Claire sobbing)
(intense music)
(machinery beeping)
Oh God.
(Claire whimpering)
(Claire screaming)
Oh God. (sobbing)
(Claire whimpering)
(key pad beeping)
(suspenseful music)
(Claire gasps)
It was fun.
(footsteps shuffling)
- Hey, how are my girls?
- How is she?
- You tell me.
- It's gonna get better.
(Eric sighs)
- No, no.
(Claire gasping)
(water running)
- Oh, so you'll take us?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
What does Monica have to say about it?
Hey, do you wanna call Monica?
My girls.
That was my baby too!
(water splashing)
(Claire sobbing)
- Of course.
(baby cooing)
(water running)
I lost our baby.
(sobbing)
No, I killed our baby.
Because I didn't wanna
stink when giving birth!
(sobbing) This is unforgivable!
Does he have a right to forgive me?
(sobbing) Do you hear me?
I'll never forgive myself ever.
(sobbing)
(hand slams)
(water dripping)
Monica would never make
these kinds of mistakes.
(birds chirping)
Bitch!
This is how you wanted to help me?
This is how you wanted to
solve my problems with Eric?
Simply by stealing my husband?
(Claire laughing)
And here I'm thinking,
why is he pushing me
to go back to work so hard?
What did I do to you?
We were fine before you
came into this house
Where are you going?
(Monica and Eric groaning)
(suspenseful music)
(Monica and Eric continue groaning)
(heart beating)
- Oh my God.
Oh my God.
(both continue groaning)
(Claire screaming)
(knife stabs)
(alarm beeping)
(Claire yawning)
(birds chirping)
- It's time to wake up, baby? (chuckles)
(lips kissing)
I have an idea.
Let's spend the entire day together.
(phone vibrating)
Eric's phone?
He's gonna need a sick day.
Yeah. He's not feeling well.
Actually, he's gonna need several days.
Yeah, I don't want him
to spread his infection
around the office.
I'll let you know how he is.
Okay, bye.
(phone beeps)
This is gonna be the
vacation that we needed.
- [Mary Voicemail] Hello,
this is Mary Clarks.
Please leave me a message
- We'll even get to go
- after the tone
- to the park.
- and I'll call you back.
- The whole family.
Let me just talk to Mom, okay?
(voicemail beeps)
Mom,
we're picking you up in 30 minutes.
We're going to the park.
It's gonna be awesome.
Okay, be ready.
I love you. Bye.
(message dings)
(soft piano music)