Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
-Who was that?
-Andrea.
You okay?
Did you leave the sliding door open?
No.
It's a bad habit leaving doors open.
Once the termites get in,
you can never get rid of them.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Everybody just wants to be famous.
And for what?
So we can pretend we're famous too...
but it's fucking fake, the whole thing.
Photoshop.
Hell, I could be famous
with these window-shoppers.
Be happy with what you've got.
You too, so easily manipulated.
I'll never understand it.
So I have to talk to you about something.
About a month ago, I got a purple letter,
an anonymous letter
inviting me to meet
an admirer in a hotel room.
I thought it was stupid.
I thought it might have been...
I don't know what I thought.
But I went, and it was once.
And I realized that I've been unhappy.
I am unhappy.
I've given you ten fantastic years,
years that I'll never regret.
But I'm asking you now to let me leave.
I don't want half of your money.
I think $5,000 is all I'll need
to start again.
I honestly don't know what got
into me, but I'm glad that it did.
Stop that.
I can't justify staying with you anymore
just to be nice.
Because I saw it on your iPad
when it was syncing
and then you deleted it from your phone!
I don't know what you're talking about!
How the fuck could you do this to me?
It's really not what you think.
Like I'm not going to have someone
follow you when you're acting like this?
I stay in hotels all over the world!
Not in our fucking neighborhood!
Calm down.
I don't have time for this.
You're hysterical.
Who is sick of everything regular?
The public.