Downloaded from
YTS.MX
(dice thudding)
(electronic whirring)
- (groans) Yeah.
- We play and call it work!
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
(electronic whirring)
(groaning continues)
(intense thudding)
(leaves rustling)
- Ahoy!
Looky what we got here.
Headripper, cut his lights.
(leaves crunching)
(Drustan exhales loudly)
(leaves continue crunching)
(dramatic instrumental music)
Oi!
Oh, I've seen this face before.
What do you think he's
thinking in his little brain?
- An orc with a brain bigger than a man's?
Quite the conundrum.
(Mograh yells)
(blow thudding)
- If I wanted to hear your talk,
I'd rip it out your face,
and smack against me sword!
Ain't that right, Headripper?
(Headripper growls)
Do you know why he's called Headripper?
You see,
when people talk,
and he don't understand them gits,
he thinks rippin' their heads off
makes 'em easier to understand.
He ain't the sharpest tool.
Ain't that right, Headripper?
(Headripper growls)
- You talk lot for an orc.
(gasps) I suppose you have a brain?
(Mograh groans)
Is that what I
should call you then?
Brain, does it work?
(Drustan gasps)
- Clearly one as civilized as yourself
must have heard of Mograh the Merciless?
- Him,
(Headripper growls)
I've heard of.
You, I'm afraid not.
(Mograh yells)
(leaves rustling)
- Oi, do you fight in a den?
(armor clatters)
Stupid pea brain!
Must I do everything me self then?
(blow thuds)
(Headripper groans)
(intense dramatic music)
Lazy moppet!
You stay here and watch this dog.
(leaves crunching)
(blow thuds)
(Drustan groans painfully)
(leaves continue crunching)
(bag clatters)
(blow thuds)
(Headripper growls)
Yes, Master, find the Bloodstone I will.
Search every village in
the Grimmock Mountain.
Oi, I'm no moppet.
(leaves crunching)
(Headripper growls)
(blow thuds)
(intense dramatic music)
(stuffed animal rustles)
(objects clattering)
(book thuds)
(pendant clanks)
(bag rustles)
(intense dramatic music)
(Mograh sighs)
(intense dramatic music continues)
Ranger.
(leaves rustling)
- [Drustan] 'Twas in
this moment, I realized,
the search for my daughter
may have come to an end.
Was all my waiting and tracking in vain?
I'd been bested by this vile creature.
Mograh may have been an orc,
but an exceptionally
clever orc he truly was.
Perhaps, by design?
A by-product of dark wizardry indeed.
If 'twas my end,
I knew in my heart,
in the afterlife, I
could tell my sweet Reina
I tried to avenge her.
(dark ominous music)
(suspenseful dramatic music)
(whimsical instrumental music)
(arrow shuffling)
(bow creaks)
(whimsical instrumental music continues)
(arrow whooshing)
(blade tapping)
(intense whooshing)
(blade continues tapping)
(whimsical instrumental music continues)
(intense whooshing)
(blade continues tapping)
(intense dramatic tones)
- Daddy, don't leave!
- Reina, love, you know daddy must do
as the king orders, right?
And besides, who else will be the eyes
and ears of Lieutenant Brander Noke?
- He's hairy, though.
- Yes, indeed, he is.
Quite a hairy man, isn't he?
And you know who else will be there?
Flynt Tanner.
He'll have daddy's back.
- Big man.
- Indeed, he is.
And let's not forget Corser, daddy's mate.
I served with him since basic.
- I'll miss you, Daddy.
(dramatic instrumental music)
(whimsical tones)
(blade tapping)
(intense whooshing)
(blade continues tapping)
(intense dramatic music)
(footsteps pattering)
(intense dramatic music continues)
(somber dramatic music)
(leaves rustling)
- Oi, Headripper.
Feelin' like your king of the castle then?
Hackin' and sackin' defenseless pasties.
Oi!
(armor thuds)
(Headripper growls)
(armor clangs)
Feelin' sensitive, are we?
(Headripper growls)
That sack of skulls ain't doin' it for ya?
Oh, I ain't tryin' to steal your loot.
Or maybe I is.
(bag clatters)
Who was it who found them
pasties in the village?
Me!
Who was it that got himself
ambushed by rangers?
Oh, that's right!
You!
What's that, Master?
I'm the smartest orc you've ever seen?
Why, you're too kind, Master.
What's that?
You've got a message for Headripper?
Pea brain!
(Headripper growls)
Forget you're worthless trophy skulls,
and find the Bloodstone!
Oh, and do whatever
Mograh the Merciless says,
'cause he's smarter than you.
(sighs loudly) Time to tell
the Master we've got no slaves,
no trophies,
(skull thuds)
and no Bloodstone.
He will skewer us and feed
us to the fire breather.
(Headripper growls loudly)
(dramatic instrumental music)
- [Drustan] Everything reminds me of her,
the Jays singing,
tree branches dancing in the wind.
Orc raiding parties have
scoured my home village
in the Grimmock Mountains.
Alone on the outskirts of the Short Hills,
I track the wretched green skins
responsible for killing my family.
My daughter's body never recovered.
Only a tear from her dress.
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
(pencil scratching)
My brother rangers
inform me these orcs are slavers.
I suspect Reina to be with them.
They had better pray not a
single scratch be on her!
(scroll rustles)
I hold a hawk-delivered-letter
from Lieutenant Wolf.
I fear his orders will be to
abandon my daughter's search
and fall back in the ranks.
Time is my greatest enemy now.
I hope orders align with my will.
- [Lieutenant Noke] Drustan,
I hope this letter reaches you
by the time you return to your village.
Our brothers in the north have
trapped the orcs responsible
for the destruction of your home.
You'll find them in the Short Hills.
Through their bravery and inquisition,
they discovered the true
motive behind their pillaging.
One, simply known as the Master,
has ordered them to find the Bloodstone.
At this point, little else is known.
For the rest of our brothers,
the time to seek out
and extinguish the orcs
who raided your village
has come to a halt.
We've just received
orders from Count Thriese
to eliminate trolls in
the The Bickerburg Hills
I understand if choose to stay behind
and pursue the orcs
who slewed your family.
We can fend off the trolls without you.
Revenge may seem a satisfying conquest.
Just remember, killing the orcs
won't replace the feelings
of loss that pain your soul,
but will serve as a good
distraction in the interim.
Be wary of the one they call Mograh.
He and his companion take
orders directly from the Master,
not infamous for enslaving
and toying with prisoners.
May your loved ones reach
the heavens in peace.
Lieutenant Brander Noke.
(ominous dramatic music)
(apple thuds)
(leaves crunching)
(intense dramatic music)
(bear rustles)
(leaves crunching)
(taps bag)
(footsteps pattering)
(suspenseful dramatic music)
- [Drustan] A dispute amongst them.
(armor clangs)
(feet clomping)
There's only two sets of tracks,
not a third.
Perhaps, the large one
decided to carry Reina.
(leaves rustling)
(eerie ominous music)
No.
(intense whooshing)
(Drustan groans angrily)
No!
(footsteps pattering)
(intense dramatic music)
Die creature!
(bow creaking)
(Headripper groans)
(blade clanks)
Your soul is deep.
(bow creaks)
(arrow whooshing)
By order of the King,
(Mograh thuds)
you will die for your sins!
(arrow whooshing)
(arrow clanks)
(leaves rustling)
(intense dramatic music continues)
(Drustan screams)
(armor clanks)
- Oh, fresh meat.
(Headripper growls)
Oh, invitin' him for
afternoon tea sounds better?
(Headripper growls)
Of course, we kill him!
You stupid git.
(Headripper growls)
But first, we slave him.
(Headripper growls loudly)
It's settled then.
(Headripper growls)
(ominous dramatic music)
(leaves crunching)
(ominous dramatic music continues)
- [Drustan] Two arrows
'tis all it would take.
(leaves crunching)
(ominous dramatic music continues)
- I think that pasties
is in the woods with us.
You heard him squeal a klick back.
- [Drustan] Those heinous
creatures deserve to die.
(Headripper growls)
- I say we find him, slave him,
and bring him back to the boss man.
(Headripper growls)
- [Drustan] I could end it now.
I could avenge Reina.
- Bring him back to the boss' lair
after we squeeze him for the Bloodstone.
- [Drustan] But knowing
where the Master is
could be paramount.
(Headripper growls)
- Oh, you've got a better plan, then?
- Decide!
(arrow screeches)
- I don't think he's got it, stupid!
But he might know where it is!
- [Drustan] Avenge your daughter,
or possibly save many lives?
(Headripper growls)
- Oh, shut it, you!
(exhales loudly)
(pants heavily)
(pendant clanks)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(leaves crunching)
(arrows clatter)
(ominous dramatic music)
- [Drustan] Please don't hurt me.
- Ahoy!
Looky what we got here.
(bow clatters)
Headripper, cut his lights.
(leaves crunching)
(dark ominous music)
(blow thuds)
(Drustan groans)
Oi, I've seen this face before.
(Mograh yells)
(Drustan thuds)
All right,
(armor clatters)
you find it then.
Stupid pea brain!
Must I do everything me self then?
(armor clatters)
(Headripper grunts)
Lazy moppet.
You stay here and watch this dog.
(leaves crunching)
(blow thuds)
(Drustan groans painfully)
(body thuds)
(bag clatters)
(leaves crunching)
(blow thuds)
(Headripper growls)
(intense dramatic music)
(leaves crunching)
(Headripper growls)
(blow thuds)
- (groans loudly) I'd be angry as well
if I were treated like you.
But surely, you must realize
you're more powerful than
Mograh the Messiness?
(Headripper growls)
And I know
you're smarter than he.
Your reputation precedes your greatness.
(bag clatters)
(pendant clanks)
(leaves rustling)
(Mograh sighs loudly)
(leaves crunching)
- Ranger.
No.
- Mograh is only merciless
because of you, Headripper.
- Oh, think you're pretty
clever then, Ranger?
Headripper, this one's an orc hunter.
Hold him still, so I cam pluck
him right between the eyes
with his own arrow.
(arrow scratching)
Well, what you waitin' for?
Move!
You lazy moppet!
(Headripper growls loudly)
(bow thuds)
(gasping) Headripper, I'm sorry.
Don't.
(Mograh speaks indistinctly)
(leaves rustling)
(arrow clatters)
(Mograh gasps)
(body thuds)
(arrow scratching)
(Headripper grunts)
Stop what?
Calling you stupid?
But you are stupid, you mindless bog!
(Headripper growls)
(arrow scratching)
Oi, I'm not your enemy.
(Headripper growls)
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I know where we can
get more trophy skulls,
more than you can count!
Well, maybe more than that.
(Headripper growls loudly)
Lets keep this pasties
for ourselves, yeah?
Forget about the Master.
(leaves rustling)
Oh, come on, boy!
Don't you remember all
the good kills we had?
(bow creaking)
Oi, the pasties free!
- For my daughter!
(armor clangs)
(Headripper growls)
(Drustan grunts)
(footsteps pattering)
(Drustan yells)
(feet shuffling)
- Watch it.
Watch it now.
(Drustan grunts)
(armor clangs)
(armor thuds)
You're dead now pastie.
(bow whooshing)
(leaves crunching)
(feet shuffling)
- You scum!
Your lower than the dirt,
killing an innocent child!
(leaves rustling)
(Headripper grunts)
- She was yar.
(Headripper growls)
(leaves rustling)
(armor thuds)
(blows thudding)
Pretty little thing she was.
(leaves rustling)
(Drustan grunts)
The thing about little girls is,
(Drustan groans)
(armor thuds)
they make a perfect supper
(leaves rustling)
(Drustan wincing painfully)
right before a good killin'.
(leaves rustling)
(Drustan grunts)
(armor thuds)
(Headripper groans)
(blow thuds)
(leaves rustling)
(Headripper groans)
(armor thuds)
(Drustan yells)
(blow thuds)
(Headripper grunts)
(leaves rustling)
(blade clanks)
(Headripper groans)
(intense dramatic music)
(Drustan exhales loudly)
Go!
(Headripper growls)
(Drustan grunts)
(air whooshing)
(blade whooshing)
- Come on.
(Drustan grunts)
(Headripper growls)
(blade clanks)
(Headripper continues growling)
- Slice his limbs off!
(blade whooshing)
(blade continues whooshing)
(feet shuffling)
Surrender, and we'll
only chop you into bits.
- You creatures will
have your just reward!
- Enough!
(Headripper growls)
(blade thuds)
(blade clanks)
(Mograh groans)
(Headripper growls)
(blow thuds)
(Dristan groans)
(Headripper growls)
(Dristan continues groaning)
(head thuds)
(continues groaning)
(intense dramatic tones)
(Drustan grunts and groans)
(gagging loudly)
Oi, Headripper,
should be tell this git
his little, pastie girl is still alive?
(intense dramatic tones)
(breathes heavily)
Oh, that's right,
we didn't gut her like you think.
We sold her to them Outlanders.
(chuckles) Your vengeance is in vain.
(Drustan groans angrily)
(Headripper thuds)
(Drustan groans)
(blow thuds)
(sword unsheathes)
(Drustan yells)
(blade clangs)
(upbeat triumphant music)
(Drustan breathes heavily)
(blade clanks)
(Mograh thuds)
You will never find her.
The Master will use her
for his dark purpose.
She will be lost forever.
You will-
(blade clangs)
(Mograh gasps)
(leaves crunching)
(blade clanks)
(Drustan exhales loudly)
- I will find her, creature.
And when I do, she will be as pure
and unscathed as the day she was born.
Reina, wherever you are,
daddy's coming for you.
Don't lose hope, child.
(insects chirping)
(eerie ominous music)
(snow pattering)
(leaves crunching)
(bow clatters)
(arrows clattering)
(cloak rustles)
(bag thuds)
(belt rattles)
(coat rustles)
(coat thuds)
(cloak rustles)
(whimsical instrumental music)
(intense dramatic music)
(paper softly crinkles)
(intense dramatic music continues)
(cloak rustles)
(bag gently rustles)
(intense dramatic music continues)
(Drustan groans)
(bag gently rustles)
(coin purse clangs)
(intense dramatic music continues)
(bag gently rustles)
(suspenseful dramatic music)
(bag rustles)
(branch crunching)
(dagger clanks)
(Traveler yells)
You dare steal from a Ranger!
- I wasn't stealing!
- I'm a protector of the Borderlands.
I save vagrants like you.
- I just want food.
- So you can live to steal another day?
- No Ranger, I am hungry, nothing more.
- You from these parts?
- Mostly.
- Then point me to the Outlanders.
- Head west from here.
The forest is crawling with them.
- And their camp?
- You'll never find them.
No one has.
- I'm not your average tracker, Vagrant.
(leaves crunching)
- I'm not a vagrant.
(bag rustles)
More of a wandering traveler.
(Traveler grunts)
(apple thuds)
(arrows clatter)
(leaves crunching)
Much gratitude, Ranger.
What will you do when you find them?
(coat thuds)
- Take it, it's yours.
(cloak rustles)
(leaves crunching)
- This man has a death wish.
(eerie suspenseful tones)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(water lapping)
- My brother, why such a betrayal?
You were unmatched as our leader.
Could you not let the spoils of war
satisfy your need for retribution?
But instead, you became weak.
You chose a natural born enemy
as your companion in life.
Why, Brother?
- You got greedy, Henrik.
We are protectors of the realm,
not thieves, nor bandits.
You (spits) shame us.
- [Henrik] And who shall provide for us,
if not ourselves?
The King's hand has never
cared for us, nor executed law.
We are the law, Bjorn!
We dictate how we survive!
- And the orcs,
trading with green skins?
Tell me, Brother,
how is it just to have
captives mend your clothes
and cook your meat?
(Henrik groans)
(blow thuds)
- This could have been yours, Brother.
We need you.
Lead us to the spoils and
riches you once promised.
(suspenseful dramatic music)
- You're right, Henrik.
I did promise you riches.
(Bjorn pants heavily)
But that was before
you were tainted by
the forces of darkness!
(headbutt thuds)
(Henrik groans painfully)
(Bjorn grunts)
(blow thuds)
(feet shuffling)
(Outlander grunts)
(blow thuds)
(hay rustles)
(suspenseful dramatic music continues)
(arrows rattling)
(footsteps pattering)
(suspenseful dramatic music continues)
(arrows rattling)
(footsteps pattering)
(hands thud)
- What?
(armor clanks)
(muffled groaning)
(body thuds)
(Drustan grunts)
(bow thuds)
(Outlander groaning)
(feet shuffling)
(swords unsheathing)
(sword whooshing)
(metal clangs)
(suspenseful dramatic music)
(leaves crunching)
(pats armor)
(suspenseful dramatic music continues)
(sword clanks)
(footsteps pattering)
(Drustan groans)
(blow thuds)
(Outlander yells out painfully)
(leaves crunching)
(stick thuds)
(Drustan groans)
(Outlander grunts angrily)
- Come on!
- No!
(foot thuds)
(Outlander groans)
(leaves rustling)
(Outlander yells)
(chains rattling)
(Outlander grunts)
(body thuds)
(dagger unsheathing)
(air whooshing)
(sword clanking)
(body thuds)
(leaves rustling)
(triumphant instrumental music)
- I swear to you,
I will let you live,
just tell me,
(triumphant instrumental music continues)
(leaves gently rustling)
where's my daughter?
- [Outlander] I'll die before I tell you!
(Drustan grunts)
(Outlander groans)
(triumphant instrumental music continues)
(sword clanks)
(whimsical tones)
- [Drustan] The time is running out.
I've been searching for Reina
out here in the Borderlands far too long.
I've lost track of the weeks.
I feel I'm close,
but all progress seems to
be halted by Outlanders,
who would rather meet death
than give up their base of operations.
It's as if they're protected
by a dark shroud of evil.
Mograh the Merciless, the
vial, wretched orc scum,
sold her to the Outlanders
right before I killed him.
She is but a child.
A sweet innocent.
A gift from the heavens
from a supreme creator.
And I still have no more clues
regarding this precious Bloodstone.
I'd sacrifice my beating heart for it
if it meant the life of my sweet Reina.
I am a powerless nothing.
(pencil scratching)
(dark ominous music)
(Caraphinneth chants
in a mystical language)
(grass rustling)
(eerie ominous tones)
(Caraphinneth continues
chanting in a mystical language)
(dark ominous music swells)
(leaves crunching)
(bones cracking)
(Mograh groans)
- [Mograh] (sighs) Oh, I
see the leaves are back.
(spits loudly)
'Bout time you showed up.
- Mograh, we have Bloodstone to find.
- You mean to tell me,
after all this time,
we still haven't found
this cursed Bloodstone?
My ever reliable elven
necromancer, Caraphinneth,
I though you were resourceful?
- Nei, I do as the Master orders.
- (sighs) He's a moppet.
(whimsical tones)
(ominous dramatic music)
(footsteps pattering)
(bow creaking)
- I hear you creature.
Present yourself.
Don't toy with me, creature.
I can pick up your scent a mile away.
State your purpose in following me,
and mind your words,
or they may just be your last.
- I am Sharia Gethyra.
I am not your enemy.
I've been following your
death trail of Outlanders
for the last 13-
- 13 1/2 miles.
Yes, I know.
Why?
- I come to seek out the
Watcher of the Woods.
- I'm afraid you have the wrong man.
- There is about one
ranger in these parts,
and that ranger is you.
You can track these Outlanders,
but you cannot defeat them alone.
I know you're searching
for someone you've lost.
You're a soldier,
trained is his tactical advantage.
I'm offering aid.
Be wise and take it, human.
- Outlanders taking captives
is common knowledge in these parts.
Clearly, I'm in search of someone.
And Watcher of the Woods?
One look at my crest
tells you I'm a ranger.
Your description of me as a soldier
is as generic as driftwood
floating down the Cassian River.
- No, Ranger, I do know you.
You're a protector of the realm.
- As are all rangers.
Now, be on your way, creature!
Do not follow me!
- Think this through.
They have her.
They have your daughter.
(ominous dramatic music)
- [Drustan] I beg your pardon?
- You've been tracking these
Outlanders for weeks now.
I know exactly where they are.
Join me, and together we can defeat them.
- How dare you use my daughter
in attempts to sway my purpose!
I don't know you from a stone in my shoe.
I do not wish to sleep with
one eye and one ear open!
Stop your pursuit!
You'd only slow me down.
I do not care for your aid!
Do not follow me, creature!
- Stop calling me creature!
You will learn to appreciate
my generosity, human!
(ominous dramatic music)
(grass rustling)
(Sharia exhales loudly)
(rock rustles)
- Have it your way, She-elf.
(dramatic instrumental music)
(bow whooshing)
(Sharia groans)
(blows thudding)
(blows continue thudding)
(Drustan grunting)
(Drustan groans)
(blows thudding)
(Sharia grunts)
(blows continue thudding)
(Drustan grunting)
(Sharia yells)
(arrows clattering)
(blows thudding)
(Drustan grunts)
(air whooshing)
(arrows clattering)
(blows thudding)
(Drustan grunts)
(Sharia thuds)
(sighs loudly)
(air whooshing)
(arrows clattering)
(Drustan grunts)
(blows thudding)
(dramatic instrumental music)
- Remove your head from the
sand, Ranger, and join me.
- I've misjudged you, Elf.
Your skills are, indeed, expert,
but my resolve to find my
daughter alone is firm.
Seek the Watcher of the Woods no longer.
You will only find solitude in your quest.
(cloak rustling)
(footsteps pattering)
(cloak rustles)
(air whooshing)
(pensive instrumental music)
(water gently lapping)
(footsteps pattering)
(pensive instrumental music continues)
- [Crickitus] We've
got the child, She-elf.
It's the Outlander way!
(dramatic instrumental music)
(Crickitus groans)
(gear clattering)
(footsteps pattering)
(Crickitus groans)
(Sharia grunts)
(hand thuds)
- Wait!
He can tell us more!
- Kindly remove your hand, Ranger!
(Crickitus groans)
(leaves crunching)
(Crickitus grunts)
(sword clangs)
(sword unsheathing)
(Sharia yells)
(Crickitus continues groaning)
(elbow thuds)
(feet shuffling)
(Sharia grunts)
(Drustan groans)
(sword clanks)
(Crickitus yells)
(Drustan thuds)
(footsteps pattering)
- Stop!
(Sharia groans)
(Crickitus yells)
(ax whooshing)
(foot thuds)
Get him!
(Sharia groans)
No!
(blade clanking)
(skin squelching)
(blade clanks)
(Crickitus groans)
Where is my daughter?
May your final act be noble
from one warrior to another.
Please tell me where she is.
- The She-elf already knows.
(head thuds)
(cloak rustles)
(Drustan sighs)
(sword sheathes)
(cloak rustles)
- All right, Sharia Gethyra.
Take me to her then.
- [Sharia] Why the sudden
change of heart, Ranger?
- This man's blood has
verified your words,
and I always trust blood over woods.
Lead the way.
(leaves crunching)
(dark ominous music)
(Caraphinneth chants
in a mystical language)
- Mograh, give your blade.
(dagger unsheathes)
- If I had a gold coin
for every time you stopped
to chant your grog.
- It is not grog, Mograh.
I prepare hideous poison
that stay in body,
even after death.
- [Mograh] And all this
time I thought I was evil.
- [Caraphinneth] Once
poison enters bloodstream,
Vital organs begin to consume each other.
Bones consume flesh,
sinews consume bone,
until there is nothing left
but blackness underneath the skin.
- Oi, give it here, Elf!
Or I'll cut you like a porker!
(Caraphinneth chants
in a mystical language)
- This poison is made from
the blood of 13 black orcs.
The essence of evil contained therein
is more powerful than the
resurrected life force
that flows through your veins.
Don't toy with it, Mograh.
I'm trying to protect you from awful fate.
- Caraphinneth, I'm sorry.
(Mograh gasping)
(breathes heavily)
You wicked witch!
(dark ominous music swells)
- [Drustan] Had I lost my way,
never did I dream not considered
traveling with a She-elf.
To associate with one
is to bring unwelcome
judgment from the kingdom.
Seemed we were desperate allies.
At this point, I held on
to any glimmer of hope
I would find Reina,
even if it meant remaining
in the company of this woodland creature.
Her proud superiority
over humans was unnerving.
As a child, I thought that
wood elves to be a theory,
and without guile.
Years of rangering in the Borderlands
have taught me otherwise.
They're hundreds of years old.
Proud beings, they are,
and rightfully so.
I suppose, after centuries
of living and fighting,
I'd be a proud creature as well.
I would travel with the
She-elf as long as needed,
then we would go our separate ways.
(footsteps pattering)
- Drop your gear, Ranger.
We'll rest here and gather our strength.
- Well, you certainly travel light.
- [Sharia] Well, I don't
require as much as you do
to sustain myself.
(arrows clatter)
- You wood elves have always
been peculiar creatures.
- Well, you humans have always been quick
to wage war on that which
you do not understand.
Do you have a name, Ranger,
or shall I just call you Ranger
for the rest of our journey?
- Why is it of concern?
If you must know, I am Drustan Lorne.
- Quite the name for a
farmer turned ranger.
- You have it wrong, She-elf.
I was not a farmer,
nor was I anything really.
Just lost in the dark shroud
that consumes most things in this world.
- [Sharia] So where
does your journey begin?
(mellow instrumental music)
- [Drustan] Life wasn't always as dark
and grim as I've come to know it.
Before the orc raiding wars
there was peace in the Grimmock Mountains.
The King's vanguard, his
elite warriors, the rangers,
stood immovable and
steadfast in their duty
to protect the Borderlands.
My Indian mother died
by the hand festering
creatures of darkness.
Hence my ever-growing hatred towards them.
My father, the trapper,
often spoke of his ancient ancestors
who were protectors of the realm.
They were legendary in
the art of the hunt.
The old man would go on and on.
Before one day,
a thieving bandit stabbed
him for 13 pieces of silver.
And so I became a child of the village.
In this place was a certain
unspeakable serenity
that permeated the very essence of life.
I knew everyone,
and in turn, everyone knew me.
We all had a similar story to tell.
I considered these fine people my family.
I grew quite fond of them.
We took care of one another.
(indistinct chattering)
- Great times
with a wonderful-
(child groans)
(fruit thuds)
(villager groans)
If that's not bad enough for you,
I'm gonna get you!
(child yells)
(villager groans)
- [Drustan] Deep down in my heart,
I always knew one day
the peaceful life I enjoyed
would be taken away.
Call it a stirring in my dreams.
The voice of destiny was calling to me,
echoing through the
ages, transcending time,
compelling me to heed her call.
Alas, it was time to meet my future.
A village steeped in tradition
held true to a rite of passage,
When one came to the age of independence,
one would see the Lady of the Woods.
And so I gathered every
needful thing for my journey.
I knew not what it truly
meant to survive in the woods.
I was a young man
with a naive notion that
all was well in the world.
Nevertheless, my eyes would soon be opened
to the raw reality that plagued mankind.
(mellow instrumental music continues)
(gentle orchestral music)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(dark ominous music)
(leaves rustling)
(dark ominous music continues)
- Give your hand.
- [Drustan] What do you see?
- No, no (shushing).
You no talk.
You listen now.
I see two ways for you.
The first path is quiet, peaceful.
You live long time,
and you alone on this path.
(bowl clanking)
(dark ominous music swells)
(sighs loudly) The second path
is filled with many great
and terrible things.
Lots of death and darkness.
But through that death, come life.
You have much pain and sorrow.
You lose your wife to the
creatures of darkness,
but you love your daughter
more than the world itself.
Soon, you seek out living ancestor
west out here in the mountain.
He is great warrior.
He train you his ways.
You become wise and strong!
You can face anything because of him.
(intense whooshing)
(breathes shakily) I see.
I am in the presence of greatness!
You, Ranger!
You do many great things for many people.
So Drustan, creature of light,
which path you choose?
(dramatic instrumental music)
(apple crunching)
(ominous dramatic music)
(apple thuds)
(ominous dramatic music continues)
(blows loudly)
(apple crunching)
- You and your poison.
Shh, listen.
There's a scared little hare
over there in them bushes.
Do us a favor,
and fetch us some supper.
(ominous dramatic music)
(liquid gurgling)
(sword clanks)
(ominous dramatic music swells)
You pathetic worm.
If not for me, you'd die out here.
(apple crunching)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(footsteps pattering)
(bushes rustling)
(footsteps continue pattering)
- Pardon me, sir.
Can you spare a coin for an old beggar?
- Sorry, old man, I haven't any to spare.
Be on your way now.
- Please, young command,
I only need one coin.
- I really do wish I could help,
but how do I know you won't just drink it
all away with grog?
- Please, sir, I beg of you,
won't you help an old man?
- I'm starting to get frustrated, beggar.
Be on your way now!
I'm searching for my ancestor.
- Oh, my dear boy,
the only one who lives in
these woods is the Ancient One
just over that hill.
- Just over that hill?
- Yes.
- Thanks, old man.
(footsteps departing)
(footsteps pattering)
(ominous dramatic music)
(knocking at door)
Hello, sir.
I am Drustan Lorne.
I'm your kin.
I've come to seek wisdom and guidance.
I've traveled long and far to meet you.
Please come out.
(knocking on door)
Are you there, sir?
(ominous dramatic music swells)
What now, old man?
I told you I didn't
have any coins for you.
(dramatic instrumental music)
(door clatters open)
(door thuds shut)
I had no idea, sir.
Please forgive my rudeness.
I have coin!
I can pay you whatever you want!
I've come all this way, Ancient One.
This is my chosen path.
You must train me!
For without your guidance,
I have no purpose!
I beg of you.
Please, sir, forgive
this misunderstanding.
(door clatters open)
- Apologies, young man,
but I have no time to spare.
I simply cannot train you.
- But I'm your kin!
You're my living ancestor.
- But how do I know you
won't just waste my time
and drink my grog?
- I've come to work hard
and be trained by you.
The Lady of the Woods
said it 'twas my destiny.
- (groans) I'm starting to get
frustrated with you, young command.
Be on your way now.
(door thuds shut)
(insects chirping)
You're still here?
(water sloshing)
- [Drustan] No, please!
Sir!
(door thuds shut)
Do you not care I will freeze out here?
(fire crackling)
(Ancient One humming)
(Drustan exhales loudly)
(Ancient One moans)
(fire crackling)
(Ancient One hums)
(Drustan sighs)
(Ancient One continues humming)
- I wouldn't.
(liquid sloshing)
(spits loudly)
(Drustan gags)
(fire crackling)
(insects chirping)
(gentle instrumental music)
(Drustan gasps)
(groans loudly)
(continues groaning)
(exhales loudly)
(gentle instrumental music continues)
(animals howl in the distance)
(mystical tones)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
- So what do you think, grog or coin?
- That's coin.
- Agreeing with.
What do you wager, grog or coin?
- Maybe grog.
- Hmm.
And what do you think?
Grog or coin?
You think about it then.
(blow thuds)
(outlander grunts)
(outlander continues grunting)
(Drustan groans)
(blade clanks)
(blow thuds)
(Drustan groans painfully)
(Drustan coughs)
- Why not just knock him out,
then take the loot?
(continues coughing)
- Where's the fun in that?
(blow thuds)
(Drustan groans)
You'll get your turn.
(blow thuds)
(Drustan groans)
Get in there!
(feet shuffling)
(blow thuds)
(blows continue thudding)
(both groaning)
(fist thuds)
That's the spirit!
(fist continues thudding)
(Boss Bandit laughs)
- Get off.
(Drustan grunts)
(blow thuds)
(blows continue thudding)
(spits loudly)
(Drustan grunts)
(sword clanks)
(blow thuds)
(blows continue thudding)
(door clatters open)
(triumphant instrumental music)
(blows thudding)
(footsteps departing)
(triumphant instrumental music continues)
- I'll get you for this one, man.
Mark my words!
(head thuds)
(gentle instrumental music)
- [Ancient One] Easy.
Relax.
- Are they dead then?
- No more than you.
- How can such disregard
for human life exist?
- Evil has its place in the world.
Where there is light there
must also be darkness.
One cannot exist without the other.
- Are they born of darkness then?
- I believe we are all born with a choice.
We choose our path,
and then fate decides if we
are to be a force for light
or a force for darkness.
- Does this mean you'll train me then?
- What do you think I've
been doing this past week?
- I don't understand.
- When I refused your request to train,
you relentlessly persisted.
You passed the test.
A warrior never gives
up, never surrenders,
and never gives in to the forces
he has the power to overcome.
- That was a test?
- [Ancient One] Aye.
- I starved for a week,
rest on disgusting water,
froze in the night,
was tormented by wolves,
and nearly beaten to death
by a thieving bandit,
and all that was a test?
- Aye.
The first of many.
- You're a sick old man!
- [Ancient One] And what have you learned?
- That I'm related to a sadist!
- You'll thank me later.
(birds chirping)
(arrow clattering)
(bow whooshing)
(arrow thuds)
- What next, old man?
- Don't let a lucky shot
be mistaken for skill.
- It 'twas not luck.
That was my weapon.
It speaks to me.
- Maybe so, but skills
still needs to be acquired.
Now, shoot it again.
(Drustan exhales loudly)
(arrow clatters)
(arrow whooshing)
(Drustan groans loudly)
One day, you shall call upon the elements
to guide you in your quest,
but until that day,
you have much to learn.
(slaps chest)
Again!
(arrow clatters)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(bow whooshing)
(arrow thuds)
(Drustan yells angrily)
Anger.
Yes!
Channel that energy!
Bend your will to it!
Again!
(arrow clatters)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
(bow creaking)
That's it.
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
Listen to the air.
It's speaking to you.
Do you hear it?
What is it saying?
Wait for it.
(bow whooshing)
(arrow thuds)
Excellent.
(Ancient One coughs)
- [Drustan] As much as
I hated to admit it,
the Ancient One cracked my hubris.
I knew he was right.
Deep down it was what I wanted,
to be trained by the ancient warrior,
to shake off the shackles of weakness.
(pencil scratching)
(mellow instrumental music)
(leaves crunching)
(bag rustling)
(necklace shuffles)
(bag clatters)
- If you are to be a force for light,
you must yield to it.
(sticks clacking)
Submit to it!
(hand slaps)
Respect it!
(sticks clacking)
(Drustan groans)
Honor its might.
(sticks clacking)
Your determination will punish you.
It will throw you in ways
you never thought possible.
Listen to the air.
The air speaks.
You must train your ears to hear it.
- And so I trained.
Until I started to hear with my ears,
I was convinced I had no problems hearing.
It was not that kind of
hearing I was lacking.
I was proud, and arrogant,
and I let it rule my being.
I would learn to be rid of such weakness
and open my heart to true strength.
It wasn't until much later I would learn
I needed to listen to the earth.
For years to come,
the Ancient One would teach me,
that if I listened to the earth,
she would never betray me.
Eventually, my body learned
to flow with the elements.
I learned how to direct,
then redirect, energy into my opponent.
In time, after weapons were mastered
and training was completed,
one spoke to me as the
Ancient One had promised.
This weapon would become
an extension of my essence.
I came to truly rely on its being.
We hunted.
We tracked everything that moved.
Soon, I came to know every
creature that walked this world.
Everything leaves an imprint in its wake.
I learned how to recognize it.
I unlocked the power of my senses.
They taught me where I needed to be.
I was ready to become one with
the elements of the warrior.
My years of hard work had paid off.
But little did I know,
my training was not yet over.
Ancient Father,
I am ready to be a protector of the realm.
It's been 4,000 days since
I arrived at your doorstep.
I've mastered everything you've taught me.
Please release me into the world,
and to give me your blessing
to fight against the forces of darkness.
- Very well, my son.
You are ready for your final test.
(dramatic instrumental music)
(arrow clatters)
(footsteps crunching)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
Become a Watcher of the
Woods of the Ancient Order.
One can have the power to overcome you
through sheer force of strength.
You must learn to hear it coming.
(bow creaks)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
(arrow whooshing)
(pants heavily)
You are now ready, my son.
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
(Ancient One coughs)
(bucket clangs)
(hand thuds)
(bucket clattering)
(pensive instrumental music)
(footsteps pattering)
(pensive instrumental music continues)
(Ancient One coughs)
(intense dramatic music)
- So Greenwood, what's your wager?
Grog or coin?
- Coin.
- Kreiger would have bet grog.
He's in the forest collectin' poison.
Kind of a shame.
He would have loved to see this.
- You boys best be moving along now.
- We've only come for
your possessions, old man.
It's not like we're gonna toy with ya,
and then cut your lights just for sport.
- I'm warning you thieves!
- That's rather rude.
Isn't it, boys?
(Ancient One sighs)
- Boss, let's just take his loot and go.
- Greenwood, have you not learned by now
I have no interest in this man's loot?
(footsteps pattering)
I want you
(sword unsheathes)
to kill the Ancient One.
(intense dramatic music continues)
- Boss, I ain't sure about this?
- You ain't sure about this?
(intense dramatic music continues)
Why should we let some
wood rat scum like him
live in our forest?
Because he's a protector of the realm?
(bucket clatters)
(footsteps pattering)
Where was the Ancient One
when my family needed him,
when I needed him?
Off fightin' in some war!
And then the elves came and killed them
all in the name of honor and light!
(footsteps pattering)
(blow thuds)
(Boss Bandit groans)
Now, brother!
Do it!
(Ancient One coughs)
I'll just do it!
(Boss Bandit groans)
(sword clanks)
(Ancient One screams)
(grass rustling)
Run.
(footsteps pattering)
(footsteps clomping)
(Boss Bandit pants heavily)
- No, no (wincing painfully).
(footsteps pattering)
(feet shuffling)
(Ancient One groans)
- Sit down.
Come on, come on.
(Ancient One grunts)
Come on.
(both thudding)
(dramatic instrumental music)
I'll track them.
I shall return soon.
- No, no, don't not pursue them.
- [Drustan] They are nearly in my sight!
Why not pursue them?
- Swear an oath to me that
you will not pursue them.
- [Drustan] Ancient Father,
you do not know what you ask.
I feel rage and vengeance,
an all consuming hate
that must be extinguished
with their blood.
- It is that very thing
that will defeat you.
(Ancient One breathes heavily)
Hate and vengeance is never
extinguished with blood,
but only grows more
powerful and destructive.
Now, swear an oath on this
day (breathes shakily)
on my life that you will
not pursue my attackers.
(continues breathing shakily)
- [Drustan] I swear.
(exhales loudly)
- You're a great warrior, my son.
(pensive instrumental music)
(footsteps pattering)
(suspenseful dramatic music)
- I can smell your fear, human.
Come out and play.
There's no need to be shy.
(fingers tapping)
(intense dramatic music)
(dagger unsheathes)
(intense dramatic music continues)
- No, no, you stay.
Mograh has game for you.
(Mograh groans)
- Well, well, if it
isn't a peasant survivor
from a town I pillaged.
Wait a minute!
I recognize your face.
You're the Map Maker.
- What do you want?
- (laughs) Caraphinneth,
"What do I want?",
the Map Maker asks.
- I'll give you whatever
you want, creature.
Just let me go.
- Oi, Caraphinneth, he called me creature,
and I thought we were playin' nice.
Tell me where I can find the Bloodstone,
and Caraphinneth here won't cause you
a tortured, agonizing death.
- The only stone I've ever seen
is hung around the neck
of the Lady of the Woods.
- The Lady of the Woods you say?
Why don't you paint me a map?
Do I have anything in my teeth?
An orc's gotta look his best
when he's meetin' the Lady of the Woods.
- Here.
This will lead you right to her.
Am I free to go now?
- Why not?
I'm an Orc of me words,
and I did say, "Caraphinneth
wouldn't cause you
a tortured, agonizing death".
It's a shame I didn't
include me self in there.
I wasn't startin' to like ya.
(ominous dramatic music)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(Reina coughs)
- Come here, little one.
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
There, all better now.
(intense dramatic music)
Shh.
Hide.
(clothing thuds)
- [Henrik] The girl eats
when she finishes the job.
You eat when she finishes the job.
- You coward.
(intense dramatic music continues)
(dramatic instrumental music)
- [Sharia] Hmm.
Drustan, you've dropped this.
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
What memories invade your mind?
- Yes, Master.
Find the Bloodstone I will.
Search every village in
the Grimmock Mountain.
Oi, I'm no moppet.
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
(intense whooshing)
- The Bloodstone, what is this artifact?
- How do you know about this?
(bow clangs)
- The orcs who slew my family
and took my daughter captive
were searching for it.
They seem to think that I,
or someone from my village,
was in possession of it.
- Try to understand, Ranger.
The Bloodstone is much older
and larger than any of us.
Forged by the hand of
King De'grun himself.
Imbued with power that can
rip the rights of creation
from the gods.
- And what of it?
- The stone is no longer whole.
Only fragments exist now.
Each one contains the
power of an ancient right
designed to bring back the Shadow King.
- King De'grun?
- [Sharia] Precisely.
- So who is this master
that wants the Bloodstone?
- Hmm, the son of the king, Prince Korlan.
(intense whooshing)
Long had the shards
of the Bloodstone been hidden
in the land of Adrasil,
long has the Shadow Prince sent out
his couriers to seek them.
On a dreadful day, not too
long ago, one was found,
which led them to the location
of the Etcher of Souls,
the blade of his father.
Blood ruins on the blade
contained King De'grun's soul print.
It is believed that another
shard of the Bloodstone
is in the Grimmock Mountains,
which contains the chanting rights
used to resurrect the Shadow King.
(dramatic instrumental music)
- Mograh, Lady of Woods
is powerful caster,
much more than I.
You must go alone.
I wait here.
- You mean to tell me,
I gots to go get that cursed
Bloodstone all by me self?
Lazy moppet!
- I stay here and resurrect
you if she kill you.
You understand.
Go now, get Bloodstone,
and bring it back to Master.
He will give you war band.
- Oh, you sure know how to
make an orc feel needed.
(dramatic instrumental music)
- [Lady Of The Woods] All these years,
and the answer is finally here.
- Well, looky what we got here.
You must be the Lady of the Woods?
I hear you can see the future.
Wait a tick!
Does that mean you knew I'd be here?
- Yes, Mograh the Merciless,
I know who you are.
- So why am I so smart then?
Every other orc I meet is always
missing part of his brain.
Why is that?
- You know the answer.
- I have been brought back many times.
And to think, I have all
me memories of lives past.
That makes me a genius then?
- I know you come for
the Bloodstone, Mograh.
- Straight to the point then.
Give it to me,
or I'll burn this entire place down!
- [Lady Of The Woods] There's no need
to make threat, Mograh.
I show where it is.
But first, your fate.
(dark ominous music)
- Well, ain't I special?
(bowl clanking)
(dark ominous music continues)
- I see two paths for you.
The first path is quiet, peaceful.
You live long time,
and you alone on this path,
you will die a painless
way where nobody sees.
Never to return to this world.
One more life, then it is over.
- What kinda caster are you?
- The second path, Mograh,
require you to take my life.
And by so doing,
the power to resurrect yourself
will be granted unto you.
You will no longer need the necromancer
to raise you from the dead.
You will never taste of death.
- Clever, it's like an upgrade.
- Spill my blood,
and this path will lead you to a ranger.
He is searching for the Outlanders,
because of you!
You sold his daughter to them.
- That's right.
Say, green skins ain't so good
at keeping little children alive.
It's just to tempting to
eat them for breakfast.
Good thing them Outlanders
is worthless bogs
who'd rather get little
slaves to cook their supper
than do it themselves.
If only they knew the Master
will make them all his slaves
when the time's right.
- Go west of here, back
to the Short Hills,
find the ranger,
find the shard of the Bloodstone.
But remember, since you will live forever,
you shall be sentenced to exist
in a never ending cycle of torture!
- Never dying is torture then?
Let me think!
So it's either I live a peaceful life
and die a painless death,
or I kill you and live forever?
- That is right.
So Mograh the Merciless,
creature of darkness,
which path you choose?
(dark ominous music swells)
(insects chirping)
(air whooshing)
- What's your name, young one?
- [Reina] Reina.
- Where are you from?
Are you from the Grimmock Mountains?
In the Borderlands?
- By the Coldfell River
(Reina wincing painfully)
- May I?
(thunder rumbling in the distance)
Do you know who I am, Reina?
- You're an Outlander.
- How do you know about Outlanders?
- Daddy told me.
- Who's your daddy, Reina?
Does he know where you are?
- Daddy will find me,
he can find anything.
He's a ranger.
(gentle instrumental music)
(hay rustles)
(gentle instrumental music continues)
- [Bjorn] You hungry?
(apple crunching)
Here, it's yours.
(gentle instrumental music continues)
(dramatic instrumental music)
- [Sharia] Drustan, we're nearly there.
- Why is it that I could
not find this place before?
I took note of our travels.
Your tracking was nothing
out of the ordinary.
How do you explain this?
- There's a dark shroud
cast around this forest.
- [Drustan] I suspected as much.
- The Master had his casters working hard
to hide this place from the world.
- You've been here before,
but for what purpose, Sharia?
- I told you, to fight the Outlanders.
- Not good enough!
I need more!
How can you possibly know where this is?
- Drustan, let it go!
Let's move on.
- No!
I've searched too long
and hard to let any stone go unturned.
Does it not stand to reason, Sharia,
who are you really?
Why did you bring me here?
- I told you,
to fight the Outlanders,
and save your daughter.
Nothing more.
- How did you know
about the dark shroud?
And more importantly, how did
you know how to get past it?
- Drustan, you're looking into
something that isn't there!
Let it go!
Let's move on.
- Your hiding something,
and I want no part of your game.
(bushes rustling)
Someone's approaching.
Hide.
(dramatic instrumental music)
(footsteps pattering)
- [Caraphinneth] Wait, Mograh.
I smell human.
- That's funny, I smell elf.
- I'm serious, watch yourself.
- What are you so worried about?
I can resurrect myself.
I killed the Lady of the Woods.
Where is this Outlander?
- [Caraphinneth] Patience,
Mograh, he comes now.
(leaves rustling)
(Mograh growls)
- You don't scare me, green skin,
or shall I say pale skin?
You know, for an orc,
you're quite colorless.
Has anyone ever told you that?
- Where is the girl pastie?
- What girl?
- [Mograh] The one I sold you
right before I died.
- (scoffs) That's a good one,
an orc who re-animates himself,
and tries to claim what
is rightfully mine.
I wish I had a necromancer by my side.
Do you charge for this service?
(dagger unsheathes)
- Bring me to the girl!
- [Henrik] Why is she so important to you?
She's just a worthless peasant
who can't even sew trousers.
- You stupid git, she's
the daughter of a ranger.
- [Henrik] This ranger
could never find her.
The dark shroud protects her.
- [Caraphinneth] You
underestimate this ranger.
He travels with She-elf.
She leads him to your camp.
- Sharia.
How do you know?
- [Caraphinneth] I smell them.
They're close.
We don't have much time.
- I'll bring you to the girl,
but you pay double your selling price!
- Greedy, predictable, pastie Outlander,
this is why we'll be friends forever.
- [Caraphinneth] Now,
Henrik, bring us to her.
Do this, and I resurrect
you next time you die.
- Follow me.
- Drustan, wait.
- I have no need for your
assistance anymore, She-elf.
They will leave me back to their camp.
I appreciate you taking me this far,
but this is where we go our separate ways.
- Stupid human.
You have no idea who you're dealing with.
- Then tell me.
Perhaps I shall sway my mind.
So be it.
(arrows clattering)
(ominous dramatic music)
(footsteps pattering)
(ominous dramatic music continues)
(footsteps clomping)
(sword swooshing)
(Outlander groans)
(blow thuds)
(arrows clatter)
(Outlander grunts)
(arrow whooshing)
(ominous dramatic music continues)
(arrows clatter)
(bow creaks)
(footsteps pattering)
(arrow whooshing)
(sword clanks)
(Outlander groans)
(arrows clatter)
(bow clanks)
(arrow whooshing)
(arrow clatters)
(Outlander grunts)
(blades clanking)
(Outlander groans)
(body thuds)
(bow creaks)
(arrow whooshing)
(dark ominous music continues)
(footsteps pattering)
(door creaks open)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(footsteps pattering)
(bow creaks)
- You dare wage war on your kin, Sharia?
- You are not my kin, Outlander.
You betray all that you once were.
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
(dark ominous music)
(blades clanking)
(blows thudding)
(Henrik groans)
(dark ominous music continues)
(blades clank)
(gear clattering)
(Bjorn grunts)
(blows thudding)
(blades whooshing)
(blades clank)
(Bjorn groans)
(Drustan yells)
(blow thuds)
(Bjorn grunts)
(blow continues thudding)
- I'm not your-
(Bjorn groans)
(blows thudding)
(Bjorn continues groaning)
(foot thuds)
(Henrik groans)
(both grunting)
(blows thudding)
(both groaning)
(footsteps pattering)
(Caraphinneth yells in
a mystical language)
(Drustan yells)
(Bjorn yells)
(both grunting)
(Bjorn screams painfully)
(headbutt thuds)
(Drustan groans)
- I'm not your enemy, Ranger!
(Caraphinneth chants
in a mystical language)
(Mograh groans)
(skin squelching)
(continues groaning)
(pants heavily)
(sword unsheathes)
- You'll say anything to stay alive!
(Drustan yells)
(sword whooshing)
(Drustan groans)
(sword clanks)
(blow thuds)
(Drustan groans)
(continues groaning)
(blow thuds)
(Bjorn groans)
(Caraphinneth chants
in a mystical language)
(Bjorn grunts)
(sword clanks)
(Drustan yells)
(body thuds)
(Drustan groans)
(foot thuds)
(ominous dark music)
(legs shuffling)
(sword clanks)
(Caraphinneth chants
in a mystical language)
(Drustan groans)
(sword clanks)
(Drustan continues groaning)
- The mighty elven warrior.
What's the matter, Sharia?
You're nothing without your blades.
Here.
(dagger whooshing)
Have this one.
(footsteps pattering)
(both grunting)
(feet shuffling)
(both continue grunting)
(arrows clatter)
(Drustan groans)
(Bjorn thuds)
(Caraphinneth chants
in a mystical language)
(intense whooshing)
(Caraphinneth continues chanting)
(Sharia gagging)
(Sharia grunts)
(dagger clanks)
(Caraphinneth screams)
(blow thuds)
(Bjorn groans)
- For my daughter.
(footsteps pattering)
(Sharia grunts)
(Drustan groans)
(body thuds)
(continues groaning)
(Sharia groans)
Are you mad, She-elf?
- [Sharia] He's my husband!
(dramatic instrumental music)
(Sharia groans)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
- Forbidden love.
(dagger clanks)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
I understand.
(hands thud)
(intense dramatic music)
(dagger clanks)
(intense dramatic music continues)
(footsteps pattering)
- Not so fast!
I've waited a long time for this.
Now, pastie ranger,
give me your Bloodstone,
or witness me cut her
little pretty head off.
- I don't have the Bloodstone.
You and your kind have raided
and killed all that were in
my village searching for it.
No one has it, Mograh.
- And I beg to differ, Ranger.
The Lady of the Woods said
right before I cut her
lights, you'd have it.
And if I found you, I'd get it.
I'd live forever.
(dramatic instrumental music)
(intense whooshing)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
The thing about
the Lady of the Woods is, she never lies.
(intense dramatic music)
(stuffed animal rustles)
(intense dramatic music continues)
(necklace thuds)
Oi, Caraphinneth, finish him.
(Caraphinneth grunts)
(arrows clatter)
(air whooshing)
(Drustan groans)
(skin squelching)
(Caraphinneth grunts)
(whimpers softly)
(Mograh thuds)
(skin squelching)
(Caraphinneth grunts)
(Drustan grunts)
(Caraphinneth groans)
(body thuds)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(sword clanks)
(leaves rustling)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
(Henrik pants heavily)
(bow creaks)
(arrow whooshing)
(Henrik groans)
(Henrik continues groaning)
(bow creaks)
(Henrik groans loudly)
- Wait!
(continues groaning)
He is my brother.
(Henrik breathes heavily)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
(sword clanks)
(Mograh thuds)
(whimsical tones)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
- So you'll kill me then?
Your own brother?
You have no loyalty, Bjorn.
You will die!
She will betray you!
You know not what you choose.
- It didn't have to be this way.
- Your stupid and weak!
Curses be upon you, Bjorn!
(Henrik groans)
(skin squelching)
(gurgles loudly)
(pants heavily)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
- Goodbye, brother.
May you fair better in the afterlife
than you did in this one.
(ominous dramatic music)
(sword clanks)
(ominous dramatic music continues)
- [Reina] Daddy!
(dark ominous music)
(dramatic instrumental music)
- Reina, my child.
You are so strong and brave.
You are my everything.
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
Never forget how special you are.
(smooching softly)
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
(water rushing)
Reina, love, this is our new home now.
This is where you stay
when I fight for the king.
You're with family now.
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
- Hi, Reina.
I'm Evaline.
Would you like to come play?
(dramatic instrumental music continues)
- Thank you.
- We are not your enemy, Ranger.
- It would seem,
given the rare circumstances
of the situation,
which was the only option that could work.
I am the last surviving Outlander.
- Only we know where the hidden camp is
that the dark shroud protects.
- [Drustan] I suppose it's the
safest possible place then.
- For them both.
- I couldn't agree more.
(intense dramatic music)
- Ranger!
(intense dramatic music continues)
- [Drustan] It's finally over.
(bag rustles)
The long awaited rest.
I feel free to act, free to serve.
My sweet Reina safe and
sound with newfound friends
who have become family.
Curious how the shedding
of blood does that.
How it renders preconceived ideas
of what we once thought were
just and true irrelevant.
But how did I become this,
a creature of light?
Was I forged in the furnace
of war like so many of us?
I think not.
I was saved,
saved by a guardian
who saw better than me.
Wrapped by sorrow from the
death of the Ancient One,
I grew powerless to resist the urge
to track down the thieving
bandits who stole his life.
A promise I had made knowing full well
I hadn't the strength to fulfill.
The flesh is weak,
and I succumb to the poison of vengeance.
After many days of tracking,
I finally took hold of their scent.
What would happen next
could only be explained as fate incarnate.
(ominous dramatic music)
- For a thievin' bandit like yourself,
I didn't think you had it in ya.
- [Drustan] Only two bandits.
Where's the third?
No matter, I could just
end them with arrows,
but they need to be punished.
- [Boss Bandit] They were ugly,
(laughs) maybe that was why?
- [Drustan] They don't
deserve a quick end.
(fruit thuds)
(Drustan groans)
(blow thuds)
(liquid sloshing)
(blows continue thudding)
(Boss Bandit groans)
- Oh, you're mad (laughs).
(blow thuds)
(arrow clatters)
(blows continue thudding)
(sword clanks)
(air whooshing)
(skin squelching)
You and your poison.
(Drustan groans painfully)
(Boss Bandit laughs)
(Drustan continues groaning)
What you're experiencing right now
are the effects of a
decade long obsession.
Kreiger here loves his poison.
Now, I know Kreiger would love to
explain the details of his concoction,
but, well, years of
dedication to his craft
have shriveled his tongue.
Oh, don't worry,
(Drustan groans painfully)
his poison won't kill ya.
It'll just
(Drustan groans)
incapacitate ya long
enough for us to kill.
(Drustan continues groaning)
(ax unsheathing)
(footsteps pattering)
(blow thuds)
(arrows clatter)
(both grunting)
(sword clanks)
(male groans)
(metal clangs)
(metal clanks)
(Drustan grunts softly)
(apple crunching)
- (sighs) What happened?
- You were caught in a moment of weakness.
You were spared.
- Thank you.
- But how eager you were
to forsake your oath.
- Who are you?
How do you know of my oath?
- I am the watcher of these woods,
and I know that you swore an
oath to your ancient ancestor
that you would not seek
vengeance upon his killers.
As I said, you were weak,
and now I have spared you.
- [Drustan] Spared me from what?
- An awful fate, my friend,
one that would consume your every thought,
one that would lead you straight
to the forces of darkness.
- And how do you know of this?
- I was where you were once
after the death, Kiera.
I was a lost soul.
The Ancient One helped me
fight against the darkness that crept in.
I became a force for light.
After I pledged myself to
protect the Borderlands,
I fought the forces of
darkness for quite some time.
And I remembered the
Ancient One telling me
of a lost love and family he once had.
I returned to these part.
I've watched you train
for quite some time.
I saw your potential
in skill and the heart.
(fire whooshing)
I witnessed his passing,
and I witnessed your
oath sealed by his blood.
(intense whooshing)
- It would seem I owe
you a life debt, Ranger.
- On the contrary.
It is he who owes you a life debt.
This here is the last remaining bandit.
He claims he was forced
to kill the Ancient One,
that he had no choice in the matter.
I leave judgment to you, Drustan.
As rangers in the Borderlands,
we are the blade of the king.
We are judge, jury and executioner.
So what will it be, brother?
Will it be justice or mercy?
(birds chirping)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(whimsical tones)
(dark ominous music)
(child chants indistinctly)
(triumphant instrumental music)
(gentle ethereal music)