Downloaded from
YTS.MX
>> Announcer: LIVE FROM THE
BARKER HANGAR IN SANTA MONICA,
CALIFORNIA, IT'S THE 28th ANNUAL
"SCREEN ACTORS GUILD AWARDS."
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
JOIN US AS THE ACTING COMMUNITY
HONORS THE YEAR'S GREATEST
PERFORMANCES IN FILM AND
TELEVISION.
GETTING THE PARTY STARTED WITH
TAITTINGER CHAMPAGNE IS
DESEAN K. TERRY.
>> Announcer: AWARDS SEASON IS
BACK!
AND WE'RE TOGETHER AGAIN.
>> WE'RE GOING TO NEED YOU TO
GET ON DOWN HERE.
HEY THERE.
LET'S GO!
SO, UMM, I GOT MY SAG CARD WHEN
I WAS 11, MAKING MY FIRST FILM.
AND I WAS SO EXCITED TO BE ON A
FILM SET AND FOR ALL THE FREE
SODA.
YOU KNOW, AS MUCH SODA AS I
WANTED, I WOULD DO A SCENE,
DRINK A SODA, DO A SCENE, DRINK
A SODA.
I WAS HITTING IT HARD.
AND, UMM PLEASE PAY ATTENTION TO
ME.
THIS IS IMPORTANT, MAN.
SO THE DIRECTOR COMES UP TO ME
AND HE SITS ME DOWN, AND HE
SAYS, NICK, YOUR FACE IS GETTING
ROUNDER.
OKAY, YOUR FACE IS CHANGING FROM
THE BEGINNING OF THE SHOOT.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED YOU TO STOP
DRINKING SO MUCH SODA.
IT WAS THE BEST N I EVER GOT.
I'M NICHOLAS BRAUN, AND I AM AN
ACTOR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
LET'S GO!
>> MY LOVING MOTHER WAS ONE OF
THE MOST BELOVED WOMEN ACTRESSES
OF HER GENERATION, AND SHE
PASSED HER LOVE AND RESPECT FOR
HER CRAFT TO HER CHILDREN.
MY BROTHER AND SISTER ARE
WORKING ACTORS TODAY.
I AM VERY PROUD TO SAY I AM AN
ACTOR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> OH, ME.
MY FIRST KISS IN A FILM WAS ALSO
MY FIRST KISS IN REAL LIFE.
I WAS 13 AND THE BOY I KISSED
ONLY WORKED FOR THAT ONE DAY.
IT WAS ALSO HIS FIRST ACTING
JOB.
I WONDER IF THAT GOT HIM HIS SAG
CARD?
YEARS LATER, THE DIRECTOR TOLD
ME THAT HE PUT THE VERY FIRST
TAKE OF THE KISS IN THE FILM.
SO I GUESS I WAS A NATURAL.
I'M ELLE FANNING.
AND I'M AN ACTOR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ OVERLAPPING SPEAKERS ]
>> SORRY.
>> LOOK, IN A TIME LIKE THIS,
THE STAR OF THE SHOW SHOULD GO
FIRST.
>> GOOD IDEA.
[ OVERLAPPING SPEAKERS ]
>> ONE OF YOU SHOULD GO FIRST.
YOU'RE BOTH FORMER NOMINEES.
>> YOU HAD LIKE FOUR MOVIES COME
OUT THIS YEAR, TAKE IT.
>> BUT DAVEED, YOU'VE BEEN
KILLING IT, TOO.
"SNOW PIERCER."
>> I AM OBSESSED WITH IT.
>> MY ALL MEANS YOU SHOULD GO
FIRST.
>> SERIOUSLY, IT SHOULD BE ONE
OF YOU GUYS.
♪
>> ARE THEY PLAYING US OFF?
>> WOW!
>> CAN I JUST TAKE TIME TO THANK
MY PUBLIC?
>> NO.
I'M DAVEED DIGGS AND I'M AN
ACTOR.
>> LET'S START THE SHOW!
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, DAVEED DIGGS,
LIN-MANUEL MIRANDA AND
LESLIE ODOM JR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THERE'S NO CHANCE WITHOUT ME.
>> WELCOME TO THE 28th ANNUAL
"SCREEN ACTORS GUILD AWARDS."
IT IS SO GOOD TO SEE YOU IN
PERSON.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
APPROPRIATELY ENOUGH THE THEME
TONIGHT IS "TOGETHER AGAIN."
>> RIGHT, FINALLY WE RETURN TO A
WORLD WHERE ALL WE HAVE TO DO TO
HANG OUT LIKE THIS IS GET
DRESSED UP, SHOW UP, GET
SWABBED, SANITIZED, SCREEN,
BOOSTED, AND PCR CLEARED WITHIN
48 HOURS.
NOW WHO IS READY TO PARTY?
>> SERIOUSLY, WE'RE FOLLOWING
THE MOST UP-TO-DATE SAFETY
GUIDELINES TONIGHT.
IF ANYONE BREAKS THE RULES, OUR
COVID COMPLIANCE OFFICERS ARE
FROM "SQUID GAME."
>> ALMOST ALL OF OUR NOMINEES
ARE HERE TONIGHT.
>> ANDREW GARFIELD IS NOMINATED
TONIGHT FOR HUS OUTSTANDING
PERFORMANCE IN "TICK, TICK
BOOM."
SIT A MUSICAL ABOUT WRITING A
MUSICAL.
>> NOW THAT YOU'VE DONE A
MUSICAL ABOUT WRITING A MUSICAL,
EVER THOUGHT ABOUT DOING A
MUSICAL ABOUT DOING A MUSICAL
ABOUT WRITING A MUSICAL?
>> JUST NOW.
AND NETFLIX JUST BOUGHT IT.
THANK YOU.
>> LADY GAGA IS UP FOR FEMALE
ACTRESS AND LEADING ROLE
TONIGHT.
TO ADD TO HER COLLECTION OF
ACCOLADES, WHICH INCLUDE AN
OSCAR, 12 GRAMMYS, AND I DID NOT
KNOW, THIS AN ULTIMATE FIGHTING
CHAMPIONSHIP BELT.
THAT'S AMAZING.
>> ALSO TOM NATED, JAVIER
BARDEM.
A PREVIOUS SAG AWARD WINNER FOR
"NO COUNTRY FOR OLD MEN."
HIS WIG FROM THAT FILM MAKES AN
APPEARANCE THIS YEAR IN
"BELFAST."
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> SO GOOD LUCK TO ALL THE
NOMINEES TONIGHT AND AGAIN,
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
WITHOUT FURTHER ADO, LET'S ENJOY
SOME OF THE PAST YEAR'S
INCREDIBLE PERFORMANCES.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO WORK.
♪
♪ I CAME, I SAW, I CONQUERED
♪ NEVER GOT NO PRIZE
>> I'M GOING TO SHAKE UP THIS
WORLD.
♪ I WAS REPLACED BY MONSTERS
♪ NOW LOOK AROUND, AS FAR AS WE
CAN SEE ♪
♪
>> YOU HAVE TO DISTURB THE PEACE
OR YOU CAN GET NO PEACE.
>> OH, THAT IS A VERY GOOD LINE.
>> EACH THOUGH YOU'RE BRIGHT,
YOU STILL HAVE TO WORK REALLY
HARD.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WHILE TONIGHT IS A
CELEBRATION, WE ARE ALL AT THE
SAME TIME HOLDING A PLACE IN OUR
HEARTS FOR THE PEOPLE OF UKRAINE
AND SENDING OUR THOUGHTS,
PRAYERS, AND HOPES FOR IMPENDING
PEACE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME,
JESSICA CHASTAIN AND
OSCAR ISAAC.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> HELLO.
THOSE HIGHLIGHTS WE SAW, THEY
WERE MAKING ME REALIZE HOW MANY
INCREDIBLE PERFORMANCES ARE OUT
THERE.
I'VE BEEN PUTTING IN A LOT OF
HEAVY SCREEN TIME.
>> IT'S NOT JUST YOU, OSCAR.
THAT IS EVERY EVENING OF MY LIFE
THIS PAST YEAR, MINUS THE
OCCASIONAL BOX OF WINE.
>> INDEED, INDEED.
OUR FIRST AWARD TONIGHT GOES TO
ONE OF FIVE ACTORS WE HAVE LOVED
WATCHING.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
MALE ACTORS IN A SUPPORTING
ROLE.
S IS SO I'M GOING TO FIGHT LIKE
HELL TO STAY OUT ON THE WATER.
>> JARED LETO, "HOUSE OF GUCCI."
>> WHY DID YOU NOT TALK TO ME?
GUCCI IS MY NAME, TOO!
[ APPLAUSE ]
BRADLEY COOPER, "LICORICE
PIZZA."
>> SHE CALL?
>> NO.
>> DAMN IT, STEVE!
THERE'S NO GAS IN THE CAR,
STEVE-O!
>> CODY McFEE "THE POWER OF THE
DOG."
>> HOW LONG DO YOU THINK IT WILL
TAKE TO FINISH THAT ROOM?
>> I'LL HAVE IT FINISHED BEFORE
YOU GO BACK TO SCHOOL.
>> WELL, CONTINUE BE VERY LONG,
PHIL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> BEN AFFLECK "THE TENDER BAR."
>> YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
TROY KOTSUR!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> WOW!
WOW!
THANK YOU SO MUCH TO ALL THE
MEMBERS OF SAG.
I AM SO PROUD TO BE A MEMBER.
I'VE BEEN A MEMBER SINCE 2001,
AND SO NOW I FEEL LIKE I'M
FINALLY PART OF THE FAMILY.
AND I KNOW YOU ALL ARE ARTISTS,
AND I KNOW WHAT YOU ALL KNOW
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO BE A STARVING
ACTOR.
BACK THEN I USED TO SLEEP IN MY
CAR.
I SLEPT IN MY DRESSING ROOM
BACKSTAGE.
I COUCH SURFED, AND ALL OF THAT,
YOU FEEL ME, RIGHT?
AND SO THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I'M SO GRATEFUL TO SAG TO
PROTECT US ACTORS.
AND NOW, THE PRODUCERS, THANK
YOU SO MUCH FOR HAVING FAITH IN
OUR PROJECT.
THEY REALLY BELIEVED IN US, AND
THEY BELIEVED IN OUR AMAZING
DIRECTOR, SHAWN HADER, WHO IS A
FINE DIRECTOR.
I LOVE OUR CAST, MARLEY, DANIEL.
AMELIA, DANIEL AND AMY, THANK
YOU SO MUCH.
WHAT A TALENTED CAST.
AND I'M SO GRATEFUL TO APPLE TV
PLUS FOR ALL OF THEIR SUPPORT
AND ACCESS, LIKE BURNED IN
CLOSED CAPTIONING, PROVIDING ASL
INTERPRETING SERVICES AND
BELIEVING IN US DEAF ACTORS AND
CASTING US AUTHENTICALLY AS
ACTORS WHO ARE DEAF.
SO HATS OFF TO APPLE TV PLUS.
AND FINALLY, MY WIFE.
SHE IS STILL HERE WITH ME TODAY.
SHE'S BEEN WITH ME THROUGH ALL
THESE YEARS OF STRUGGLE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING MY
BACKBONE, AND THANK YOU FOR
SUPPORTING ME.
I LOVE YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND MY DAUGHTER, MY DAUGHTER,
KEIRA, TOO.
YOU KNOW, KEIRA, THIS AWARD IS
NOT FOR YOU TO HANG YOUR JEWELRY
ON, ALL RIGHT?
KEEP THAT IN MIND.
AND FINALLY, THANK YOU TO MY
WIFE FOR REMINDING ME TO CHECK
MY FLY BEFORE WALKING ON THE RED
CARPET.
THANK YOU.
LOVE YOU ALL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: AND NOW,
CATE BLANCHETT,
TYLER TERRY AND MERYL STREEP.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> TONIGHT'S FIRST NOMINEE FOR
CAST IN A MOTION, TWO ASTROM
HERS DISCOVER A COMET ON A
COLLISION COURSE TO EARTH AND
SCRAMBLE TO WARN THE PUBLIC.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, ARMAGEDDON
ISN'T SEXY.
>> WELL, YOU THOUGHT IT WAS.
AND WHILE THE THREAT OF
HUMANITY'S IMMINENT EXTINCTION
MIGHT BE INTERESTING, IT'S
NOTHING TO GET WORKED UP FOR.
>> A METAPHOR OF THE CLIMATE
CRISIS WE ALL FACE.
AND A CATASTROPHIC --
>> I HEAR THERE'S SOMETHING YOU
DON'T LIKE THE LOOKS OF.
>> WE DISCOVERED A LARGE COMET.
>> IT'S HEADED DIRECTLY TOWARDS
US.
>> THIS COMET IS WHAT WE CALL A
PLANET KILLER.
>> HOW BIG IS THIS?
CAN IT DESTROY MY EX-WIFE'S
HOUSE, IS THAT POSSIBLE?
>> THERE IT IS, A GIANT COMET.
>> COMES TOWARDS EARTH!
>> CAN YOU SEE IT?
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME
SELENA GOMEZ AND MARTIN SHORT.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU'RE VERY KIND AND RIGHT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL, HERE WE ARE, AT THE SHAG
AWARDS, HONORING THIS YEAR'S
BEST PERFORMANCE IN ADULT FILMS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
IT'S THE SAG AWARDS.
>> OH, WELL, THAT MAKES SO MUCH
MORE SENSE.
I WAS SURPRISED TO SEE MERYL
STREEP.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHAT A SHAME THE GREAT STEVE
MARTIN COULDN'T JOIN US TONIGHT.
FOR THE THREE OF US ARE REALLY A
FAMILY.
>> WE OFTEN EAT MEALS TOGETHER
IN TOTAL SILENCE.
>> IT'S TRUE.
ALL RIGHT, THEN, LET'S GET ON
WITH DOING GOD'S WORK AND GIVE
ANOTHER ACTOR AN AWARD.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> YES.
LEAVE THE AUDIENCE WANTING LESS.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR FEMALE
ACTOR IN A SUPPORTING ROLE.
CATE BLANCHETT, "NIGHTMARE
ALLEY."
>> YOU'RE A SMALL, SMALL MAN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
RUTH NEGGA, "PASSING."
>> YOU HAVE A TRUE, GOOD LIFE,
AND YOU'RE FREE.
FREE AND SAFE.
>> CAITRIONA BALFE, "BELFAST."
>> I ASKED MYSELF, WHAT THE HELL
AM I DOING?
[ APPLAUSE ]
KIRSTEN DUNST, "THE POWER OF THE
DOG."
>> I PLAYED IN THE CINEMA FOR
HOURS AND HOURS.
I'M SO SORRY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
ARIANA DEBOSE, "WEST SIDE
STORY."
>> YOU THINK THAT I'M GOING BACK
HOME TO PUERTO RICO WITH SIX
KIDS?
YOU ARE DREAMING.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> ALL RIGHT.
WHO'S EXCITED?
>> I'M EXCITED.
>> ALTHOUGH IT'S HARD TO EXPRESS
BY EXCITEMENT, BECAUSE THE BOTOX
IS FRESH.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> ALL RIGHT.
MINE, TOO.
AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
OH, WAIT, WHY WON'T IT COME OUT?
>> THERE IT IS.
>> ARIANA DEBOSE, "WEST SIDE
STORY"!
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> ARIANA DEBOSE CELEBRATES HER
FIRST WIN AND FIRST NOMINATION.
THIS IS HER FIRST WIN WITH THE
SCREEN ACTORS GLD AWARDS.
♪
>> OH, MY GOSH.
THANK YOU.
MY HEART IS BEATING IN MY CHEST
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S TAKEN A LONG TIME FOR ME TO
FEEL COMFORTABLE CALLING MYSELF
AN ACTOR.
MY ROOTS COME FROM THE DANCE
WORLD, AND THE BROADWAY STAGE,
AND THE PERSON WE SEE ON THE
SCREEN TOOK EVERY BIT OF ME, BUT
SHE TOOK TEN YEARS TO MAKE, AND
I'M EXTREMELY PROUD OF HER AND
OF OUR FILM.
AND I REALLY DO BELIEVE WHEN YOU
RECOGNIZE ONE OF US, YOU
RECOGNIZE ALL OF US IN A WAY.
SO THANK YOU, SAG, FOR THIS
RECOGNITION.
A FEW PEOPLE, STEVEN SPIELBERG,
MY GOD, THANK YOU FOR BELIEVING
IN THE POSSIBILITY OF NOT ONLY
MY TALENT, BUT OF THAT OF MY
COLLEAGUES.
THANK YOU TO THE ENTIRE CAST AND
CREW OF "WEST SIDE STORY,"
BECAUSE WHAT A LABOR OF LOVE.
AND IT'S A BEAUTIFUL CINEMATIC
EXPERIENCE.
AND I'M THRILLED THAT PEOPLE GET
TO SEE IT.
OUR PRODUCERS, DISNEY, AND
EVERYONE AT THE STUDIOS, AND
CHRISTY, THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE TONIGHT TO SUPPORT ME.
I LOVE YOU TO MUCH.
KEVIN McCULLOM.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
AND JUST THANK ALL OF YOU, ALL
OF YOU STARING AT ME, SO MANY OF
YOU.
LADY GAGA, YOU'RE AMAZING.
I'VE WATCHED SO MANY OF YOU FOR
A VERY LONG TIME.
YOU HAVE INSPIRED ME AND
CONTINUE TO DO SO.
I'M THRILLED TO BE AMONG YOU, SO
THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>>> COMING UP, LADY GAGA, JARED
LETO, VANESSA HUTCHENS.
PLUS, LISA KUDROW ARE TOGETHER
AGAIN, WHEN "SCREEN ACTORS GUILD
S>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, JUNG
HO-YEON AND HALEY SEINFELD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THE CHARACTERS IN THIS
CATEGORY ARE ALL FOCUSSED ON
LONG SHOTS.
>> SOLVING A MURDER, WINNING
ENGLISH SOCCER MATCHES WITH AN
AMERICAN FOOTBALL COACH, AND
SENDING ACTORS OUT TO FIND WORK.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
MALE ACTOR IN A COMEDY SERIES.
>> MARTIN SHORT, "ONLY MURDERS
IN THE BUILDING."
>> IS THAT DILLEN?
>> I'M OVER HERE.
"FACE-OFF?"
>> JASON SUDEIKIS "TED LASSO."
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU
WALKING AROUND WITH YOUR TIRED
FACES.
NO, THANK YOU.
THE ONLY FACE I WANT TO SEE FROM
YOU IS WHAT, COACH?
>> GAME FACE.
>> DARN TOOTING.
>> STEVE MARTIN, "ONLY MURDERS
IN THE BUILDING."
>> I CAN SEE YOU'RE GOING TO BE
A SEXY BASSOONIST, BASED ON YOUR
SHIRT ONLY --
>> I'M GOING TO STOP YOU BEFORE
YOU SAY I'M NOT SEXY.
>> PLEASE, STOP ME.
>> MICHAEL DOUGLAS, "THE
KOMINSKY METHOD."
>> I COULDN'T GET A PERMIT FOR A
VIKING FUNERAL.
>> MAYBE IN VENTURA COUNTY, BUT
NOT HERE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> NICE DRESS.
IT'S STUPID THEY'RE ALL WEARING
THE SAME THING.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
ENJOY THIS FOR WINNING NOTHING.
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
>> THE ACTOR GOES TO JASON
SUDEIKIS FOR "TED LASSO."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WE'VE GOT TO SAVE THESE HUGS
UNTIL I'M DONE.
JUST FREEZE, HOLD IT.
NO HUGGING.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL YOU
GUYS FIRST AND FOREMOST.
MY ENSEMBLE CAST ON "TED LASSO."
THANK YOU TO ALL THE WRITERS,
EVERYBODY POST PRODUCTION, IN
PRODUCTION, OUR COVID CREW THAT
KEPT EVERYBODY SAFE ALL THAT
SEASON.
THANKS TO MY KIDS.
THANKS TO EVERYBODY I GOT TO
TAKE IMPROV CLASSES WITH, MY --
YEAH, MY FAMILY, AND THIS CHOSEN
FAMILY HERE.
SO THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME
LADY GAGA AND JARED LETTO.
>> WELL, TONIGHT'S NEXT NOMINEE
FORECAST IN A MOTION PICTURE
TELLS A STORY OF INTRIGUE,
EXCESS, AND BETRAYAL.
THE COLLAPSE OF THE GUCCI
FAMILY'S CONTROL OVER THEIR
WORLD RENOWNED FASHION HOUSE.
THE OUTSIDER MARRIES INTO THE
FAMILY AND HER AMBITION BEGINS
TO UNRAVEL THE FAMILY LEGACY.
>> AND THEN THE FINANCIAL STAKES
GROW, THE HUMAN COSTS DO, AS
WELL.
UNTIL LIVES ARE RUINED AND EVEN
LOST, AND AS PALO WOULD SAY --
BOOF.
>> AN ODYSSEY OF AMBITION,
GREED, AN VENGEANCE.
THIS IS "HOUSE OF GUCCI."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> IT WAS THE NAME THAT SOUNDED
SO SWEET.
>> CAN YOU KEEP A SECRET?
>> I HAD NO IDEA I MARRIED A
MONSTER.
>> YOU CAN'T.
YOU MARRIED A GUCCI.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND NOW, ROSARIO DAWSON AND
HAVE NECESSARIA HUTCHINS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> EVERY ACTOR HOPES TO BECOME
ONE WITH THEIR CHARACTER IN A
WAY THAT YOU CAN'T IMAGINE
ANYONE ELSE PLAYING THE PART.
>> THE FIVE ACTORS IN THIS
CATEGORY HAVE ACHIEVED THAT,
OWNING THESE ROLES AND GIVING US
PERFORMANCES THAT ARE SLY,
SMART, AND FLAT OUT HILARIOUS.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
FEMALE ACTOR IN A COMEDY SERIES.
HANNA WADDINGHAM "TED LASSO."
>> I THOUGHT BEING INVULNERABLE
WOULD PROTECT ME, SO I PUSHED
PEOPLE AWAY FOR YEARS.
ELLE FANNING, "THE GREAT."
>> LET US PUT IT BEHIND US,
AGREE TO ACCOMMODATIONS AS
APPEASING FOR ALL, AND FINISH ME
OFF.
>> JEAN SMART, "HACKS."
>> ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
LET'S GO.
>> SHE DIDN'T KNOW.
>> JUNO TEMPLE, "TED LASSO."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SANDRA OH, "THE CHAIR.
"
>> CLIMATE CHANGE, RACISM, THE
PRISON INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX,
HOMOPHOBIA.
THESE -- OH, I'M SORRY.
IT'S MY DAD.
I'LL CALL HIM BACK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
JEAN SMART FOR "HACKS."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: JEAN SMART
CELEBRATES HER FIRST WIN AND
FOURTH NOMINATION.
SHE'S ALSO NOMINATED FOR FEMALE
ACTOR FOR A TELEVISION MOVIE AND
FOR HER ROLE IN "MARE OF
EASTOWN."
♪
>> OH, YOU GUYS!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I LOVE ACTORS.
NOBODY GETS US, YOU KNOW?
SERIOUSLY, WHAT WE DO IS
VALUABLE.
I MEAN, WE ARE THE TRIBE'S
STORYTELLERS, SINCE MAN CRAWLED
OUT OF THE CAVE AND SET A FIRE
TOGETHER.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
WE ARE THE WORLD'S OLDEST
PROFESSION.
SOMETIMES IT FEELS LIKE WE'RE
THE OTHER WORLD'S OLDEST
PROFESSION.
BUT THANK YOU TO HBO MAX AND
UNIVERSAL, CASEY AND EVERYBODY
FOR THEIR UNBELIEVABLE SUPPORT
OF THE SHOW.
AND MY GOD, OUR SHOW RUNNERS,
I -- I TELL PEOPLE I WORK FOR
JPL AND THEY GO HUH?
OKAY.
AND MY CAST WAS CAST IN HEAVEN.
AND MY PARTNER IN CRIME, HANNA,
AND MARK AND CAITLIN AND ROSE
AND PAUL AND MEGAN AND POPPY.
I JUST CAN'T TELL YOU, YOU MAKE
IT A JOY TO COME TO WORK EVERY
DAY, WITH OUR AMAZING CREW AND
OUR INCREDIBLE DP, ADAM BRICKER.
I ALMOST SAID ADAM DRIVER, THAT
WASN'T RIGHT.
AND OUR PRODUCTION DESIGNER,
JOHN CARLOS.
BUT THIS HAS BEEN SUCH A JOY AT
THIS STAGE OF THE GAME.
UNBELIEVABLE TREAT.
AND MY REPRESENTATIVES WHO ADORE
SCOTT HENDERSON AND DANIEL
THOMAS AND AMY.
I LOVE YOU ALL.
AND TO MY TWO CHILDREN, FOREST
AND CONNOR, YOU ARE MY LIFE.
THANK YOU AND PLEASE, EVERYBODY,
PRAY FOR PEACE AND THANK YOU,
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> Announcer: TOGETHER AGAIN,
PLEASE WELCOME LISA KUDROW AND
MERA SAVINO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WOW, "TIME AFTER TIME."
>> YOU LOOK CUTE.
>> I KNOW.
THANKS.
>> SO DO YOU.
>> THANKS.
>> OF COURSE.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT THIS IS THE
CUTEST ANYONE'S EVER LOOKED AT
AN AWARDS SHOW?
>> TOTALLY.
>> I JUST REALIZED THIS, WE'RE
WEARING GREAT ENSEMBLES, WHILE
AT THE SAME TIME PRESENTING TWO
GREAT ENSEMBLES.
>> YOU ARE SO RIGHT.
YOU ARE SO RIGHT, AND THESE CAST
ENSEMBLES ARE SO HILARIOUS.
AND YOU KNEW THAT ENSEMBLE HAD
TWO MEANINGS.
YOU'RE A GENIUS.
>> AHH, THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, HERE ARE THE
NOM ENSEMBLE IN A COME
SI SERIES.
>> "THE ENSEMBLE OF "HACKS."
>> I DO WANT TO DRIVE OFF A
CLIFF.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS WHAT
SHE'S DOING TODAY.
IS IT WORTH IT?
>> ABOUT $100,000.
>> 100 GRAND?
>> AND SOME STOCK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THE ENSEMBLE OF "THE KOMINSKY
METHOD."
>> THE HOUSE?
>> YES.
>> COME ON, THAT DUMP IS
WORTHLESS.
IT'S A KNOCKDOWN.
>> YOU TOLD ME THE HOUSE WAS
LOVELY AND HAD GOOD BONES.
>> THAT'S JUST WHAT YOU SAY.
>> SHAME ON YOU!
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THE ENSEMBLE OF "TED LASSO."
♪
>> HE'S SAYING THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG WITH US.
I BELIEVE IN COMMUNISM.
IF TOM HANKS AND MEG RYAN CAN GO
THROUGH STRUGGLES AND END UP
HAPPY, SO CAN WE.
>> THE ENSEMBLE OF "THE GREATS."
>> I'M WINNING.
>> I LOVE THAT YOU THINK THAT.
>> I REALLY WANT TO KILL HIM.
>> REASON AND COMPASSION IS
BETTER THAN VIOLENCE.
>> LET'S JUST BEARD HIM, LIKE
CIVIL IZED MEN.
>> THE ENSEMBLE OF "ONLY MURDERS
IN THE BUILDING."
>> IT'S THE BOONDOCKS YOU NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT.
>> I DON'T KNOW, IT'S SO PBS-Y.
MAYBE MABEL SHOULD GIVE IT A
TRY.
>> I WOULD RATHER DIE.
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
>> "TED LASSO."
♪
>> OH, MY GOSH!
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE A COMPLETE
GAGGLE OF IDIOTS, WE'RE SO
APPRECIATIVE.
THANK YOU SO, SO MUCH.
WE WISH WE WERE THERE WITH YOU.
THANK YOU SO APPLE, TO WARNER
BROTHERS FOR JUST MAKING
EVERYTHING SO PERFECT!
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE WISH WE WERE THERE!
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, WILL
SMITH, FAITH HILL AND TIM
McGRAW.
PLUS, ALEXANDRA DADDARIO AND
ROSS BUTLER ON THE "SCREEN
ACTORS GUILD AWARDS."
HILL AND TIM McGRAW.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> HEY.
>> THE ACTORS IN THIS CATEGORY
DEPICT GAME PLAYING MANIPULATORS
OFTEN MIS-SEEING THEMSELVES AS
MUCH AS ANYONE ELSE.
>> HURRY, HURRY, RUSH TO YOUR
TABLE.
POWER TO LIFE ITSELF.
THESE CHARACTERS AREN'T WORRIED
ABOUT SELLING THEIR SOULS,
THEY'RE WORRIED ABOUT GETTING
THE BEST PRICE.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
MALE ACTOR IN A DRAMA SERIES.
>> JEREMY STRONG "SUCCESSION."
>> LET ME OFF, OKAY?
PAY UP AND LET ME OUT.
I DON'T WANT TO BE YOU.
I'M A GOOD GUY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
"BILLY CRUDUP," THE MORNING
SHOW.
>> YOU'RE JUST SO CAUGHT UP IN
RULING OVER YOUR ROTTEN LITTLE
THIEFDOM, THAT YOU DON'T SEE THE
WORLD SPREADING OUT AROUND YOU.
>> KIERAN CULKIN "SUCCESSION."
>> THE THREE OF US TO ASK AND TO
SAY, DO NOT DO THIS, PLEASE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> LEE JUNG-JAE, "SQUID GAME."
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> BRIAN COX, SUCCESS.
>> YOU BUST IN HERE, GUNS IN
HANDS.
YOU TALK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WOW.
THAT WAS IMPRESSIVE.
AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
>> LEE JUNG-JAE!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: LEE JUNG-JAE
CELEBRATES HIS FIRST WIN AND
SECOND NOMINATION.
HE'S ALSO NOMINATED TONIGHT WITH
THE ENSEMBLE OF "SQUID GAME."
♪
>> Translator: OH, MY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THIS IS TRULY HUGE THIS HAPPENED
TO ME.
I DID WRITE SOMETHING, BUT I
DON'T THINK I'M GOING TO GET TO
READING IT.
THANK YOU SO, SO MUCH, SAG AFTER
AWARDS.
AND THANK YOU TO THE GLOBAL
AUDIENCE FOR ALL OF YOUR LOVE
FOR "SQUID GAME."
THANK YOU.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: AND NOW, PLEASE
WELCOME THE PRESIDENT OF SAG,
FRAN DRESCHER.
>> HI, EVERYONE.
FIRST, I WOULD LIKE TO EXTEND
PRAYERS TO THE PEOPLE OF
UKRAINE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND TO SAY WE ARE VERY GRATEFUL
TO THE DGA, THE WGA, AFM AND
TEAMSTERS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WANT TO THANK YOU FOR ELECTING
ME AS YOUR SAG-AFTA NATIONAL
PRESIDENT.
AND I THOUGHT IT WAS A BIG DEAL
BEING LEFT-HANDER OF THE YEAR.
WE PERFORMERS ARE THE CENTER OF
THE SHOW BUSINESS WHEEL.
BECAUSE OF US, YOU TUNE INTO THE
TV, THE THEATERS, TO LAUGH, CRY,
BE INSPIRED AND DREAM.
WE ARE THE LARGEST ENTERTAINMENT
UNION IN THE WORLD, AND WE HAVE
A RESPONSIBILITY TO THAT WORLD.
TO THAT END, I HAVE FORMED THE
FIRST GREEN COUNCIL, WHICH
INCLUDES SISTER UNIONS,
ASSOCIATIONS, NGOs, AND
ENVIRONMENTALISTS.
SOME ARE HERE TONIGHT.
MERYL, CATE, AND SOME I WOULD
LIKE TO RECRUIT, ROSARIO,
DENZEL.
TOGETHER, WE WILL BUILD THE
GREEN COUNCIL LEGACY, WITH AN
INDUSTRY WIDE BAN ON, YES,
SINGLE USE PLASTIC.
AND A NATIONAL SEXUAL HARASSMENT
COMMITTEE WE FORMED.
IN D.C., WE FIGHT FOR TAX
PARITY, MUSIC FAIRNESS, VIOLENCE
AGAINST WOMEN AND CROWN ACTS.
LET UNITY AND INCLUSION BE OUR
CREDO, AND ALWAYS CELEBRATE THE
MANY DIVERSE THREADS THAT MAKE
UP THE FABRIC OF THE HUMAN
EXPERIENCE.
THIS INDUSTRY IS THE GREATEST
INFLUENCER ON THE PLANET.
WE MUST ALWAYS LEVERAGE THAT FOR
THE GREATER GOOD.
PLEASE, ENJOY YOURSELVES AND
GOOD LUCK.
AS A FORMER MS. NEW YORK
TEENAGER FIRST RUNNER-UP, MY
MOTHER SAID, YOU'RE ALL WINNERS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME,
AUNJANUE ELLIS, SANIYYA SIDNEY,
DEMI SINGLETON, AND WILL SMITH.
♪
>> HELLO, EVERYBODY.
>> TONIGHT'S NEXT NOMINEE FOR
CAST IN A MOTION PICTURE PROVES
JUST HOW POWERFUL A MAN AND A
WOMAN WITH A PLAN CAN BE.
>> A 78 PAGE PLAN, A FATHER'S
BLUEPRINT FOR RAISING HIS
DAUGHTERS TO BECOME CHAMPIONS ON
AND OFF THE COURT, WRITTEN
BEFORE THEY WERE BORN.
>> THIS TRUE STORY FOLLOWS A
FAMILY AS THEY FACE SEEMINGLY
INSURMOUNTABLE ODDS WITH
INCREDIBLE DETERMINATION, AND
ALWAYS WITH UNCONDITIONAL LOVE.
>> YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO WATCH THE
MOVIE TO FIND OUT HOW THINGS
TURN OUT FOR HIS DAUGHTERS,
VENUS AND SERENA.
>> THIS IS "KING RICHARD."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WE'RE A TEAM, WE'RE A FAMILY.
♪
AT YOUR AGE, I HAD TO FIGHT
EVERY DAY.
AND I AIN'T HAD NO DADDY TO
STAND IN THEIR WAY.
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU TO LOOK UP
AND SEE YOUR DADDY RUNNING AWAY.
>> YOU DONE YOUR JOB.
>> YOU ARE A CHAMPION, VENUS
WILLIAMS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: AND NOW, PLEASE
WELCOME, ROSS BUTLER AND
ALEXANDRA DADDARIO.
>> ALTHOUGH THE NOMINEES IN THIS
CATEGORY PLAY CHARACTERS FACING
WILDLY DIFFERENT CHALLENGES,
THEY DO SHARE TWO THINGS IN
COMMON.
>> LIFE HASN'T TURNED OUT THE
WAY THEY EXPECTED IT TO.
AND THEY'RE GOING TO DO
EVERYTHING THEY CAN TO COME OUT
ON TOP.
>> HERE ARE THE FIVE UNTOPPABLE
>> JUNG HO-YEON, "SQUID GAME."
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
JENNIFER ANISTON, "THE MORNING
SHOW."
>> DOES YOUR LIFE HAVE ANY
MEANING OR PURPOSE LEFT AT ALL?
NOBODY WILL RESPECT ME IF THEY
THINK I SLEPT WITH YOU.
>> ELIZABETH MOSS, "THE
HANDMAID'S TALE."
>> I ASKED THE INTERNATIONAL
CRIMINAL COURT TO CONFIRM THE
CHARGES AGAINST THIS MAN AND PUT
HIM ON TRIAL.
I ASK FOR JUSTICE.
>> TEN OR FIVE YEARS, REMAKE
ATM, AND DESTROY IT, RAZE IT TO
THE GROUND.
>> REESE WITHERSPOON "THE
MORNING SHOW."
>> LIFE JUST TURNS OUT TO BE A
SERIES OF DISAPPOINTMENTS WITH
JUST ENOUGH TIME IN BETWEEN THEM
FOR THE NEXT ONE TO CATCH YOU BY
SURPRISE.
>> I'M YOUR BOSS, I'M GOING TO
MAKE SURE IT WORKS OUT.
>> YOU'RE MY BOSS?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE MY FRIEND.
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
>> Announcer: JUNG HO-YEON
CELEBRATES HER FIRST WIN AND
SECOND NOMINATION.
SHE'S ALSO NOMINATED TONIGHT
WITH THE ENSEMBLE OF "SQUID
GAME."
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
>> Translator: FIRST AND
FOREMOST, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I HAVE SAT MANY A TIMES WATCHING
YOU ON THE BIG SCREEN, DREAMING
OF ONE DAY BECOMING AN ACTOR.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU.
MAKE ME DREAM AND OPEN THE DOOR
FOR ME.
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
I LOVE YOU!
THANK YOU!
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: COMING UP, THE
CAST OF "CODA."
>>> PLEASE WELCOME --
DANIEL DURANT, EMILIA JONES,
TROY KOTSUR, AND MARLEE MATLIN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>>> SET IN A NEW ENGLAND FISHING
COMMUNITY, THE NEXT NOMINEE
FORECAST IN A MOTION PICTURE IS
A STORY OF A CHILD OF DEAF
ADULTS OR "CODA."
THE TEENAGER IS TORN BETWEEN
PURSUING HER OWN STREAMS AND
CARRYING OUT THE
RESPONSIBILITIES AS THE ONLY
HEARING PERSON IN HER HOME.
>> HER BUDDING TALENT AND
GROWING INDEPENDENCE UPSETS NOT
ONLY THE FAMILY'S EQUALLIBRIUM
BUT LIVELIHOOD AS WELL.
>> IT'S THE STORY OF A COMING OF
AGE NOR A SON AND DAUGHTER AND A
TURNING POINT FOR THEIR PARENTS.
IN OUR CASE, VERY SEXY PARENTS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THIS IS "CODA."
♪
>> INTERESTING.
>> I WANT TO DO THIS.
I'VE NEVER DONE ANYTHING WITHOUT
MY FAMILY BEFORE.
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, FROM
HER HOME IN ENGLAND, PLEASE
WELCOME KATE WINS LET.
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
I WAS MEANT TO BE THERE WITH YOU
IN PERSON AND I'M HEART BROKEN
NOT TO BE.
BUT I COULDN'T PASS UP ON THE
OPPORTUNITY TO GUSH ON AN ARTIST
WHO IS ACTING ROYALTY, HELEN
MIRREN.
SHE'S THE OPPOSITE OF GRAND.
INSTEAD, SHE'S AN ACTRESS WHO
WANTS TO ROLL UP HER CLEAVES
WITH THE REST OF US AND JUST GET
ON WITH THE JOB.
SHE LOVES COLLABORATION, SHE
LOVES TO ACT, SHE LOVES TO PLAY,
WE ALL ASSUME SHE WAS
CLASSICALLY TRAINED IN HER
CRAFT, BUT SHE WASN'T.
HER PARENTS WERE AGAINST HER
BECOMING AN ACTRESS AT ALL.
SO IT'S SAFE TO SAY HELEN
COMMITS HEART AND SOUL TO GIVING
TRUTHFUL PERFORMANCES, AS WELL
AS SO MANY ACTRESSES TO ASPIRE
TO BE JUST LIKE YOU.
I CAN SAY, HELEN, THAT YOUR
COMMITMENT AND INTEGRITY INSPIRE
US ALL.
HER ACTING POWER IS IMMEASURABLE
AND MAGNETIC, FROM ATTORNEYS AND
ASSASSINS, HER PERFORMANCES GIVE
US REAL HUMAN BEINGS,
UNVARNISHED AND UNUNTETHERED.
BUT THE PRIVILEGE OF WATCHING
HER IS ONLY RIVALED BY WORKING
WITH HER.
SHE RAISES THE BAR, BRINGING US
ALL TOGETHER.
SHE'S A CHAMPION OF OTHERS.
SHE'S STAGGERINGLY BEAUTIFUL AND
FLIES THE FLAG FOR WOMEN ABOVE
THE ABLE OF 45 AND CONFIRMS WHAT
WE HAD HOPED ONE DAY MIGHT BE
RECOGNIZED IN THIS INDUSTRY, THE
WOMEN JUST GET BETTER WITH AGE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WE TREMBLE IN ANTICIPATION OF
WHAT SHE WILL DO NEXT.
NOW LET ME PASS THE BATON TO
ANOTHER ADMIRER OF HELEN'S, THE
SPECTACULAR CATE BLANCHETT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU, KATE.
AND WE'RE ALL VERY SAD YOU CAN'T
BE HERE THIS EVENING.
SO WE GOT ANOTHER KATE.
WHEN IT COMES TO CHARACTERIZING
HELEN'S PROFESSIONAL AND
CREATIVE GENIUS, AS WITH ANY
GREAT ARTIST, WORDS ALONE NEVER
SUFFICE.
HER WORK SPEAKS FOR ITSELF.
♪
>> NOW, REMEMBER, CHARM AT ALL
TIMES.
♪
OH, THIS IS GOING TO BE FUN.
>> I'VE LEARNED A FEW NEW
TRICKS.
DON'T CALL ME MUM, I'M NOT THE
BLOODY QUEEN.
♪
>> IF HE'S NOT HERE IN ONE
MINUTE, I'LL BITE YOUR OTHER EAR
OFF.
♪
>> WHO DID YOU WRITE THE LETTER
TO?
>> I WROTE THE LETTER TO DAD.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU'RE
DOING.
IT WOULD BE A TERRIBLE MISTAKE
TO GO AGAINST ME.
>> COME HERE.
I'M TALKING TO YOU.
>> DON'T TREAT ME LIKE ONE OF
YOURS.
IT'S JUST ME, ME.
NO ONE ELSE EXISTS.
GET ON WITH THE JOB AT HAND,
WHICH IS FINDING A COPY CAT
KILLER.
LIE AT MY MERCY OR MY ENEMIES.
PEOPLE WANT GLAMOUR AND TEARS.
I'M NOT VERY GOOD AT THAT.
I NEVER HAVE BEEN.
I PREFER TO KEEP MY FEELINGS TO
MYSELF.
WHAT GIFT DO YOU THINK A GOOD
SERVANT HAS?
IT'S THE GIFT OF ANTICIPATION.
WE MAY BE OLDER.
>> SEXY AS EVER.
>> THANK YOU.
I TAKE THAT AS A GREAT
COMPLIMENT.
>> I HAVE TO DO IT AGAIN TO KEEP
THESE MEMORIES ALIVE.
THIS IS THE WORK.
THIS IS ACTING.
WHAT DO YOU DO WHEN YOU LOVE
SOMETHING BUT IT STOPS LOVING
YOU BACK?
>> YOU LOVE IT MORE TILL IT
SURRENDERS.
>> THE WORK I'M DOING GIVES ME
PLEASURE AND PURPOSE.
>> I HAVE GIVEN THIS EVERYTHING
I HAVE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> OH, MY GIDDY AUNT.
IT IS MY GREAT, GREAT HONOR TO
PRESENT THE SCREEN ACTORS GUILD
LIFETIME ACHIEVEMENT AWARD TO
THE ONE, THE ONLY DAME HELEN
MIRREN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WELL, LIFETIME ACHIEVEMENT,
LIFETIME ACHIEVEMENT.
SOUNDS SO GRAND.
I SUPPOSE I'M STILL ALIVE, SO BY
THAT MEASURE, I'M ELIGIBLE.
BUT HONESTLY, ANY ACHIEVEMENT
THAT I'VE SUCCEEDED IN IS THE
RESULT OF MY MANTRA, WHICH IS
BASICALLY, WITH ON TIME AND
DON'T BE AN ASS.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, SAG, SO MUCH FOR
THIS.
I HATE TO SAY THE WORD "SAG" AT
MY AGE.
SO IT'S S.A.G. FOR ME.
I'M SIMULTANEOUSLY AND
ENORMOUSLY PROUD, AND DRIVEN
WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT I
ABSOLUTELY DO NOT DESERVE THIS.
AND THERE, THERE IS THE CONFLICT
THAT I BELIEVE YOU ALL
UNDERSTAND.
INSECURITY VERSUS EGO, HUH?
THAT COCKTAIL THAT I BELIEVE
MOST ACTORS SIP IN THE EVENING
AS THEY CONTEMPLATE THE
WONDERFUL GIFT THEY RECEIVED THE
MOMENT THEY DECIDED TO BECOME AN
ACTOR.
SO, ANY WAY, I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT WHAT TO SAY TONIGHT AND I
WAITED FOR INSPIRATION.
AND THEN IT GAME.
IT GAME TO ME, TO ALL THOSE
PEOPLE WITH WHOM I HAVE SHARED
MY PROFESSIONAL LIFE, THE
ACTORS.
I WILL TALK ABOUT ACTORS.
OH, MY GOD, WHAT A BRILLIANT
IDEA.
I LIKE TO THINK INSIDE THE BOX.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO OF COURSE, WE KNOW IT TAKES A
MYRIAD OF TALENTED PEOPLE TO
MAKE A DRAMA.
IN FACT, FOUR OF THEM ARE
SITTING AT MY TABLE.
A WRITER, TWO DIRECTORS, AND AN
AGENT.
AND I THANK THEM FOR THEIR
PARTICIPATION IN MY LIFE.
BUT NOW PORTION IT IS THE ACTORS
I ADDRESS.
FROM FOLLOWING MY DREAM OF
FOLLOWING IN THE FOOTSTEPS OF
ELLENOR DUSA THROUGH THE
INSPIRATION OF OTHERS, RILEY, B.
CARTER, COLEMAN, COLE, AND
KIRBY.
I JOINED A TRIBE OF ROADS AND
VAGABONDS A LONG TIME AGO.
AND IT IS YOU ACTORS I WANT TO
THANK FOR ALL YOUR WIT AND
HUMOR.
I'VE LAUGHED MY WHOLE LIFE,
HONESTLY.
YOUR GREAT INTELLIGENCE AND YOUR
INCREDIBLE ENERGY, AND YOUR
HELPLESS DEDICATION TO OUR
CHOSEN PROFESSION.
I GET REALLY PEED OFF WHEN I
HEAR ABOUT ACTORS BEING MALIGNED
AS A GROUP.
IT'S EASY, ISN'T IT?
WHEN IN MY EXPERIENCE, WHICH BY
NOW IS CONSIDERABLE, THE
OPPOSITE IS TRUE.
WE LOVE AND ADMIRE EACH OTHER'S
WORK.
TOGETHER, WE LAUGH, WE WEEP, WE
WORRY, WE CHANGE CLOTHES, WE
THROW UP AND WE SUFFER DIARRHEA.
DON'T YOU?
I MEAN, I DO.
A FEW YEARS AGO, I HAD THE
FEARSOME AND WONDERFUL CHALLENGE
OF PERFORMING AT THE ANCIENT
GREEK THEATER.
IT SEATS LIKE 4,000 OR
SOMETHING.
AND STANDING IN THAT
2,000-YEAR-OLD SPACE, I FELT THE
GHOSTS OF ALL THOSE ANCIENT
GREEKS AND VAGABONDS.
I FELT THEIR FEAR, THEIR SWEAT,
THEIR EMOTION.
AND I FELT AT ONE WITH THEM.
ACTORS.
I'M SORRY, YOU'RE A MAGNIFICENT
TRIBE.
STRETCHING ACROSS CULTURE,
HISTORY, AND TIME.
THIS IS FOR THE ACTORS.
THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>>> WHEN WE RETURN, BENEDICT
CUMBERBATCH, JESSIE PLEMONS, AND
MAGGIE GYLLENHAAL.
AND LATER, THE SCREEN ACTORS
GUILD AWARDS.
>>> TOGETHER AGAIN, PLEASE
WELCOME KERRY WASHINGTON AND
TONY GOLDWYN.
>> IN SERIES TELEVISION, IT'S NO
SECRET THAT THE SUCCESS OR
FAILURE OF A SHOW IS A RESULT OF
THE ENTIRE TEAM'S COLLABORATION
AND CHEMISTRY.
EACH ACTOR SHINING INDIVIDUALLY,
WHILE COLLECTIVELY GIVING OFF A
DAZZLING LIGHT.
>> THE INCREDIBLE ENSEMBLES IN
THIS CATEGORY ILLUSTRATE JUST
THAT.
RADIATING THEIR SHARED
BRILLIANCE FROM MANHATTAN TO
MONTANA, FROM SOUTH KOREA TO A
NEAR-FUTURE NEW ENGLAND.
SHOULD I READ THE NOMINEES FOR
ENSEMBLE IN A DRAMA SERIES?
>> NOPE.
IT'S HANDLED.
>> Announcer: THE ENSEMBLE OF
"YELLOWSTONE" --
>> YOU'RE JOHN DUTTON, AREN'T
YOU?
>> YEP.
>> DON'T YOU DIE ON ME NOW.
>> RIGHT A WRONG?
THERE'S NO SUCH THING.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: THE ENSEMBLE OF
>> SOMEONE SHOULD COVER IT.
>> HE CAN DO IT.
>> THIS IS YOUR SHOW.
>> AND WE'RE BACK.
>> TWO.
>> I KNOW I COME WITH A HISTORY
NOT ALL OF YOU LOVE.
>> ONE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: THE ENSEMBLE OF
"SUCCESSION."
>> I NEED TO KNOW WHAT EVERYONE
IS THINKING.
>> THERE ARE CAMERAS OUTSIDE,
AND THEY DON'T NEED TO SEE THE
FBI MEETING RESISTANCE.
>> YOU SOUND DERANGED.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: THE ENSEMBLE OF
"THE HANDMAIDS TALE."
>> WE CAME HERE TO FIGHT.
>> NO, YOU CAME HERE TO FIGHT.
>> WE CAN'T SAVE HER.
SOME WOMEN DON'T WANT TO BE
SAVED.
>> WE'RE THE ONES WE'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
>> "SUCCESSION."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: THE 19 ACTOR
ENSEMBLE OF "SUCCESSION"
CELEBRATES ITS FIRST WIN AND
FIRST NOMINATION.
♪
>> OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAN READ
THIS.
ANY WAY, NEVER MIND.
LISTEN, OH, HERE WE GO.
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
FOR EVERYTHING.
AND, YOU KNOW, WE JUST WANT
TO -- WE THANK HBO WHO HAVE
REALLY TAKEN CARE OF US.
WE WANT TO THANK OUR FANTASTIC
WRITERS.
JESSIE IS A GENIUS, NO QUESTION
ABOUT IT.
AND THESE GUYS, YOU KNOW, YOU
CAN'T WORK -- OH, SARAH.
SHE'S NOT HERE.
AND MATTHEW.
THERE'S SO MANY NOT HERE.
BUT WE LOVE THEM AND WE WISH
THEY WERE HERE.
BUT, NO, THE OTHER THING I WANT
TO SAY IS ABOUT THE CASTING
PEOPLE, THE PEOPLE WHO CAST US.
WE'VE DONE A GREAT JOB,
ESPECIALLY ON THIS SHOW.
AND I THINK THEY NEED A SPECIAL
HAND.
WE KIND OF UNDERESTIMATE THE
CASTERS.
COULD YOU HOLD THAT?
ONE OTHER THING I WOULD LIKE TO
ADD, WHICH I THINK IS IMPORTANT
TO ME AND I HOPE IMPORTANT TO
YOU, AND AS ACTORS AND
PERFORMERS AND WRITERS AND
DIRECTORS.
THIS IS A THING THAT'S COME TO
ME ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON IN
UKRAINE.
IT'S TRULY, TRULY AWFUL.
REALLY AWFUL WHAT'S HAPPENING.
IT'S PARTICULARLY AWFUL IN TERMS
OF THE -- WHAT IT'S AFFECTING
THE OTHER PEOPLE, PARTICULARLY
IN OUR PROFESSION.
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE WAS A
COMIC, YOU KNOW, HE WAS A
WONDERFUL COMIC PERFORMER.
AND WE SHOULD RESPECT THAT FOR
HIM AND TO COME TO THE
PRESIDENCY WAS AMAZING.
BUT THE THING THAT IS REALLY
DISTRESSED ME IS WHAT'S
HAPPENING IN RUSSIA, TO MY
FELLOW ACTORS AND ACTRESSES AND
PERFORMERS AND WRITERS AND
CRITICS, THEY ARE TOLD UNDER
PAIN OF HIGH TREASON THEY CANNOT
SAY A WORD ABOUT UKRAINE.
I THINK THAT IS AWFUL.
I THINK WE SHOULD ALL STAND
TOGETHER, AND ALSO, FOR THOSE
PEOPLE, THE PEOPLE IN RUSSIA WHO
DON'T LIKE WHAT'S GOING ON, AND
PARTICULARLY THE ARTISTS, I
THINK WE SHOULD JOIN AND
CELEBRATE THEM AND HOPE THAT
THEY CAN MAKE A SHIFT.
BECAUSE I BELIEVE THEY CAN.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU!
[ APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I KNEW YOU WOULD COME TO IT.
THANK YOU.
♪
>> Announcer: AND NOW,
CAITRIONA BALFE, JAMIE DORNAN,
JUDE HILL, AND CIARAN HINDS.
♪
>> WHETHER A STORY BEGINS IN A
TOWN, A CITY, OR THE CLOSE KNIT
WORLD OF 1969 NORTHERN IRELAND,
THE NEXT NOMINEE REMINDS US OF
THE LASTING IMPACT OF WHERE WE
COME FROM.
>> WHEN THE WORLD SEEMED TO BE
COMING APART AROUND THEM, A
WORKING-CLASS FAMILY EXPLORES
THE TRUE MEANING OF HOME AS THEY
WRESTLE WITH WHETHER TO LEAVE
THE ONLY PLACE THEY'VE EVER
KNOWN.
>> INSPIRED BY DEEPLY PERSONAL
CHILDHOOD EVENTS IN HIS OWN
LIFE, WRITER/DIRECTOR
KENNETH BRANAGH TELLS A STORY OF
LOVE, LOSS, AND FAMILY.
>> A HEARTFELT TRIBUTE TO
CHILDHOOD BROUGHT TO LIFE ON THE
SCREEN.
THIS IS "BELFAST."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> TOUCH MY FAMILY AND I'LL KILL
YOU.
>> ARE WE GOING TO HAVE TO LEAVE
BELFAST?
>> WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
>> THIS IS WHAT?
>> THIS IS WAR.
>> DON'T LOOK BACK.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> I WANT MY FAMILY WITH ME.
I WANT YOU HERE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, BENEDICT CUMBERBATCH
AND JESSE PLEMONS.
>> IT'S SUCH GREAT PERFORMANCES
APART IS NOT ONLY HOW AN ACTOR
INTERPRETS WHAT IS WRITTEN IN
THE SCRIPT BUT HOW THEY FILL IN
THE BLANKS IN BETWEEN.
>> THE FIVE WOMEN IN THIS
CATEGORY ARE MASTER
PRACTITIONERS OF THIS ALCHEMY,
EACH CONTRIBUTING TO THE
INSPIRED ELEMENTS THAT BRING
THEIR CHARACTER INTO EXISTENCE.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
FEMALE ACTOR IN A TELEVISION
MOVIE OR LIMITED SERIES.
>> KATE WINCE LET, JENNIFER
COOLIDGE, CYNTHIA ARIVO, JEAN
SMART, MARGARET QUALLEY.
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
>> KATE WINSLET "THE MARE OF
EASTTOWN."
>> KATE COULD NOT BE WITH US
THIS EVENING, SO WE ACCEPT THE
ACTOR ON HER BEHALF.
>> AND WE'RE VERY HAPPY FOR HER
TO ACCEPT AS HER.
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME,
MAGGIE GYLLENHAAL.
>> AS GERTRUDE SAYS IN "HAMLET,"
"ALL THAT LIVES MUST DIE,
PASSING THROUGH NATURE TO
ETERNITY."
I WATCHED MY MOST CHERISHED
TEACHER SAY THOSE WORDS ON STAGE
SHORTLY BEFORE SHE HERSELF
PASSED AWAY.
AND THEY LEFT A LASTING MARK ON
ME.
THERE HAS BEEN A LOT OF PAINFUL
LOSS THIS YEAR.
AND TONIGHT, WE HONOR OUR
BELOVED PEERS WHO HAVE GONE
BEFORE US.
TO THEM WE SAY, THANK YOU FOR
YOUR WORK AND INSPIRATION.
AND IN SOME CASES EVEN, THANK
YOU FOR BEING A FRIEND.
>> IN CASE I DON'T SEE YOU
AGAIN, I WOULD JUST LIKE TO SAY,
SO LONG.
>> WHEN A MAN'S DONE ALL HE CAN,
ALL THAT IS LEFT IS TO HOPE THAT
GOD WILL SEE HIM THROUGH IT.
>> YOU CAN'T LIVE FOR THE
FUTURE, JUST LIKE YOU CAN'T LIVE
IN THE PAST.
♪ I FEEL JUST LIKE A SAILBOAT
>> LIKE THE MAN SAID, JUST A
LITTLE BIT OF SOUL.
♪ DON'T KNOW WHERE I'M HEADED
>> GIVE IT TO ME STRAIGHT,
DOCTOR.
I CAN TAKE IT!
♪ I'VE SEEN THE SUN
♪ FELT THE RAIN ON MY SKIN
♪ I'VE BEEN LOST AND FOUND
>> WE'VE GOT NO TIME TO WASTE.
>> WHY CAN'T GOD BE A WOMAN?
>> THAT WOULD BE SILLY.
>> THIS FROM A MAN WHO HAS A
COLLECTION OF WHOOPEE CUSHIONS.
>> I'LL TRY TO LIVE EVERY DAY
FOR ITSELF.
EACH ONE IS LIKE A GIFT.
>> THE GAME IS OUT THERE.
IT'S EITHER PLAY OR GET PLAYED.
>> I SUPPOSE A MAN HAS TO DECIDE
WHEN HE WANTS TO STAND UP AND BE
A MAN.
>> I CAN'T DO THAT HOLLYWOOD
STUFF, MAN.
I CAN'T SAY THAT STUFF THEY WANT
ME TO SAY.
>> I WANT TO HAVE FUN AND BE
ROMANCED, BE LOVED.
I'VE GOT A RIGHT TO LIVE MY LIFE
THE WAY I WANT TO LIVE IT.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY ASPIRIN?
>> I'M SORRY, I JUST TOOK MY
LAST MYDOL.
>> NEW SUPER COMET.
>> I WILL DRINK TO THAT.
>> SEE YOU IN THE NEXT LIFE.
♪
>> YOU HAVE MEDDLED WITH THE
FORCES OF NATURE!
>> THAT'S THE WAY IT IS, FOLKS.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT WILL HELP ALL
THIS?
>> LET'S GET HIM DESSERT.
>> MY FRIEND, THE FILM NEEDS AN
ENDING.
>> LIFE IS GOING TO GIVE YOU ONE
SHOT.
>> SOMETIMES LIFE JUST ISN'T
FAIR, KIDDO.
>> I WILL LEAVE YOU WITH A
SIMPLE OBSERVATION.
THE REWARDS WERE IN THE JOURNEY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, SELMA HI YAK.
>> THE ACTORS NOMINATED IN THIS
CATEGORY DELIVER PERFORMANCES
THAT DON'T JUST CAPTURE YOUR
ATTENTION, THEY SLAP THE PHONE
OUT OF YOUR HOUSE AND SUPER GLUE
YOUR ASS TO YOUR COUCH OR
WHATEVER YOU'RE WATCHING ON.
OKAY.
AND HERE ARE THE NOMINEES MALE
ACTOR IN A TELEVISION MOVIE OR
LIMITED SERIES.
>> YOUEN McGREGOR.
MICHAEL KEATON.
OSCAR ISAAC.
EVAN PETERS.
MURRAY BARTLETT.
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
MICHAEL KEATON, "DOPESICK."
♪
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I HAVE STAGE FRIGHT.
COME ON, MICHAEL!
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
SORRY.
QUICK TRIP TO THE MEN'S ROOM.
IT IS PACKED, BY THE WAY.
THIS IS SO NICE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
REALLY.
I'M TRULY -- I'M SO GRATEFUL.
UMM, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S AN ARGUMENT TO BE MADE,
IT'S A LEGITIMATE ARGUMENT.
LOOK HOW NICE EVERYONE LOOKS.
A NIGHT LIKE TONIGHT IS
SELF-SERVING, NARCISSISTIC, YEP.
IT'S A LEGITIMATE ARGUMENT TO BE
MADE.
THAT SAID, I WILL TELL YOU, AND
I'LL SPEAK FOR MYSELF, I AM SO
FORTUNATE.
I MEAN, WE COULD SPEND A WEEK
HERE TALKING ABOUT HOW FORTUNATE
I AM, AND I KNOW YOU WOULD ALL
LOVE THAT.
YEAH, EVERYONE WANTS TO HEAR
MIKE RAMBLE ON FOR A COUPLE OF
HOURS.
I'M SO BLESSED TO DO WHAT I DO,
AND SO FORTUNATE.
AND I'M ONLY GOING TO SPEAK FOR
MYSELF.
I HAVE A JOB WHERE I CAN BE PART
OF A PRODUCTION, LIKE
"DOPESICK," OR -- THANK YOU, OR
WHATEVER.
THAT ACTUALLY CAN SPAWN THOUGHT,
CONVERSATION, ACTUAL CHANGE.
WHO GETS TO HAVE THAT JOB?
SERIOUSLY?
HOW FORTUNATE AM I THAT GOOD CAN
COME FROM SOMETHING I DO JUST
BECAUSE I LEARN TO BECOME AN
ACTOR?
THERE'S MASSIVE INEQUITY IN THE
WORLD.
IN "DOPESICK," WHEN YOU TALK
ABOUT ADDICTION, THE WAY TO HEAL
THE PROBLEM IS TO ACCEPT THAT
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM.
NOT OUR COUNTRY.
THE ENTIRE WORLD.
ECONOMICALLY, RACIALLY,
SOCIALLY, FINANCIALLY.
THERE'S MASSIVE INEQUITY IN THE
WORLD.
THERE JUST IS.
THERE'S FAIR, AND THERE'S
UNFAIR.
THERE'S NOT A LOT OF ROOM IN
BETWEEN.
I CAN FEEL RIGHT NOW THE ROLLING
THUNDER OF EYE ROLLING ACROSS
PEOPLE SAYING THINGS TO ME LIKE,
SHUT UP AND DRIBBLE.
SHUT UP AND ACT.
THE ACTING, I'LL QUIT.
THE SHUTTING UP, NOT SO MUCH.
I AM BLESSED TO BE ABLE TO DO
SOMETHING THAT MIGHT IMPROVE
SOMEONE'S LIFE.
I'M THE MOST FORTUNATE PERSON.
I SWEAR TO GOD, I'M SO GRATEFUL
FOR THINS LIKE.
THIS IS NICE.
I WILL TELL YOU, WE HAVE A
FELLOW ACTOR IN ZELENSKYY, WHO
DESERVES SOME CREDIT TONIGHT FOR
FIGHTING THE FIGHT.
I SPENT OUT MY PREEMPTIVE THANKS
TO EVERYONE INVOLVED IN THIS,
ESPECIALLY MARNY.
BUT MOSTLY, -- GIVEN THE SUBJECT
MATTER --
THIS IS FOR MY NEPHEW, MICHAEL,
AND MY SISTER, PAM.
I LOST MICHAEL -- IT HURTS.
TO MY SISTER PAM, THANKS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> Announcer: AND NOW, PLEASE
WELCOME JEFF GOLDBLOOM.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, WILL.
GREAT SCREEN ARTISTS OF OUR TIME
OR ANY TIME, HAVE DELIVERED A
QUINTET OF TRIUMPHANT SHAPE
SHIFTINGS FOR THE AGES,
ENTERTAINING AND RENDERED IN
SUCH A WAY THAT HAVING SEEN
THEM, EVERY ONE OF US KNOWS
SOMETHING DEEPER AND TRUER ABOUT
WHAT IT MEANS FOR A HUMAN BEING.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR FEMALE
ACTOR IN A LEADING ROLE.
>> Announcer: LADY GAGA, "HOUSE
OF GUCCI."
>> WHEN -- TO LET YOU THINK, I
WOULD EVER LET ANYONE RUIN MY
DAUGHTER'S LIFE.
>> Announcer: JESSICA CHASTAIN,
"THE EYES OF TAMMY FAYE."
>> THIS IS AN EMOTIONAL
INTERVIEW FOR ME.
I WANT TO PUT MY ARM AROUND YOU.
>> AND I WANT TO PUT MY ARMS
AROUND YOU, TAMMY FAYE.
>> Announcer: OLIVIA COLMAN,
"THE LOST DAUGHTER."
>> I'M GOING TO CUT YOUR TONGUE.
THIS IS UNACCEPTABLE!
I'M CALLING THE POLICE.
>> Announcer: NICOLE KIDMAN
"BEING THE RICARDOS."
>> THERE IT IS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> IN THE GRAPES.
"RESPECT."
>> DON'T TALK TO HER LIKE THAT.
>> HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MIND?
>> MAYBE.
MAYBE I FOUND IT.
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
>> Announcer: JESSICA CHASTAIN
CELEBRATES HER SECOND WIN AND
FOURTH NOMINATION.
SHE PREVIOUSLY WON AN ACTOR WITH
THE CAST OF "THE HELP."
>> WHOA!
WOW.
OKAY.
I'M REAL SURPRISED.
THANK YOU, SAG-AFTA FOR THIS.
I'M COMPLETELY STUNNED.
THANK YOU.
I WANT TO THANK MY TEAM.
I HAVE THE BEST TEAM EVER.
PAUL, HILDA, STEVE, NICOLE.
MY PRODUCER PARTNERS, KELLY AND
RACHEL AND GIGI.
AND EVERYONE IN THIS ROOM KNOWS
THAT A PERFORMANCE IS ONLY AS
GOOD AS THE PEOPLE AROUND YOU.
SO I HAVE THE BEST ACTING TROUPE
ONE COULD HAVE WITH ANDREW
GARFIELD, I MEAN, I'M SO LUCKY.
THIS IS A DREAM OF MINE TO PLAY
TAMMY FAYE.
SHE WAS A TRAILBLAZER.
AND SHE WRAPPED HER ARMS AROUND
THOSE WHO WERE REPEATEDLY CAST
ASIDE AND SHE LAUNCHED HERSELF
INTO DECADES OF LBGTQ LOVE, AND
I WORKED ON THE PROJECT FOR TEN
YEARS, AND I HOPE THAT I MADE
HER STORY -- WE MADE HER STORY
THE WAY THAT SHE WOULD BE PROUD
OF.
I WANTED TO BE AN ACTOR MY WHOLE
LIFE.
SINCE I WAS A KID, IT'S THE ONLY
THING I EVER THOUGHT ABOUT.
THERE WERE YEARS OF STUDYING AND
AUDITIONING, AND NOT GETTING
JOBS.
AND I KNOW WHAT THAT FEELS LIKE
AND THE LONEINESS OF WHAT THAT
FEELS LIKE.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO ARE
STRUGGLING, AND FEELING UNSEEN,
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW TO KEEP
GOING, BECAUSE YOU'RE ONE JOB
AWAY.
I PROMISE.
AND THE THING THAT KEPT ME GOING
WAS YOU.
IT WAS EVERYONE IN THIS ROOM.
AND IT WAS THIS COMMUNITY.
AND I LOVE MY ARTISTIC FAMILY.
AND MY HEART IS WITH OUR
INTERNATIONAL FAMILY ALL OVER
THE WORLD RIGHT NOW WHO IS
FIGHTING FOR THEIR SAFETY AND
THEIR FREEDOM.
AND I LOVE YOU ALL SO MUCH.
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
♪
>> Announcer: COMING UP, REESE
WITHERSPOON.
AND THE AWARD FOR OUTSTANDING
CAST IN A MOTION PICTURE, WHEN
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, REESE WITHERSPOON.
>> HI.
HI, EVERYBODY.
SO NICE TO SEE SO MANY OF YOU IN
PERP.
IT'S BEEN SO LONG.
ALL FIVE NOMINEES IN THIS
CATEGORY PLAY MAVERICKS, A
BRASH, BULLYING CATTLE RANCHER,
TENNIS COACH, RICHARD WILLIAMS,
BROADWAY'S JONATHAN LARSON;
TELEVISION'S DESI ARNAZ; AND
LEGENDARY TROUBLEMAKER, MACBETH.
EACH PERFORMANCE IS SO WHOLLY
REALIZED THAT WE'RE ABLE TO MAKE
SENSE OF THEIR CHARACTERS' PATHS
TO EVEN THEIR MOST UNEXPECTED
DECISIONS.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR MALE
ACTOR IN A LEADING ROLE.
>> Announcer:
BENEDICT CUMBERBATCH, "THE POWER
OF THE DOG."
>> IS IT THAT YOU LIKE OR MONEY?
WAKE THE HELL UP!
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: ANDREW GARFIELD,
"TICK, TICK...BOOM."
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
WILL SMITH, "KING RICHARD."
>> IT'S GOING TO BE HARD FOR
ANYBODY.
BUT FOR YOU, YOU'RE NOT JUST
GOING TO BE REPRESENTING YOU,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE REPRESENTING
EVERY LITTLE BLACK GIRL ON
EARTH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: JAVIER BARDEM,
"BEING THE RICARDOS."
>> YES, HE DIDN'T TELL YOU --
FOR THE CRIME OF BEING THE MAYOR
OF A CITY.
I WAS CHASED TO THIS COUNTRY,
LUCY!
>> Announcer: DENZEL WASHINGTON,
"THE TRAGEDY OF MACBETH."
>> THEY DESERVE NO MORE.
THE SOUND AND FURY, SIGNIFYING
NOTHING.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
WILL SMITH FOR "KING RICHARD."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WILL SMITH CELEBRATES HIS
FIRST ONE AND THIRD NOMINATION.
HE WAS PREVIOUSLY NOMINATED IN
THIS CATEGORY FOR "THE PURSUIT
OF HAPPINESS."
♪
>> WOW!
YES.
THANK YOU ALL.
THAT MAY HAVE BEEN ONE OF THE
GREATEST MOMENTS OF MY CAREER
JUST NOW.
BECAUSE MY NAME WAS CALLED FOR
"KING RICHARD" SITTING NEXT TO
VENUS WILLIAMS.
AND HER SISTER.
RICHARD WILLIAMS IS A DREAMER
LIKE NO ONE YOU'VE EVER KNOWN.
HE HAS A POWER OF BELIEF THAT
BORDERS ON INSANITY.
AND SOMETIMES TIPS OVER THE
BORDER, WHICH IS ABSOLUTELY
NECESSARY TO TAKE SOMETHING FROM
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU PUSHED EVERY SINGLE DAY.
YOU DEMANDED AUTHENTICITY, AND
YOU DID IT IN SUCH A BEAUTIFUL
AND QUIET AND POWERFUL WAY.
AND YOU DID IT WONDERFUL
JUSTICE.
SANAYA AND DEMI, THESE TWO
LADIES, IT WAS SUCH A GREAT
HONOR FOR ME TO -- I'M SORRY,
I'M SUPPOSED TO WRAP UP.
I'M GOING TO DO THIS REAL FAST.
YOU GUYS ARE ACTORS, SO YOU KNOW
HOW SOMETIMS YOUR ON-SCREEN
REAL LIFE.
AND TO WALK YOU AROUND THIS ROOM
TONIGHT TO PARENT YOU ON THIS
FILM, TO DELIVER YOU INTO THIS
BUSINESS HAS BEEN ONE OF THE
GREATEST PLEASURES OF MY LIFE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
VENUS, SERENA, THE WILLIAMS
FAMILY, YOU ENTRUSTED ME AND OUR
GROUP WITH YOUR STORY.
YOU DIDN'T AGREE TO PUT YOUR
NAME ON IT UNTIL YOU SAW THE
FINAL PROJECT.
I GET THAT.
IT'S COOL.
THAT'S REAL, THAT'S REAL,
BECAUSE WE BE MESSING STUFF UP
SOMETIMES.
BUT WHEN I GOT THE CALL AND YOU
WATCHED THE MOVIE AND YOU SAID
YOU LOVED IT, I JUST WANT TO SAY
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT WAS MY DEEPEST PLEASURE TO
HONOR YOUR FAMILY AND TO TELL
YOUR STORY TO THE WORLD.
THANK YOU ALL.
I'M THANKING TO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: TOGETHER AGAIN,
PLEASE WELCOME DAVEED DIGGS,
LIN-MANUEL MIRANDA AND
LESLIE ODOM JR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WELL, WE'RE DOWN TO OUR FINAL
AWARD.
GENTLEMEN, LET'S DO THE HONORS!
>> THE NOMINEES FOR CAST IN A
MOTION PICTURE ARE --
"DON'T LOOK UP."
"HOUSE OF GUCCI."
"KING RICHARD."
"CODA."
"BELFAST."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE ACTOR GOES TO --
"CODA"!
>> Announcer: THE CAST OF "CODA"
CELEBRATES THE COLLABORATION OF
SIX ACTORS IN ITS CAST.
♪
>> I DON'T NEED THIS FOR SURE.
THAT'S WHAT I PAY THE
INTERPRETER FOR.
ANY WAY, GOSH, I'M STUNNED.
I'M STUNNED.
OKAY.
GET IT TOGETHER.
WE NEED TO THANK SAG-AFTA.
YOU GUYS, YOU VOTED FOR US.
WE WANT TO THANK APPLE TV PLUS.
YOU GUYS OVER THERE.
FOR TRUSTING US, FOR BELIEVING
IN US.
OUR MOVIE.
YOU BOUGHT IT FOR $25 MILLION AT
SUNDANCE.
ONLY $25 MILLION!
OH, MY GOD.
THE PRODUCERS, SHAWN, OUR
DIRECTOR, AND WRITER.
WE TIP OUR HAT TO YOU.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR WRITING THE WORDS,
INCLUDING "DEAF CULTURE, WE LOVE
YOU."
THANK YOU FOR DIRECTING US.
OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD.
THE INTERPRETERS, THANK YOU ALL
THE "CODA" INTERPRETERS.
AND ALL CODAS EVERYWHERE, ALL
OVER THE WORLD.
MY KIDS, FOUR OF THEM, ARE
CODAS.
OKAY.
LOOK, YOU ARE ALL OUR PEERS.
WE, DEAF ACTORS, HAVE COME A
LONG WAY.
35 YEARS I HAVE BEEN SEEING SO
MUCH WORK OUT THERE, AND ALL
THIS TIME, I'VE WATCHED ALL OF
YOUR FILMS.
AND I PAY THE DEEPEST RESPECT TO
ALL OF YOU.
IS MERYL STREEP HERE?
SHE IS, YES?
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY, I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, LOVE YOU.
OKAY.
THIS VALIDATES THE FACT THAT WE
DEAF ACTORS CAN WORK JUST LIKE
ANYBODY ELSE.
WE LOOK FORWARD TO MORE
OPPORTUNITIES FOR DEAF ACTORS,
DEAF CULTURE.
THANK YOU.
AND I'M GOING TO KEEP YOU ONE
THING.
DO THIS.
THIS IS I LOVE YOU.
THANK YOU.
WE LOVE YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪♪
>> SEE YOU NEXT YEAR.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> UNITED IS PROUD TO BE THE
EXCLUSIVE AIRLINE OF THE 28th
ANNUAL SCREEN ACTORS GUILD
AWARDS.