Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
- Remind me what this
thing's supposed to do again.
- Only save mankind.
- Oh, right.
- Shut up and turn
the camera on.
Is it on?
- Uh...
Rolling.
- Connection good?
- It says all
receptors are linked.
- Functioning at full capacity.
- Punch it.
- Powering up.
- Crawford, what is this thing?
- The Resonator.
It's alive.
- You getting this?
You feel that?
- Brian, are you getting this?
Brian?
- Brian!
- So, after sitting in this
musty old house for 12 hours
and witnessing total
manifestation, I go home,
look at my camera.
Everything I got's
been wiped clean.
- What about your EVP?
- All of it, gone.
That place is unprecedented.
Mara to the world of the living.
Give us a sign.
- Sorry.
- I don't know why
you're so worried.
- I'm not worried, but I know
Crawford, something's up.
- Mara, the guy's a freak.
- He's probably got some math
equation stuck in his head.
- That's not it, okay?
He stopped texting me.
He's never at his place anymore.
Yesterday in class,
he barely spoke to me.
- Quantum physics isn't exactly
the setting for romance.
- He's been checked
out for two months.
- Well, then break up with him.
Sure, he's hot in an
unwashed genius kind of way,
but his mood swings are
really effecting your juju.
Look, you're one of the
smartest girls on campus.
Act like it.
Ghost on him.
- He's not a keeper.
- Ladies.
- Hey, Brandon.
- I gotta go.
- Ah, well, happy Friday
to you to.
What's wrong?
Oh, more Tillinghast drama.
- Yeah.
- Well, I've just
the cure for that.
Let's all meet up
at Stu's tonight.
- I'm in.
- Yeah.
- Well, Mara.
What do you say?
Miskatonic brainiacs
all together,
a little fray of festivities?
- I have a full day.
- And I'm gonna spend
the next week six hours
cutting up a cadaver.
Come on, like.
I'll even get
your boy to show up.
- Speaking of.
- Crawford?
Crawford!
- Hey.
- Okay, what is wrong with you?
- Nothing.
I have a lot on my mind.
- Are you seeing someone else?
- What?
No.
No, things are just
complicated right now.
Very, very complicated.
- Well, let me help you.
- I can't, not yet anyway.
Besides, there are
unsavory points to the story
that you're better
off not knowing.
- Are you in trouble?
- No, no.
No, I promise, okay?
We're good, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay?
- We're meeting up at Stu's
tonight, you want to go?
- Uh.
Yeah, yeah, okay, yeah.
Just for a little bit, okay?
Trust me.
You'll understand
everything soon enough.
- For some, the idea
that an afterlife
was created by an
omnipotent god is a myth.
A blessed ruler, King of Kings.
Lord of Lords.
However, hundreds of years
of human experience suggests
it's not only
plausible, it's a fact.
Mr. Tillinghast.
- Crawford.
- Yo, heads up.
- Uh.
Repeat the question.
- Is there an afterlife?
Do God, heaven and hell exist?
- Religious ideologies
were created
to control simple minds.
- You sound sure of yourself.
- Dimensions in our
conscious reality
go far beyond imaginary
gods and realms.
- Meaning?
- The end of the human
experience, or death,
is just one stop on
a perpetual journey.
- So, what makes you so sure?
- We all know energy never dies.
It can only evolve
or move forward.
The so-called universe
is never ending,
especially if you consider
the notion of true reality.
- You paid close attention
to your father's work.
- Well, he was right.
Especially if you can
fathom there are in fact,
multiple universes all
stacked on top of each other
like pages in a ream of paper.
- I'm
aware of the notion.
How do you prove such
a colorful theory?
- I'm really,
really good at math.
- You should stick to
solving math problems.
Your theory is intriguing,
but it's difficult to
wrap your head around
from a spiritual point of view.
- You don't see God
but you believe he exists?
Just because you can't
comprehend something
doesn't mean it isn't so.
- Yo, Crawford!
Where are you heading, man?
- Working on Project X.
- It figures.
How's that thing going anyway?
- Catastrophic, but
thanks for asking.
You didn't tell anyone did you?
- Hell no, man.
People can figure out that
you're nuts on their own time.
You know, you've been
working on that thing
since I cheated off you the
first time in Butler's class.
What the hell is it anyway?
- Only my dead father's
mission in life.
I figured I'd
finish what kept him
so checked out all those years.
- Ah, so just
another overachiever
chasing the love he never
got from his father.
- Yeah,
something like that.
- Mm, classic.
- Tillinghast.
Been looking for you.
- Professor Wallace.
- Have you seen Brian Hemingway?
- No, last time I
saw him was Friday.
- Hm, his mother called
and said he didn't
show up for Sunday dinner.
Nobody's seen him
on campus all week.
- No, but I'll keep an eye open.
- Mr. Johnson.
- I've been at
practice every day.
- Practice, of course.
It's humorous that you
attend a university
that shapes the greatest
minds in the world
and your focus is football.
- What can I say?
I kick ass.
- How nice?
I hope your forward pass is
better than your baseball swing.
Tillinghast, one more question.
Professor Gordon said
there's some components
missing from his lab.
Electronics, cable, plutonium.
You wouldn't know anything
about that, would you?
- Of course not.
Not really my style.
- Tillinghast, your father
and I were competitors,
but that does not mean that
I'm not rooting for you.
Especially since his death.
I know it's your passion
to continue with his work,
but you don't want
to lose your head.
I'd be interested in
seeing your progress.
You know, should you
have a change of heart
and decide that you want to
pick up where he left off.
I'd even be willing
to mentor you.
- Thanks, Professor,
but my father's work
died when he did.
- Of course, it did.
- And then he says, "I
hope your forward pass
"is better than your swing."
- Oh.
- I'll get the drinks.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- All right.
To the most brilliant minds
Miskatonic's ever known.
- Cheers.
One for the dead!
- Oh.
- Speaking of brilliant minds,
you finally gonna tell us
what the hell you been up to?
- Where you been, man?
- Yeah, where have you been?
- Um.
- Go ahead, tell 'em.
- Wait, you know,
what's been going on?
- Hey, don't shoot
the messenger.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
But this is not for publication.
- What is it?
- Monumental.
Just before my dad died,
he was on the verge
of a very big
scientific breakthrough.
The kind of thing that would
change the world forever.
After years spent
exploring the theory
that we live in a
multi-dimensional universe,
he finally figured out a way
to prove that they exist.
- Shut up.
- Yeah, more importantly, he
found a way to look into them.
- How?
- He was close to finishing
a prototype for a device.
One that emits a
sonic vibration that
stimulates the pineal gland.
- The third eye.
- Yeah.
- You finished building it?
- No, it was destroyed in
the explosion when he died.
I originally thought the
plans burnt up with it.
- But?
- When I was
helping my mom move,
I found copies of his notes.
- You rebuilt it.
- Where?
- I'll show you.
- Multi-dimensional philosophy,
dimensional imagery.
Korean cheerleader bondage.
Hm, if anything, you got
good taste, Tillinghast.
What in the world would you
need 20 cell phones for?
Mathematical certainty.
Fourth dimension tesseract.
Nuclear fusion core components.
How to dissolve a human body.
Busy, busy, busy.
- Wallace.
- Yes?
Hello, who is it?
- This is the Resonator.
- Whoa.
- It's beautiful.
- What is this place?
- My uncle used to
grow weed in here.
There's a great power grid.
Doesn't air pulse
a lot of juice.
- What exactly is this
thing supposed to do?
- One way to find out.
- Don't touch it.
It has a uranium micro core.
- Uranium?
Dude, are you out of
your fucking mind?
- Are we safe?
- If you don't come
into contact with it.
Don't ever touch the casing,
especially if it's powered up.
- Let's see what it does.
- What's this?
- Human heart.
Fresh.
Thought you gave up meat, buddy.
- That's funny.
- Where'd you get it?
- Forensics lab.
I wanted to see how soft tissue
was affected by the Resonator.
- Crawford Tillinghast,
always going the extra mile.
- Yeah.
- So, what exactly
does this thing do?
- A lot.
That is, when it's
fully functioning.
Admittedly, there
have been a few kinks.
My father was an expert
in studies of the brain.
Behavioral, neurology,
dysfunction.
He spent a lot of time
studying mental patients.
Over the course of his
tenure, he developed a theory,
that people diagnosed
with schizophrenia
are not in fact mentally ill.
- What's wrong with 'em?
- Nothing.
They're actually evolved beings
somehow straddling our world
and the parallel universes
at the same time.
- Which explains why
they see things we don't.
- Correct, he believed their
senses were in overdrive.
- So, he created this to
disprove their diagnosis.
- At first.
Then he realized
that schizophrenics
aren't the only ones who
can have these experiences.
You have psychics, people who
have paranormal encounters.
- Tweakers.
- Yes, actually--
- Angels and demons.
Alien sightings.
- Or, or what you think
is an alien sighting.
- Yeah, the deeper he
dug the more he realized
that the people who witnessed
these kinds of phenomenon
all have one thing in common.
- Their brains have
hypersensitive pineal glands.
- Correct.
- So, this stimulates
the pineal gland
so that the average person
can also see these entities.
- Yeah.
- Brilliant.
- Yeah, if it actually works.
You've tried it?
And?
- It really works.
- Let's get this party started!
- I told you it
was a good reason.
- So, all this time you knew
what Crawford was up to?
- Yeah.
- Why didn't you say anything?
Could have spared
Mara a lot of worry.
- Because he asked me not to.
And the fact that all
this is bullshit anyway.
- I don't know.
I've experienced some
pretty fantastic phenomenon.
Anything's possible.
- Come on, you cannot
possibly believe
that that thing does what
Crawford says it does.
Look, his old man was nuts.
And Crawford, he's
a close second.
I love the guy, I do,
but that Adderall habit's
clearly taken its toll.
Speaking of tolls.
Have I told you that we
should go out sometime?
- Only if you bring
a girl for me.
- I love threesomes.
What is it?
- Something's here.
I can feel his energy.
- And that would be
our cue to go back.
- No.
- Stay behind me, and
keep your eyes open.
And a couple of warnings.
- Warnings?
- The Resonator creates
minor side effects.
Slight headache.
You may feel mildly aroused.
- More than normal?
- Shut up.
- Stay focused.
It's your senses going into
overdrive, and don't move.
They can't see you,
if you stay still.
Ready?
Remember, if you see anything
at all, point it out.
Some of them can be
testy.
- Get real.
- Here we go.
- This thing
leak radiation?
- Not as far as I know.
Just keep your eyes open.
The moment you see one of
them, I'm shutting it off.
- Crawford.
- Whoa.
I...
I am a big fan of this thing.
- Please tell me we just looked
into the future.
- Yeah.
- Just checking on you.
- I'm good, just
frustrated.
- Don't
beat yourself up.
You said you had the Resonator
working before, right?
- Sort of.
- Then you'll get
it working again.
You're right, this
thing could change the world.
- Every time I think
I'm getting close,
something goes wrong.
- Well, you just
had a testing phase.
It's not like anything
tragic has unfolded.
If anybody can do it, it's you.
I believe in you.
- Thanks.
Hey, listen, I'm gonna
get a couple hours sleep
then head back to the lab.
- Tell everyone to meet me
there tomorrow night at eight.
- Okay.
Crawford?
- Yeah?
- I love you.
- Good night.
- Can I ask you something?
- Yeah.
- Does my telling
you that I love you
have any effect on you at all?
- I'm sorry, Mara.
That phrase wasn't
exactly thrown around
a lot in my family.
It doesn't mean I don't care.
- Gotcha.
Guess it's good night then.
- You shouldn't
be playing God, Crawford.
- Dad?
- There are things
in our universe
not meant for the
eyes of mortals.
Dismantle it, son.
You're not only risking lives,
you're manipulating time itself.
- I can get it to work properly.
- You saw for yourself, the
results can be disastrous.
- It can help people, I know it.
- My calculations were wrong.
The device, it has the
potential to tear a hole
in your dimension that
can never be closed.
Destroy it before it's too late!
- He's right, Crawford.
Don't be an asshole.
- All right, I've
got this figured out.
Hey, listen up!
Come over here.
- But I still have
egg rolls to destroy.
- Crawford, you have to eat.
- Bear, go wide.
- I'm serious,
I think I fixed it.
- Time for another
bite of the show.
- Last time it bifracted,
the power source got yanked,
the pins in the
connector shorted,
and corrupted the program.
I fixed the pins, reinstalled
the operating system,
and according to this...
- It's Showtime.
- Remember, keep your distance.
If you see anything
at all, point it out.
- I can't leave it on for long.
- What's that for?
- Insurance.
Connection good?
- Says all power sources linked.
- Full capacity?
- Yeah.
- Punch it.
- Whoa, head rush.
- Don't move.
- My head.
- That's your dopamine,
try and stay still.
It can see you when you move.
- You feel that?
- Yes.
- It's happening.
- Take me!
Take me.
I want you inside me.
- Crawford,
you must end this.
Power down the device and
never turn it back on.
There's things not meant
for the eyes of mortals.
Crawford.
Son.
I'm working, please
find your mother.
Son, you can't help me.
Please!
Son.
Turn it off.
- You did it.
- Turn it off!
- No!
Bear,
keep a look out.
- Tell me
she's gonna be okay!
- Hold the chest compressions.
Carrie, put your hand here.
Bear, Bear, tear some
tape, and the stints,
pour it over the gauze.
- Come on, Mara!
- Come on, we gotta keep going!
- This can't be happening.
- A little late for that!
Everybody back!
Clear!
- Mara,
don't do this.
Do it again.
You're gonna be okay.
I'm so sorry.
- Missed
you in Trig today.
- I had a long night.
- Same.
- How is she?
- Lacerated oblique,
but she's gonna be fine.
- I was able to track
down a bunch of ice.
She's feeling good, considering.
You should call her.
- Yeah, I will.
- So what are we gonna do?
We all agree that
this has to go, right?
- Brandon.
- No, Crawford.
We could have been taken
out by those things.
- I am on the precipice of
something revolutionary.
- You're on the
precipice of mass death.
Look at yourself.
You have no idea what this
thing is actually capable of!
It's taking its
toll on you, man.
You're not
even thinking straight.
- I just need to
reconfigure the vectors--
- Your Dad's gone, Crawford!
He's dead!
I know, man.
I know you love the
guy a lot, but this,
this is never gonna
bring him back!
You proved his
theory, now move on!
It's dangerous.
Take it apart.
You can rebuild it once you
know more about it, but.
Come on, look what
happened to Mara.
- Okay.
I'm sorry I put
you all in danger.
- Why was Brian's
coat in your car?
His jacket, it was in your car.
- He must have left it there.
- No, no.
Saturday night, after me and
him ganked that shit for you
from Gordon's lab, he said
that he was coming here.
You said you hadn't
seen him since Friday.
He was here after that.
- You're gonna
pile on too, Bear.
- Brian was here?
- Is that true?
- Where the fuck is he?
- Canada.
Quebec to be exact.
Jail.
Twink like that should
be very popular.
I spoke to his mother.
It seems your friend was
running prescription meds
across the border.
It's very sloppy.
I also saw some very interesting
campus security video.
It seemed you all
have been very busy
with your after hours thievery.
Do not say one word
about any of this
to anyone or you all
will end up in jail.
Okay, this is the moment
where you run back to class
before I have to expel you.
Bye-bye.
Crawford Tillinghast.
So much for your father's
efforts dying when he did.
- He knows about
the stolen stuff!
- Now what do we do?
- Lay low, till he leaves.
- No, I can't lose
my scholarship
over Crawford's
stupid love machine.
- Oh, Mara
isn't picking up.
- Fuck it.
- No, no.
We need to talk to Mara first.
- It doesn't work.
- It was working last night.
- No.
No, they're right.
The resonator needs
to be reconfigured.
The beings that came
through were uncontrollable.
I have to contain
the scope or anyone
near it is a sitting duck.
- Turn it on.
- No.
- It's not ready.
- Turn it on.
- Stand back.
Over there!
- That's it.
Now activate it.
You idiot!
The sheriff is gonna be
very interested to learn
who stole the uranium.
And not to mention your
obvious responsibility
for Hemingway's disappearance.
Yes, that's right.
We both know he's not in jail.
Now, you have one hour
to get that working.
If it's not functioning
when I return,
you'll be looking at some very
serious jail time or worse.
- It's dangerous.
- Don't talk to anyone.
If your friends call,
you tell them that you've
decided to take their advice,
and you're dismantling
it, understand?
Good boy, Crawford.
Now, you play your cards, right,
you'll earn a
little extra credit
at the end of the semester.
Good for you.
- You're up.
- Yeah.
- Amoxicillin.
That'll spare you any infection.
- Thanks.
- How are you feeling?
- Well, I won't be doing
sit-ups anytime soon,
but I'm walking.
- Have you heard from Crawford?
- No.
- Wallace showed up.
- What?
Why?
- He knows what
the Resonator is.
- Where's Crawford?
- Still at the warehouse.
- He was about to dismantle
it, and then he just shows up.
- Wallace told us to leave
and not to tell anyone
about the device.
Guys, I have a really
bad feeling about this.
- Hey, random question,
but your parents have any guns?
- That will be quite
enough of that.
Go fuck yourself.
- Nice form.
- Wallace.
- Your programming
skills are very advanced.
It warms my heart to see you
getting the most out of
the curriculum, Crawford.
- What are you doing?
- What does it look
like I'm doing?
I'm using science to
preserve humanity.
Alter history,
dominate the world.
Just a typical Tuesday actually.
- We can work on this together,
but my calculations are wrong.
- I'll be the judge of that.
- Wallace, listen to me.
You cannot power this thing up.
There will be unspeakable death
if it gets out of control.
- You sound like
your pathetic father.
So worried that someone is
gonna steal his thunder,
that he's gonna lie to keep
this monumental discovery
to himself.
- Do not turn it on!
- What you don't
understand is your father
and I both created
the Resonator.
I designed the schematic and
he took it to the next level.
Unfortunately, our motives
were completely different.
He wanted to help mankind.
I wanted to become a God.
That's why he had to go.
- You killed him.
- That's it.
That's it.
I can feel it.
What your father failed
to tell you, Crawford,
about these beasts,
if you want you control them
you would have to become
one of them.
I can feel it!
- Told you I kick ass.
- Time to join your
father in hell!
At last.
- Get away from my son!
It has the potential to
tear a four-way dimension
that can never be closed.
There are things not meant
for the eyes of mortals.
Never toy with our home.
- Crawford.
Whoa, hello to you too.
- How are you feeling?
- Great, how are you?
- Good.
You are so beautiful.
There's something I've
been meaning to tell you.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry I've been so distant.
I should've said this
1000 times before the day.
- What?
- I love you.
- I sure hope so.
I love you too, Mr. Tillinghast.
- If it isn't the most
brilliant minds Miskatonic U
has ever known.
Well, happy Friday to you too.
Let me guess, more
Tillinghast drama?
- Hey, guys.
- Yo, Carrie, want to
meet up at Stu's tonight?
- I'm in.
- Well, Mara, what do you say?
Miskatonic brainiacs
all together?
Little Friday festivities?
- I have a full day.
- And? I'm gonna spend
the next six hours
cutting up a cadaver.
Come on.
What's wrong?
- Today's Friday?
- Uh, yeah.
- Crawford!
What up?
We nabbed those components
you wanted from Gordon's lab.
- Oh yeah, sorry.
This is my bud from upstate.
He just enrolled.
Gang, meet Herbert West.
- How do you do?