Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[traffic sounds]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[siren]
[electronic humming]
[car alarm]
♪♪
♪ This part I do alone ♪
♪ I’ll take my lead ♪
♪ I’ll take my lead
on this road ♪
♪ I need something to hold ♪
♪ Make me believe
in make beliefs ♪
♪ ’Cause after the light
is it dark ♪
♪ Is it dark all alone ♪
♪ All alone ♪
♪♪
♪ It’s 5am my time again ♪
♪ I’ve soaking up
the moon, can’t sleep ♪
♪ It’s 5am my time again ♪
♪ I’m calling and
you know it’s me ♪
♪ I’m pushing myself further ♪
♪ I’m just trying to feel
my heartbeat beat (beat) ♪
♪ I wrap my hands
around your neck ♪
♪ You love it when
I always squeeze ♪
♪ It’s 5am I’m high again ♪
♪ And you can see
that I’m in pain ♪
♪ I’ve fallen into emptiness ♪
♪ I want you
’cause we’re both insane ♪
♪ I’m staring into the abyss ♪
♪ I’m looking at myself again ♪
♪ I’m dozing off to R.E.M. ♪
♪ I’m trying not
to lose my faith ♪
♪ And I love it when
you watch me sleep ♪
♪ You spin me
’round so I can breathe ♪
♪ It’s only safe for
you and me ♪
♪ I know you
won’t let me OD ♪
♪ And if I finally
die in peace ♪
♪ Just wrap my body
in these sheets ♪
♪ And pour out the gasoline ♪
♪ It don’t mean much to me ♪
♪ Around, around ♪
♪ Around, around we go ♪
♪ In this game called life
we are not free ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ And I love it when
you watch me sleep ♪
♪ You spin me ’round
so I can breathe ♪
♪ It’s only safe for you
and me ♪
♪ Don’t let me go ♪
♪ I know you won’t let me OD ♪
♪ Don’t you let me go ♪
♪ And if I finally die
in peace (oh yeah) ♪
♪ Just wrap my body
in these sheets ♪
♪ And pour out the gasoline ♪
♪ It don’t mean much to me ♪
♪ Oh, ooh ♪
♪ Oh, whoa ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey! ♪
♪ Let’s go ♪
♪♪
♪ We’re going back in time ♪
♪ I’d like to see you try ♪
♪ Unpacking thoughts through
tunnels in your mind ♪
♪ I’ll fix you mushroom tea ♪
♪ And cross the restless sea ♪
♪ Release yourself
to escape reality ♪
♪ It doesn’t phase you ♪
♪ I need a breakthrough ♪
♪ I only want what’s
right in front of me ♪
♪ It’s quite unusual ♪
♪ Seeking approval ♪
♪ Begging for it desperately ♪
♪ I said ♪
♪ How do I make you love me ♪
♪ How do I make
you fall for me ♪
♪ How do I make you want me ♪
♪ And make it last eternally ♪
♪ How do I make you
love me (ohh ahh) ♪
♪ How do I make
you fall for me ♪
♪ How do I make you
want me ♪
♪ And make it last eternally ♪
♪ I can see the real you, girl ♪
♪ You don’t have to hide ♪
♪ Forget ’bout
what your daddy said ♪
♪ I’ll teach you how to shine ♪
♪ And all the things you
tolerated ♪
♪ Made you cold inside ♪
♪ But I can light you up again ♪
♪ Like embers of a fire ♪
♪ It doesn’t phase you ♪
♪ I need a breakthrough ♪
♪ I only want what’s
right in front of me ♪
♪ It’s quite unusual ♪
♪ Seeking approval ♪
♪ Begging for it desperately ♪
♪ I said ♪
♪ How do I make you love me ♪
♪ How do I make
you fall for me ♪
♪ How do I make you want me ♪
♪ And make it last eternally ♪
♪ How do I make you
love me (ohh ahh) ♪
♪ How do I make
you fall for me ♪
you want me (ohh ahh) ♪
♪ I want you baby ♪
♪ And make it last eternally
(I want you baby) ♪
♪ I said, I want you baby ♪
♪ Oh, whoa ♪
♪ Whoa oh ♪
♪ Let’s go ♪
♪♪
[cheering]
Woo!
♪♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Take my breath ♪
♪ Ooh, baby ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Take my breath ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Take my breath ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Na, na, na ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Take my breath ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I saw the fire in your eyes ♪
♪ I saw the fire when
I look into your eyes ♪
♪ You tell me things
you want to try ♪
♪ I know temptation
is the devil in disguise ♪
♪ You risk it all
to feel alive ♪
♪ Ooh yeah ♪
♪ You’re offering yourself
to me like sacrifice ♪
♪ You said you do
this all the time ♪
♪ Tell me you love me
if I bring you to the light ♪
♪ It’s like a dream
what she feels with me ♪
♪ She loves to be on the edge ♪
♪ Her fantasy is okay with me ♪
♪ Then suddenly baby says ♪
♪ Take my breath away ♪
♪ And make it last
forever babe ♪
♪ Do it now or never babe ♪
♪ Take my breath away ♪
♪ Nobody does it better babe ♪
♪ Bring me close
to heaven babe ♪
♪ Take my Breath ♪
[shouting]
[chanting]
♪ Oh! ♪
♪ Ha, ha, ha, ha ♪
♪ Ha ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ This is easy ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Ohh, ohh ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ Take my breath away ♪
♪ And make it
last forever babe ♪
♪ Do it now or never babe ♪
♪ Take my breath away ♪
♪ Nobody does it better babe ♪
♪ Bring me close
to heaven babe ♪
♪ Take my breath ♪
♪ Nobody does it better babe ♪
♪ Bring me
close to heaven babe ♪
♪ Take my breath ♪
[cheering]
♪♪
♪ I was born in a city ♪
♪ Where the winter nights
don’t ever sleep ♪
♪ So this life
is always with me ♪
♪ The ice inside my veins
will never bleed ♪
♪ My ooh ♪
♪ Every time you try to fix me ♪
♪ I know you’ll never find
that missing piece ♪
♪ When you cry
and say you miss me ♪
♪ I lie and tell you
that I’ll never leave ♪
♪ But I sacrifice ♪
♪ Your love for more
of the night ♪
♪ I try to put up a fight ♪
♪ Can’t tie me down ♪
♪ I don’t want to sacrifice ♪
♪ For your love ♪
♪ I try ♪
♪ I don’t want to sacrifice ♪
♪ But I love my time ♪
♪ My ooh ♪
♪ I hold you through
the toughest parts ♪
♪ When you feel like
it’s the end ♪
♪ Cause life is
still worth living ♪
♪ Cause life is still
worth living ♪
♪ I can break you down
and pick you up ♪
♪ And fuck like we are friends ♪
♪ But don’t be
catching feelings ♪
♪ Don’t be out here
♪ Cause I sacrifice ♪
♪ Your love for
more of the night ♪
♪ I try to put up a fight ♪
♪ Can’t tie me down ♪
♪ Let’s go ♪
♪ I don’t want to sacrifice ♪
♪ For your love ♪
♪ I try ♪
♪ I don’t want to sacrifice ♪
♪ But I love my time ♪
♪ For your love ♪
♪ I try ♪
♪ I don’t want to sacrifice ♪
♪ But I love my time ♪
♪ Oh baby ♪
♪ I hope you know that I tried ♪
♪ I hope you know I love ♪
♪ My time ♪
♪ Let’s go,
one, two, three, go ♪
♪♪
♪ The last few months
I’ve been working on me, baby ♪
♪ There’s so much trauma
in my life ♪
♪ I’ve been so cold to the
ones who loved me, baby ♪
♪ I look back now
and I realize ♪
♪ I remember
when I held you ♪
♪ You begged me with
your drowning eyes to stay ♪
♪ And I regret
I didn’t tell you ♪
♪ Now I can’t keep
you from loving him ♪
♪ You made up your mind ♪
♪ Say I love you girl,
but I’m out of time ♪
♪ Say I’m there for you
♪ Say that I’ll care
for you but I’m out of time ♪
♪ Said I’m too late to
make you mine, out of time ♪
♪ If he mess up just a little ♪
♪ Baby you know my line ♪
♪ If you don’t trust
him a little ♪
♪ Then come right back,
girl, come right back ♪
♪ Gimme one chance,
just a little ♪
♪ Baby I’ll treat you right ♪
♪ And I’ll love you like
I should’ve loved you ♪
♪ I remember when I held you ♪
♪ You begged me with your
drowning eyes to stay ♪
♪ And I regret
I didn’t tell you ♪
♪ Now I can’t keep
you from loving him ♪
♪ You made up your mind ♪
♪ Say I love you girl,
but I’m out of time ♪
♪ Say I’m there for you
♪ Say that I’ll be there for you
but I’m out of time ♪
♪ Said I’m too late to make
you mine, out of time ♪
♪ Ohh singing, out of time ♪
♪ Said I had you to myself ♪
♪ But I’m out of time ♪
♪ Say that I’ll care for you
but I’m out of time ♪
♪ But I’m too late to make you
mine, out of time ♪
♪ Out of time ♪
♪♪
♪ I know that you’re hiding
something from me ♪
♪ That’s been close
to your heart ♪
♪ And I felt it
creeping up everyday ♪
♪ Baby right from the start ♪
♪ I know that look you give
when we’re fighting ♪
♪ We’re fighting ♪
♪ ’Cause I used
to be the one ♪
♪ Who was lying,
oh lying ♪
♪ Ohh, is there
someone else or not? ♪
♪ ’Cause I wanna
keep you close ♪
♪ I don’t wanna lose my spot ♪
♪ ’Cause I need to know ♪
♪ If you’re hurting him,
or you’re hurting me ♪
♪ If I ain’t with you,
I don’t wanna be ♪
♪ Is there someone else or not? ♪
♪ Ohh, or not ♪
♪ I don’t deserve
someone loyal to me ♪
♪ Don’t you think I see ♪
♪ And I don’t want to be a
prisoner to who I used to be ♪
♪ I swear I changed my ways
for the better, the better ♪
♪ ’Cause I wanna be with
you forever, forever ♪
♪ Ohh, is there someone
else or not? ♪
♪ ’Cause I wanna
keep you close ♪
♪ I don’t wanna
lose my spot ♪
♪ ’Cause I need to know ♪
♪ If you’re hurting him,
or you’re hurting me ♪
♪ If I ain’t with you,
I don’t wanna be ♪
♪ Is there someone else or not? ♪
♪ Ohh, or not ♪
♪ Oh, hey ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪♪
♪ I only met you in
my dreams before ♪
♪ When I was young
and alone in the world ♪
♪ You were there when
I needed someone ♪
♪ To call my girl ♪
♪ And now you’re my reality ♪
♪ And I wanna feel you close ♪
♪ But you’re defeated baby ♪
♪ Broken, hurtin’, ♪
♪ Sufferin’ from
a shattered soul ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ A shattered soul ♪
♪ Let me be there ♪
♪ Let me be there
for your heart ♪
♪ Let me be there ♪
♪ I can be there
til you’re whole ♪
♪ You weren’t touched
by a man in so long ♪
♪ ’Cause the last time
it was way too strong ♪
♪ Let me be there ♪
♪ Let me be there
for your heart ♪
♪ Let me love you ♪
♪ Let me love you like you need ♪
♪ And I’ll make it ♪
♪ Make it my responsibility ♪
♪ I’ll be there
every step of the way ♪
♪ I’ll get you back on your feet ♪
♪ Let me love you ♪
♪ Let me love you
like you need ♪
♪ And you can kick me ♪
♪ Kick me to the curb ♪
♪ It’s okay baby ♪
♪ I promise that I felt worse ♪
♪ Back then I was starry eyed ♪
♪ And now I’m so cynical ♪
♪ Baby break me ♪
♪ Kick me to the curb ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ Ohh, no, no, no ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪♪
♪ Remember I was
your hero, yeah ♪
♪ I’d wear your heart
like a symbol ♪
♪ I couldn’t save you ♪
♪ From my darkest truth ♪
♪ Of all ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ I’ll always be
less than zero ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ You tried your best
with me, I know ♪
♪ I couldn’t face you ♪
♪ With my darkest truth ♪
♪ Of all ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ ’Cause I can’t get
it out of my head ♪
♪ No, I can’t
shake this feeling ♪
♪ That crawls
in my bed ♪
♪ I try to hide it
but I know you know me ♪
♪ I try to fight it
but I’d rather be free ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ Can we meet in the middle ♪
♪ My babe ♪
♪ ’Cause you were
just like me before ♪
♪ Now you’d rather leave me ♪
♪ Than to watch me die ♪
♪ In your arms ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
Let’s go, let’s go!
♪ I can’t get
it out of my head ♪
♪ No I can’t shake
this feeling ♪
♪ That crawls in my bed ♪
♪ I try to hide it
but I know you know me ♪
♪ I try to fight it
but I’d rather be free ♪
♪ Ohh ♪
♪ I can’t get it
out of my head ♪
♪ No, I can’t shake
this feeling ♪
♪ That crawls in my bed ♪
♪ I try to hide it
but I know you know me ♪
♪ I try to fight it
but I’d rather be free ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I’ll always be
less than zero ♪
♪ You tried your best
with me, I know ♪
♪♪
[Jim Carrey] You’re tuned to Dawn FM
The middle of
nowhere on your dial
So sit back and unpack
You may be here awhile
Now that all future plans
have been postponed
And it’s time to look back
on the things you
thought you owned
Do you remember them well?
Were you high
or just stoned?
And how many grudges did
you take to your grave?
When you weren’t liked or
followed, how did you behave?
Was it often a dissonant
chord you were strumming?
Were you ever in tune with
the song life was humming?
If pain’s living on
when your body’s long gone
And your phantom regret
hasn’t let it go yet
You may not have died
in the way that you must
All specters are haunted
by their own lack of trust
When you’re all out of time,
there’s nothing but space
No hunting, no gathering
No nations, no race
And Heaven is closer than
those tears on your face
When the purple rain falls
We are all bathed
in it’s grace
Heaven’s for those
who let go of regret
And you have to wait here
when you’re not all there yet
But you could be there
by the end of this song
Where The Weeknd’s so good
and he plays all week long
Bang a gong, get it on
And if your broken heart’s heavy
when you step on the scale
You’ll be lighter than air
when they pull back the veil
Consider the flowers,
they don’t try to look right
They just open their petals
and turn to the light
Are you listening real close?
Heaven’s not that, it’s this
It’s the depth of this moment
You don’t reach for bliss
God knows life is chaos
But He made one thing true
You gotta unwind your mind
Train your soul to align
And dance til you find
that divine boogaloo
In other words
You gotta be Heaven,
to see Heaven
May peace be with you