Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Let's get started then.
Their presence
and desires
have granted me power.
You will be mine forever now!
You promised!
You said you would protect her!
I'm glad we are together at the end.
Thank you.
You guided me to the right path.
I cannot allow myself to lose
any more precious people.
My friends. I can finally fulfill my vow.
More than anyone else in the world,
I believe in you.
Everyone. Let's go!
DEMON REALM
-What?
Enemy attack!
Attack!
Release the Indura!
-But…
-We have no choice.
What?
Take this!
Let them live.
Right.
That will make things easier for us.
Time for them to pay
for squandering the Holy War.
The Seven Deadly Sins.
What?
This is the place!
Wow, this brings back memories!
What? Look, Meliodas.
Do you remember that large waterfall?
Yes. When you were a merchant's daughter,
you fell from it twice.
That's right!
You jumped into the water to save me!
After our clothes got soaked,
we tried to dry them.
It was just then that we found
a cave behind the waterfall!
We built a fire and warmed our
bodies with wine.
Then you got completely drunk.
Did that really happen?
Six months have passed since the
Seven Deadly Sins fought the Demon King.
Meliodas and I
have begun going on short trips.
Are you serious, Meliodas?
Will you really become King with
Elizabeth as your Queen?
Sure thing! I owe you a lot.
I see. You've finally made your decision.
We must arrange the ceremony
for your crowning.
No need for all that.
It's your first duty as King.
That bothersome stuff
just doesn't fit me right.
This is just a prelude to the
grander ceremonies to come.
The appointment of Holy Knights.
Negotiations with other states.
There are countless others!
First, for our honeymoon,
I plan to take a casual trip
around Britannia with Elizabeth.
Wait just a minute!
The King doesn't have time for that!
Then I guess I won't be the King.
What?
What did you just say?
Lying to the King is a grave offense!
Father, calm down.
I'm just leaving it to you
until we get back from our trip.
What?
I'll do it earnestly once I get back.
I'll be a proper King.
Father.
I want to take a trip before
becoming the Queen of Liones too.
I want to visit the nostalgic places
Meliodas and I spent together
for 3,000 years.
Once this trip is over, we'll get married
and become a real family.
Right.
Even though we've been together
3,000 years, it feels odd.
Family, huh?
I don't really understand
what being a family should feel like.
You know how my father is.
I wasn't a very good big brother
to Zeldris either.
In fact, all I did was cause him pain.
You can still do it.
We have plenty of time.
I'm sure you'll have a chance
to make things right with Zeldris!
Elizabeth.
What's wrong?
I feel magic from the pool
beneath the waterfall.
Extremely powerful magic.
Gelda, look!
Fish in this world
are smaller than in the Demon Realm.
But they look really fatty and delicious!
It seems you're in a good mood.
Of course!
If I can fill my belly with delicious food
my blood will taste better
when you feed on me!
Don't you agree?
You are so cute.
Gelda…
I am being serious.
Sorry to interrupt.
Excuse us.
Why the heck are you here?
We're allowed to go anywhere we want.
Why are you still in the human world?
Weren't you going to return to
the Demon Realm to become Demon King?
You have no right to judge me!
Zel.
That harsh tone isn't appropriate
when speaking to your older brother.
You and I are only together now
thanks to Meliodas.
Meliodas. I humbly ask…
your purpose for coming to this place.
So you're on a trip together
before you take the throne.
What is it?
-This is tasty!
-I'm just thinking how similar they are.
-I'll give it back!
-Are they really similar?
Indeed.
Zeldris said that before
he became Demon King
he wanted to spend some alone
time with me to fool around.
I didn't say that much!
I just said that
I wanted to enjoy my time with you
before I became Demon King!
That's pretty much the same thing.
I guess it makes sense that
siblings think of the same things.
I don't think of you as a brother.
It disgusts me!
I feel one small magic source.
No. This is…
Almost extinguished.
Are you okay?
You are Lord Zeldris.
Who did this to you?
The Demon Realm was attacked.
What?
Who was it? How many?
There was a Fairy and a Giant.
This is a tale of ancient times,
when the human and non-human worlds
had not yet split.
After 3,000 years,
the Holy War broke out again.
Those that put an end to this
clash of light and darkness
were the Seven Deadly Sins.
Dragon's Sin.
Meliodas.
Serpent's Sin.
Diane.
Fox's Sin.
Ban.
Grizzly's Sin.
King.
Goat's Sin.
Gowther.
Boar's Sin.
Merlin.
Lion's Sin.
Escanor.
The people called them
the Seven Deadly Sins.
FAIRY KING'S FOREST
What do you think?
Diane is almost prepared.
Roger that!
Our preparations are done too.
His grooming and fitting are perfect.
Where is King Harlequin?
What hairstyle is the best?
Your necktie is crooked.
The Fairy King can't be
afraid of getting married.
Just be as you usually are.
Marriage is one of the most
important days of your life!
Especially to women!
If I mess up, she'll hate me forever!
I can't just act as I usually do!
-Diane would never hate you.
-What?
Diane loves you no matter how you are.
Thank you, Elaine.
Unbelievable.
What a pain of a brother-in-law.
Really.
Yes! All done!
It looks beautiful.
Everyone! You came!
It is an honor to be invited
to your wedding.
I bring words of congratulations
and a gift from King Bartra--
No need for all that.
This is just about feelings
and getting into the mood.
Getting into the mood?
I wish the Captain
and Elizabeth could have come too.
But they are on their honeymoon.
Such bad timing.
NORTHERN BRITANNIA
KINGDOM OF LIONES
Wow! Amazing!
I've never seen the city so lively.
Indeed.
But it has to be lively.
After all, tomorrow is the crowning
of a new king.
And Elizabeth's wedding.
Are you really excited for that, Father?
Won't it make you sad?
Veronica! Think a little
about your father's feelings.
I'm just joking!
I must admit I feel a little sad about it.
But I believe Caroline, your mother,
is celebrating this in heaven.
Speaking of which, will they really
be back by tomorrow?
-You need to return to the Demon Realm?
Yes. It seems something bad
is happening there.
Wait a second.
Why do you want to come too?
I'm already involved. I can't ignore this.
This is an issue of the Demon Realm!
I shall resolve it!
Calm down, both of you.
I'm sorry, Gelda.
Please wait here until I return.
I will not. I'm coming too.
But…
I'm sick of just waiting.
Fine. Let's go together.
It seems like that poor fellow
escaped from this hole.
So deep inside…
Yes. No doubt about it.
It's connected to the Demon Realm.
How long are you
going to stick your nose in?
This is our problem!
You abandoned the power of
the Demon King so easily!
You have no right to fight
for the Demon Realm!
Open your eyes!
What if I fight for you?
Don't joke around!
This is a problem for me to solve!
Got it.
We'll just need to settle
this with our fists.
What?
He who wins decides what happens.
I accept.
You can't, Meliodas!
This isn't the place to fight!
It's decided! All four of us will go!
You won fair and square.
It cannot be helped.
There, there. You always act so tough.
Now that that's decided,
let's get a move on!
Dearly beloved, we are gathered here today
for the wedding ceremony
of the Fairy King Harlequin
and the Princess of the Giant Clan, Diane.
Despite being of different clans,
they were drawn together by a strong love.
I pray their love is eternal,
and that this union forges a stronger bond
between the Fairy Clan
and the Giant Clan.
-You may now kiss the bride.
-What?
Kiss?
In front of so many people?
How embarrassing!
Well, this is a common custom.
-Kiss!
Give the crowd what it wants.
Congratulations, King!
Congratulations, Diane!
King. Diane.
I hope you're both happy.
Aren't you interested
in having something like this?
-Not at all!
-Me neither!
This is delicious.
This is a new era.
This day actually came.
You didn't think it would?
No. I knew it would.
But I'm just glad that it's here.
But I wish everyone else could have come.
Captain. Elizabeth. Merlin.
And Escanor.
Also, Hawk!
Right. Did that pig return
to the Demon Realm?
I wonder if he is doing well right now?
Got you! Rolling Ham Attack!
You're really used to
life here in Purgatory, Mild.
You really are my little brother.
Of course!
I was known all over
as Captain Leftovers Hawk!
Let's go hunt the master of the valley!
We brothers can do anything!
Hey, Wild.
The food in Purgatory isn't bad.
But I really miss leftovers.
Leftovers? Are these not leftovers?
You don't know anything, Wild!
That is just half-eaten.
True leftovers
are the ultimate treat formed
by the fermentation of all sorts
of half-finished foods.
It is the epitome of gourmet.
It's decided.
Let's go feast on leftovers, Mild!
What?
Oh, to the human world!
Wait for me, Wild!
Everyone returns to the place they belong.
As the third in my line,
I plan on succeeding
the will of the first Fairy King.
That reminds me. I've never
heard about the second king.
What was he like?
Oh, do you mean Dahlia?
Actually, I don't know much either.
After all, I was born
after Dahlia disappeared from the forest.
I don't mind.
What?
An earthquake?
Tomorrow is the actual festival,
but everyone is so lively today.
Isn't that fine?
It's better for celebrations
to last as long as possible.
That's true.
-But we don't get a break.
-Catch me if you can!
Sorry!
Hey! Kids!
Don't cause trouble, you hear?
Yes!
Wait for me!
Hey. Don't just stop all of a sudden.
What is that sound?
Sound?
What is that?
The Giant and Fairy Clans
are on the attack!
Brother!
The children!
Dammit! I can't make it!
Jericho!
Found you!
Holy Knight!
We must punish the Seven Deadly Sins
and those that joined them
in ruining the Holy War.
Are you okay, Guila?
I'm fine. Save the others.
No.
I think they'll be okay.
What?
They are after us, the Holy Knights.
They aren't looking at
any of the other city folk.
Why would the Giants
and Fairies attack all of a sudden?
Don't ask me.
The Seven Deadly Sins, who ruined…
However, there is something
off about their appearance.
I felt it too.
It feels like someone is controlling them.
If that's the case,
we'll need to hold back.
Their accomplices shall be punished.
We wouldn't be able to stop them
even if we didn't hold back!
KINGDOM OF CAMELOT
Arthur.
Don't push yourself too far.
I won't. This is the last one.
Forgive me.
I couldn't live up to your expectations.
Arthur.
We must punish the Seven Deadly Sins…
and those that joined them
in ruining the Holy War.
Hurry up!
Be careful, Elizabeth!
Okay!
Let's rest for a moment.
Gelda. The Demon Realm
is in danger if we don't hurry.
Just a minute. I am parched.
Sorry. I didn't notice.
First, you need some nutrition.
You didn't get a chance to eat, right?
Right.
All right! Leave it to me!
Believe it or not, I ran a pub.
Cooking is my specialty!
Hand it over. I'll cook it myself.
This is an apology for
eating your fish before.
-Hand it over!
-You're so stubborn.
-Prepare for battle!
Dammit!
People have their habits, I guess.
He is quite stubborn.
How did cooking a fish
make it taste like this?
Make sure to eat it all!
Eat!
Meliodas! What are you doing?
Apologies, Gelda.
It would be terrible
if you drink my blood now.
It's fine.
I just wanted you to rest.
Listen, Meliodas!
I shall never take another bite
of your cooking!
It's your fault for always playing rock.
What do you mean?
I'm sort of glad.
Glad?
Yes.
I'm glad we can be together
and talk like this.
That's true.
It is kind of incredible.
The entrance is coming up! Elizabeth!
Protect against the Demon Realm's miasma!
Okay!
Saint Coat!
Don't get lost
during the shock of entering!
The miasma is weakened.
What happened?
This light. I don't like that one bit.
Gelda. Are you okay?
This is serious.
Welcome to our new base.
Meliodas the Destroyer.
And some uninvited guests.
It can't be! You are…
the second Fairy King,
Dahlia,
and the master craftsman
of the Giants, Dubs.
You two attacked the Demon Realm alone?
At least I can praise your courage!
It's not just the two of us.
We sent our large group
of allies to the other side.
-What?
-What did you say?
What is your goal?
That's simple.
You squandered our game!
SPIRIT SPEAR DARRENHEART
FORM ONE "SPIRIT SPEAR"
You will pay for that!
Watch out!
All of your accomplices will also perish!
You are the ones
who will pay for your deeds!
Zel!
Your fate is already decided.
Stop this.
Dubs. I know you aren't a fighter.
I refuse.
Sacred Treasure Lostvayne.
Sacred Treasure, release!
PHYSICAL CLONE
Form Five "Increase."
Form Four "Sunflower."
Seriously?
Second Fairy King.
I am sure you are quite powerful,
but you are nothing
compared to the current Fairy King.
My eyes! What is this dust?
ASH DUST BURIAL
It seems you picked a fight
with the wrong people!
Perish!
Combo Move!
Sphere Destruction Spear Thrust!
Really?
Is the current Fairy King's magic
so powerful?
I've never been a big fan of magic.
Zel!
I myself prefer to fight with my fists!
SPIRIT SPEAR DARRENHEART
FORM SEVEN "YGGDRA ARMOR"
Be careful, Meliodas!
I feel some strange power.
I'll finish this here!
Why are his copies attacking him?
What is this?
I am the one who made Lostvayne.
My work is like a child to me.
Well then. Let's end this.
Shall we?
Killer Fairy!
Gelda!
Staff of Imprisonment.
-Meliodas!
-Elizabeth!
Is everything cleaned up there too?
Yes.
The Demon King's sons
didn't give us much of a fight.
All that's left is the other side.
We don't need to worry about that.
Our allies will drop
the hammer of punishment.
Stop it!
Stop this! We are allies!
Did we do something bad?
Run as fast as you can!
Holy Knights! Are you okay?
What is happening?
They won't even listen to us!
I don't know the cause either.
All I know is that
they weren't a part of the last Holy War.
Hold on to me! Thunder Emperor Flash!
Gil! In front of you!
Rising Tornado!
-We made it out.
-Yeah.
That was a close one.
What on earth is happening?
Why are they attacking us
and people from their own clan?
I can't imagine why.
-What is it, Gil?
-That direction…
-Liones!
The Seven Deadly Sins,
who ruined the Holy War, and those
that joined them will be punished.
What is happening?
Fairies and Giants fought on our side
in the Holy War! We should be allies!
However, I don't recognize
any of them from the war.
So they are the ones
who weren't in the war?
I'm more concerned by that phrase
they keep muttering nonstop.
We must punish the Seven Deadly Sins
and those that joined them
in ruining the Holy War.
They don't say
we fought the Holy War together.
They say we ruined it.
What does that mean?
It won't hold any longer! It'll break!
The King's life could be in danger!
-Margaret.
-Veronica.
We need to hurry to Liones.
We'll be surrounded if we climb down!
Is there any other way?
-Calm down, both of you!
-I don't know!
There are Holy Knights in the city!
They aren't enough against this enemy.
-Look down.
-What should we do, then?
Look down!
-We're in the middle of something!
-What?
Wall!
-No way!
-Get out of the way!
-Escape!
Thank goodness! We're in Liones!
No way.
That was a direct hit. Is he okay?
This is bad! He's waking up!
Grab their weapons!
These weapons.
What is this feeling?
It feels like it is draining my power.
Don't go overboard.
Fine. Thunder Emperor Hammer!
Rising Tornado!
I told you not to go overboard.
Oh, I didn't mean to.
These weapons are amazing.
King Harlequin! Escape!
Diane. Retreat.
It appears they are under the influence
of powerful hypnosis.
And I have an idea about
the nature of this magic.
If that's it,
there's only one way to stop it.
King. Don't be too hard on them.
Okay.
POLLEN GARDEN
This is our forest!
On top of that, today is the precious
wedding day of Diane and me.
I will not allow rudeness.
Double Bow Harlit.
Ability. Range Enhancement.
Jack.
JACK
SEED OF AWAKENING
All of a sudden…
What are we doing?
They should be normal again.
No! Not yet!
We must punish the Seven Deadly Sins…
and those that joined them
in ruining the Holy War.
They weren't awakened.
It's not that.
Something they are wearing
is blocking its effects.
That makes things simple.
Snatch!
What are we doing?
This isn't our forest!
My head hurts.
Why did this happen?
Someone was controlling you.
You attacked this forest.
-What?
What happened to you?
A Fairy and a Giant appeared before us.
It was the Fairy King Dahlia, wasn't it?
The hypnosis cast on you
is a power of the Fairy King.
Then the other must be
the mast craftsman Dubs.
How did you know?
No one can mistake his work.
It was very sudden.
The Fairy King Dahlia took
control of our minds.
We grabbed the weapons
of the master craftsman Dubs.
We were driven by anger against
the Seven Deadly Sins
to do awful things. I'm so sorry!
It isn't your fault!
If that is what happened,
the others are in danger too.
It can't be helped.
Let's postpone the wedding reception.
Griamore!
What happens if you fail?
The Seven Deadly Sins.
Even though one is gone,
they are god-killers who even
defeated the Demon King.
I didn't really think of that.
I don't know much
about the Seven Deadly Sins.
I guess anything can happen.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you!
Drank it all down? You're finished!
How does Indura excretion
flavored wine taste?
It's a powerful poison
that can kill even
a Demon with a few drops!
It's tasty!
-Impossible.
-You fool.
Did you really think
that trick would work?
You're fired.
If we fail, we fail.
We have another powerful ally.
CELESTIAL REALM
There.
Brothers. Tarmiel. Sariel.
Until you are revived once again,
I shall protect the Celestial Realm.
Lord Mael.
Everyone. It's been 3,000 years.
You really…
You really are alive!
The Holy War is finished.
We don't need to hate the Demon Clan.
Don't do that! Please lift your heads.
Mael.
Please guide us.
In order to achieve your new mission.
New mission?
Thank goodness. You're awake.
Gelda.
I'm sorry, Zeldris.
In order to save you from the rubble,
I had to take a lot of blood.
I'm so ashamed.
I have no right to claim
the throne of the Demon Realm.
Don't show them
that sort of weakness.
Welcome back, King Zeldris.
They protected us.
I see.
I can't figure this out.
No matter how powerful
Dahlia and Dubs are,
they shouldn't be able
to clear the miasma.
But they have.
I feel some strange power from them.
Lord Zeldris!
Did Meliodas really destroy
the Demon King?
Yes.
I helped him do it.
What do you mean?
Why would you do that, Lord Zeldris?
I am sure you have a lot to say.
First, let's solve the problem
that lies before us.
We need to save Meliodas and Elizabeth.
Who will lend me a hand?
The traitor Meliodas?
Bloody Ellie is in the Demon Realm?
We will need their strength
to defeat Dahlia and Dubs.
I can't believe this.
I can't trust you anymore!
What was your goal for returning here?
I returned to become your king
and create a peaceful Demon Realm
without pointless fighting.
My father only saw this place
as part of his game.
To him, you were all just
breathing pawns.
And he finally tried
to make me his new vessel.
Meliodas and Elizabeth saved me from that.
That is all I have to say.
It's your decision.
Are you okay?
I'm sure Bartra
is complaining about me now.
Probably.
Anyway, what's wrong with this place?
There are not even walls for me
to break down.
I wonder if Zeldris and Gelda are okay.
Dahlia and Dubs really got us good.
About that.
I remember that Dahlia
had no interest in the Holy War.
He disappeared without getting
involved with Stigma.
Dubs also created
the Coffin of Eternal Darkness
to end the Holy War.
But suddenly, they come out
and say we ruined the Holy War?
That really is strange.
Also,
I don't remember them being so powerful.
I wonder what happened?
In order to find that answer,
we'll need to get out of here first.
Thousand God Slayer!
Well… What to do now?
I'm sure they'll come to save us soon.
I doubt that.
Ban and the others don't
know we're in the Demon Realm.
I meant Zeldris!
I don't know about that. I'm his
traitorous and oathbreaking brother.
I followed him into the Demon Realm
even though he didn't like it.
Now, now. You want Zeldris
to believe in you, right?
You need to believe in him too.
Families believe in each
other no matter what.
My father and sisters taught me that.
Let's go save everyone in
Britannia once we get out of here.
Once that's done, we can return to Liones.
Together, right?
Right. We have a lot to do.
Meliodas! Are you okay?
Hey, Zeldris!
Oh, my.
You came to save me.
Good grief. You guys
don't have the ability to feel nervous.
Don't act so shameful in front of others.
Thanks, Zeldris.
I'm glad you came.
Unbelievable. How are you my brother?
See? I was right.
My Sacred Treasure couldn't break this.
How did you do it?
You're so slow.
Weapons made by Dubs like your sword
are nullified by his magic.
I see!
I'm impressed you were able to make it
this far without being detected.
It wasn't just me.
You can't do whatever you want
to the Demon Realm!
It looks like we did.
Where were you little gnats hiding?
Were you ordered by Zeldris and Meliodas?
SPIRIT SPEAR DARRENHEART
FORM FIVE "INCREASE"
We two are now the kings
of the Demon Realm.
Bow before us!
You don't get it.
Don't you realize this is pointless?
Where did that shield come from?
Flying Saucer.
It protects the holder.
I'm quite proud of it.
Your crude weapons will
not leave a scratch on it.
What was that?
Death Scythe.
After slicing the enemy to pieces,
this work of art chops off their heads.
You two are kings?
Nonsense!
We only have one king!
The Demon King is no more!
You bunch…
follow behind him!
It's time to end this!
You are… Meliodas!
Lord Zeldris!
I was able to save Meliodas thanks to you.
You have my appreciation.
We just trusted our new king.
That is all.
Why?
Why would a traitor like you
fight for the Demon Realm?
The Holy War is over.
There is no need to spill more blood.
Lord Meliodas…
Well, then.
You two never learn!
Your Sacred Treasures
are meaningless against me.
Good reaction.
Where did that shield come from?
There's more where that came from.
Cut him to pieces!
Death Scythe!
What?
Impressive.
You were the same sort of fighter as me.
Perfect. Let's see who is stronger…
once and for all!
There's no doubt about it! I'm stronger!
They can't keep this up.
My wounds.
What's happening?
Don't worry about them.
You are Bloody Ellie!
I wish you wouldn't call me that anymore.
Didn't Zeldris tell you?
She is an ally.
Gelda.
Who are you worried about?
Do you really think your new king
and the brother
he respects would really lose?
How could he… That was my finest work.
Who forged that sword?
These swords come a dime a dozen.
Impossible!
Some common sword cannot destroy my art!
You are top-level as a craftsman,
but you are a pitiful warrior.
A great warrior can turn a common
sword into a masterpiece.
A novice can turn a masterpiece
into a common weapon.
Remember that!
Ominous Nebula!
Flying Saucer!
Those who cannot protect
themselves without tools…
don't belong…
on the battlefield!
Get over here!
It's over!
Killer Fairy!
My attack…
I see.
I guess it's my turn.
Apologies, Dahlia.
I'm sure you're a good fighter.
But I have fought some
real monsters in my day.
Hey, Meliodas.
He can't hear you.
Oh, my. Did I go overboard?
-Meliodas.
-Yes.
What was that?
Cheat Hope?
You truly have my thanks.
If you hadn't arrived,
my Kingdom would be in shambles now.
I'm sorry. It ruined your wedding.
It's fine. Don't worry about that!
We couldn't really
celebrate like that, anyway.
However, the main issue remains.
What do you mean, King?
If you have something to say, say it.
I think that Dahlia and Dubs
were controlling all of the others.
But if someone else
was controlling them…
There is a mastermind
who was controlling the second fairy
king and the master craftsman.
Who could do that?
I don't know.
However, to be honest,
I don't think those two started this.
Aren't you overthinking this?
-Right, Gil?
-Yes.
It seems like his intuition
wasn't off this time.
I need to let the others know.
The world is facing a grave threat.
Long time no see, Mael.
It seems they got you good.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
But this is a problem
for our Goddess Clan…
No, this problem affects all clans now.
Tell me. Did that really control
Dahlia and Dubs?
She might have grown senile
after a 3,000 year-long sleep.
I guess she can't tell
the enemy from an ally.
Please!
Reconsider your thoughts!
Supreme Deity!
This is our first encounter,
Seven Deadly Sins.
While sealed away in sleep,
I watched everything through
my daughter Elizabeth.
I expected nothing less from those
who put an end to the Demon King.
It seems like ordinary soldiers
were no match for you.
The one who controlled Dahlia and Dubs
was you, wasn't it?
Why are you after us?
They sacrificed much to
destroy the Demon King
and end the Holy War.
What crime is that?
Fools. It should not have ended.
You never should have ended the Holy War!
What do you mean?
Enough.
I've had enough talk.
If you want to fight, we'll give you one.
Very well.
You cannot understand
the nature of this world anyway.
Listen, my creations!
All those on the side
of the Seven Deadly Sins
are to be destroyed.
Grand Holy Knight Howzer!
Whose side are we on?
Fools! Follow your hearts! It's obvious!
Someone who calls herself a god
and looks down upon everything?
Or those who shed blood and tears
many times to protect us!
There is one answer!
Please! They are being controlled
by the Supreme Deity!
Don't kill them!
Ice Anker!
Bomb Shock!
Everyone! Avoid their vitals!
Watch out!
I'm sorry.
For my own selfish desires.
No. It isn't selfish.
They are your precious allies.
Thank you.
Let's go, Gil!
You got it, Howzer!
Crazy Wind!
Thunder Emperor Hammer!
-Combo Move! Spider Net Crash!
Everyone! Open your eyes!
No matter what…
I won't let you in!
Don't underestimate me!
We are soldiers who survived the Holy War!
Fools.
-What?
God Thunder.
I see.
You can withstand my attack.
Such power!
Even Gideon's Lightning Rod
couldn't absorb everything.
She even hit her own allies.
If she strikes again,
neither we nor the others
can survive.
One more strike then.
Don't underestimate us!
ASSAULT HUNT
That's right! We destroyed the Demon King!
How bothersome.
Stop right there!
Breaker Off!
What do you think I am?
I can only hold it for a second.
That's plenty of time! Rush Rock!
Hit her at the same time!
-You got it.
-Yeah!
-No way.
-Our attacks didn't work.
I see.
Just like magic attacks
didn't work on the Demon King,
physical attacks don't work
against the Supreme Deity.
It's no use. You're no match
for the Supreme Deity.
Then let's defeat her with magic!
True Spirit Spear Chastiefol!
Form Four!
Sunflower!
DIVINE POWER OF TEN WINGS
Not a bad attack.
Unfortunately,
the pure magic of the Sacred Tree
is far too close to my own magic.
God Thunder.
Dammit. First the Captain's old man.
Now the Princess' mom.
Who do you think you are?
You withstood my God Thunder.
Only a survivor of Purgatory
could do that.
What do you think?
A little taste of your own God Thunder!
I am the power of light.
The best you can do is leave a scratch.
Then let's see who lasts longer!
This is futile.
And yet, it seems like it's
pissing you off good!
You make me laugh.
Do you think you can win?
We might have next to no chance.
But we can't give up!
For our friend who fought with us
and died in order to protect us!
For Escanor!
We have won the present and future
together with our allies!
We won't let it be stolen for no reason!
Get out of here.
You don't belong here!
We'll be finished if that hits us!
This is your fault, Ban!
You made her really mad!
Why me? It was King!
Leave me out of this.
I'll eliminate you all.
Full Counter!
FULL COUNTER
You…
It seems you got really irritated.
You finally arrived.
Took you long enough.
Hey, Gil!
Yes. I knew he would come!
-Meliodas!
It's okay now.
Lady Elizabeth.
Buddy. Had a fun honeymoon?
I guess, but it would have been nicer
to have a bit more time.
Captain!
Why did you go on a honeymoon
during our wedding?
Didn't you say your wedding
was next month?
What? Was that right?
I've never been good with dates.
Accursed child, Meliodas.
You are the source of all evil.
You lured my daughter Elizabeth
and ruined the Holy War.
Is that all you can say?
You can't say
anything else to say, can you?
Vanish from my sight!
OMINOUS BIND
Where did that come from?
That? That isn't my doing.
Hurry up and finish her, Meliodas!
Zeldris!
Thousand God Slayer!
Combo Move!
Dark Execution!
Meliodas!
Aren't you satisfied
by killing your father?
Must you also attempt to murder
your lover's mother?
This must be painful for you.
Your real mother is the Supreme Deity.
No.
You are my only real parent.
You loved me no matter what I am.
I love you for that, father.
Elizabeth.
Please leave this world.
That is no way to speak to your mother.
You may have
given birth to me,
but there was no emotion in that.
If you loved me,
you wouldn't cast a cruel spell
like Eternal Reincarnation on me.
Thanks to Meliodas
and many of my companions,
I was able to break that wheel of fate.
Now that the curse is lifted,
I am released from the burden
of being your daughter.
Please stop causing more strife.
If you continue to hurt
my family and treasured friends
I will fight you.
You don't understand anything.
The Demon and Goddess Clan
are bound to an eternal conflict.
Continuing the Holy War
is the only way to maintain the balance
of this world.
Continue the Holy War to maintain balance?
Why is that necessary?
There's no reason.
When I was possessed by the Demon King,
I could see all of his thoughts.
The Demon King and Supreme
deity were born with a mission
to continue with an eternal conflict.
To them, the Holy War
is just a game.
Unforgivable.
An inferior creation has no right
to speak of a god's intentions!
Elizabeth!
Gelda. Thank you.
This makes us even
for the Demon King battle.
I shall destroy you
and start the Holy War anew!
Fool. If you had gained that power
surpassing the Demon King
you would have been able to defeat me!
I agree with you there.
If you hadn't given up that power,
we wouldn't have struggled like this!
But thanks to that,
we can fight together
side by side like this!
DARK PROMINENCE
Unbelievable. What a troublesome brother.
Once this is over,
you owe me a drink!
Sure!
You chose to destroy
the balance of this world.
You are bringing forth an age of Chaos!
No matter what kind of age it is,
we'll decide our fate ourselves!
We're done playing along with your games!
-Combo Move! Tyrant Killing!
Thanks.
Captain!
I expected nothing less.
-You are our hero!
-Amazing!
Meliodas!
The age of gods is over.
Well then…
Now…
Let's celebrate their wedding!
It's time for an extravagant banquet!
Father!
Hey, Hawk and Wild. You showed up.
Of course! You okay, King?
My body is as soft as a cushion! Fret not.
Meliodas? My father is calling you.
Meliodas? Where are you?
You're a weird one.
You became the king of a human kingdom.
I'm sure you'll have it tough too.
But good luck, new Demon King.
That name sounds weak. Don't call me that!
Really?
By the way,
will you and Gelda get married?
I have no interest
in the customs of humans!
Even without doing that,
my heart belongs to Gelda.
She's a good woman.
Yes.
Come to the Demon Realm sometime.
Can I?
I'm just telling you
to help repair the castle and town.
I see.
Goodbye, Meliodas.
Yeah!
The age of gods is over.
And thus, the age of Chaos
for humanity begins.
Subtitle translation by: James Burns