- [traffic rumbling]
- [♪ soft music playing]
Good evening Los Angeles...
Currently 62 degrees
in the City of Angels.
Playing nothing but
the greatest hits...
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext
[music abruptly stops]
[♪ sentimental
piano music playing]
[♪ sentimental piano
music continues]
[♪ music swells then stops]
[♪ "This Is The Day"
by The The playing]
[♪ music crackling
and oscillating]
[♪ music continues on radio]
Oh, here we go.
- You ready for this?
- What, for living with you?
- Yes ma'am.
- Er...
You know, if you wanna pull the rip
cord, you kind of have to do it soon.
Max, will you take
the next right?
- Why?
- Please.
I know where I'm going.
Hun, I have seen what happens next
and I need you to listen to me.
Please, please take
the next right.
That's right. You can see the future.
I forgot who I was dealing with.
- Should have said something.
- I have. So many times.
Jesus.
Jesus, Harriet, what,
you trying to kill us?
No, I love you. I am trying
to save you, you idiot.
I love you too. Trying
to save me from what?
Please just stop the car.
Just stop the car, Max!
Baby, just let me drive.
God, sometimes I just wish
I didn't miss you this much.
I'm sitting right...
[car horn blares]
♪ This is the day your
life will surely change ♪
♪ This is the day when
things fall into... ♪
[♪ music distorts and fades]
- [alarm ringing]
- [phone buzzing]
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[dog whimpering]
[dog whines]
[sighs] I know.
[shower running]
[sound compresses]
[muffled sounds of
headphones thudding]
[extremely muffled snapping]
[♪ "Me and My Shadow"
by Peggy Lee playing]
♪ and my ♪
♪ shadow ♪
- ♪ strolling down the avenue ♪
-  [man, muffled] Thanks. Bye.
♪ Me ♪
♪ and my ♪
♪ shadow ♪
♪ Not a soul to tell
my troubles to ♪
♪ And when it's... ♪
- Morning, Headphones.
- Morning, Delores.
[ ♪ soft music playing]
[woman] How can I
start over without him?
Sometimes I'm angry. I
pick a fight with a ghost,
and then I feel guilty about it.
I feel you, Anne. And thank you.
Loving someone you
lose, loving in general,
can sometimes feel like
having a mental illness.
It's just not covered
by health insurance.
[group chuckles]
So does anyone have anything
else to say before we wrap up?
Okay then, uh, let's call it.
Loss might be forever,
but grief is only temporary.
Exactly. Alright,
good week you guys.
Hey, if there's anything I can do to
make the room more comfortable for you.
No, it's good. It's
good. Thank you.
Two years is coming up.
Yeah, it is.
- You taking your meds?
- Yeah.
Any more seizures?
No, no. Avoiding all triggers.
Music in general, so...
Okay. We know it's not
just about the music.
You're making a conscious choice
to hide out in your grief.
I get it.
Okay.
Just take care of yourself.
I will. Thank you.
[cars honking]
[car honks]
Shit.
[ ♪"Pump Up the Jam by
Technotronic playing from car]
I'm so sorry.
Really?
- [sharp whistling]
- ♪ While your feet are... ♪
[♪ music distorts]
[♪ music crackling
and oscillating]
- [♪ music continues at party]
- [partygoers chattering]
♪ And you'll find
out if you do that ♪
- Is she that high?
- No. No. This is all her.
- Hi.
- I love you.
- Love you too, you freak.
Be right back.
♪ Get your booty
on the floor... ♪
Where you goin', Hare?
Harriet, come dance with me.
- Sam, I miss you.
- What?
[music stops]
[driver] Lady?
Lady? Are you okay?
[muffled] What's happening?
Talk to me. Are you okay? Do I need
to call an ambulance? What's going on?
- What's going on?
- I'm fine.
You sure you're okay?
I got the worst of it, I'm
fi... I'm gonna call it a day.
Yeah, call it a day, and then tomorrow
I get a call from your lawyer?
Can I get a photo of
your insurance card?
[cars honking]
- [person] Let's go!
- Can I get your...?
Yeah, I'll give you my number, and
you call me, and we can sort it out.
- Okay.
- I'm really sorry.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Speak.
- I have to talk to you, is it safe?
[sighs] It's safe.
[♪ "Don't Push It Don't Force
It" by Leon Haywood playing]
Hi.
♪ I'm ready ♪
- I didn't mean to interrupt.
- Yes, you did.
♪ Don't push it, don't force
it Let it happen naturally ♪
- Such good advice.
- What?
The lyrics. Leon Haywood.
This song is a monster.
♪ Don't push it, don't force
it Let it happen naturally ♪
Your EQ is off.
♪ It will surely happen
if love was meant to be ♪
That's better.
♪ Patience isn't
my best virtue ♪
What?
I had a Max moment.
Shocker.
No, like a bad one in public. One of our
songs was blaring out of some guy's car.
Did it get weird?
- Yeah, I passed out in the street.
- Where'd it take you?
Halloween, 2018. You had that
party. You were dressed like Prince.
I was?
Yeah, but I couldn't play out the memory.
I had to unplug and get out of there.
Oh my God, 2018. I was still
seeing that guy Shane, right?
- Morris, I passed out in traffic.
- He sucked.
Well, relax. You're here
now, okay, in one piece.
You've been really good about
not having spells in public.
They're not spells.
Okay. Whatever they
are, you're fine.
TikTok still rules the world, and
I'm still single as a dollar bill,
so the space time continuum
seems to be intact.
It's gonna be two
years tomorrow.
I know, baby.
But maybe it's time to start
living in the present tense again.
You know I can't like this.
So you're just gonna spend the rest
of your life looking for a song?
What if I can save him?
What if I can change that moment
and the accident never happened?
I would listen to every record
that ever existed to find it.
How about
no time travel for you tonight?
Just give yourself a break.
He won't turn right and
you won't stop the car.
I know, I know.
I can't seem to change
anything he does.
That's... I do hope
that you figure it out.
I miss the girl that
I met freshman year,
who used to take me so far
out, underground karaoke clubs,
drag queen bingo, raves in
an abandoned dumpling palace.
Oh my god. Don't. No.
Are they new?
They are.
- Can I borrow some, try them?
- Sure.
♪ ... push it, don't force
it Let it happen naturally ♪
I'm spinning at Counterpoint
Records tomorrow night.
Might be cool if you roll
through. I'll play the safe stuff.
Yeah. Yeah.
Live, baby. Live.
Maybe.
Okay, great. Pass
some of these out.
- At the library?
- We'll take what we can get.
Cool.
The missing record will
reveal itself. Okay?
Thank you.
[light switch clicks]
[♪ atmospheric music playing]
[♪ "Loud Places" by
Jamie XX playing]
[♪ music crackling
and oscillating]
[♪ music continues at festival]
[Harriet breathing heavily]
- ♪ I go to loud places ♪
- [crowd cheering]
♪ To search for someone ♪
♪ To be quiet with ♪
♪ Who will take me home ♪
- Production's good.
- Well, I came for Kendrick, not this shit.
I like it.
Better than the shoegaze shitshow
you usually make me listen to.
How many times have I come to see
you play disco and house music?
As many times as you wanted
to. 'Cause it's good shit.
'Cause you can hear the production.
'Cause you can dance to it.
Like you can to this.
Yacht rock has great production. Some of
the best engineered albums of all time.
Sonic wallpaper, like eating a
ham sandwich on Wonder Bread.
People write dissertations
on Steely Dan.
I'll accept that, 'cause
Donald Fagen was a genius.
You're annoying.
I like ham sandwiches.
[person in crowd whistling]
May I?
No one ever told you not to
take anything from strangers?
I'm Max. Now we're
not strangers.
That's my spliff, by
the way. You're welcome.
Thanks.
- What?
- Mad Max.
I've never actually
even seen the original.
It's all about Tina
Turner in Thunderdome.
We'll watch it together.
- Will we? What makes you say that?
- I can see the future.
Oh, can you?
So what happens next?
I'll follow you into that crowd,
and actually start to believe
in love at first sight.
Which until now I thought
only happened in movies.
- Or Shakespeare.
Or most romantic era poetry,
Lord Byron, et cetera.
Sorry.
- ♪ And I don't know how ♪
- You're very sure of yourself.
♪ To follow you ♪
- So how does this end up?
- [♪ song fades into somber piano music]
Tragically.
Well.
Well?
Thanks for the hit.
[♪ piano music fades
back into song]
What in the name of Luther
Vandross just happened?
I just met the guy who's
gonna change my life.
You in your bag.
I can't hold you.
So that's it? You're just
gonna like, let him walk away?
He's totally feeling it.
Wait for it.
Hey, future girl.
What's your name?
Harriet.
Well, Harriet, you coming?
Damn.
[♪ music swells]
- [music stops]
- [vinyl record player crackling]
[sighs]
[♪ "Play it on My Radio" by
Niki and the Dove playing]
[sound of pen writing]
♪ There's a song that
I'm looking for ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Nobody plays it nowadays ♪
[phone ringing]
[clears throat]
Hi, Mom.
Yeah, I'm just getting
up for work. I...
I know. I'm fine.
Yeah, everything's good.
I'm good. I'm back on track.
I think I'm gonna get
back in the studio soon.
How are you? How's New York?
[♪ melancholy music playing]
Yeah, I was thinking Thanksgiving, but
I'm just about to run out the door.
Can I actually call you back?
Love you too.
Just kind of feels like I'm on
autopilot, you know? Like...
I mean, I cried more over
my dog than I did my dad.
I'm not sure if that's right
or wrong, but just what I felt.
Thank you Robert.
Who else would like to
share anything today?
[person coughs]
I would.
Oh, okay, Harriet.
What's on your mind?
Um...
Today marks two years since
my boyfriend Max passed away.
It's a big milestone.
[♪ sentimental
piano music playing]
Yeah, it's just that I
see him all the time.
It's just so easy to be
pulled back into the past.
But I think I know what I need to do to
fix it, so I'm just gonna focus on that.
- [door opens]
- I don't know, maybe I wouldn't be, um...
standing here feeling miserable
and sounding ridiculous. So...
Okay, um, how do you mean?
I...
[chairs crashing]
Awesome.
[Dr. Bartlet] Don't
worry about those.
We've got some open seats here.
- Harriet, continue.
- I'm good. I'm finished. Thank you.
Okay, um, well thanks for that.
- [Harriet exhales]
- Anyone else?
Anyone else?
New guy?
[whispers] Um...
[♪ "Next To You (Marcy Rising
edit)" by Locussolus playing]
- [muffled] Oh!
- [Harriet grunts]
- You okay?
- Yes.
Let me help you.
Sorry. Thank you.
- Yeah, of course.
- Such a klutz.
Happens to the worst of us.
- [chuckles] You okay?
- Yeah, I just...
Ego bruised.
What's... what's all this?
Uh, they're uh... they're
trying to save the record store.
- Ah. They're an endangered species.
- They are.
Thanks.
Hey, I'm sorry for interrupting
you in there earlier.
Oh God, no. It's the first time
I've said anything in there,
so I'm sure you saved me
from sounding like an idiot.
No.
Thank you.
Sure.
Sorry. Have we met?
- Not that I know of.
- Right. Sorry.
Um, thank you.
[♪ atmospheric music playing]
[phone dings]
[♪ "To Turn You On (Disco Punisher
Remix)" by Roxy Music playing]
- Hey.
- [store owner] Hey, Headphones.
[Morris] Sound good?
So why are you so
afraid of bass lately?
- What are we listening to?
- Uh, you're better than that.
- I know it's Roxy, but it's an edit.
- Look in the 12 inch promo section.
Tom, where's the 12
inch promo section?
You're right there.
It's just on your left.
Yes.
You came.
Figured I'd come to the rescue.
Okay, Batman.
[laughs]
No, I mean I can at
least buy a few records.
Do you work here?
No. My friend's DJ-ing as a
favor. He knows the owner.
My parents used to listen
to this album over and over.
It's a classic.
- And I love how music can do that.
- What?
Pull you back to
some moment in time.
Yep.
Excuse the nostalgia.
No, you're standing
neck deep in nostalgia.
- I like this version.
- I know. I'm actually looking for it.
- Is this it?
- Yes.
Tom, do you have
another copy of this?
That's a limited edition.
We just got the one.
I guess it's mine.
Do you even have
a record player?
[chuckles]
Yes.
Wow.
I can't believe you're
actually doing this to me.
Okay, um...
- What about joint custody?
- Of the record?
Of the record.
If you, um
give me your number, maybe we can discuss
the details of the custody agreement.
Oh, we're doing this.
Expect a call from my lawyers.
- [locks phone]
- Will do.
I will go now.
Okay.
Hey buddy. If you're gonna steal that,
you're gonna have to pay for it first.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh, how much is this?
[Tom] To you? Fifteen bucks.
- [man] Keep the change.
- [Tom] Cheers.
[♪ soft music playing]
[sound decompresses]
[♪ somber music plays]
[♪ "Gaps in the Clouds"
by Yellow Days playing]
[♪ music crackling
and oscillating]
[♪ music continues on speaker]
- ♪ All this time I was just... ♪
♪ ...running around ♪
♪ A beautiful mind
between those eyes ♪
You really gonna leave
me here all alone?
[Max] You gonna let
me go in by myself?
What kind of girlfriend are you?
- Max, I have to tell you something.
- You love me madly?
- Seriously.
- It doesn't get any better than this?
♪ Ooh life ♪
What were you gonna tell me?
I'll tell you next time.
♪ Oh, I've been dancing
for quite a while ♪
♪ It's cold out but
those blue eyes they... ♪
[music stops]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[man] If you wanna see your record alive,
meet me at Civil Coffee at four PM.
What... Who is this?
It's David.
From the record store, uh,
the grief support group.
I was, I was joking.
- Hi.
- Did I wake you up?
No, sorry. [Scoffs]
- Yeah. No. Unless you don't want to.
- No, I-I do. I'll, I'll see you at four.
Um...
Bring proof of life.
I'm sorry. It's something I think
they say in hostage situations.
Yeah.
- Uh, okay.
- Okay. I'll...
- I'll see you then.
- I guess, bye.
Bye.
[ ♪"Sémaphore" by
Requin Chagrin playing]
[entry bell rings]
- Hi. Hi.
- Hi. Sorry.
- What are you listening to?
- What?
- What are you, what are you listening to?
- Uh, nothing.
I can hear the music
from your headphones.
I mean, I'm just uh, shuffling
through random Spotify playlists.
Oh, you gonna keep
those on the whole time?
Yeah. I kind of have to.
- Okay.
- Sorry. It's a medical thing.
What kind of medical thing?
Um...
I actually don't know how to
talk about it. It's complicated.
Okay.
Well, I hate talking anyway.
I'll just say stupid shit.
- So maybe keep the headphones on.
- Right. And just sit here awkwardly.
Perfect. I'll just stare at you while
you drink coffee and listen to music.
- Make it super weird.
- Good.
As for me, I'm great. My life
is perfect. Figured it all out.
Mm. Right. Same, actually.
You will not find someone more
functional and well adjusted.
Hence all the counseling
with Dr. Bartlet.
- How long have you been doing that for?
- Just since everything.
I was in an accident with my
boyfriend. Well, was my boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
Just can't seem to pull
myself back together.
What about you?
My parents.
My mom got sick and passed away.
A few months later my
dad went in his sleep.
It was beautiful in this kind of sad
way. Like he couldn't live without her.
But it's fine 'cause I always
wanted to be an orphan.
I'm joking.
- Take good care of her.
- Oh, I will.
[ ♪ " Running" by Helado
Negro playing from headphones]
It's good.
I'll send it to you.
♪ You got me running,
running, running... ♪
- [sharp whistling]
- [♪ funky music playing in coffee shop]
- Sorry. Sorry.
- What?
[sound compresses]
[♪ "Music Sounds Better with
You" by Neil Francis playing]
[♪ music crackling
and oscillating]
[♪ music continues]
I don't know. It's, uh, isn't
looking good for you, is it?
No, it is not.
Yep. You are absolute toast.
- Ah!
- I wish I didn't have to do this.
What you doing? Where're you
going? No, I like this song.
[music stops]
[sound compresses]
- Sorry.
- You okay?
I'm really sorry.
[♪ somber music playing]
[♪ "Make Me Believe in
You" by Patti Jo playing]
[Morris] So you just ran off?
[Harriet] Well, yeah. I didn't wanna have
a fit in front of him and freak him out.
So you had a fit in front of him,
freaked him out, and then ran off.
Well yeah, when you put it like that,
it doesn't sound quite so rational.
Well, not your best move. You could
have talked your way out of it.
And say what? "Hey,
I travel back in time
every time a song reminds
me of my boyfriend."
How am I supposed to be
with someone else like this?
It's time to move on.
Sell his Hi-Fi, the records. Dump his
busted-ass chair out on the street.
See this new guy.
- Max would want that.
- No, he wouldn't.
You lost yourself
when you lost him.
Asshole.
Asshole?
All I've been is supportive.
Lately I just feel sorry for you.
- I get it. You're sick of my shit.
- Yes, I am fed up with your shit.
You... you're pissing away your life and
talent. You could've been the next...
Alan Parsons.
Morris, I was never
gonna be Alan Parsons.
Okay.
Girl, I'm here for you,
but I'm the last man standing.
You've pushed everyone else away.
You gotta accept reality, Hare.
Do you like this guy?
Yeah, I just...
It feels like I'm cheating.
Like, I'm not trying to be insensitive,
but you can't cheat on a dead guy.
Sorry, but it's, it's true.
Yeah. But it won't be true
when I find the record,
and I stop him from
buying the chair.
To say I'm concerned about
you is such an understatement.
Do you have a gig coming up?
Yeah. Bears in Space.
You need a plus one?
[♪ atmospheric music playing]
[entry bell rings]
[David] Edie?
[Edie] Yeah?
You wanna ask those customers
downstairs if they need any help?
No, not really.
Cool. I have an idea then.
When this place goes under,
you can get a job at Starbucks
and pay down your college debt.
I have a better idea.
We sell this place and then
we let it become a Starbucks.
Or we could spend every day
here, haunted by our parents.
I'm not having this conversation
again. We're not selling.
I could pay off my college debt.
You could move back up to SF.
Okay. You want to deal
with the probate court?
Pass.
I'm going to the desert
with everyone next week.
You could shut the store, live
a little, and come with us.
No, thank you. But go have fun.
Can't tell if you're
being passive aggressive.
Neither can I. Look, you do you,
but you're closing up tonight. Okay?
Fine.
- How's the counseling thing going?
- Good.
- You're welcome to join, you know.
- I'm good.
There was this girl there...
Mm-hmm?
Please don't do the
wounded bird thing again.
All right. I appreciate
the reminder. Thank you.
Anytime.
- [customer] Can I get some help, please?
- And that's all you.
- Smile.
- Don't tell me what to do.
Love you too.
Listen, there's a reason why,
in more than a few languages,
the word for love and the word for
suffering are one and the same.
Think about that.
Everybody gets it.
Everybody's experienced it, so much
so that they have one word for it.
You know, we're lucky we have two.
Is that lucky? I don't know. Anyway
either way, we're not alone
on this planet in our group...
Hey.
- Doing okay?
- Look, I...
Yeah, I'm, I'm so sorry
about the coffee shop.
You deserve so much
better than that.
I know you're going through
your own everything right now.
It's no worries at all.
Will you let me make it up to you?
I can do way better, I promise.
Sure.
[♪ "Ooh I Love It" by The
Salsoul Orchestra playing]
I will take these off inside.
Um, it's called a line darling.
The back is down toward Canada.
Oh, we're on Morris's list.
- Name?
- Harriet Gibbons.
You're not in
Silver Lake anymore.
- We don't live in Silver Lake.
- Sure you don't. Have fun.
Thank you.
♪ We got a good rhythm goin'
and the time is right ♪
- [crowd cheering]
- [♪ music continues]
♪ We're going up and down
and 'round and 'round ♪
♪ We ain't gonna stop
'til we shock this town ♪
♪ Don't stop Keep
it coming y'all ♪
♪ Don't stop Just
keep it coming ♪
♪ We're gonna keep doin'
it 'til we get it right ♪
it if it takes all night ♪
♪ Oh no no ♪
♪ Don't stop For sure ♪
♪ Don't you love it don't
you love it Ooh I love it ♪
you love it Oh I love it ♪
♪ Don't you love it don't
you love it Ooh I love it ♪
you love it Oh I love it ♪
♪ Love it when you shake it
hate it when you take it ♪
♪ Love it when you wanna
take a love break ♪
♪ Love break, love
break, love break... ♪
- Hi!
- Hey!
David, Morris. Morris, David.
I didn't get a chance meet
you at the record store.
- Right.
- Yeah. That's my bad.
- Lovely to meet you.
- You too.
Girl, that boy is fine.
- Have fun!
- Okay.
[♪ "Feel the Music (feat.
Celeda)" by Hifi Sean playing]
♪ Feel the music, take control ♪
♪ Of your mind, body, and soul ♪
♪ Your spirit is tight,
release the fight ♪
♪ Come on and dance
with all your might ♪
♪ And make me feel the music ♪
♪ Make me feel the music ♪
Quite the dancer.
- It's all those years of training.
- Seriously?
No.
[Harriet laughs]
So let me get this straight.
You have to wear headphones everywhere
except record stores and drag discos.
I know. I don't make sense.
Why? What's up with you?
I guess I'm
haunted by music.
Haunted by music? Okay.
- Do you work in music or something?
- I used to. That was the original plan.
Well, I don't make sense either
so. We both have that going for us.
Really? You seem to
make sense to me.
I just put what was
my life on hold to
take care of the mess that my
parents left for my sister and me.
Sounds fun.
- So fun.
- Mm-hmm.
[phone dings]
This was nice.
What?
I don't know. Tonight.
Whatever this is.
[car pulling up]
This is me.
Oh, you're leaving?
Yeah. I mean quit while
we're ahead, right?
- No, I have work in the morning.
- You're always running off.
Night.
Thanks for setting
the night on fire.
[stammers] I dunno
why I said that.
Night.
Hi, for Harriet?
What's up?
[♪ ethereal music playing]
Shit.
[vinyl record crackling]
[♪ "Say Yes to Heaven"
by Lana del Rey playing]
♪ If you dance I'll dance ♪
♪ And if you don't
I'll dance anyway ♪
♪ Give peace a chance ♪
♪ Let the fear you
have fall away ♪
♪ I've got my eye on you ♪
♪ Say yes to heaven ♪
♪ Say yes to me ♪
♪ If you go I'll stay ♪
♪ You come back
I'll be right here ♪
♪ Like a barge at sea ♪
♪ In the storm I stay clear ♪
♪ 'Cause I've got
my mind on you ♪
♪ I got my mind on you ♪
My husband, before he died, said
this thing that stuck with me.
He said, "Live your dash."
On his tombstone is the date of his
birth and the date of his death.
And in between is the dash.
I don't know, maybe it's
a little NutraSweet but,
I always thought there were
pretty decent words to live by.
Hey.
- You have any plans tonight?
- Do you have plans tonight?
- [chuckles] Go ahead.
- No, I don't have plans.
Good. Neither do I.
Good.
- You up for something?
- Yeah.
Great.
Is this yours?
It is now.
[Harriet gasps]
Holy shit. This is incredible.
Yeah. It's just been
collecting dust in the garage
so I thought I'd finally
take it out for spin.
Wanna go for a ride?
Yeah!
Hop in.
Where are we going?
I'm not sure yet.
[engine roars]
[engine purring]
This move always work?
What do you mean?
Pull up in a fancy vintage
car, drive a girl around LA...
- Yes, exactly.
- Every time?
- Let's listen to some music.
- We don't have to listen to anything.
- [radio clicks]
- [♪ jazz music playing]
Nope.
- [radio clicks]
- [♪ upbeat mariachi music playing]
[♪ "I'm Like a Bird" by
Nelly Furtado playing]
♪ You're beautiful,
that's for sure ♪
♪ You'll never ever fade ♪
♪ You're lovely, but
it's not for sure ♪
♪ That I won't ever change ♪
- ♪ And though my love is rare ♪
- [David tunelessly joins in]
[both singing] ♪ Though
my love is true ♪
♪ I'm like a bird,
I only fly away ♪
♪ I don't know
where my soul is ♪
where my home is ♪
♪ And baby all I need
for you to know is ♪
♪ I'm like a bird,
I only fly away ♪
♪ I don't know
where my soul is ♪
- ♪ I don't know where my home is ♪
- [Harriet] Right.
- [both laughing]
- ♪ Your faith in me brings me to tears ♪
♪ Even after all
these years end ♪
What?
Will you pull over?
- Right now?
- Yeah.
- [keys jingle]
- [engine stops]
- [radio clicks on]
- [radio DJ] 101.7 KLAU.
[♪ "Heybb!" by binki
playing on radio]
[♪ music crackling
and oscillating]
♪ Hey baby Hey! Hey! ♪
♪ You got me feelin'
punch-drunk crazy so crazy ♪
Oh my God! Oh my God!
What?
- What's the matter?
- No. I'm sorry.
- [music stops]
- [David] Harriet. Hey. Hey.
- Oh God.
- What happened?
I have to go.
- I-I should take you to a doctor.
- [panting] I'm fine.
Harriet. Harriet! Harriet, wait.
- I...
- Are you okay?
[heavy breathing]
No.
Let me just take you home.
Okay.
[David muffled] Harriet.
[sound decompresses]
[dog collar rattling]
- [dog panting]
- [light switch clicks]
[dog whining]
[♪ ambient music playing]
- I didn't realize you had a dog.
- I inherited him.
David, this is just...
This is just too
fucking difficult. I...
I had figured out how
to live with this.
[crying] I had sealed off my apartment. I
got a job at a library. It was all safe.
It was all safe and...
Hey, hey, hey. Hey. Come here.
Two years ago my boyfriend Max
and I got in a car accident.
And I suffered a traumatic head
injury and I was in a coma for a week.
- And ever since then...
- So that's why that just happened.
- Sort of.
- I assume you've seen doctors about this.
Psychiatrists, neurologists,
multiple psychiatric evaluations,
- therapy, everything.
- And what did they say to do?
Doesn't matter. Nothing works.
Remember when you said certain
songs pull you back into the past?
Yeah, we have that in common.
It's just for me,
it's different.
Certain songs pull me back to when Max
and I heard them for the first time.
For the duration of the
song, I am back in the past,
literally reliving my life.
So you have these episodes, where you
hallucinate that you're back in the past?
David, I know how this sounds.
I turned off the radio
and so the episode ended?
I turned off the song in the past
so that I could come back early.
Right.
That's the headphones.
Yeah. 'Cause I could be
triggered by any source,
anytime, anywhere, so they stopped me
from going back unless it's my choice.
What is all this?
[♪ ambient music playing]
It's a list of songs from
certain times in our life.
That's him?
Yeah.
He's a good looking dude.
So you just sit in this room,
go back in time and hang out
with your dead boyfriend?
Look, I have a
busy day tomorrow.
David, please. I
really like you.
And I like you too.
Maybe you just need some
time to figure things out.
[door shuts]
[sobbing]
[♪ "Friday I'm In Love" by
Phoebe Bridgers playing]
♪ I don't care if
Monday's blue ♪
♪ Tuesday's grey
and Wednesday too ♪
♪ Thursday I don't
care about you ♪
♪ It's Friday, I'm in love ♪
♪ Monday you can fall apart ♪
♪ Tuesday, Wednesday,
break my heart ♪
♪ Thursday doesn't even start ♪
♪ It's Friday, I'm in love ♪
♪ Saturday, wait ♪
♪ Sunday always comes too late ♪
♪ Friday, never hesitate ♪
♪ I don't care if
Monday's black ♪
♪ Tuesday, Wednesday
heart attack ♪
♪ Ooh Thursday
never looking back ♪
♪ It's Friday, I'm in love ♪
[♪ "Powa" by Tune-Yards playing]
[♪ music crackling
and oscillating]
[♪ music continues]
- Maximilian.
- Yes, my love?
♪ Rebel, rebel, no ♪
- ♪ Lightening dances in my head ♪
- What do you wanna do today?
- All of it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- What exactly does that entail?
Um...
Uh, walking with you and the
dog to get a cup of coffee.
[grunts] Staring
at you adoringly.
That's a good boy.
And uh, reminding you just how
offensively attractive you are.
- What do you think happens to us?
- What do you mean?
Do we wind up together?
Huh? You're the
Bonnie to my Clyde.
I don't think it worked
out so well for them.
- [phone locks]
- What? What are you talking about?
Come here.
I love you. Let's
just have a Sunday.
We're moving in together.
You're gonna mix my record.
We'll wake up, smell the
coffee, enjoy the moment.
Rinse and repeat. It'll
be great. We'll do it all.
We'll just, let's just do
it one day at a time. Okay?
What's wrong?
Okay.
Who are you selling them to?
Some tech bro from NorCal
who's overpaying for them.
I told him they were David
Mancuso's alternates at the Loft.
Were they?
Could have been. I got 'em
from some guy in New York
who said he'd been
to the Loft, so...
Do you think Max and I
would still be together?
I don't know. I mean...
I loved him but the dude
kind of beat to his own drum.
Yeah, he did.
You didn't get a chance
to really figure out
whether you were right
for each other or not.
If I hadn't been
such a dick that day,
then there wouldn't have
been an accident at all.
That's just stupid. So what?
This whole fantasy is you torturing
yourself over your own guilt?
What did you ever do wrong, except
make his shitty music sound good?
- His music wasn't shitty.
- Don't.
Hot as all hell, but he was like
a bush league Mumford and Sons.
Like a distant cousin.
You're not the gatekeeper
of musical taste.
Yes I am.
I went to his shows. I
wanted to kill myself.
I loved them.
Agree to disagree.
What would your life be like if you
somehow changed the past and saved Max?
Even if he was the one,
would he want to be with
this person you've become?
But if I find the right
song and he doesn't die,
then I wouldn't be this
broken version of myself.
- I'm talking about reality, Harriet.
- So am I.
David has just thrown this
huge wrench in my life.
I had structured
things so specifically.
- In order not to live your life?
- In order to keep things in order.
Tell me you didn't screw
things up with David.
We kissed.
So there's hope for you.
And then I screwed
everything up.
- Wait, did you tell him about this?
- Yeah.
[scoffs] Girl. Come on.
You're a straight up saboteur.
Oh my God. Says the guy whose longest
relationship is the course of the night.
- I made it past brunch.
- Mm-hmm.
I love you.
We've done some
serious time together.
I love you too.
[♪ soft music playing]
David is an opportunity.
You can't just go back and
get it if you let it pass.
You met someone new, like
a really cool, nice guy.
How is this a bad thing?
Thank you for meeting me.
Sure.
At least now you know
what you're getting into.
Right. You travel through time.
David, I know this all
sounds and seems insane,
but I promise I am
really, really trying.
I've never been good at
paying attention to red flags.
And I know I am a walking red
flag. I am very aware of that.
I really don't wanna like you.
I really don't wanna
like you either.
[♪ calming music playing]
Where are we?
You'll see.
Seriously, what is this?
[woman] David?
- Hey.
- Hey. It's been a minute.
- How have you been?
- Good. Yeah. How's Edie?
- Oh you know, she's always good.
- Hm.
- Oh. This is Harriet.
- Hey.
Hi.
That's good. Thanks.
- Thanks.
- [woman] Have fun.
[elevator starting]
[♪ ambient music playing]
How do I look?
Great. You look great.
- Oh my God.
- You'll fit right in.
[Harriet laughs]
[♪ atmospheric music playing]
Thank you so much for this.
- What's up?
- This is your place?
Yeah. My sister and I,
we grew up upstairs.
[♪ sentimental music playing]
Wasn't there an old
record player here?
- What record player?
- The Garrard.
How do you know about that?
You told me about it.
I did?
Yeah.
It's upstairs. I'll show you.
It was my parents.
I kept what was left
of their records.
These?
Yeah.
Are they all from the store?
Yeah. All of these.
You... Are you okay?
Yeah. I just... Are
these all of them?
Yeah.
[Harriet gasps]
Oh my god.
Oh my God. This is it.
This... This is it.
- What are you talking about?
- David, I've been here before.
- No, not again with this.
- No, please.
- I don't believe in time travel, Harriet.
- I know.
Please, please just trust
me. Please I need...
I just, I just need ten
minutes of your trust.
- N-no. Okay. I'm just gonna take you home.
- I just have to try something.
Where's the best hiding
place in the store?
If I could hide something
where only you would find it.
Please. David, please. I am asking
you to suspend your disbelief for me.
For us. For ten minutes.
I think I can actually
prove this to you.
Okay.
There's a... old school desk next to
the register. It's been there forever.
Okay.
Go down to the desk.
Look in the drawer.
[♪ music swells then fades]
[vinyl record crackling]
[♪ "Fantasia in D Minor"
by Mozart playing]
[♪ music crackling
and oscillating]
[♪ music continues
playing in store]
Oh, Hare. Come check this out.
I found it. I can't believe
I found it. I can save you.
From what?
- From this chair.
- Oh, I love this chair.
- We're not getting it. Absolutely not.
- It's a great chair. 30's Art Deco.
No. We're not getting it.
Come on, let's just go.
But it's so comfy. Um, how
much does the chair cost?
- I think around 450.
- See, it's too much. Please come on.
There are a million other stupid chairs
that we can get. Come on. Let's just go.
- Let me see if I can knock it down.
- No. Honestly, it's fine. Please.
Tom darling, what's the best
we could do on the club chair?
I'm not getting it for you.
- I'm getting it for me.
- 380.
David. I am begging you.
Who the hell is David?
No... look, I will buy you
any chair that you want.
Then we'll have our entire lines to
get a any chair. Please just leave it.
What's up with you?
I'm getting the chair.
[Max sighs]
Well, what's the
word, hummingbird?
- Heading out.
- Will we see you next weekend?
Probably will stay up north.
- See you later, Dad.
- Take care, son.
Can we say 300?
Tom? Can you bring the Samsung?
- Can I help you?
- I need an old desk. An old school desk.
Yeah. We got some
desks right there.
- Hare, what are you doing?
- One sec.
[♪ music crackles and distorts]
[Harriet grunts]
"What's the word, hummingbird?"
It worked?
How?
Your mom had silver hair in a braid.
She called your Dad "Tom, darling."
He called her angel.
You saw them?
Yeah.
Can you take me back there?
What do you mean?
To the past with you,
so I can see them one last time.
David, I wish I could but I, I'm
not in control of any of this.
I don't know what I'm doing.
You traveled back in time.
Yeah, but I'm just visiting.
I'm wasting time. Max still buys the
chair. The accident still happens.
You just changed the past.
No. I can only change
what I do in the past.
I haven't been able to change what
anyone else does or what happens to them.
[♪ soft ambient music playing]
I knew I had seen you before.
What?
I saw you back there.
You were headed back
up north. You...
You looked so good.
So happy.
I saw you.
You saw me.
[♪ atmospheric music playing]
[♪ "New Romance" by
Beach House playing]
♪ Days go by ♪
♪ No reply, the smoke
high on the avenue ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪ know that you're not ♪
♪ gonna leave it anyway ♪
♪ Pick me up, I
know you're close ♪
♪ The headlights
running down the wall ♪
- [engine stops]
- [music stops]
- [David] Hey.
- [Edie] How was the drive?
Easy.
♪ Live your life with arms wide open
Today is where your book begins ♪
♪ The rest is still unwritten ♪
That was... special.
Okay...
Harriet's up.
- Harriet!
- I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
- [person] Come on, Harriet. Come on.
- I can choose for you.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You got this.
Sorry in advance.
[clears throat]
♪ I'm not in love ♪
[group cheers]
♪ So don't forget it ♪
♪ It's just a silly
phase I'm going through ♪
♪ And just because ♪
♪ I call you up ♪
♪ Don't get me wrong, don't
think you've got it made ♪
♪ I'm not in love ♪
♪ No, no ♪
It's your turn. It's you.
♪ It's because ♪
- Come up. It's your turn now, please.
- No, no.
Get up there. Come on.
You. Up, up.
Come on, okay?
Up. It's you. It's you.
I'm out.
- Okay.
- No. Please, please.
♪ But then again ♪
♪ That doesn't mean you
mean that much to me ♪
Oh, this is high.
[clears throat]
♪ So if I call you ♪
♪ Don't make a fuss ♪
♪ Don't tell your friends
about the two of us ♪
- You can.
- Charming.
- Yeah.
♪ I'm not in love, no, no ♪
- Sing with me, sing with me.
- No.
[singing falsetto]
♪ It's because ♪
- Yeah. And that... that's a wrap.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Oh wow.
Okay. Tough act to swallow.
How do we skip the ads? Oh shit.
How do we skip ads again?
[♪ upbeat ad jingle playing]
[♪ music crackling and oscillating]
- ♪ 1-877-Kars4Kids ♪
♪ K-A-R-S, Kars 4 Kids ♪
- What?
♪ Donate your car today ♪
What's that look?
♪ 1-877-Kars4Kids ♪
Can I ask you a weird question?
Yeah. Weird away.
If something happened
to you, something bad,
and I could, I could stop it. But
it would mean we would never meet.
Would you want me to?
What?
If I could save your life but
we wouldn't know each other.
Max, please. Just
answer the question.
No. No, I wouldn't
wanna never know you.
I don't know what that life would look
like. I don't. No. I like our life.
Well what if, what
if it were me?
What if something
happened to me?
- Nothing would happen to you.
- Max.
No. I would want you to live.
- And we would never meet.
- Well, then you're gonna live.
[♪ sentimental music playing]
You have to live.
'Cause I love you madly.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- What happened?
You fell and hit your
head pretty hard.
Where's the dog?
Don't worry. My sister has him.
God, this is just gonna keep
happening over and over.
And I think I know
what I have to do.
What?
If I do it, I lose you too.
Hey, Disco.
Is she okay?
I got her home.
You okay?
Holding on to all this
doesn't keep them alive.
Let's sell this place.
Seriously?
Yeah, you were right.
It's time.
[♪ ethereal music playing]
[dog whines]
Does not remembering
mean it didn't happen?
I mean, what about
us? What if...
If we can't remember? Does that mean
we just go back to being strangers?
I don't know.
We still lived it.
This moment is real.
Whether we remember it or not.
And we met before.
Twice.
I hope some part of
you remembers me.
I hope so too.
I don't want to lose you.
[♪ somber music playing]
Maybe it won't change anything.
Maybe.
Like, nothing changes
and you're stuck
wearing headphones for
the rest of your life.
Or you just disappear.
Leave me alone
here with your dog.
I think that's the most terrifying and
amazing part of being a human being.
What?
Our capacity to move on.
[vinyl record crackling]
[♪ "Loud Places" by
Jamie XX playing]
I'll look for you.
And I'll look for you.
♪ I go to loud places ♪
♪ To search for someone ♪
♪ To be quiet with ♪
♪ Who will take me home ♪
♪ You go to loud places ♪
♪ To find someone who ♪
♪ Will take you higher than ♪
[♪ music crackling
and oscillating]
[muffled] ♪ Didn't
I take you to ♪
♪ Higher places you
can't reach without me ♪
So how does this end up?
Tragically.
Well.
- Well.
- Thanks for the hit.
What in the name of Luther
Vandross just happened?
I'm letting the love
of my life walk away.
Hey, future girl.
What's your name?
Harriet.
Well, Harriet. You coming?
I love you.
What?
Have fun.
♪ Reach without me ♪
[music stops]
[♪ mellow dance music playing]
Come on, Tango. Come on.
Oh. Careful.
[phone ringing]
Hi.
Yeah, I'm meeting Nelly
at the studio in 45.
Just walking the dog
and grabbing a coffee.
[indistinct chatter]
- [Max] Oh.
- [Harriet laughs]
Hi. You must smell my dog.
Sorry. Uh, can I do an
iced Americano, please?
♪ But I never lost myself ♪
♪ I never lost myself ♪
I could do a little more
compression on the drums.
Yeah, yeah. Go for it.
Play it from the top again.
- [keyboard clicks]
- [♪ mellow dance music starts again]
I like that.
- Yeah. It's really good. I like it too.
- Good.
♪ Everybody loves
you when you're up ♪
[music fades out]
Hey.
- Oh my God. Look at you.
- Hello.
- Hi beautiful.
- Hi.
- You look amazing.
- You look good.
- Hey.
- You look great.
[♪ "To Turn You On (Disco Punisher
Remix)" by Roxy Music playing]
[Harriet] Ready?
[announcer] Ladies and
gentlemen, Roxy Music.
[crowd cheering]
♪ Is it raining in New York ♪
♪ On Fifth Avenue ♪
♪ And off Broadway after dark ♪
♪ Love the lights don't you ♪
♪ I could walk you
through the park ♪
♪ If you're feeling
blue or whatever ♪
♪ Spring Summer whenever ♪
♪ Winter through Fall ♪
♪ I'd do anything
to turn you on ♪
♪ Anything to turn you on ♪
[♪ ethereal music playing]
[♪ "To Turn You On (Disco Punisher
Remix)" by Roxy Music continues]
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/myu8g
Help other users to choose the best subtitles