Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
I think that all the life experiences that people have...
I experience it all through climbing
There are times...
I just give up
So, we can start now
Can I do it?
Yes, go on
Wow!
Turn, turn, turn so it doesn't stick
It's easier if you turn it on the worktop?
Yeah
Enjoy!
And to you
This haircut is on point!
I remember that
It was fashionable
Why don't you wear it like that now?
Janja was already dancing here
I was dancing here
She was very active
We really thought we should put her in some sports club...
so that she would get tired during the day...
so we could have some peace and quiet in the evening
Twice per week dancing lessons
And twice per week climbing lessons
The climbing began to overlap with her dancing classes
My wife asked her
"Janja, now you have to decide what
you are going to continue with"
"Climbing or dancing?"
"You need to decide"
We bought second-hand climbing shoes for starters
What about the belt?
That too
Go Janja!
Even as a little girl, Janja was very strong...
showing her incredible strength
Before soccer on national TV...
Janja is like superhero!
Come on, you alright?
Doesn't matter though
No matter what, you know, all this shit...
we'll just work through it
Let’s go. Go! Go!
Ever since I started climbing...
my goal has been...
to become the strongest climber in the world
That's what I was seeking...
and I still am
I want to not only become strong as a climber,
but also strong as a person
I’ve found an incident described on a page here...
where Miho was angry
We found her cute because she is the youngest
Even when she was angry, she was cute
So we were looking at her and smiling, her sisters and I
But Miho didn’t like it at all and was angry
Even then, she didn’t like losing
She never wanted to be defeated by her older sisters
But of course, it was impossible to imagine how far I could go
I only had this unfounded self-confidence
that I would somehow be ok...
that I would become strong
I just believed that
You're my sugar
Yeah, look at you
There you go, Brookie-poo
The achievement, it's so big
We are on the moon and back, and moon and back...
and moon and back
Can I climb here?
Yeah
Thank you
Enjoy your day
Same to you
I'm sad
This is stylish, don't you think?
She never wants to see herself losing
That state of mind...
is what has allowed her to reach her current performance level
In 2018 Boulder World Cup, she was the overall champion
I think that was an important moment for her
My own country is hosting the Olympic Games...
so I am really looking forward to it
Being from Tokyo, a climber
Being in a position to aim for a medal there...
is really a miracle
I want to do it now
I feel that I really want to use the energy...
that's been building up inside me
- Dear viewers of S/
- PARK!
I’ve been selected for the Olympic Games
As I have been until now...
I will continue working hard
I want to do great things for Japan
Many people have been rooting for me
I want to prove myself worthy of that
I have a responsibility. I really do
Because I’ve been chosen, I have to do it
Keeping that in mind, I will practise diligently
I realised after the announcement was over
I realise now that I was at my wit’s end
Look at this
This cut was really bad yesterday, but look at it today
Look how quickly I heal
Really deep cuts, too
We've been trying to learn how to fit a carpet ourselves...
and I'm just tucking it all the way in on the edges...
It's weirdly satisfying, but kind of
frustrating at the same time
I always drink carbonated water
I go to the fridge and there isn't any
But now, even such a small thing can make me feel irritated
I just live as usual, but when
something happens...
suddenly everything seems impossible
There are times I just give up
But you have to survive
It might sound like an exaggeration...
but all kinds of pressure...
I was suppressing inside
Oh, my back's sore!
They did the first epidural...
Go, go, go
Come on, come on. You can do it!
Come on, hold it!
Yeah, like this. Keep going, keep going!
It's like I'm climbing stupidly
Stupidly, yeah. Weirdly
Yeah, well...
Damn it!
I knew it! You won't help yourself on purpose
What the fuck?
I'm moving away
It's pointless to keep doing this because I keep moving away
Yes, I can see
What now?
I can't
Quiet!
Look, can I just say one thing?
You came here and said, "I can't",
and you started getting nervous
What if you just turned a little?
That's what I couldn't do
Could you at least try?
No
Without saying, “I can’t”
So how the fuck am I supposed to
turn my leg from this position?
This is how
How?
The same way you just did
But I can't
Come on
I'm exhausted
Because you don't calm yourself down
Because you don't just take a breath. Just that. Take a breath
If you pull through it you can do it
But you have to believe
If you are not all in...
even if you are Janja, it's not possible to win
Hey, I think your phone fell on the floor
When you sit down to watch her in the Olympics...
how are you going to feel?
How shall I put it?
The bigger the scale of the event...
the more tense I become
She was not the kind of child...
to show her emotions
I think because she is competitive
She would keep saying that she wanted to get stronger
I think I can be proud of her strong mindset
I feel tension
In my training and in my everyday life, I feel it constantly
But when it comes to the competition...
because I am prepared to give it my all, the anxiety is gone
Just you wait
The person in the photo is Miho’s grandfather. Her Grandpa
He was really looking forward to the Olympic Games, but...
he died one month before the World Championships started
He’s watching over her
Miho too wanted to show [the Olympics] to him
She said, "Let’s take him with us"
But this morning she was saying...
"Grandpa may be in the stadium already"
Yes!
I can already breathe a little easier
Oh, I knew it!
She slipped
I knew that she would slip
Oh damn
Janja is anxious
You lost your speech, didn’t you?
Unbelievable
She wasn't careful enough
I can't relax
No
There's no going back
Climbing is about to start, please...
Do it!
Amazing! Amazing!
So happy
Well done, well done
There were many difficult times and moments...
when I thought I would give up, when I felt disheartened
What I realised by winning the medal...
it really made me stronger
The value of every day's experience on this journey...
I think it’s greater than the value of the medal