(gentle instrumental music)
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
- [Announcer] "All My Friends" is filmed
before a live studio audience.
(audience cheering)
(indistinct chatter)
- Okay, this is really
starting to shape up.
I think this could be the
best set we've ever done.
- That looks super cool to me.
(audience laughing)
- Woohoo! Korey is ready to rock!
- I'm excited, too.
Give me some skin, girl.
(audience laughing)
- What?
- I'm just trying to high five.
- No thanks.
- Aren't you excited about the set list?
- Yeah, but I don't feel the need
to engage in skin-on-skin
Neanderthal expressions of joy.
(audience laughing)
- Burn on you, dude,
'cause she didn't want to high five you.
Sorry.
(audience laughing)
- Hey gang, what is up!
(audience cheering)
- [All] Hi James!
- Wow, is that what I think it is?
The set list for tonight's show?
- Yup, and I think it's a good one.
- Let me check it out.
Okay, wow, I like this.
This is amazing, this is brilliant.
Bravo, Nancy, yes!
- Thank you.
(audience laughing)
- Eye roll times a hundred.
Little Miss needs to bow a lot.
(audience applause)
- [All] Hey Pat.
- Oh, hey y'all.
- Hey Pay, what's that?
- Oh this?
Oh, this is my world
famous spicy Pat nachos.
- Nachos!
(audience laughing)
- Those nachos look yum yum delish.
Can I have a bite?
- Uh, I can give you a small one.
You know, I'm really hungry for my nachos.
- Okay, I promise you it's gonna be
a teeny tiny baby bite.
- Okay.
(audience laughing)
Well, you might as well finish 'em,
since you put your greasy fingers
all over my world famous nachos.
(audience laughing)
- Ugh, nachos are freaking grody, dude.
- Is that the set list for tonight?
- That is, my good man.
This is the set list.
Nancy worked really hard on it.
And we think it might be the
best set we've ever done.
I hope he likes the set list
and the order of the songs.
(audience laughing)
(paper ripping)
(audience exclaiming)
- What are you doing, Pat?
- I hate this.
You know I can't do these
particular songs all in a row.
I need to pace myself
in order to give a great performance.
You know this!
- I know it might be
hard, but you can do it.
And we all think this can be
the greatest set we've ever done together.
- I said no!
(audience exclaiming)
I don't want to do it in that order.
I am offended you guys
would even consider this.
I don't want to go on stage with you.
With any of you.
As long as you keep on
ganging up on me like this.
- Yo, yo!
(audience cheering)
What is all this commotion?
- He just tore up the set list.
- He tore up the set list.
(all talking over each other)
(audience laughing)
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
- Understand.
- You guys are giving me a damn headache.
One at a time.
(audience laughing)
Pat.
- These guys are having
a nervous breakdown
about the cool set list.
And I just think it's too hard,
and I don't think I'm gonna play tonight.
- Now now, Pat, listen.
These guys are not just your band mates,
these are your good friends.
They got your back, they believe in you.
- I don't know.
- Pat, you can do it.
- Ooh, I know what we can do.
We can ask Tyler.
He's really good at set lists.
- Hey, that's a great idea.
But, where is Tyler?
- I think I might know.
(knocking on door)
Tyler, you in there?
- [Tyler] Yeah.
- Do you mind if I come inside?
- [Tyler] Okay.
(audience laughing)
- What are you doing in here?
- I don't know.
- How long have you been in here?
(audience laughing)
- Poor Tyler.
(melancholy music)
He's been through a lot.
It's a big show for him.
For all of us, really.
- Yeah, okay.
(audience laughing)
Now that we've found Tyler,
let's get you guys to the stage.
Pat, I know you're not
excited about the set list,
but listen, we believe in you.
And you know, sometimes
you have to push yourself
to the top of the mountain
with the help of all my friends.
- Yeah, I'll try.
(audience applause)
- Let's go.
(bright music)
- Let's go!
- Let's do it!
Let's have a great show!
(audience applause)
Come on!
- Let's go!
(all cheering)
- Rock and roll!
Have a bitching show!
Let's go, you guys!
Show 'em what you're working with.
Come on, let's go, baby.
Yes yes yes yes yes yes!
Fuck!
(door slams)
(audience laughing)
(bright music)
(people chattering lightly)
- Okay.
Hey everybody.
Happy holidays.
We're LCD Soundsystem.
("On Repeat" by LCD Soundsystem)
♪ A beat's on repeat, beating on me ♪
♪ From every car in the street ♪
♪ It's a constant repeat, on repeat ♪
♪ Of your paranoid heartbreaking beats ♪
♪ On repeat ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ It's a five song repeat beating on me ♪
♪ While your favorite
band helps you to sleep ♪
♪ And here comes the new stylish creep ♪
♪ From every car in the street ♪
♪ On repeat ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ Don't tell nobody what,
what you really want because ♪
♪ They can tell everybody
else what you really want ♪
♪ Then you're fucked ♪
♪ So act like it's for
yourself or it's all your art ♪
♪ And they go and tell everybody else ♪
♪ That you're really great ♪
♪ We are just people ♪
(music resumes)
(light moaning)
♪ You're enfranchised and entrenched ♪
♪ So now that it's yours ♪
♪ Real life is a compromise ♪
♪ But your beats are half-assed,
streak is beating on me ♪
♪ Well, I'm drunk and weak ♪
♪ It's hell for me to sleep ♪
♪ I wish I could complain
more about the rich ♪
♪ But then all their children
would flee the schools ♪
♪ And come to every show ♪
♪ No one wants that ♪
♪ I wish I could complain
more about the rich ♪
♪ But then all their children
would flee the streets ♪
♪ Come to every show ♪
♪ Drugged and unwashed ♪
♪ I wish I could complain
more about the rich ♪
♪ But then all their children
would flee the schools ♪
♪ And come to every show ♪
♪ Unwashed and drugged and ♪
♪ Beats are on repeat, beating on me ♪
♪ On your radio ♪
♪ Beats on repeat, beating on me ♪
(song concludes)
(bright music)
- Oh, this is gonna be fun.
- We got Cheese Puffs, and Kisses,
and James' favorite cookies.
- Oh and don't forget the spiked eggnog!
- Everything the band likes.
(audience laughing)
Now all I have to do is mop up
and make this place spic-and-span
for the after party.
(water splashing)
(humming)
(audience laughing)
- Brian, didn't I tell you,
you have to add soap to the warm water,
or you're just moving
around dirty damn water.
(audience laughing)
- I'm trying, I swear.
- We know, Brian.
We all know.
(audience laughing)
(melancholy music)
("I Can Change" by LCD Soundsystem)
♪ Tell me a line ♪
♪ Make it easy for me ♪
♪ Open your arms ♪
♪ Dance with me until I feel alright ♪
♪ It's good in the dark ♪
♪ Good in the dark ♪
♪ But into the lover's light ♪
♪ Here comes another fight ♪
♪ So ring the alarm, ring the alarm ♪
♪ Bar me and hold me and cling to my arm ♪
♪ Here it comes, here it comes ♪
♪ And what you're asking me now ♪
♪ Disastrous now ♪
♪ Hoping and hoping, and hoping ♪
♪ The feeling goes away ♪
♪ Never change, never change ♪
♪ Never change, this is
how I fell in love, oh ♪
♪ Never change, never change ♪
♪ Never change, that's just
who I fell in love with ♪
♪ In love, oh ♪
♪ So this is the time ♪
♪ The very best time ♪
♪ So give me a line and take me home ♪
♪ Take me over ♪
♪ But dashing the hopes ♪
♪ Dashing the hopes ♪
♪ And smashing the pride ♪
♪ The morning's got you on the ropes, no ♪
♪ And love is a murderer ♪
♪ Love is a murderer ♪
♪ But if she calls you tonight ♪
♪ Everything is all right ♪
♪ Yeah, we know ♪
♪ And love is a curse ♪
♪ Trapped in a hearse ♪
♪ Love is an open book ♪
♪ To a verse of your bad poetry ♪
♪ And this is coming from me ♪
♪ And I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change if it helps
you fall in love, no ♪
♪ I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change if it helps
you fall in love, in love ♪
♪ Turn on the light ♪
♪ Make it easy for me ♪
♪ Fill the divide ♪
♪ Fumble in the kitchen 'til it's right ♪
♪ Such an awful sight ♪
♪ But there's love in your eyes ♪
♪ Love in your eyes, love in your eyes ♪
♪ But maybe that's just your lover finds ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ And I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change if it helps
you fall in love, no ♪
♪ And I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change if it helps
you fall in love, in love ♪
♪ And I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change if it helps
you feel in love, feel love ♪
♪ And I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change, I can change ♪
♪ I can change if it helps
you fall in love, in love ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
(song concludes)
(clearing throat)
- Thank, thank you all.
Thanks so much for coming.
(tapping cowbell and synthesizer)
Let's do it.
(tapping drumsticks)
("Other Voices" by LCD Soundsystem)
♪ Your feet touch the floor ♪
♪ I just open the window
and let the light in ♪
♪ The light burns your eyes ♪
♪ But it eases with each passing frame ♪
♪ Yeah, your head like a block ♪
♪ Filled with unwritten letters to some ♪
♪ Far away friends ♪
♪ Oh you'd write on
your hand to remember ♪
♪ If somebody, if someone
would just, pass you a pen ♪
♪ Make your way to the toilet ♪
♪ These morning illusions
are all part of the dance ♪
♪ And these doors all have locks on them ♪
♪ Like tinfoil hats, man ♪
♪ Made for resisting, other voices ♪
♪ Time isn't over, times aren't better ♪
♪ But it's letting you down ♪
♪ You keep going back to it ♪
♪ You keep going back to the well ♪
♪ Oh, that shit's a dictator ♪
♪ Time won't be fucked with ♪
♪ Buddy, no no no ♪
♪ You can't be believed ♪
♪ And you cannot believe
what you're told ♪
♪ You're still a baby now ♪
♪ You're still a baby with
those soft feet and everything ♪
♪ You're still a baby
for better or worse ♪
♪ Or for an hour or so ♪
♪ Until it's, other voices ♪
♪ Please, if you're coming home ♪
♪ Take me to the side ♪
♪ I'll know it's time to change ♪
♪ To runaway ♪
♪ From you ♪
♪ You're still a pushover
for passionate people ♪
♪ And you're just a baby now ♪
♪ You're just a baby now ♪
♪ With those soft feet and dull eyes ♪
♪ Resisting, other voices ♪
♪ And you're still a pushover
for passionate people ♪
♪ You're still a pushover
♪ You're still a pushover for ♪
♪ Tell 'em Nancy ♪
♪ This is what's happening
and it's freaking you out ♪
♪ I've heard it, heard it ♪
♪ And it sounds like the 90's ♪
♪ Who can you trust ♪
♪ And who are your friends ♪
♪ Who is impossible ♪
♪ And who is the enemy ♪
♪ These are the halls that
we're currently haunting ♪
♪ And these were the
people we currently haunt ♪
♪ Push back the walls ♪
♪ Push back the calendar ♪
♪ We've got, we've got friends
who are calling us home ♪
♪ You're still a baby now ♪
♪ You're just a baby now ♪
♪ You should be uncomfortable ♪
♪ Fight back on me now ♪
(bright music)
- Alright.
- (sighs)
(door shuts)
- James, what's wrong?
- Well, I think I'm singing pretty good,
but I keep thinking about
the set list and Pat,
and I just want this
to be the most perfect
holiday special ever.
It's a lot of pressure.
- Honey, I know what you need.
You need a hug.
That's right, come on in here.
Oh yes.
(audience sighing)
- This is good, yeah.
- Come here.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You got a lot of people
(audience laughing)
depending on you.
You act like you just started
on that shit yesterday.
You were born to do this.
You're a mother fucking rockstar.
Get your bitch ass back
out there on that stage,
and do your fucking job.
Now come on, let's go!
(audience laughing)
- Okay, thank you.
- Okay, let's go.
- I can do this, alright.
- Okay baby.
There you go, you can do it!
(audience applause)
Alright.
Fuck yeah, shit.
(majestic music)
("Tonite" by LCD Soundsystem)
♪ Every song is saying the same song ♪
♪ There's only tonight, tonight, tonight ♪
♪ Tonight, tonight, tonight ♪
♪ I never realized all these artists ♪
♪ Thought so much about dying ♪
♪ But truth be told we
all have the same end ♪
♪ Could make you cry, cry, cry, cry, cry ♪
♪ But I'm telling you ♪
♪ This is the best news
you're getting all week ♪
Ladies and gentlemen, (indistinct)
♪ And still it's ruling the airwaves ♪
♪ What remains of the airwaves ♪
♪ And we're frankly thankful ♪
♪ For the market psychology
you're hipping us to ♪
♪ Yes, todos lot hits are
saying the same thing ♪
♪ There's only tonight, tonight, tonight ♪
♪ Tonight, tonight, tonight ♪
♪ Then life is finite ♪
♪ But shit, it feels like forever ♪
♪ It feels like forever ♪
♪ Oh is everybody feeling the same thing ♪
♪ We're all wild ♪
♪ Except for you ♪
♪ And you know who you are ♪
♪ This is a love song ♪
♪ You're getting older ♪
♪ I promise you this;
you're getting older ♪
♪ And there's improvements unless ♪
♪ You're such a winner ♪
♪ In which case, the
future's a nightmare ♪
♪ And there's nothing I can do ♪
♪ There's nothing anyone
can do about this ♪
♪ But oh, I'm offering you
this chance to get even ♪
♪ But oh, you know very well
the dialect of negation ♪
♪ Sure enemies haunt you
with spit and derision ♪
♪ But it's friends who are the ones ♪
♪ Who can put you in an exile ♪
♪ But that's not right ♪
♪ And you're too sharp to be used ♪
♪ Or you're too shocked from being used ♪
♪ By these bullying
children of the fabulous ♪
♪ Raffling off limited edition shoes ♪
♪ And what's it you do again ♪
♪ Oh I'm a reminder ♪
♪ The hobbled veteran of
the disk shop inquisition ♪
♪ Set to parry the cocksure
of men's sick filth ♪
♪ With my own ramblings ♪
♪ Every lover favors the same stuff ♪
♪ It's all touch me, touch me,
touch me, touch me tonight ♪
♪ We maybe realize what it
is we need before we die ♪
♪ And luck is always better
than skill at things ♪
♪ We're flying blind ♪
♪ Oh good gracious ♪
♪ I sound like my mom ♪
♪ But out of the little
rooms and onto the streets ♪
♪ You've lost your internet
and we've lost our memories ♪
♪ We had a paper trail
which led to our secrets ♪
♪ Now embarrassing pictures
have now all been deleted ♪
♪ By versions of selves that
we thought were the best ones ♪
♪ 'Til versions of versions
of others repeating ♪
♪ Come laughing at everything
you thought was important ♪
♪ While still making mistakes ♪
♪ That you thought you had learned from ♪
♪ And beautiful people
know better than you ♪
♪ That cost in the long run ♪
♪ But they don't know the short game ♪
♪ And terrible people
know better than you ♪
♪ They're used and abused of
the once so dear listener ♪
♪ So you will be taunted
and badgered until death ♪
♪ You're missing some party
that you'll never get over ♪
♪ You hate the idea that
you're wasting your youth ♪
♪ That you stood in the background
oh until you got older ♪
♪ But that's all lies ♪
♪ That's all lies ♪
(song concludes)
("American Dream" by LCD Soundsystem)
♪ Wake up with somebody near you ♪
♪ And at someone else's place ♪
♪ You took acid and looked in the mirror ♪
♪ Watched the beard crawl
around on your face ♪
♪ Oh, the revolution was here ♪
♪ That would set you free
from those bourgeoisie ♪
♪ In the morning everything's clearer ♪
♪ When the sunlight exposes your age ♪
♪ But that's okay ♪
♪ That's okay ♪
♪ Grab your clothes and
head to the doorway ♪
♪ If you dance out, no one complains ♪
♪ Find some place where
you can be boring ♪
♪ Where you won't need to explain ♪
♪ That you're sick in the head
and you wish you were dead ♪
♪ Or at least instead of sleeping here ♪
♪ You'd prefer your own bed, come on ♪
♪ You just suck at self-preservation ♪
♪ Versus someone else's pain ♪
♪ So you feel drained ♪
♪ And insane ♪
♪ He was leather and you were screaming ♪
♪ Swinging chains against the stage ♪
♪ And you couldn't know he was leaving ♪
♪ But now more will go
with age, you know ♪
♪ So get up and stop your complaining ♪
♪ You know you're the only one ♪
♪ Who's been destroying all the fun ♪
♪ Look what happened
when you were dreaming ♪
♪ And then punch yourself in the face ♪
♪ So you kiss and you clutch ♪
♪ But you can't fight that feeling ♪
♪ That your one true love is
just awaiting your big meeting ♪
♪ So you never even asked for names ♪
♪ You just look right through
them as if you already came ♪
♪ It's a drug of the heart and
you can't stop the shaking ♪
♪ 'Cause your body wants what
it's terrible at taking, oh ♪
♪ And you can't remember the meaning ♪
♪ But there's no coming back
against this California feeling ♪
♪ Dream ♪
♪ Sha-bang, sha-bang ♪
♪ American dream ♪
♪ Sha-bang, sha-bang, oh oh ♪
(song concludes)
(taps drum stick)
- Could we...
I guess we're gonna take a small break.
Our drum, our drummer, we're
gonna take a drummer break.
We'll be right back.
(bright music)
(audience laughing)
(door slams)
(sighs)
- Ugh!
(taps glass)
- Pat!
(audience gasps, laughs)
- Okay, here I go again.
(audience laughing)
- Pat, what are you doing back here?
- I'm just so frustrated.
You know, I don't know how the expect me
to play all these complicated
drum parts all in a row.
I mean, these arms can only drum so much!
(peanuts dump)
(audience laughing)
- Do you want to tell me when you're done
making a mess so I don't
have to re-mop a third time?
(audience laughing)
- Listen, you're using that as a crutch.
And crutches are only
here to make you stronger,
and you can do this.
Your friends have faith in you.
The people have faith in you.
You need to get it together,
and get out there and do what you do.
- You're right.
- You can do this.
- I can do this.
All my friends love me.
- They do.
- They wouldn't ask me to do something
unless I had the power inside of me.
I'm gonna go out there and drum.
- Go drum.
- I can drum!
- You can drum!
- I wanna drum!
- Go drum!
- Yeah!
- Let's get it!
(audience cheering)
- Yeah!
- Yes! Yes baby!
(audience laughing)
Yeah!
- Go!
Yes, baby.
- Yeah!
(audience laughing)
- Here we go again.
("Thrills" by LCD Soundsystem)
♪ Oh, I'm on fire ♪
♪ Because you want me ♪
♪ But my desire ♪
♪ Is going to crush me ♪
♪ 'Cause you are loud ♪
♪ Ooh, I'm all chills ♪
♪ 'Cause you adore me ♪
♪ You adore me ♪
♪ But I'm still all kills ♪
♪ I need my thrills ♪
♪ Thrills, thrills, ooh ♪
♪ Don't you really want to wake up ♪
♪ Next to you, stop ♪
♪ Oh, I'm on fire ♪
♪ Because you love me ♪
♪ But my desire ♪
♪ Is going to level me when you stop ♪
♪ But I'm all chills when you adore me ♪
♪ When you adore me ♪
♪ But ooh, I see those kills ♪
♪ I need my thrills ♪
♪ I need my thrills, shots ♪
♪ Wow, I'm on fire ♪
♪ Because you love me ♪
♪ But oh, my desire ♪
♪ Is going to level me ♪
♪ When you're in town ♪
♪ But oh, straight up chills ♪
♪ Because you release me ♪
♪ You release me ♪
♪ But oh, still all kills ♪
♪ I need my thrills ♪
♪ I still need my thrills ♪
♪ Thrills, thrills, thrills ♪
♪ Don't you make me wanna wake up ♪
♪ Next to you ♪
♪ Thrills, thrills, thrills ♪
♪ Don't you make me wanna wake up ♪
♪ Next to you ♪
♪ Thrills, thrills, thrills ♪
♪ Don't you make me wanna wake up ♪
♪ Next to you ♪
♪ Thrills, thrills, thrills ♪
♪ Don't you make me wanna wake up ♪
♪ Still inside you ♪
(song concludes)
("Oh Baby" by LCD Soundsystem)
♪ Oh baby ♪
♪ You're having a bad dream ♪
♪ Here in my arms ♪
♪ Oh sugar ♪
♪ You came to me ♪
♪ You having a bad time ♪
♪ Bring me along ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh lover ♪
♪ You run from me ♪
♪ We move like a bad scene ♪
♪ Shot in the dark ♪
♪ Oh but please ♪
♪ Please wake me ♪
♪ For my love sits patiently ♪
♪ Please baby please ♪
♪ For my love waits, wait and see ♪
♪ Oh love ♪
♪ You came to me ♪
♪ Are you having a bad time ♪
♪ There in your home ♪
♪ Oh sugar ♪
♪ Give in to me ♪
♪ You're just having a bad dream ♪
♪ Then ring the alarm ♪
♪ Oh but please ♪
♪ Please wake me ♪
♪ For my love sits patiently ♪
♪ Please baby please ♪
♪ And my love plays wait and see ♪
♪ Oh I'm on my knees, yeah ♪
♪ I am on my knees ♪
♪ I promise I'm clean ♪
♪ And my love life waits ♪
♪ And you're already gone ♪
♪ Yeah, you're already gone ♪
♪ You're already home ♪
♪ And my love life stumbles on ♪
♪ Oh baby ♪
♪ Lean into me ♪
♪ There's always a side door ♪
♪ Into the dark ♪
(music concludes)
(exciting music)
- One cinnamon for Pat,
and a cinnamon for James,
and cinnamon for Al.
(audience laughing)
Perfect.
Looks so beautiful.
(audience laughing)
Abby, hey.
Now, please be very careful.
I worked really heard
on this eggnog spread.
- Oh, can I see?
- [Both] Whoa!
(audience laughing)
Whoa!
- Chill, bro ham.
You know I don't mess with egg drinks.
I'm lacto-free.
In fact, I have a little tummy ache.
- Oh, I got something for you.
(audience laughing)
Here, take a hit of this.
- Sweet.
- To the head, to the head, yeah.
- Oh, it's already working.
- Okay great, now get on back out there
and do stuff!
- [Both] Whoa!
(audience laughing)
- Psych, Brian!
(gentle music)
(audience laughing and clapping)
("Emotional Haircut" by LCD Soundsystem)
♪ I'm not sure I want to
step outside with my ♪
♪ Emotional haircut ♪
♪ It seems that I've been misunderstood ♪
♪ The look of great concern ♪
♪ And the emotion in your eyes of my ♪
♪ Emotional haircut ♪
♪ It's better to me ♪
♪ It's much better than it used to be ♪
♪ 'Cause I got eyes
going every which way ♪
♪ I got eyes all over the place ♪
♪ And I got tired of the
hotel room and the TV ♪
♪ And look at what they
taught you in high school ♪
♪ They never told you about ♪
♪ Emotional haircut ♪
♪ It ain't a disease ♪
♪ It's just harder to
do whatever you please ♪
♪ So dream yourself tonight ♪
♪ To a little love life ♪
♪ Now we all get ideas ♪
♪ I know I should shut
'em down with this ♪
♪ Emotional haircut ♪
♪ Now I ain't Dionysian, man ♪
♪ Oh no buddy, no need to
be concerned with this ♪
♪ Emotional haircut ♪
♪ It's part of the game ♪
♪ Yeah man, it's just part of the feat ♪
♪ So let's raise a glass
to the bodies in here ♪
♪ Oh, raise a glass to
the bodies in here ♪
♪ We're gonna toast to the
bodies all soak up the bass ♪
♪ Man, you're in love with
the bodies in here and your ♪
♪ Emotional haircut ♪
♪ Oh just get on the street ♪
♪ Fuck the shuffle, put
this shit on repeat ♪
♪ You've got numbers on
your phone of the dead ♪
♪ That you can not delete ♪
♪ And you got life-affirming
moments in your past ♪
♪ That you can not repeat ♪
♪ Yeah you've numbers on
your phone of the dead ♪
♪ That you cannot delete ♪
♪ And you're losing all
your skin to bones ♪
♪ 'Cause you just can't sleep ♪
♪ I know you can't calm down ♪
♪ Out of your windows
and onto the streets ♪
♪ Out of your windows ♪
♪ Out of it tonight ♪
♪ You know what it does ♪
♪ It puts me up on my feet ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ It puts me on the floor ♪
♪ But can you hear the heartbeat ♪
♪ Can you hear the heartbeat ♪
♪ Just listen to the heartbeat ♪
♪ Just listen to it now ♪
♪ Listen to it now, listen to it now ♪
♪ You better do it now, man ♪
♪ Listen, it's coming down ♪
(music concludes)
(bells jingling)
("Christmas Will Break Your
Heart" by LCD Soundsystem)
♪ Christmas will break your heart ♪
♪ If your world is feeling small ♪
♪ And there's no one on your phone ♪
♪ You feel close enough to call ♪
♪ Christmas will crush your soul ♪
♪ Like that laid back rock 'n' roll ♪
♪ But your body's getting old ♪
♪ And it's much too tired to be so bold ♪
♪ Christmas will wreck your head ♪
♪ Like some listless awkward sex ♪
♪ So you refuse to leave your bed ♪
♪ Get depressed when no one checks ♪
♪ Yeah, Christmas will break your heart ♪
♪ Like the armies of
the unrelenting dark ♪
♪ Once the peace talks fall apart ♪
♪ But still I'm coming home to you ♪
♪ Christmas will shove you down ♪
♪ So just lay back in the snow ♪
♪ But that quiet wind won't wake ♪
♪ What inside you has grown cold ♪
♪ And Christmas will drown your love ♪
♪ Like a storm down from above ♪
♪ On your fading memories of ♪
♪ A normal life ♪
♪ Oh, while I thought to make you mine ♪
♪ Believing in the line ♪
♪ That your heart would melt with time ♪
♪ And though you're out with them again ♪
♪ Your thick and fickle friends ♪
♪ They might replace the love that ends ♪
♪ But still I'm coming home to you ♪
♪ To you, to you, to you ♪
♪ Yes you ♪
♪ What if you're done ♪
♪ What if you don't want it anymore ♪
♪ What if they're gone ♪
♪ So what if they don't love you anymore ♪
♪ I'm coming home ♪
♪ Can you see me ♪
♪ Can you still see me ♪
♪ Hey mama, take my hand ♪
(song concludes)
(bright music)
(door slams)
(audience laughing)
- Yay!
- So sick! I can't believe it!
- Join me.
- I'm so happy!
(all chattering)
- Join me, you guys.
Get some eggnog.
- That was incredible.
(all chattering)
- It was so good, it was such a good show.
Oh my god.
- We did it.
Thank you, Pat, for trusting us.
- You killed it, Pat! Yeah!
(audience laughing)
- We knew you could do it, Pat.
- I love you, guys.
Thanks for believing in me,
even when I didn't believe in myself.
- Well, I think we all learned
a little bit about trust
and compassion, didn't we?
- Pat, Pat, Pat.
Because you did such a great job,
I made this especially for you.
Just the way you like it.
- Thank you so much, Brian.
- Wow.
- Abby, care for a bite
of my world famous spicy Pat nachos?
- If they're gluten free, then definitely.
Otherwise, I'm gonna have my world famous
IBS all up in this house tonight.
(audience laughing, clapping)
- Guys, to all my friends.
- [All] To all my friends.
(glasses clink)
(gentle music)
(exciting theme music)
(music concludes)
- Absolutely.