Downloaded from
YTS.MX
This program is rated G
and is suitable for
general audiences.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
♪ And the lights
are on display ♪
♪ There's a big old tree
for all to see ♪
♪ Where the children
run and play ♪
♪ I look out
through my window ♪
♪ Somethin' just
don't seem right ♪
♪ Till I said hello
and heard her voice ♪
♪ On the other
end of the line... ♪
Weatherman says
we're getting six
to eight inches--
which means we can expect 12.
Anything else?
Uh...
just the check, please.
Thank you.
You in town for the holidays?
Oh, just passing through.
Will be,
once this storm lets up.
Mm-hmm.
Do you know where I might find
a place to stay for the night?
Covington Creek Inn.
Just across the bridge.
Can't miss it.
You have yourself
a Merry Christmas.
You, too.
♪ ...It's funny
how going back ♪
♪ Can get you
back where you belong ♪
♪ It's the difference
in just a melody ♪
♪ And my favorite
Christmas song ♪
♪ Now, it's Christmas
Christmas ♪
♪ I'm hurrying' on my way ♪
♪ Christmas, Christmas ♪
♪ Like I'm riding
in a one-horse sleigh ♪
♪ Well, I don't have to hear
no jingle bells ♪
♪ Just the ringing
of the phone ♪
♪ Mama just called
and said... ♪
Y'all have a good night.
Careful on those roads.
We still on
for Dominoes tomorrow?
If you promise
to go easy on me.
I'll think about it.
Any luck?
No, the lines are still down.
John is stuck in traffic,
and Bobby is home alone.
If the power goes,
he's gonna need help
with the generator.
How much longer
on your shift?
I'm here till 1:00.
I'll cover for you.
Head home.
No, Paul--
I still don't have
the snow tires on my car.
It's probably best to give
the plows a head start.
Thank you.
I will make it up to you.
It's fine.
Hey, are you, uh,
are you still looking
for someone to cover your shift
over Christmas?
I thought you were going
to your folks' for Christmas.
Well, we decided to stay
and do something small here.
Amy said that you were
talking about going home...
You know,
between the two of us,
we could cover your whole week.
Are you talking about
Christmas?
Yeah.
Let us do this for you, Paul.
You should go.
We've got incoming!
What have you got?
Pulled her from the river
about 15 minutes ago.
- Let's go.
- All right.
You know, she's lucky
you found her when you did.
Any longer in that water,
and the outcome could have been
very different.
She gonna be okay?
She's stable.
CAT scan revealed
a minor concussion.
Were you able
to locate her family?
She's not a local,
and we didn't recover
any identification
at the scene,
but if she did have any,
it's probably long gone by now.
She's alone?
As of now,
but we'll sure do our best
to rectify that.
Good night, Paul.
Mr. Bennett!
This is Carl Wagner
with Venture Insurance
with a great offer
this holiday season for you!
I'm calling with a--
Hey Paul! It's Ben.
I was just checking in
to see if there was any word
on you getting some time off.
We'd love to have you
down here for Christmas.
Hey, tell him.
Tell him what I said.
All right, all right.
I'll let him know.
Marissa wants me to tell you
that she's making
your favorite apple pie.
With homemade ice cream!
I love you, Paulie!
[Ben, laughing] Okay, okay.
He's sufficiently bribed.
He's good.
Anyway, I hope to see you soon.
I miss you, little brother.
I know we have
a lot to catch up on,
but it's not all bad news,
I swear.
Look, we'll talk about it
when you get here.
Well, the sheriff
stopped by earlier.
He was hoping to talk
to that young woman
they brought in last night,
but she's still not up.
Were they able to figure out
who she is?
No, I guess we won't know
until she tells us.
Good morning!
Let's get a little sunshine
in here for you.
Everybody's very eager
for you to wake up.
You see, everyone knows
everyone in this town,
except no one seems to know you.
For now,
you are quite the mystery.
Where am I?
Hey.
It's okay.
You're fine, you're safe.
You're in the hospital.
Hospital? What?
You took a little spill
last night
into the river.
You've got a mild concussion,
a few bumps and bruises.
Yeah, it's...
going to be sore for a bit,
but Dr. Grant's gonna come in,
and he's gonna give you
something for the pain, okay?
Now, what's your name?
Um...
I don't know.
Okay.
It's okay.
I remember waking up here
and talking to...
Paul.
...Paul,
but when I try to remember
anything before, it...
there's nothing.
Okay.
Well, between the impact
from your fall
and the time
spent in the water,
normally, you'd be looking
at acute trauma
to the temporal lobe,
which can result
in retrograde amnesia.
Amnesia?
But...
I still remember things.
I can walk,
I can talk...
Yes, those are procedural
and motor-related,
likely unaffected.
Our minds and our bodies
do unique things
to protect us,
and to be honest,
your symptoms
are not even
a textbook scenario.
This is a rare case.
It's quite possible
that you're going to recall
all kinds of things
Just not who I am?
Well, do we know
how long this lasts?
There's no set time frame
for recovery.
The best thing you can do
is surround yourself
with familiar things.
Okay, well, do we know
how I got in the water?
Was there anybody with me?
The accident was reported
by the motorist involved.
It was late,
you were attempting
to cross the bridge alone.
The car turned into its skid,
and you fell
over the guard rail,
trying to avoid it.
I'm afraid we're...
we're still trying
to track down your family.
Okay, so is there anybody
looking for me?
The storm made a mess
of a lot of things out here.
There's power outages
all over the state.
Phone lines were down.
Okay, and where is here?
Covington. Maine.
Listen, for now,
I think the best thing
is for you to just rest up.
We'll let you know the minute
we make contact.
She had a pin
from the diner on her.
Oh, sure.
I served her last night.
Never did get a name, though.
Did she pay with a card?
Cash.
I'll be right back.
I'll give you a minute.
Did she say anything
about where she was going,
or coming from?
Just that she was looking
for a spot
to ride out the storm
for the night.
Oh, and, uh,
she left this behind.
I hung onto it,
in case she came back.
It seemed like
it might be important.
Paul!
Any chance I can
get a few minutes
with our Jane Doe.
Yeah, she's in room four.
Well, that's the thing, son.
She's not.
Give me a minute.
I like this game.
Doubles are always placed
cross-ways
at the end of the chain...
- Okay.
- Paul!
Pull up a chair, join us.
You are supposed to be in bed.
I was getting stir-crazy,
staring at the same four walls.
Can I put this here?
You don't want to do that...
Uh...
yes, you do want to do that.
Spoil sport.
Sheriff Crowley's here.
He needs to speak with you.
Do the police
have new information?
I don't know,
but just hang tight,
I'll grab a wheelchair, okay?
I don't need a wheelchair.
It's hospital policy.
Thank you for the game.
Come back any time.
Hey, whoa! Wait!
Are you coming?
Charleston, South Carolina.
That ring any bells?
No...
We think that might be
where you were headed.
"Charleston Counts Down
to Annual Tree Lighting."
You ducked into
Maisie's Diner last night.
You had some cherry pie
and a cup of coffee.
The waitress found that
on the table after you left.
This is all?
Turn it over.
"Please come.
Mark."
Mark...
Anything?
That's all right.
We reached out
to the sheriff's department
in Charleston.
They're checking in
with the festival committee,
and see if they know
who that might be.
In the meantime,
you hold onto that.
If anything comes back to you,
just give me a shout.
Okay.
- All right?
- Yeah.
I should get back to my rounds,
but is there anything
I can get you before I go?
You know what?
I could go for some pie.
One slice of cherry,
one hot coffee,
straight from Maisie's Diner.
Think it will help?
Well, Dr. Grant says
I need to surround myself
with familiar things,
so...
Mm!
Nope.
I don't know
why anyone would drink that.
Okay, hold on.
Because I...
got you covered.
I'll try this.
Okay.
Better.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay. Let's see if that pie
rings any bells.
Needs ice cream.
I checked with Eleanor.
You had it plain.
No bells.
Hmm.
It was a good thought.
I just realized,
I'm not sure
what I should call you.
Well, Dr. Grant
has decided on Jane,
so...
Okay.
What's your story?
You want to talk about me?
We could talk about me,
but that would be
a very short conversation.
So, where did you grow up?
Did you grow up around here?
I'm from Georgia.
A little town called Pickering.
Do you have family there?
Some.
Are you going home
for Christmas?
I was thinking about
heading down there.
You're undecided.
It's complicated.
Well, hey,
now that Sheriff Crowley
has his first real clue,
you know,
it's only a matter of time
till somebody walks
through that door
and claims me.
Right?
Right.
I'm gonna see
if I can find you some ice cream
for that pie, okay?
Thank you.
♪ On the first day
of Christmas ♪
♪ My true love sent to me ♪
♪ A partridge in a pear tree ♪
♪ On the second day
of Christmas ♪
♪ My true love sent to me ♪
♪ Two turtle doves ♪
♪ And a partridge
in a pear tree ♪
♪ On the third day
of Christmas ♪
♪ My true love
sent to me... ♪
And they really
don't have any leads?
No, they can't find anyone
who knows her.
Poor girl.
All right,
I think that's enough.
There might be
more snowflakes in here
than there are outside.
Thanks for your help.
Yeah, of course.
Merry Christmas!
I told you I'd be home
for Christmas.
Dr. Grant says
most people
get their memories back.
Which means some don't.
Recovery is a long process,
but you're gonna get there.
I've been here almost a week.
The phone lines are back up.
Sheriff Crowley
has shown my picture
to half the town.
I don't think anybody
is looking for me.
Well, maybe
they want to be here, but...
they just can't be.
Why not?
Things come up.
People get stuck.
Sometimes, it's not as easy
as it should be
to get to the places
that we're needed.
Have you decided yet?
If you're going home?
Yeah, I, uh...
I actually waited too long
to decide,
so all the flights are booked.
Maybe next year.
I think you should.
You should go.
I know you said
it's complicated,
but no reason
both of us should be alone
on Christmas.
Let's get out of here.
Hey.
I thought your shift
ended a while ago.
It did,
but I just had to do
something before I left.
About Christmas.
Does your offer
to cover my shift
still stand?
Of course.
Okay, great. Thanks.
Yeah.
Hey.
I thought you'd be
on the road by now.
The car's all packed.
I just,
I wanted to drop this off.
It's a little thank you
for covering my shifts.
Aw, well, I am happy to do it.
I'm glad
you're going home, Paul.
It will be good for you,
to get to see them, and...
Anyway.
You have a safe trip.
You need anything at all,
you let us know.
I will.
Thank you.
- Merry Christmas.
Please, just reconsider.
At least until we can find
someone to help you.
You can't keep me here.
- I have to do this.
- What's going on?
They told me you left.
I was just about to.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
I can't just sit here
and wait for somebody
to find me.
I've tried that,
and it's not working.
Releasing you
in your current condition
is not in your best interest.
Before I fell in that water,
I was on my way
to the tree-lighting ceremony.
I will find my answers there.
I know I will,
and you were the one
that told me
I need to surround myself
with familiar things.
I can't do that here.
Christmas Eve is in two days.
I can't wait any longer.
How do you expect
to get there?
South Carolina is a long way.
I will pawn my watch,
buy a plane ticket.
They will never let you
on the flight.
You don't have I.D.
I will find a way.
That is where I was going.
and that is where I will go.
I could take her.
It's on my way.
You'd really do that?
You need to get home.
So do I.
All right, follow me.
We'll get your paperwork
started.
Are you sure about this, son?
Okay, this has
three hours on it,
but you can always add more.
I put the station's number
in there
as one of your contacts,
so you can stay up to date
on things going on back here.
Now, listen,
if you get
to the tree lighting,
and you don't find
what you're looking for,
the second contact in there
is Sheriff Connie Hargrove
from Charleston.
She'll be expecting your call.
I really appreciate this.
My pleasure.
Now, is there
anything else you need?
Clothing, or...
No, no,
we've got that covered.
We ran over to the store.
Bertie took a peek
at your tags.
Should be the right sizes.
Yup.
What?
Oh, and a little pocket money,
to get you where you're going.
We took up a collection.
Um...
Thank you, guys
Thank you, that's, um...
Merry Christmas.
Thank you!
Wow!
I need to make a few
adjustments to our route
if we're gonna make it
to that tree lighting
on the 24th.
I was able to get another room
at the B&B tonight,
but still nothing for tomorrow.
Everything's all booked up.
Thank you for doing this.
It'll be fun!
Be nice to have a co-pilot.
Someone to read the map,
in case I get lost.
Do you plan on getting lost?
No one plans on getting lost.
Hey, thanks for that tree.
I know it was you.
Might have been Santa.
This is me.
I know that
she doesn't look like much,
but she'll get us
where we need to be.
Hey, I promise
I'll pay you back.
I'm gonna pay everybody back.
You know,
once we get to Charleston,
and I find my life again.
I know.
What's in Covington?
What do you mean?
Like, what are you guys
known for?
Ah.
Well, we are 20 minutes
from the Canadian border.
Population under 5,000.
Okay.
So if I was going
to South Carolina for Christmas,
what was I doing
all the way up here?
Maybe you were on a work trip.
In the middle of nowhere?
Covington isn't nowhere.
Hmm.
It's just north of nowhere.
Mm-hmm.
Any idea
how you're going to find Mark?
When you get there?
I'm hoping he'll find me.
Who do you think he is?
Relative?
A friend?
A husband.
It never occurred to you
that you might be married?
Well, I don't have a ring.
It could have fallen off
in the water.
♪ ...Till I said hello ♪
♪ And I heard her voice ♪
♪ On the other end
of the line ♪
♪ Now it's Christmas ♪
♪ Christmas ♪
♪ I'm hurrying on my way ♪
-♪ Chris-- ♪
I was liking that song.
You ever had a song
come on the radio,
and it just...
hits a little
too close to home?
Oh, they didn't
give us napkins.
Glove compartment.
Ben?
Who's Ben?
My brother.
Oh, you have a brother?
Is he older or younger?
He's older.
Is that who you're spending
Christmas with?
I missed last Christmas.
I couldn't miss another one.
Here.
Thank you.
Trade you an onion ring
for a french fry?
Yes, please.
Okay.
I'd much rather try these.
♪ In heaven
the bells are ringing ♪
♪ Ding dong merrily on high ♪
♪ Come hear
the people singing... ♪
Hello, hello!
You must be Mr. Bennett.
I'm Barbara.
We spoke on the phone.
Sorry for the late check-in.
Oh, sometimes
it takes us longer
to get where we're going--
especially round the holidays.
Um, first door and second door
at the top of the stairs.
Great. Thank you.
Have a good evening.
Good night.
Uh, come in.
Hey.
If it's okay,
I'd like to be on the road
by 8:00 in the morning.
Yeah, of course.
"Beyond Tomorrow"?
Oh, yeah.
I just turned it on.
Have you seen it?
I used to watch this
with my parents.
Yes, well,
I'm broad enough now.
Is that your laugh?
No.
It is.
- No, it's not--
- There's no use denying it.
We both heard it, that was it.
This does not leave this room.
It's okay.
Oh, there it is again.
I like it.
It's a good laugh.
Hey, do you want
to watch this with me?
Yeah.
...or you get sick
or something,
don't forget we're friends.
You'll let me know
if you need me, won't you?
How can she just leave him?
I mean, after all
they've been through?
I guess she thinks
it will make him happy.
It's getting late.
You should get some rest.
I'm not tired.
Yeah, my mistake...
Good night, Jane.
Good night, Paul.
♪ Away in a manger ♪
♪ No crib for His bed ♪
♪ The little Lord Jesus ♪
♪ Laid down His sweet head ♪
♪ The stars
in the bright sky ♪
♪ Looked down
where He lay... ♪
Yeah, my flight
gets in at 4:00.
I'm excited to see you, too.
I have some news.
Good morning.
Thanks.
Wow, this looks great.
Is everything all right?
Fine.
I think I remembered something.
What was it?
I'm not sure.
It was a phone call.
I don't know,
it went really fast,
and it was hard to understand.
It's a good thing, right?
It means your memory
is starting to come back.
Yeah, I mean,
I was thinking
it would come back at once,
not in small, little,
confusing pieces.
Well, enough little pieces
come back,
eventually, you'll have
the bigger picture.
Good morning.
Morning.
I hope you slept well.
Great, thank you.
When you've finished,
you're welcome
to help decorate the tree.
Thank you for the invitation,
but we've got a really big day
ahead of us on the road.
Of course, I understand.
Um, well, when you're all ready,
I'll get you all checked out.
We can't let her decorate
that whole Christmas tree
by herself.
We don't have time.
Maybe one of the other guests
will help her.
Um...
There's no other guests.
Okay.
So, someone's waiting for you
at this tree lighting?
That's the hope.
And you really
don't remember anything?
No.
Oh...
Did you make this?
No, that's...
my late husband Martin's
handiwork.
He carved a new one
every Christmas.
You're not going to put it
on the tree?
No, it was
a tradition we shared.
It doesn't feel right
to do it without him.
Now, um...
would you care
to do the honors?
Me?
You're the tallest one,
and I don't have a step stool.
Sure.
Aw...
Do you always
make your own bows?
I had Martin
pick out the ribbons.
For the first 20 years
of our marriage,
I couldn't talk him into
anything besides plain red.
"Nothing wrong
with the classics,"
he used to say
Perhaps what
you're going through
is a blessing.
You've got a clean slate.
There's no melancholy
memories to dwell on.
No regrets.
No happy memories, either.
So we're gonna have to skip
our lunch stop
if we want to make it
to Lexington by 8:00.
It was worth it, though,
wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
Oh, good!
I didn't miss you.
Just a little something for you.
I thought it might help
to write down
what you know about yourself.
Keep it all sorted out.
The North Star
has guided many
a weary traveler home again.
Thank you.
You stay strong.
You keep your chin up.
God gives
the strongest soldiers
the toughest battles.
Merry Christmas.
Nellie, I know you.
There's no way anyone
gets out of your booth
without giving up
their life story.
Not this one.
She was real quiet.
Honestly,
she seemed a little blue.
You told my deputy
that she had a purse
and a suitcase.
Mm-hmm, that's right.
But you can't describe
either of them?
The suitcase was...
purple,
and it had letters on it.
Letters?
What do you mean?
A monogram?
An "R" maybe, or a "B"?
All right, well,
we have a purple suitcase,
and a monogram.
Anything else, Sheriff?
Yeah, how about some of
that famous homemade pie?
Now, you know as well as I do
that river stretches for miles.
That bag might be halfway
to the Piscataqua by now.
Yeah, it could be.
Now, how about that pie?
You got it, Sheriff.
Any news from Sheriff Crowley?
Um, he said that
they put out an alert
on the suitcases
I was carrying,
and one had a monogram.
Then you must have
someone in your life.
What?
No one buys themselves
monogrammed luggage.
Hmm.
What are these?
Ah, okay,
you are about to make
a very important self-discovery.
Are you an eggnog
kind of person,
or hot cocoa?
Well, what are you?
I don't want to unduly
influence your selection.
Okay.
That.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- You sure?
Okay.
So?
- It's good.
- Good.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
So you're really
not going to tell me
which one you prefer?
No.
That's not fair.
Can't let you hog
all the mystery.
You want the cocoa, don't you?
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
Oh, the guy at the counter
gave me a lead
on a hotel for the night,
and I already looked it up.
Hi.
Yeah, I would like to book
two rooms
for this evening.
I know it's almost Christmas,
but your website
listed a vacancy?
I understand.
Merry Christmas to you, too.
Well, this might be
more difficult than I thought.
We could sleep in the car.
We're not going
to sleep in the car.
Well, then,
what are we going to do?
I have some family nearby.
Just outside of Charlottesville,
maybe an hour.
- Really?
- Yeah,
my cousin, Jack,
and his wife, Katie.
Do you think that
they'd let us spend the night?
Unless you'd rather we didn't?
No, I'll make the call.
Okay.
Merry Christmas!
Come in, come in.
Thank you so much
for having us.
I know it was last minute...
Oh, are you kidding me?
We're happy to have you!
Uh, sweetheart?
Paul's here!
Katie made up the couch
in the den.
I could take the couch.
You've done
so much for me already.
It's probably better
for my back, anyway.
Paul...
Merry Christmas!
We've missed you!
This is my friend, Jane.
You have such a lovely home.
Oh, thank you.
It's so nice to meet you.
Come with me,
I'll show you to your room.
Oh, thank you.
I'm glad you're here.
It's been too long.
Um...
I want you to know,
we all understood
why you did what you did.
I know you think
you have to carry this alone--
Paul!
Hey, bud!
How are you?
He's only asked
when you were getting here
every 15 minutes.
I got a new sled!
Do you wanna see?
Yeah.
Why don't you help Paul
with his bags first?
Okay.
You got it?
So how do you and Paul
know each other?
We met at the hospital.
I thought you two were...?
Well, I thought
the two of you...
Oh, no! No.
Uh, we're just, um...
We're friends.
Oh.
Yeah.
When are you due?
Three more months.
Can't come soon enough.
I am ready for this little guy
to join us.
It's a boy?
We thought about
keeping it a surprise,
but that lasted
until my third sonogram.
Hey, are you sure
I can't help?
No, I am almost finished.
Uh, hand me that can
of cream of mushroom soup?
Thank you.
All right, everyone, dig in!
I know what I'm starting with.
These scalloped potatoes
look amazing.
Well, Jane helped.
I just handed you the can.
So how's the little guy?
He's finally asleep.
Oh, good.
This pie is out of this world,
and, apparently, I know my pies.
Jack's a chef.
Really?
I work downtown
at a hotel off the square.
Have you ever considered
opening up a restaurant
or something?
As a matter of fact,
he found the perfect location.
We have a baby on the way.
The restaurant can wait.
He said the same thing
when Charlie was born.
It wasn't the right time.
You know, you never know
what life will bring,
so why save dreams for tomorrow
when there is
a perfectly good today?
Right?
Right.
So...
have you settled on any names?
We were thinking about,
um... Ben.
Oh.
Like your brother?
Yeah...
Well, I'm sure
that he's very flattered.
Have you told him yet?
Ben passed away last January.
Just, uh...
excuse me for a second.
Uh, I'd better go see
if he's all right.
Just...
give him a minute.
Why didn't you say anything?
You've got your own problems.
You don't need to listen
to mine.
I'd like to.
I wasn't there.
I was supposed to visit
last Christmas.
I spent every Christmas
with Ben and his wife,
but I couldn't get work off.
At least
that's what I told them.
That's what I told myself.
Truth is,
it was really hard
to see him that way.
You know, sick.
I see that kind of thing
every day at work,
but...
it's different...
when it's someone you love.
You know, he was doing good.
He was doing
really, really good,
fighting the cancer.
It was just that one Christmas.
You know, I just told myself
I needed more time...
I thought I had more time.
You know, I've never
told anyone that before.
I'm so sorry.
I have the gift
that I bought him last year,
and I'm bringing it to him,
to say goodbye.
Couldn't sleep?
Did you remember something?
Oh, no, this, um...
I'm writing a story.
A story?
Yeah.
I can't remember anything
about my own life,
but I just keep having
all these thoughts
springing up.
I needed to put them
somewhere, so...
After I started,
I just couldn't stop.
Can I read it?
Uh, maybe-- No.
Maybe when it's done,
but no.
How about you?
I just needed
a glass of water.
Is that it?
I guess not.
Would it help
to talk about him?
What was he like?
He was great.
Smart, kind.
Really outdoorsy.
Loved fishing.
In fact,
I think I have...
Yeah, there.
We rented a cabin on a lake
a few years back.
Oh, my gosh,
how big is that fish?
It's not that big,
but it was bigger
than anything I'd caught,
and he definitely didn't let me
forget about that.
Oh, this is at the graduation
from my nursing school.
Seems like
he was really proud of you.
Yeah.
I guess so.
I haven't looked at these
in a long time.
Do you have more?
Yeah. Sure.
Hey, Paul.
Hey.
About last night.
I didn't mean to upset you.
You know, I thought
it would be easier,
to just push
the memories of him away,
but...
...it was like losing him
all over again.
I don't want to forget him.
Ben is a great name,
and he would be honored
if you chose it.
Are you sure you can't stay
a little longer?
No, we need to hit the road
if we're gonna
make it to Charleston by 7:00.
Listen,
you should think about
the restaurant,
like Jane said.
Don't wait.
All right,
I should head up there,
see if she's ready.
Oh, you won't find her there.
She's playing with Charlie
in the backyard.
Whoa!
You!
Hey, come on! Come on!
Okay.
Oh...
you gave up our position.
We don't have much time.
What?
On the count of three,
I go right, you go left.
You with me?
Yeah, I'm with you.
Okay.
One, two, three,
go!
Get him, get him, get him!
Yay!
You give us a call
when you're all settled in.
Will do.
It was real nice to meet you.
Don't be a stranger.
I won't.
Sorry, I'm not as fast
as I used to be.
- Merry Christmas, Paul.
- Merry Christmas.
It's been so nice
to see you like this.
Happy.
I thought you could use this.
Oh, my gosh, thank you.
It's all good.
Thank you, thank you
so much for having us.
Any time.
Okay, well, merry Christmas.
Thanks so much.
- Merry Christmas.
Can I take that for you?
- Sure.
- Great.
Hey, do you want me to drive?
You don't have a license.
Well, it's not fair
that you need to drive
the entire way.
Well, it might not be fair,
but it's legal.
You can barely
keep your eyes open.
My eyes are fine.
I'm gonna take these,
thank you so much.
Wait, wait, wait.
Please don't do this.
Jane...
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Uh...
You know what, you're right.
You should drive.
You have quite the arm.
I wonder
if you used to play baseball.
We need gas.
We should probably stop up here.
Grab lunch?
We're making great time.
Yeah, it's not that.
It's just...
I remember something else.
What was it?
I was in a house,
and there was a man there,
and I was leaving.
It felt like
we got in a fight?
Who was he to you?
I don't know.
Do you think
it's the same person
from the letters?
Mark?
Maybe.
He just, he looked hurt.
It looked like I hurt him,
or something.
I don't know, I just,
I never...
I've been so desperate
to fill these blanks,
you know,
I haven't stopped to consider
that maybe I might not like
what I find.
You know, maybe my subconscious
is trying to hide something
from me.
Like...
what if I'm just
a terrible person?
You're not a terrible person.
Well, how do you know that?
Because I know you.
I don't even know me.
You don't see it, do you?
The effect that you have
on people.
You...
you've got this light in you.
It's obvious to anyone
who spends
five minutes with you.
You may have made
some mistakes in the past--
we all have--
but it doesn't define
who you are in the future.
You know,
mistakes can be forgiven.
Are you working on your story?
Yeah.
Trying to figure out the ending.
I hope it's a happy one.
Me too.
Stonestreet Inn.
Confirming my reservation.
Stonestreet Inn?
Yeah, it's the nicest hotel
in Pickering.
To be fair,
it's the only hotel
in Pickering,
but it's still very nice.
Well, I thought that you'd be
staying with family.
My parents passed
a few years ago.
Well, what about
your sister-in-law?
We haven't spoken.
Why not?
It's like I said,
I wasn't there for Ben.
Marissa was furious.
I don't blame her.
Well, so you're going
all the way home
and you're not
going to see anyone?
I'm going to see my brother.
You just told me
that mistakes can be forgiven.
Some can.
This one can't.
I'll get this.
Traffic looks good.
We should hit Charleston
by 6:00.
Close your eyes.
Hold out your hands.
Open them.
What's this for?
A gift.
Try it on.
Come on!
Come on.
How do I look?
Something to remember me by.
Come on.
Let's head back to the car.
♪ There's music
in the city... ♪
I think the universe
wants you to listen.
♪ There's a big, old tree
for all to see ♪
♪ Where the children
run and play... ♪
It's pretty catchy.
♪ I look out
through my window... ♪
Oh!
♪ Somethin' just
don't seem right... ♪
All right, here we go.
♪ ...Till I said hello ♪
♪ And heard her voice ♪
♪ On the other end
of the line ♪
♪ Now it's Christmas ♪
♪ Christmas ♪
♪ I'm hurrying on my way ♪
♪ Christmas, Christmas ♪
♪ Like I'm riding
in a one-horse sleigh ♪
♪ Well, I don't have to hear
no jingle bells... ♪
Last stop.
You ready?
Ready.
Don't worry,
it does this sometimes.
You just gotta--
Well, could be a few things.
Best-case scenario,
it's a shot battery.
Worst-case scenario?
If it's the alternator,
you need to leave it here
for a day or two,
while we hunt down the part.
Oh, no, we don't have
a day or two.
We cannot get stuck here.
Is there anything
that you can do?
I was just about to lock up
when I got the call.
It's Christmas Eve.
I know it's a lot to ask,
but it would really
mean a lot to us
if you could help us out.
Please.
All right.
Tell you what,
leave your number on the pad.
Give me an hour.
I can't promise anything,
but I'll do the best I can.
Right.
Thank you so much.
Yup.
We don't have time for this.
The mechanic said
it would be an hour.
We'll be back on the road
by 4:30.
We'll be cutting it close,
but we'll get there.
Yeah, that's if he can fix it.
The tree lighting ends at 8:00.
What if anybody who knows me
is gone before I can get there?
Then I'm back
to where I started.
What...
What am I going to do?
♪ The weary world rejoices ♪
♪ For yonder breaks
a new and glorious morn ♪
♪ Fall ♪
♪ On your knees ♪
♪ Oh, hear ♪
♪ The angel voices ♪
♪ Oh, night ♪
♪ Divine ♪
♪ When Christ was born ♪
♪ Oh, night ♪
♪ Divine ♪
♪ Oh, night... ♪
♪ Di... ♪
♪ ...vine ♪
- Oh, hey!
- Hi! Hi!
Hi, buddy.
Where did you come from?
Do you see his owner?
Uh...
no.
Are you lost?
Yeah, I know the feeling.
Check his collar,
see if his address is on there.
Okay.
No, wait, stop!
No!
Wait!
The plow guy found this
while he was salting
the back roads.
Recognized it
from the description we put out.
We have a few articles
of clothing in here.
We've got a t-shirt,
a pair of jeans.
See what you can pull
off of that.
It's been in the river
for a few days.
Yeah, well, it's worth a shot.
Huh.
What do you make of that?
I don't know,
maybe she's got
a little one at home.
Should we call our Jane Doe?
No.
No, let's see what we get
off the laptop first.
Okay.
There's no car in the driveway.
It's Christmas.
They might be away.
Sorry!
Can I help you?
Oh!
Oh, sweetheart!
We were so worried about you.
He slipped through the fence
last night.
My son's been looking for him
all morning.
Where did you find him?
Outside the church.
Just happened to be
at the right place
at the right time, I guess.
I stopped believing
in coincidences
a long time ago,
especially at Christmas.
I can't thank you both enough.
We're just happy
that he's home.
Do you mind just waiting here
for one second?
Just hang on.
These are Winter family
Christmas croissants.
We make them at my bakery,
but they are
my husband's favorites.
Aw, thank you.
Seriously,
thank you both so much.
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
- Oh, merry Christmas.
Aw...
Well, we should
get back to the garage.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, if the car isn't fixed,
we'll get a train,
or a cab.
Something.
We'll figure it out.
I won't leave you
until you're where you belong.
I promise.
Thank you.
Here, why don't you take those?
Hello!
Merry Christmas, Rebecca!
Merry Christmas, Mark!
Jane?
Rebecca!
Who's Rebecca?
I'm Rebecca!
I have a name,
and it's Rebecca!
Rebecca!
That's a good name, right?
That is a great name.
It's a great name!
Rebecca who?
I don't know.
I don't even care!
Rebecca, I--
Hour's up.
We should get back.
Yeah.
Hello?
Just give me a sec, guys.
Let's hope for the best.
We're due for some good news.
It's Mark.
Who?
The man in my memories.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Well, he must be
pretty important then,
if you keep remembering him.
Yeah.
That's a good thing, right?
Because he'll be
waiting for you there,
and...
you'll get your answers.
Right.
Um...
Sheriff Crowley's calling.
Hello?
You did?
Uh-huh.
No.
Merry Christmas to you, too.
They find anything?
My suitcase.
Was there anything
useful inside?
Um...
Yeah, my laptop,
which they can't get on.
Um...
some clothes...
A sweater?
A little girl's sweater.
Could I be a mom?
How could someone...
How could I forget
something like that?
A child-- my own child?
Good news!
You're all set.
Replaced the battery.
The battery?
That's all it was?
You two got yourselves
a Christmas miracle.
Let's get you home.
♪ ...And it warms my heart
to feel her love ♪
♪ And know
how much she cares ♪
♪ It's funny how going back ♪
♪ Can get you back
where you belong ♪
♪ It's the difference
in just a melody ♪
♪ And my favorite
Christmas song ♪
♪ Now, it's Christmas ♪
♪ Christmas ♪
♪ I'm hurrying on my way ♪
♪ Christmas, Christmas ♪
♪ Like I'm riding
in a one-horse sleigh ♪
♪ Well, I don't have to hear
no jingle bells ♪
♪ Just the ringing
of the phone ♪
♪ Mama just called and said ♪
♪ It's time
for you to come home ♪
♪ Mama just called and said ♪
♪ It's time
for you to come home ♪
I think you should call her.
Who?
Marissa.
It's hard enough as it is
just making the trip.
I...
I don't think I can face her.
I think you should try.
Why is it so important to you?
In less than an hour,
I'm going to find out
what's waiting for me
in Charleston...
...but even
if I get my answers...
...I'm not sure I'll be okay
unless I know you're okay, too.
♪...O night divine ♪
♪ O night... ♪
Wait, wait, your bag!
Okay, I'm going
to park the car,
and then I'll meet you inside.
Okay, uh, I'll be at the tree.
Okay.
- See you there.
- Yeah.
Rebecca?
You made it!
Oh...
I'm so glad you're here.
I was worried
you wouldn't come.
You're here!
I missed you!
We really missed you.
Mark?
Yes?
Why are you
looking at me like that?
Dad, can I go hang out
with Ava?
- Sure, but stay close.
- Okay.
I'll see you later.
I, uh...
I don't know who you are.
What do you mean,
you don't know who I am?
I mean, I thought
that when I saw your face,
it would all just
come back to me,
but I...
I still don't--
Rebecca, what's going on?
Rebecca?
It is you.
I cannot believe it.
You have some nerve coming here.
?
You should be.
Mom and Dad have been trying
to reach you for days.
They are beside themselves
with worry.
Annie, I'm sure that she has
a very good explanation.
Yeah, well, she can't
answer her phone?
Are you ignoring
their calls, too?
Sweetheart...
Did you know about this?
Yes, but--
And you didn't tell me?
Mark...
Hello!
Rebecca, Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas, Mark!
Where's Annie and--
There you are!
Just in time for dinner!
Come here!
Oh, it's so good to see you.
Oh, you look great.
Oh, my gosh,
you look great...
Mark!
Would you have let me
if I had?
I remember!
What?
Oh, my gosh, I remember,
just like they said I would!
You're Annie!
You're my sister!
Okay, what is going on here?
I don't know,
she's been acting very strangely
since she got here.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh, I have made
a horrible mistake.
I...
Uh...
What?
Paul?
Paul!
This turkey is amazing,
but I am totally stuffed.
You did good.
How's everything
at your office?
Well...
I've been waiting
to have you all together
to tell you--
You got the promotion.
I knew it.
No, actually,
I have decided
to pursue my writing full-time.
You know, I've got
three short stories published
this year,
and it's just--
it's time to make the leap.
Well,
that sounds very...
exciting.
What are you going to do
about money?
Insurance?
Have you thought
of any of these things?
Of course, I have.
I've saved up enough
to get me through
the next six months.
And then?
And then
I will reassess, Annie.
Come on, Peanut,
time for bed.
You can't just drop
all of your responsibilities
to chase
some silly, little dream.
I mean,
what are you going to do
about the nursing home?
You agreed
to pay for half the price.
You know that mom and dad
cannot handle it on their own.
I said I would and I will.
- How?
- I will figure it out.
You could not wait
till after Christmas?
You had to do this now?
I should have known
that you were gonna react
like this.
- What--
- You've never trusted me
- to make my own decisions!
- Well, how can I,
when you go and do
something like this?
For once in my life
I would like to feel
like you believed in me.
Oh, grow up.
Oh, my gosh.
I shouldn't have come.
This was a mistake.
I am trying to help you.
Yeah, well, maybe
I'd be better without it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Please don't do this.
Merry Christmas, Mark.
Just give her time.
I'm guessing
Annie didn't think I'd come.
I don't think she thought
it was a possibility.
Look, I love you,
and I love my wife,
but you both can be
incredibly stubborn sometimes.
Last Christmas,
you two said some things
you probably wish you hadn't.
So you invited me here
without telling her,
or without telling me
I wasn't welcome?
I knew deep down,
that neither of you wanted
to spend
another Christmas apart.
What do I say to her?
Say what you feel.
This is your chance.
What if she doesn't
forgive me?
She will.
Someone just needs
to make the first move.
Retrograde amnesia.
Amnesia?
Well, are you hurt?
What did the doctors say?
Oh, bumps and bruises,
honestly.
I cannot believe this.
You spent
the whole last week alone?
No, not alone.
I'm glad you're okay.
I need to go
and check on Casey.
Of course.
Here, let me help you
with those.
Okay.
Thanks, Mark.
Yeah, of course.
Hi.
It's Paul.
How's Maine?
Snowy.
So I've heard.
Sugar?
No, thank you.
Well, it was good
to hear from you, Paul.
It's been a while.
Sorry.
I understand.
I'm sure the hospital
keeps you very busy.
That's not what I meant.
I'm...
I'm really sorry
that I wasn't here for you
when you needed me.
Or when Ben needed me.
He understood how hard it was
for you to see him like that.
But I'm a nurse,
and...
I see that stuff every day,
and I couldn't even...
Ben wanted to keep
the worst of it from you.
He was always trying
to protect you.
He was...
so, so proud of you, Paul,
and he loved you very much.
He never blamed you,
and neither did I.
I miss him.
I know.
Me too.
I didn't even say goodbye.
There's so many things
that I wanted to tell him,
that I needed to tell him.
So tell him.
He'll be listening.
I shouldn't have left
that night...
...and I never should have
waited an entire year
to apologize.
I do have a confession
to make, though.
I'm not supposed to be here.
I wasn't planning on coming.
I rented a cabin up in Maine.
I was planning
on spending Christmas there,
working alone.
Then the storm hit,
the accident happened,
and I never made it there.
Mark had sent me
that invitation,
and I chose to ignore it,
but when I couldn't remember
who I was,
I looked at the clipping,
and I thought that...
That you were headed here.
The only thing
that mattered to me
was finding out who I was,
and who I belonged to.
What's this?
It's a gift from a friend.
Open it.
They're stories
that I wrote along the way.
Annie, even when
I had nothing left,
even when I didn't know
who I was,
I had this.
This is who I am...
...and I know that you think
that it's just some silly dream,
but it's my dream.
It's not a silly dream.
But I worry about you, Rebecca.
I'm your sister.
It's my job.
I don't want to fight anymore.
I don't want another year
to go by
where we're not talking, okay?
I miss you.
I missed you, too.
Is that cherry pie?
Yup.
That's...
That's for the, uh,
the party tomorrow.
Well, I don't think anyone
would miss a piece.
I'm really glad you came.
Me too.
Okay, because
it's Christmas Eve,
your mom and I decided
you can open one present.
But only one.
Okay.
Ooh...
Rectangular.
There's all of the colors...
There's, like...
Okay...
"Jane,
if you're reading this,
it means that you've finally
reached your destination.
I hope the life
waiting for you
is worthy of the amazing
person that you are.
I wanted to thank you
for making a hard trip
one of the highlights
of my life.
I'm not sure I could have
done it without you.
Have a very Merry Christmas.
I hope you get
everything that you want.
Paul."
Sorry it took so long
to get here.
You know, sometimes,
it's easy to get lost
along the way.
I miss you.
You know, after you died,
all I could think about
was all the times
that I could have
just gotten in my car,
come see you,
that I could have picked up
the phone to call you...
...till it just became easier
not to think about you at all.
I don't want that, Ben.
I want to remember yesterday
and bring you with me tomorrow.
You know, no regrets.
We don't know how long we get,
you know?
But as long as
there's a tomorrow...
it's worth seeing
what's going to happen.
That's what I'm going to do.
So...
Merry Christmas, Ben.
I love you.
You were right.
This is the only hotel
in this entire town.
What are you doing here?
You left before I got a chance
to say goodbye.
Oh.
So you're here to say goodbye?
No.
I am here to invite you
to our Christmas party.
It's nothing wild,
just friends and family.
Your memories?
I got 'em back.
Just like
Dr. Grant said I would.
That's great.
Yeah, my, um...
my sister was there,
waiting for me
at the tree-lighting ceremony,
my brother-in-law, Mark.
Brother-in-law?
Brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law...
And my niece.
You know,
I had to explain to her
why the sweater I bought her
was still up in Maine
in a very soggy suitcase,
'cause I hadn't had
a chance yet to mail it.
Everything I wanted
was waiting for me.
Family.
Forgiveness.
I thought I'd be happy.
I am. I am happy,
but...
...there's still
something missing.
When I finally made it home,
and got to see
a lifetime full of memories,
I...
...I realized that...
I've never quite met
anyone like you.
Well, I have definitely
never met anyone like you.
You said
you hoped I got
what I wanted for Christmas.
This is it.
It's you.
♪ Well, I don't have to hear
no jingle bells ♪
♪ Just the ringing
of the phone ♪
♪ Mama just called and said ♪
♪ It's time
for me to come home ♪
♪ The pies are in the oven ♪
♪ You can almost
taste the air ♪
♪ And it warms my heart
to feel her love ♪
♪ And know
how much she cares... ♪
Jack! Will!
Hot chocolate is ready!
♪ ...Can get you
back where you belong ♪
♪ It's the difference
in just a melody ♪
♪ And my favorite
Christmas song ♪
♪ Now, it's Christmas ♪
♪ Christmas ♪
♪ I'm hurryin' on my way ♪
♪ Christmas, Christmas ♪
♪ Like I'm riding
in a one-horse sleigh ♪
♪ Well, I don't have to hear
no jingle bells ♪
♪ Just the ringing
of the phone ♪
♪ Mama just called and said ♪
♪ It's time
for me to come home... ♪
It must be nice,
finally knowing
where you belong.
Yeah.
It is.