Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
You punk...
Think you can pick a fight with yakuza
and get away with it?
As of today
this is Tokyo Manji Gang's territory
Got it?
No...stop!
Shit
[ Alarm ]
Yo! Get up!
Get up!
- Sorry...   - Shut the alarm!
- Sorry!   - Turn it off!
OK, it's off. Sorry
Don't rely on me to get you up!
Thanks...
Ugh
This is still edible
Don't hesitate, Takemichi
Just do it
A dumptruck rode up onto
the sidewalk
in Shibuya yesterday
killing two pedestrians
The victims were Hinata Tachibana, age 27
and Naoto Tachibana, age 25
Both were pronounced dead
at the hospital
Tachibana...
Hinata...
The only girlfriend I ever had is dead...
The victims were Hinata Tachibana, age 27
and Naoto Tachibana, age 25
Police believe an escalating turf war
between Tokyo Manji Gang known as "Toman"
and yakuza are behind the...
Morning
Good morning, Manager!
I told you
no smartphone during work
Porn, right?
- No...   - You can go now
Go to a club and get laid
No girlfriend at your age?
And still a virgin?
Trying to set a record?
Are you mad?
Like, "If I was still in high school
I'd kick you hard"?
Guys like you glorify the past
You peaked in high school
Am I right?
Sorry...
That's all you ever say
I bet you've gotten away with
apologizing your whole life
Sorry...
Move
Darn guy needs to shave
I hate guys with stubble
So what if I'm a virgin?
I'll set a world record!
I did have a girlfriend
even though she was my one and only...
Was that my peak?
Where did I go wrong?
This crappy life...
Ow!
What the hell, Takemichi?
- Did I just die?   - Huh?
Akkun?
- Is it you?!   - What, dude?
Yamagishi! Oh my god!
- What's wrong with you?   - What's up?
Makoto!
Still scratching your crotch
Takuya!
- What?   - What's with you?
We're the Mizo High 5, right?
Wait a minute... What?
You're so obsessed with Tachibana
you can't even think straight
Why is Hinata Tachibana dating you?
I get it!
This is a flashback
What's a flashback?
You know!
When you see your life flash before you
right before you die?
You're really funny
Let's go
What the hell?
Who is this lame punk?
Oh my god, I remember now
This was me, back in the day!
Enough already!
Get serious!
We need to get into fight-mode
Fight?
With who?
Shibuya High sophs
Make way for the future hair stylist
Takemichi, call Masaru again
Masaru?
Masaru at Shibuya High
Your mad dog cousin
He'll keep the seniors away, right?
Oh, yeah... I remember now
Where's your phone, Takemichi?
Whoa! Flip phone!
What? Flip phone?
July 2nd... 2010?
Takemichi
I'll take on the boss
You take his #2
Hold on...
Can I get something straight?
It seems we're going to fight
Seems? We are
But why?
They treat us like wimps!
Wimps...
who cares?
You're gonna whack 'em
with your backhand, right?
I'm counting on you
I was cool...
I was so cool back then!
- So cool   - Yeah, cool
Yo, Shibuya High soph!
- Come down here!   - Running away?
Idiot!
Idiot
Was that cool?
- Yeah, perfect   - Yeah, Takemichi
That's good
Yo!
So you're the ones
messing with our sophomores
It's the seniors!
For real...
That's... Kiyomasa
Mr. Kiyomasa to you
Mr. Kiyomasa of Tokyo Manji Gang...
Tokyo Manji Gang...
Shit, Takemichi!
Call Masaru, quick!
Sorry!
That's Masaru right there...
They were out of cream puffs
so I bought an éclair
Cream puffs and eclairs
are totally different
Yes. Total opposites...
Masaru, the mad dog?
Loyal dog, more like!
Go buy me some cream puffs!
We came to fight!
Where's the punchline?
There isn't one
Akkun, no!
- I can't turn back now   - You have to!
He'll will thrash us
and make us slaves for life!
What are you talking about?
Let's run!
Run!
Hold it!
No one gets away
This was the start of my lifetime of apologies
Ready? Bark!
Let me hear you bark
We got beaten up every day
I dropped out of school to escape
Nothing went right after that
- Sorry!  - You piece of crap!
Notthing goes well
You're in the way
Sorry
Apology...
after apology...
Sorry
My life went off track
because of him...
I'm sorryyyyy!
Kneel!
Head on the ground
From today
you're property of Toman
Answer!
Yes! Please!
50-page essay on the difference
between cream puffs and éclairs
You're too easy on them!
These punks can't write
Neither can you!
You have 'til tomorrow
That really hurt...
Don't tell anyone I cried...
You alive, Akkun?
How about you guys?
Is everyone OK?
Yamagishi?
Where's my glasses?
Your date with Tachibana...
Sorry you missed it
Shut up!
Is your leg asleep?
Lamer!
This flashback sucks
I thought I escaped all this
Why am I reliving it?
Where you going, Takemichi?
This ain't no joke!
This isn't how it should end!
I know my life sucks
I know my life sucks!
Hinata Tachibana...
What did she look like?
[ TACHIBANA ]
You always appear out of nowhere
Hinata...Tachibana...
Did you fight again?
I'll fix you up
I have some bandages
Does it hurt?
What the...
- Sorry   - Does it hurt that much?
Why do you keep fighting
when you always get hurt?
Aren't you tired of it?
I was. 10 years ago
10 years ago?
Nothing...
Anyway, I'm glad I met you
What?
I saw you yesterday and today
and I'll see you tomorrow
Actually, I'll be dead 10 years from now
This is a just flashback...
Dead?
You won't die
Why not?
Because you're tough
Who, me?
Let's just say you die 10 years from now
But you're still with me
10 years from now, right?
Unfortunately
I'll be even more worthless then
Then be a man
And be with me 10 years from now
Why did you decide to go out with me?
I'm going home
See you tomorrow
Tomorrow...
You're tall for a middle schooler
How tall are you?
Sit down
Sit down!
I bet you drink milk every day
That's Tachibana's brother...
- Where's your money?   - Found it
I'll buy you a roll
Why are you messing with a middle school kid?
Who are you?
Get lost, punk
- Punk?   - He's so cool!
I'm emotionally unstable right now
I'll kill you!
Here
Thanks
Don't tell your sister
It ain't cool
OK. I won't tell her
You're so big
You should learn how to defend yourself
I don't like fighting
The victims were Hinata Tachibana
and Naoto Tachibana
What's wrong?
I know...
You protect her!
You protect Tachibana!
What are you...
This sounds crazy but listen!
I die 10 years from now
then time travel back to my high school days
It sounds unreal
but you and Hinata
are gonna die on July 1, 2020
In a truck accident
involving the street gang called Tokyo Manji Gang
- Street gang?   - Listen!
You protect Tachibana!
Unfortunately...
I just see it on the news
Pitiful, huh?
What am I talking about?
This is a flashback...
I'm in love with your sister
I'm crazy about her
I remember now
She really sees me
A poor loser like me
What are you saying?
Just remember!
10 years from now on July 1
I'm off to my next flashback now
I'm counting on you
Are you OK?
He's awake
- Did I die?   - You're alive
I'm alive?
I survived?
And died?
- I'm alive!   - Yes!
This detective rescued you
just in time
Long time no see, Takemichi
Naoto!
Why are you wearing a suit?
Is this a flashback?
What year is this? Where am I?
July 2, 2020
You wet yourself a little, that's all
No way...
But why are you alive, Naoto?
I knew it
In the world you know
I'm supposed to be dead
"In the world I know"?
What the hell is that?
On July 2, 2010
you appeared and prophesied that
my sister and I would die 10 years later
Wasn't that a flashback?
You travelled back in time
Somehow I survived
and was able to rescue you
Time travel?
I should've died yesterday
Yeah. I saw it on the news
But you warned me
and here I am
You changed my destiny
I believed you that day
and became a detective
To protect my sister
So...is Tachibana alive too?
She died
I couldn't change that
How did you survive then?
Ow!
I warned her many times
but she wouldn't believe me!
I don't blame her
She knew nothing about Toman!
Ow, that hurts...
It's going to hurt a lot more
What do you mean?
Did you forget what you said?
Toman is responsible for my sister's death!
Sorry...
You can't even kill one lousy person
You haven't progressed at all in 10 years
That's her pet goldfish from 10 years ago
She won it at the festival you both went to
I adopted it
Back then, Toman was just a street gang
Now they're a powerful
crime organization
They developed drug routes
and are behind many
unexplained deaths in recent years
Even the police can't pin them down
This is insane...
Who's this?
Manjiro Sano
Tokyo Manji Gang's leader and...
Tetta Kisaki
another key player
Manji wouldn't be what it is today
if these two had never met
I called you because I want you
to travel back in time again
Are you crazy?
Shaking hands with me seems to be the key
Remember our handshake 10 years ago?
At that moment, your essence disappeared
No way...
Your mission is to return to high school
and stop Sano and Kisaki from meeting
They met in July 2010
I'm going home
Takemichi!
I can't do it!
I can't!
What do you expect from a loser like me?
I believed in you 10 years ago!
It's your turn to trust me!
The next time you return
I believe my sister will be alive
Hinata Tachibana...
Alive...
Once you complete your mission
shake my hand and come back
I'm telling you, I don't think I can do it
- Not a loser like me   - Takemichi
You can change destiny
What day is it?
You OK, Takemichi?
Akkun, Makoto, Takuya, Yamagishi
So I'm really here
Of course you are
We have no right to refuse
Why?
It's a gladiator match sponsored by Toman
That's right!
I remember now
Kiyomasa forced us to fight...
Next match!
From Mizo High, Takuya!
From Shibuya High
Kishino!
Can you fight, Takuya?
You're kind of sickly, right?
I'll avenge you
- Buy me a beef bowl later...   - Let's go!
Takuya
I wanna fight in his place
But if we defy Kiyomasa, we're dead
I have to do this
Do what, Akkun?
Look at that
Akkun stabbed Kiyomasa on July 7
We'll never laugh again
as long as you're alive...
What day is it?
The 7th
We should be at the fireworks festival
Akkun, don't do it...
Takemichi
How did you know?
Go back
I'll take care of this
Stop this match!
What do you think you're doing?
These matches are getting boring
Kiyomasa! King versus slave
Fight me
You talking to me?
I don't see any other lame kings around here!
Takemichi...
Move!
Has he lost his mind?
Kiyomasa, you belong to Toman, right?
If I win
introduce me to Manjiro Sano
You punk!
How dare you call his name?
You die. Right now
Takemichi!
You can run and beg forgiveness
all your life
but you'll still be
a worthless piece of shit
Then be a man
And be with me 10 years from now
Takemichi! Enough!
Mr. Kiyomasa! I'll fight!
- Takemichi!   - Don't do it
You guys need to shut up
For the first time in my life
I ain't running away
Shut up, all of you!
If I win...
I wanna meet Manjiro Sano
You...
Someone! Bring me a bat!
Stop, Takemichi!
- Takemichi!   - You'll die!
Enough! Give it up!
I can't!
I can't give up now!
There's a reason
why I can never give up
Give me the bat!
Fine
You'll have to kill me to win
Yo, Kiyomasa
You lost your audience
It's him!
It's the boss!
The big boss?
No, that's Draken, the #2
The small one's the boss. Mikey
The leader of Toman?
Remember this angle when you bow to the boss
Yes, sir...
Your head's right in the strike zone
Wanna see what happens
if I use this?
My apologies!
Your name?
Takemichi...Hanagaki
I see
Takemitchy
From today, we're buddies!
What?
What Mikey says goes
Right Takemitchy?
So who's in charge here?
Gladiator matches are stupid
Don't disgrace Toman's name!
We're sorry!
What, Boss?
Kenchin, I dropped my bean bun
- It's still good!   - The 3 second rule!
- Pick it up! Hurry!   - Go buy a new one!
Don't call me Kenchin
See ya, Takemitchy
That's Manjiro Sano...
Is our life of slavery over?
It's over!
Lie down here. Just do it
From today, you're Takemitchy
What Mikey says goes. Right?
- It wasn't like that   - Stupid
Thanks...
I wet my pants a bit, though
You were so cool
Takuya
What?
- Nothing   - Were you copying me?
I wasn't copying you
This fight was too much
Nah, he just bashed my head
into the railing, that's all
Railing?
Why do you have to fight day after day?
I'd like to live in peace, too
She's so cute!!
Life was good 10 years ago!
Why don't I just stay here?
She's my girlfriend...
I wish I was a guy
What?
Then I could protect you
No, I'll protect you, Hina
I can't imagine a world without you
So I'll protect you
You called me Hina...
Yeah. First-name basis
I...
was a real loser until now
I ran away from trouble
and apologized whenever
But I...
Naoto!
You came back
I didn't mean to shake your hand
So my theory was correct
What date and time did you return to?
July 7th. Around 5 pm
And you shook my hand...
Around 8 pm?
What's going on over here?
I knew it. It all makes sense
So what happened to me?
When you went back in time
you were fast asleep, like in a coma
Suspended animation
It seems you can travel back
to the same day and time as now
So if you travel back in time today
it'll be 10 years ago today
If you stay a week
you'll return to this world a week later too
I'll be fired from my job
Who cares?
My sister's life is on the line
What about your mission?
I met Mikey
- Mikey?   - Manjiro Sano, head of Toman
That was fast...
But I haven't met Kisaki yet
Forget Kisaki
But he can't meet Sano, right?
Kill Sano
If Manjiro Sano dies
they'll never meet
Then my sister will live
It's simple
But I can't...
How much damage have they done?
The head of Manji killed my sister
Does he deserve to live?
Kill Mikey?
How am I supposed to do that?
Think outsiders can just
walk in here and leave alive?
Mikey?
There you are, Takemitchy!
Hey. Watch your back
Let's go, Mikey
I'm bored, Takemitchy
Let's go play
Out of our way, trash
They're carpet, Kenchin
Congratulations! You've just been promoted
Line up...
In a row!
- That's it   - Closer together
The other way around
Nice
- How's that, Mikey?   - Perfect
Nice?
Naoto!
Takemitchy
The guy's a demon
How can I kill him?
What do you wanna eat?
Anything
Just getting my shoes on
Hurry up
Wait a minute!
Hina...
Who are you?
What was that for...?
Why are you taking him?
He's not going with you
Let's go
- Hina, this is...   - It's OK
I'll protect you
Slap him and walk away?
Are you kidding me?
I'm dead serious
I'm 100% serious about Takemichi
Your hand...
Please let her go
Can't hear you
Hina's shaking
Let her go, idiot
You're shaking too
So what?
I promised to protect her!
I won't give up
Not this time
I see
I thought we could be buddies
So? How do you wanna die?
Promise me one thing
Don't lay a finger on Hina
Takemichi...
Says who?
Faked you out!
Ow!
You think I'd beat up a girl?
"I won't give up!"
Who says that over a girl nowadays?
Old school guy, huh?
I didn't say that!
- You did   - No, I didn't
You were cool
Thanks
Um!
You're Takemichi's friends?
Sorry! I misunderstood!
Maybe you did
Can we borrow him for a minute?
Please do
I'm going back to class
- Bye   - What about me?
- You come with us   - No...
She slapped Mikey
thinking we were abducting you
She's a freak!
I'm really sorry...
She's a good girl. A real gem
But you'd better protect her
when she "misunderstands"
Yes, sir
Um...
Why are you bothering with a guy like me?
Stupid question
We live in different worlds, so to speak
We breathe the same air
I have a brother, 10 years older
He died, though
He was weak
but reckless too
A weakling who's gutsy enough
to pick a fight with someone tougher
You remind me of him
He's way better looking, though
Whoa!
Thugs aren't cool anymore
But back in my brother's day, they were big and cool
picking fights
They took care of their own shit
What's so uncool about that?
Why can't guys like us
have a place to live how we want?
I'm going to make our own era...
Toman is a team
Each member is ready to die for each other
Die for each other...
We'll take it as far as we can
Come with us, Takemichi Hanagaki
I like you
Tough guys are a dime a dozen
But you'll take on anyone
to protect something you care about
That's rare nowadays
Wanna come to our meeting?
Meeting?
I don't think I should...
It'll be fine
[ TOKYO MANJI GANG ]
Hey, you!
Who said you could enter my line of sight?
I'm sorry!
- Get lost   - I'm sorry!
I knew it
I knew this would happen
Hey, Hanagaki
Kiyomasa...
The past is water under the bridge, OK?
Sure
- Water under the bridge?   - That's the past
I didn't say anything about the future
Evening, Boss!
Kiyomasa!
How dare you show your face around here
Take off the uniform
You're out for good
Start the meeting!
[ TOKYO MANJI GANG ]
The mood changed...
We're here today to discuss "Moebius"
It's going to be an all-out war
Some of you may have heard
that Pah's buddy got into it with Moebius' boss
Can we go home now?
I'm not done with you!
He'll hurt anyone
even a woman
That's not how we fight!
So what's it gonna be, Pah?
Moebius is big
We'll suffer casualties
I don't wanna cause trouble
That's not what I asked
Wanna fight or not?
I wanna fight
I wanna kill them!
Of course you do
Hey!
Anybody here gonna feel troubled
if we avenge Pah's buddy?
Anybody here
wanna make peace with Moebius?
Nobody, right?
It's decided
We crush Moebius!
July 13
Showdown at Musashi Festival
Whoa!
So this is Toman's boss...
What, punk?
Mikey may be a good guy after all
Sano, a good guy?
Are you kidding?
He's the head of Tokyo Manji Gang
I know that's bad
- But he's not really evil...   - What are you saying?
Forgive Sano for killing my sister?
Never!
I wish I could kill him!
I swear, he's not like that!
When Hina slapped him
he just laughed and forgave her
He's capable of laughing!
The Tokyo Manji Gang of today
isn't what Mikey envisioned
So I want to talk to him in person
Ask him why Toman changed
I don't care
Just go back in time, kill Sano
and destroy Toman
It's the only way to save my sister!
Nobody can see him now anyway
Unless you know someone in their executive ranks
Do I?
That's Akkun!
Atsushi Sendo isn't a member
He was arrested for stabbing Kiyomasa
I stopped him
I stopped him, didn't I?
I did...
Things are a little off
What do you mean?
Takemichi
Even if you meet Sendo, don't say anything
Aren't you coming?
They're Toman. I'm a cop
Welcome
Good evening
Any preferences?
Akkun...
You must be Mr. Hanagaki, the owner's friend
He's in the VIP Room
Owner...
Long time, no see, Takemichi
Long time...
I...
was waiting for you
Wow
You're lucky, Takemichi
You haven't changed at all
I wish I had, but...
You stay the way you are
So you own this huge club
We live in different worlds
But my world is empty
The guy with you was a cop, right?
Uh, no...
Naoto Tachibana
Hinata's brother
He saved you on the train tracks that day
How'd you know?
Because it was me...
That day
I pushed you off the platform
It was me
It can't be...
It's true
- I tried to kill you   - Stop it!
It's not even funny!
Akkun...
You would never...
You were gonna stab Kiyomasa
to save Takuya
You're tough, but kind-hearted...
I...
consider you my best friend!
It's been 10 years
but that...
has never changed!
That's nice to hear
But I still tried to kill you
I'm Kisaki's slave now
I'm terrified of him
You haven't progressed at all in 10 years
How did it come to this?
Toman wasn't like this 10 years ago
Once Draken died
Mikey changed
Draken...
died?
He shouldn't have died
Hey
You can travel through time, right?
That's the only way certain things make sense
How did you know that I tried
to stab Kiyomasa?
How did Naoto Tachibana know
you were going to fall on the tracks?
What?
I wish we could stay innocent
like we were back then
Ow! That hurts!
- Does it?   - Yeah!
Wait. My nose is running
Akkun
I don't really understand
but I know you're trying
Akkun, be careful
I kinda admired you back then
Crying, but never giving up
Akkun, watch out!
If...
you can really go back...
save everyone, will ya?
Crybaby hero
Akkun
Akkun!
Takemichi!
No! Akkun!
[ THE MIZO HIGH 5 ]
Are you OK?
They want to question me
I'll go
It's fine
I filled them in
Please rest for a while
Naoto...
Find out about the day...
Draken...Ken Ryuguji, died
You should calm down...
Just do it!
Akkun said...
Mikey changed when Draken died
If Draken didn't die
Toman wouldn't be like this
Ryuguji was stabbed to death
by a fellow gang member
They were still minors
so their names aren't disclosed
I'll find out
I had my doubts
if I could save Hina
If I could change anything
But it's not a matter of "if"
I just have to do it
You've changed, Takemichi
Who cares if I've changed?
Destiny has to be changed
Takemichi...
You don't know anything yet!
Why'd you shake my hand, you idiot!
Makoto's crotch turned black
from all that scratching
Hilarious, huh?
Akkun?
- It's Akkun!   - Huh?
- Akkun! It's you!   - What the hell, dude?
Ow!
Stop it, you idiot
What's your problem, Takemichi?
You're alive...
Sorry, Akkun
I have to go to see Naoto!
That idiot shook my hand
before telling me anything!
What's with him?
Akkun!
Your dream of becoming a hair stylist!
You will be!
I know it!
Of course I will!
See you at school!
Hawaii?
That idiot!
On a school trip. Why?
Thanks!
I'm off to Hawaii!
Are we still on for tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
On for what?
You promised we'd go to the Musashi Festival
Crush Moebius!
Ryuguji was stabbed in the stomach by a fellow gang member
July 13
Showdown at Musashi Festival
- Showdown at Musashi Festival!   - Showdown?
Moebius…
stabbed Draken
- What day is it?   - The 12th
Tomorrow...
I just remembered something
You always appear out of nowhere
I have to stop the fight with Moebius!
Or else Draken, Akkun and Hina will die!
[ SETAGAYA HOSPITAL ]
That's Pah's best friend's girl
Head crushed, left retina detached
Bruised all over
Scars on her face may never heal
Moebius...
Who the hell are you?
You did this to my daughter?
Go home, trash!
- Dad!   - Go home, trash!
We didn't touch her
We're sorry
Why are you bowing your head?
- What the...?   - Just do it!
It's our responsibility
We are very sorry
Does bowing your heads
help my daughter heal?
You worthless shits!
Mikey!
Dad, please...
Why...?
Why would you do that to her?
Bring her back!
Bring my daughter back!
Toman members
have families too
People we love
We can't hurt innocent people
Or make them cry
We have to settle...
our feuds amongst ourselves
You don't have to bow your head
but have a heart
You're so nice, Kenchin
Sorry, Kenchin
I'm glad you're the one by my side
I knew it!
Draken is Mikey's conscience
As long as he's alive
Toman won't change!
Wait!
Takemitchy. What's up?
The feud with Moebius
Do you have to go?
What the hell?
You're out of line, punk!
Why?
I have a bad feeling about it
If you go on with it
someone may die
I've heard enough! Get lost!
I can't do that. I've...
I already decided
to go head to head with Moebius
Mikey!
Give it up!
Pah
What did you say?
Who's gonna die?
I can't...
You may have your reasons
but it's too late now
Mikey!
Moebius is here
Moebius! It's starting already
We heard you wanted to fight
so here we are
We'll bill you for expenses!
No! Don't fight!
That girl the other day was tougher than you
Osanai, you're a piece of shit
Just like I thought...
I'll kill him
He's mine
No, Pah!
You can't fight Moebius
Who're you?
A boxer, huh?
Bring it!
Come on, bring it!
Pah!
Shut up and watch
It's his fight
He's unconscious
Mikey! Stop them!
Why? He hasn't given up yet
It's gone too far
Too far, Mikey!
Stand there
and I'll show you what my Moebius hook looks like
Sorry...
I'm not worthy
Why?
You haven't lost
What is he talking about?
How hasn't he lost?
On your knees!
Gonna fight, Mikey?
I'll kill you in 10 seconds
Whoever thinks Pah lost
step forward
I'll kill you
Toman is mine
As long as I'm the boss
no one loses
You're all property of Mikey now
From today, Moebius
belongs to Toman
Is it over?
Watch out, Mikey!
I couldn't... stop it
Wanna know why you lost?
Because you're trash
That's why my hand hurts!
He can't hear you anymore
You're right
Thanks Takemitchy
You saved us
Draken didn't die!
The feud with Moebius is over!
Hinata is alive!
Akkun too!
Mission accomplished!
It was exactly
10 years ago today
Draken is alive right here
That will never disappear
Takemichi is there
10 years ago today
The victim was Hinata Tachibana
age 27...
Which one should we go for?
This one
- I did it!   - Wow!
Darn Takemichi, at the festival with Hina
Should we go tease them?
Grow up
So you're OK with Takemichi
losing his cherry today?
Of course not! Never!
The seeds have been planted
Let's take one each
I don't have a goldfish bowl
You can have this one
Moebius...
Sorry, Hina
What?
Wait right here
I'm really sorry!
Mikey's late
Kenchin's late
Why is Moebius here?
Kiyomasa...
Draken kicked me out of Toman
I lost everything
But he's a monster
You can't take him head on
So stab him when he's down
Our feud's not over yet
The feud...
isn't over yet
Destiny hasn't been changed!
Draken will be stabbed
by Kiyomasa!
Kiyomasa! Found a live one
What's up, Draken?
Thought it was over?
Crush 'em one at a time!
Moebius is late
They're under us, right?
We have to make that clear!
Who said they were coming here?
Osanai. Unit 3 got the message
Not me. Must've been Unit 2
It wasn't you?
We've been duped...
- Out of my way   - Hey, Mikey!
Someone may die
Who the hell are you?
Draken shouldn't be by your side
It should be me
What are you looking at?
Bring it on!
You monster
You think hanging with Mikey
made you tough?
Sit!
You stink, slave
Anything to say?
I'm sorry
He's saying something
Louder
I'm sorry
Takemichi...
Takemichi!
Are you OK?
- Hina   - I'll take these off
Leave me alone
Leave me alone!
If I were...
Draken...
Or Mikey...
This would be nothing
Shit!
I can't do anything
I'm just a piece of trash!
No matter how hard I try
I can't change anything
I can't save anyone
I told you
You're strong
Remember when we first met?
- Let's go   - I can't
I'm not asking. Come with me
Wanna be crushed?
Punk? Talking to me?
I can't stand it anymore
I'll crush you!
How does it feel?
Who're you talking to?
Wipe it up!
The floor's a mess
Yes, sir!
What? You next?
I'll shred you, punk!
Please stop!
I don't want to be shredded or crushed!
Girl, call the police!
- This guy's crazy!   - Fly away, birdie!
Um...
Sorry
I couldn't think of any other way...
You say, "I can't do it"
"I'm shaking in my pants"
But you always try your best
You're not Draken
Or Mikey...
You sob out loud for others
You grit your teeth
Even if that's all you can do
that's you, Takemichi
The guy
I love
Are you OK?
No!
No! This is me!
I may be pitiful
but I'm gonna protect you
I'll make it up to you,10 years from now
I'll come to see you
You can do it!
I'm really outnumbered here...
Give up now
You gonna take them all on?
I knew you were stupid
but are you deaf, too?
I'm not alone
That's Mikey's motorbike
Hey, big boy
What's your name again?
Mikey!
Osanai! Whose hair are you pulling?
Mitsuya, Unit 2...
He's tough
How many of them are there?
Don't bother counting
You made us wait so you could attack Kenchin
So what if we did?
Whose plan is this?
You don't need to know
'cause I'm gonna kill you anyway
Still alive, Kenchin?
It's festival day!
I'm ready to party!
Stop blabbering!
Kill 'em!
Crush 'em!
I'm getting tired
The end of peace for Toman
The war's started
Draken!
Kiyomasa!
Right to the liver
It's over
Draken!
Draken... been stabbed!
Move!
Worry about yourself!
He's alive!
Draken's still alive!
Takemitchy! Take care of him
Who, me?
Me...
You're all he's got!
I won't...
...let anyone die!
Sorry, no passage
Hanagakiiiii!
Go Takemichi!
We owe them!
Takemichi! You're still a virgin, right?
I called the ambulance
Just a little...
Further...
You should've minded your own business
Thanks
Takemitchy
I'm heavy, huh?
I'll take care of my own shit
Let me down
I'll fight him
Draken
Think I'd run away?
Be scared shitless?
Who do you think I am?
Shut up and rest
This is my fight!
This is my life...
My revenge!
What are you talking about?
Let's settle this
Gladiator style!
Then I'll...
bet a 100 million on Takemitchy
Wanna die?
No one wants to die, you idiot!
I...
always blamed you
Get up
I thought it was your fault
my life was screwed up
But that's bullshit!
Persistent idiot!
You...
...don't deserve to change my life!
I'll take you down now
and change my own destiny!
Don't bite me, you lame piece of shit!
So what if I'm lame? Or pitiful?
That's me...
Takemichi Hanagaki!
Mitsuya, Pah
You alive?
I got some juice left
What about Draken?
Boss!
- Yo   - You're late, Mikey!
Where were you?
Shut up
Here
Eat this
This is no time for a snack!
Never mind. Here
You guys eat, too
Kenchin would never
break a promise
He wouldn't die on us
He promised we'd go as far as we could
So just trust him
He's going to live
The surgery was a success
Yesssss!
Kenchin
Don't ever do that again
Kenchin...
- See ya. Thanks   - Thank you
[ MANJIRO SANO ]
Naoto! Where's your sister?
Where 's Hina?
You always appear out of nowhere
Hina...