Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Tis the season.
Branch's down here
looking like a whole snack.
And... gotcha!
‐ Buckle up, kids.
‐ Hey, love the bow tie.
Well, you know,
it is the holiday season,
which is why
I brought you these.
Mitten‐settia, my favorite.
That's too bad, I'm allergic.
Yeah, too bad.
And we're done with that.
Ugh.
Uh, Poppy, I know
we're going on a picnic
but do we really need
this much food?
It's not food,
they're invitations
that we're going to deliver
for the first annual
Trolls kingdom
sacred holiday Giftswap.
First annual, what?
What happen to the whole
balloon ride
over Trolls kingdom
hang out kinda thing?
Branch, we're still doing that.
We're just multitasking.
‐ Multitasking. Right.
‐ Alright, here's the deal.
I put a name inside
each of these invitations...
Whoever gets your name
is your secret person.
‐ Ooh.
‐ Pa‐pa‐pop. Secret.
Then in three days,
we all meet back in Pop village
and let the gift giving
commence!
You onboard, Branchifer?
‐ No.
‐ That's what I like to hear.
Now, help me dump
these over board.
♪ Like a fool,
I went and stayed too long ♪
♪ Now, I'm wondering if your
love's still strong ♪
♪ Ooh baby, here I am ♪
♪ Signed, sealed, delivered,
I'm yours ♪
♪ Then that time
I went and said goodbye ♪
♪ Now, I'm back
and not ashamed to cry ♪
♪ Ooh baby, here I am ♪
♪ Signed, sealed, delivered,
I'm yours ♪
♪ Here I am, baby ♪
♪ Signed, sealed, delivered,
I'm yours, I'm yours ♪
♪ Alright ♪
♪ Here I am, baby ♪
♪ Signed, sealed, delivered,
I'm yours ♪
♪ Alright ♪
♪ I've done a lot
of foolish things ♪
♪ That I really didn't mean ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, baby ♪
♪ I did not did not ♪
♪ Here I am, baby ♪
♪ You got, gotta give it to me ♪
♪ Gotta give it to me ♪
♪ Alright, yeah ♪
♪ Here I am, baby ♪
Party time.
Ooh, invitations.
Me next. Me next!
I want one! Give me one!
Don't push, son. Be polite!
Excuse me.
Little bit of help, please.
Come on, Tiny. Goin' up.
Oh, yeah.
Oh! I got my daddy!
I know the perfect gift.
A holiday rhyme.
♪ It's the holiday season
that special time of year ♪
♪ Poppy's rolling out
the gifts ♪
♪ And she's bringing
lots of cheer ♪
♪ My gift is for my daddy ♪
♪ None other than Guy Diamond ♪
♪ Gonna give him
something special ♪
♪ That'll really blow
his mimond ♪
Mimond? Hold up.
Is that even a word?
I can't think of a rhyme.
What's happening to me?
Sounds like you lost your flow.
I've lost my flow?
What am I gonna do for my dad's
holiday gift if I can't rhyme?
You know, you should
see my friend Rhyme‐a‐Saurus,
he'll help you
get your flow back.
Of course.
Good looking out, Legsly.
And to you, Tiny baby sir.
Oh, wait. We almost forgot
to grab our own invitations.
Oh, man.
Giftswaps are so my jam.
Yeah, you do give
the best gifts.
It's super intimidating.
Oh, no.
Oh, interesting.
‐ Cool.
Yeah, totally, so cool.
‐ Well...
‐ Totally cool.
Better get to work on a present
for whoever this is.
Yeah, yeah. Same here.
Gotta take care of this...
this person's gift.
Okay, catch up with you.
Later, Branch. Bye.
"Rhyme‐a‐Saurus swamp."
"No need to be nervous.
Read sign out loud
to fetch my service."
Okay, well, I just did that...
Oh, what the...
Hey there, little friend.
You seem like your not okay.
I hope that I can help you rhyme
and have you on your way.
I'm looking for a word
that rhymes with diamond
so I can finish my rap
and get my flow back.
Got any suggestions?
Ah, let me get I wanna think.
Consult the page review the ink.
Diamond, diamond, diamond.
Almond, science, climate.
Climate! Yes!
Climate is the best
I could find.
Get outta shot
if you don't mind.
Ah, okay.
♪ It's the holiday
holiday season ♪
♪ Gotta give my dad somethin'
that is pleasin' ♪
♪ He's a special man,
a real, real, real special man ♪
♪ That's why I wanna give him
everything that I can ♪
♪ He's my homie,
his name is Guy Diamond ♪
♪ Wanna give him
something special ♪
♪ that'll really
blow his climate ♪
Climate? No!
I'm not feeling that.
Right. Well, then.
Travel by land,
sail the mighty seas.
You need to consult
with the great Wind Breeze.
Wind Breeze?
Okay, well, how do I find her?
‐ Uh, she's right there.
‐ Hello.
‐ Definitely go with that one.
‐ Oh, yeah. Duh.
You're a life saver, Poppy.
It won't fit.
Hmm. Oh.
This is a holiday miracle.
‐ Peppermint Trollcaccino.
‐ Hah, you just read my mind.
Wow, Poppy,
that is one massive gift.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Who's the lucky troll?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's a secret... Giftswap.
This vault is locked.
‐ Oh, yeah, that's cool.
‐ Okay, I respect that.
It's Branch! I got Branch!
Isn't that so exciting? Ah!
Wait, you got your boyfriend?
That's a lot of pressure.
Pressure? Come on.
It's me we're talking about.
The gift master.
The giftanator.
I've got it covered.
‐ Who did you get?
‐ Mr. Dinkles. Whoever that is.
Oh, that's Biggie's pet.
He's a worm.
A worm? That's awesome.
But, what do I get a worm?
Get him a hat.
He lost his old one.
Contemplating his existence
Monsieur Dinkles clings
to solace of his trusty hat.
See.
I'm full of giftsparation.
And there's plenty to go around.
Alright guys, not gonna lie.
I've been kinda freakin' out
over what to get
the Ultimate gift giver.
But I think I've figured it out.
Woah, nice vision board, Branch.
And not at all, insane looking.
Thank you. Okay.
As everybody knows
giving the wrong gift
can be a real relationship
death sentence.
If I go to small,
I'll disappoint her.
If I go to big,
I'll freak her out.
I can't let that happened.
So, I came up with an equation
that led me to
the perfect gift for Poppy.
A, represents Queen Poppy.
B, is all of her
Queenly responsibilities.
C, is the amount of time spent
doing her hair every morning.
Therefore...
Well, you both see
where I'm going with this?
Poppy, never stops multitasking.
So, I'm gonna build her
something will save her time.
I give you the world's
first troll hair doer.
I just need to go
to Poppy's place
and get the exact
measurements of her head
without her noticing
and I'm good to go.
Well, that doesn't sound
creepy at all.
Tiny?
Are you playing some kind of
holiday hide and seek?
'Cause, if so, you win.
Tiny!
Tiny, where are you?
Sick cave, Wind Breeze.
Well, come in,
sweet sparkle child.
Your father is
quite worried about you.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I don't wanna worry him.
But I can't get home
until I get my flow back.
Uh‐uh‐uh.
I already know why you're here.
Alright. Just gotta sit back
and get mystical.
Whoa!
Why don't you love me?
Tiny, why don't you love me?
And we're done. Your back
should be completely healed.
My back? What?
No, I came here
to get my flow back.
I really need to get rhyming
so I can get my daddy
his holiday gift.
What do I do now?
Well, you go see the Cloud Monks
at the temple
on the top of that mountain.
I gotta go all the way up
to that mountain?
No, no, not that mountain.
That mountain.
Okay.
This is for my daddy!
Come on. Tiny, you can do it.
Whoa! That's one.
Wow, Poppy, you are
so good at gift giving.
Hey, when you gots it,
you gots it.
"Operation Measure Poppy's Head"
is a go.
And then I realized, "Why am I
not using double sided tape."
I mean, it's basically twice
as good as single sided tape.
The clue's in the name,
you know what I mean?
Branch, what you doin'
there, little bud?
Oh, hey, wassup...
Branch! What a nice surprise.
Yeah. Surprise.
Just came by to borrow some
wrapping paper for my gift.
Whoa! Poppy, is this
your Giftswap present?
‐ It looks great.
‐ Nope. That one's mine.
But it was Poppy that
turned it up so pretty.
Sure was. Totally. Guys!
My gift box for Branch
is out in the open.
He's gonna know I got him.
Oh, my pumpkin pie.
We're on it, Poppy.
Well, look at the time.
We better be hitting the road.
We gotta go, um...
go take care of our cats.
What?
When did you get cats?
Ah...
Meow. Meow, meow.
Okay, see you around, bye.
Uh, anyway like I was saying,
I just need to borrow
some wrapping paper
and then I'll be on my way.
Okay, here you go.
Now let's get you outta here.
Wait, wait, wait.
I‐I...
‐ I wanna remember this.
‐ What? Why?
Because...
Picture!
Perfect. I'll cherish
this moment forever.
Poppy got me?
And the gift is so big.
Wait,
you forgot the wrapping paper.
I'll probably just
use grocery bags.
You know, reuse,
reduce, recycle.
Now, that boy is odd.
‐ Hmm...
‐ Wow, looks good.
Mm‐hmm.
Poppy's gonna love that.
Yeah, you're right.
It's not big enough.
Her gift was ginormous.
I'm gonna build
a scrap booking machine
and attach it
to the hair stylist.
Sweet.
Now it's definitely done.
Agreed.
Still gotta go bigger.
I'll attach a smoothie maker
so Poppy can her hair done,
make scrap books
and drink her favorite
blueberries‐banana smoothie.
Great idea.
It's perfect.
Prince D, you wanna
take her for a spin?
‐ Uh, yeah, no.
‐ Alright. Here, I am.
My hair's getting done
and then I'm like,
"Oh, rats, I forgot
to make a scrap book
for Biggie's half birthday."
It's working.
It's working!
Yep. Sure is.
And now for the final touch.
A smoothie maker!
So what did you end up
getting Poppy?
What?
Ooh!
I think I broke my butt.
Guys, how am I suppose
to get my flow back
if you're all doing
this vow of silence thing?
"You already have the Gift."
Pff, that's nonsense tea.
"Look through the clutter."
What clutter?
Come on, Tiny.
What makes him so special?
What do you mean,
"What makes him so special?"
He's just my...
Daddy!
Yeah! Okay!
I think I got it now!
♪ Been around the world
tryin' to get my flow back ♪
♪ Couldn't find a single rhyme
everything I said was whack ♪
♪ But then a cloud monk
gave me tea and hit a gong ♪
♪ And I finally realized
that I had it all along ♪
♪ So I'mma flip this back
like I flip a burger patty ♪
♪ Thought I had to
rhyme with Diamond ♪
♪ When I could've
rhymed with Daddy ♪
You did it, son.
Yes! I got my flow back!
Dude, did that guy's
tattoo just talk?
Hey, you just broke
your vow of silence.
You just broke
Wait, does that mean...
♪ I got my flow back, uh ♪
♪ I got my flow back, yeah ♪
Oh!
‐ Ow!
‐ Wassup, Branch?
You look, uh...
You look bad, man.
No other way to say it.
What happened?
I failed, Tiny.
I tried to make Poppy a gift
and it blew up in my face.
‐ Literally.
‐ Say no more, bro.
‐ Let Tiny help you out.
‐ Yeah? Okay.
You just need to look
through the clutter
and focus on what's important.
You already have the gift, dude.
You already have it.
Bla‐laow!
You see it now, don't you?
Nope, not even a little bit.
Oh, come on! The winds even blew
in a magical way.
"Look through the clutter."
You always know just what to get
to make someone feel special,
don't you, Poppy?
I'm sure Branch
is gonna love his gift.
Yeah.
I hope you're right.
Hello, everyone!
Who's ready for
the Holiday Giftswap?
Come on, dad, let's go.
Ooh, it's lit.
Wooho! I love it!
Ah! Cool!
A "Never‐break‐guitar"?
I've always wanted one of these.
I know.
Here you go, little dude.
Merci.
So, um...
‐ Who did you get? Oh.
I'll tell you if you tell me.
Uh, both of us at the same time?
One, two three.
‐ You.
Okay, um...
Do you wanna go first?
Well, I made you this really,
really cool thing.
I'm sure it's great.
But it exploded
and blew me into a tree.
Oh, that's not‐‐ not so great.
Yeah, I may have
over done it a bit.
Anyway...
this is all I could
scrape together.
Here.
I know it's kinda lame.
Branch...
you scrap booked...
for me?
Yeah.
And I think I permanently glues
two of my fingers together
doing it.
I love it.
It's a gift
only you could give me.
Okay, um, now it's my turn.
Ooh!
‐ Huh?
Well, that sucks.
Oh, hey‐hey, cool.
An invisible mountain bike?
No way!
I got the same thing.
I...
I didn't get you anything.
Because when I tried
to think about
what to get the coolest Troll
in the whole world
I‐I totally drew a blank.
I mean, what do you even
get someone who is so sweet,
and so funny,
and kind and cute
and, like, weirdly
over prepared for everything.
You know...
the thing I like most about
the holidays is just...
being together...
with you.
Aww.
Somebody uk me.
♪ You always wanted
to be hiding ♪
♪ Like no one wants you around ♪
♪ Hold your head
a little higher ♪
♪ It's pretty simple ♪
♪ I'm in luck! I'm in luck!
I'm in luck! ♪
♪ 'Cause we're together now ♪
♪ Never stop looking up if it's
love don't need to mess around ♪
♪ Together now ♪
♪ I said I didn't
wanna light up ♪
♪ Light up ♪
♪ So turn the radio down ♪
♪ Maybe I was in denial ♪
♪ But I've changed a little ♪
♪ I'm in luck!
I'm in luck! I'm in luck! ♪
♪ 'Cause we're together now ♪
♪ Together now ♪
♪ Looking up, looking up,
looking up ♪
♪ Don't need to look around ♪
♪ 'Cause I know ♪
♪ I'm in luck! I'm in luck!
I'm in luck! ♪
♪ 'Cause we're together now ♪
♪ I'm in luck! I'm in luck! ♪
♪ I'm in luck!
'cause we're together now ♪
♪ Oh, 'cause we're together now
'Cause way together now ♪
♪ Go together better than
a snowflake on a sweater ♪
♪ Or a Tiny Diamond funk on
my daddy's favorite record ♪
♪ Now my journey's
finally over wow ♪
♪ I just wanna set that down ♪
♪ Through rainy stormy weather ♪
♪ How we'll always
be together now ♪
Oh, I love you, daddy.
I love you too, son.
It feels so good
to see you again, you know.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Hah, come here.
♪ Together now ♪
♪ The bad days are over ♪
♪ 'Cause we come together ♪
♪ 'Cause we don't stop ♪
♪ Looking up, looking up,
looking up ♪
♪ Don't need to look around ♪
♪ 'Cause I know ♪
♪ I'm in luck! I'm in luck!
I'm in luck! ♪
♪ 'Cause we're together now ♪
♪ Together now ♪
♪ Now, now ♪
♪ I'm in luck! I'm in luck!
I'm in luck! ♪
♪ The bad days are over ♪
♪ 'Cause we come together ♪
♪ 'Cause we come together now ♪
Wow, Poppy. Maybe next year we
exchange songs instead of gifts.
I love that idea.
I hope you guys don't mind.
I brought a few of my buddies.
‐ Hey.
‐ Everyone!
Everyone keep your
mouths closed,
we don't know
where that's coming from.
Wait, what?
‐ Guys, wait‐‐
‐ Hey, hey, Branch?
How about another balloon ride
over Troll Kingdom?
No multitasking?
Nope. Just you and me.
Oh, yeah!
Queen Poppy, on the way!
Happy holidays!