Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Boba's ship, when it starts up,
is something like this.
(WEAK HORN BLOWING)
(LAUGHS) Wait a second.
Let's see if this'll... Here it is.
(HORN BLOWING)
-(SHIP WHOOSHING)
-(BLASTER FIRING)
NARRATOR: Boba Fett,
only four lines of dialog...
BOBA: As you wish.
He's no good to me dead.
What if he doesn't survive?
Put Captain Solo in the cargo hold.
NARRATOR: ...and six minutes 32 seconds
of total screen time...
Boba Fett? Where?
NARRATOR: ...and this
somewhat unceremonious introduction.
Bounty hunters.
-We don't need that scum.
-Yes, sir.
NARRATOR: So how did this become this?
MAN: The universe's
most famous bounty hunter,
Boba Fett.
It's Boba Fett.
MAN: Whoa!
(PINBALL PINGING)
(ALL YELL)
(WHIRRING)
Dude, it's Boba Fett's ship.
(LAUGHS) Look,
the Giant Chicken is Boba Fett.
Boba Fett, you didn't know who he was,
where he came from.
He didn't get much screen time.
I never thought
they'd be talking about him after 1980.
Despite his lack of screen time,
next to no dialog, he's everywhere.
-You a big fan of the Fett?
-He signed it for me. Dude, look at that.
(WHOOSHING)
BURTT: Okay, we'd like to introduce
Boba Fett. And here he is.
A new character.
-Uh, can you speak to us, Boba?
-(ON MIC) Certainly.
(CROWD CHEERING)
JOHNSTON: Star Wars had become
this phenomenon.
Now we had to top that.
Nobody wanted it to be
just another sequel.
We had to do something better.
We sort of jumped in on Empire.
We had to hit the ground running.
Because there were more shots
and there were more complicated designs.
Ralph McQuarrie and I
had traded sketches back and forth
and sort of had a direction
for this prototype suit.
And it evolved into Boba Fett.
I liked the design. I don't think
we even changed that much of him.
There were different versions of it.
Each character, when we do it,
we do other alternative versions of it
to see where we go.
VILMUR: The design for the character,
the armature
and all the gadgets and weaponry,
is something we've
never seen in Star Wars before.
One thing that stood out above the rest
is his "T" visor.
Medieval in its styling,
it's something that speaks to, you know,
the days of sword and sorcery.
It just gives him that added dimension
of magic and mystique.
JOHNSTON: I don't remember if Ralph
added the "T" shape or if I did it,
or if George came by and said,
"Hey, give him a 'T' shape."
I don't know.
I don't remember where that came from.
But during the whole process of evolution,
a lot of stuff like that would happen
where somebody would suggest something
and the other guy would take it
and say, "How about this?"
FILONI: It shows you
the power of a design.
Anything out there
that resembles that visor
is just Boba Fett.
JOHNSTON: The Boba Fett suit itself
was originally intended to be an army
of what George called Super Troopers,
and the plan was
to build 100 of these suits,
and to have them sort of be
the Empire's upgraded stormtroopers.
BURTT: They wanted to show
what Boba Fett looked like
to the crew in England.
And I made a, kind of, stand up,
you know, introduction.
"Here's the new character, Boba Fett"
Boba has sort of a radio voice.
There's a speaker built into him here.
And also, there's a certain amount
of telemetry going on.
And certain amount of feedback
for some reason.
It was just a show-and-tell
of the character,
but it was a very functional costume.
This is a range finder. Is this...
This is... This tilts down here.
There's a flamethrower here.
This is a dart-throwing device.
Very deadly.
These also shoot some sort of darts,
projectiles from each knee.
Sure, have him turn around
and get a shot of the jetpack.
Can you do it, Duwayne?
(JETPACK WHOOSHING)
We put the costume on Duwayne Dunham,
who was part of our editing team.
I just happened to be the size
to fit that costume.
And George said,
"Hey, why don't you put this on him?"
"Okay."
George is standing there and he's looking,
and he says, "You know, we need a cape."
I said, "George, there's a Star Wars towel
right there in the garage. (LAUGHING)
"We use it when we rinse off
after a volleyball game at lunch."
That was the first introduction of Boba
in some sort of physical form to us,
months before
the film went into production.
Apparently, there was a budget issue.
And once the original suit was built,
George decided that
we didn't have the money
to turn them into an army.
But we had this one suit.
And George said, "Let's make him
a different kind of a character.
"Let's make him a bounty hunter."
So the first thing I did was
I painted the entire thing silver,
so that when I put
the subsequent layers of paint on,
it would look like something hit the suit
and broke the covering away,
whether it's paint
or some kind of metallic finish,
and you would see the metal underneath.
And from that, I just started
mixing rail road colors
and just painting it up and damaging it.
I would take a heat gun,
I heat the plastic,
and I think I had a rock or something
that I would then press
into the hot plastic to make a dent.
George never came by and said,
"I don't know,
I don't like that orange on there."
You know, he said,
"Just take it and run with it."
There was no sort of interim stage.
He went from white plastic to Boba Fett.
I said, "This is a good character.
People like the bad guys."
And then later, they were doing
this holiday special.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
And there wasn't much
of our involvement.
But I came up with the idea,
"Why don't we take the Boba Fett character
and put him in that?
"Make a little movie out of it?"
I am Boba Fett. Follow me, friend.
Boba's first appearance in film.
SANSWEET: So he really predates
by a couple of years
the actual release
of The Empire Strikes Back.
FILONI: Beautiful work, very stylized.
It's just very simple,
kind of fantasy storytelling.
Chewbacca suspected all along
there was something bad about Boba.
How did you know, Chewie?
It wasn't until the last ten years
that any of us realized
that a month before
the Star Wars Holiday Special came out,
Boba Fett was actually
in this Marin County parade.
BURTT: George Lucas,
who lives in the town,
wanted to do something very local
that was exciting about Star Wars.
And so, they put Vader
and this strange character, Boba Fett,
that people didn't know,
into the local parade.
It's hard to imagine a local parade
where Star Wars characters,
not just like people in costumes,
the actual screen-use costumes
are walking down the street.
But that's exactly what happened.
Duwayne was inside it at the time.
And it was a strange sight
because Boba hadn't been put on film yet
and become well-known.
DUNHAM: At first glance, you didn't say,
"Oh, that's a stormtrooper."
You said, "Whoa, who is that?"
VILMUR: Vader was a known
quantity at that point.
But the fans definitely responded to Fett.
LUCAS: And that's where
it really started.
You know, and then, over time,
we put him in the movies.
I think what made Boba Fett really popular
was that he was a mystery.
Like Darth Vader, the helmet was his face.
I liked that
we didn't give him any backstory.
He was just one of the bounty hunters.
George never worried
about stuff like that.
He never felt like
he had to give you a big backstory.
DARTH VADER: ...but I want them alive.
No disintegrations.
BOBA: As you wish.
Less is more with Fett.
He's enigmatic.
We don't know what to expect from him.
(BLASTER FIRING)
He's encased in
this battle-worn scorched armor
that we just know nothing about.
And all of these mysteries
form kind of this amazingly cool vision
of who this guy is.
He wears the poncho.
It's just like Clint Eastwood.
He is an icon drawn out
of George's appreciation for Westerns,
and, I think, the gun fighters
of Sergio Leone's films specifically.
I mean, I jokingly said at one point,
"If Boba Fett is a bounty hunter,
"why can't he wear spurs
like we hear in the Westerns, you know?"
Although I said it half-jokingly,
Bob Rutledge,
who was in charge of the foley,
actually took my suggestion of spurs
like these
and did foley footsteps for Boba.
(SPURS CLINKING)
Within the DNA of Star Wars
is a deep appreciation
for movies that George liked,
that he was inspired by,
of different genre.
And so spurs make absolute sense
when you think of it that way.
As surely as, you know,
Obi-Wan looks like a samurai.
That makes perfect sense
if you understand
who the creator of Star Wars,
the person that devised it all is,
George Lucas.
It's just part of the appreciation
of the art form really.
Boba Fett in both, The Empire Strikes Back
and Return of the Jedi,
that was Jeremy Bulloch.
BULLOCH: His half-brother, Robert Watts,
was a producer,
and he called Jeremy one day and said,
"There's a little part
in The Empire Strikes Back.
"Get your agent to get onto it."
Jeremy said,
"I can't. I'm in the theater."
"Yes, well, just go along." And he did.
And tried the suit on
and everything fitted perfectly.
So he got the part.
He said when he put the costume on
and walked onto the set,
there was absolute silence.
Everybody was amazed
at what it looked like.
379J take 1.
FILONI: What was interesting
about what Jeremy captured was
in his posture and in the armor,
he did carry that kind of
Eastwood gun-slinger contrapposto stance.
Like, he had the way about him.
371A take 1.
Every little subtle move that Boba has
in these films, you remember.
VILMUR: Jeremy actually had a face role
in The Empire Strikes Back.
He was an unnamed Imperial officer
who was actually dragging Princess Leia
away from Luke
and he was a pilot in Revenge of the Sith.
We're receiving a message
from the chancellor's office.
-Send it through.
-Yes, sir.
And then, I mean, Jeremy the person,
after the films, at conventions.
(CROWD CHEERING, CLAPPING)
BULLOCH: It was in the mid-'90s
when they re-released the films
when it just took off.
Then eventually, I went and I sort of
dealt with all the setting the tables up
and everything.
So we did it as a partnership,
which was nice.
We went to Poland,
and the whole town came out to meet him.
Lots of lovely memories.
And sometimes, he would stand
in front of the table,
he wouldn't sit down so that
he could be there if they wanted pictures.
And always took time
to chat to people and everything.
He loved all that.
FILONI: He really appreciated
what that character meant to people,
what his performance had meant to people.
(CROWD CHEERING, CLAPPING)
He had a phenomenal relationship
with Star Wars fans.
He's one of the originals.
This is the lovely metallic one, isn't it?
-MAN: Yes, it is.
-It just shines.
It was a deep loss to all of us
and the fans when he left us last year.
BULLOCH: That's what he used to write
on his photographs.
"Stay cool. Stay cool.
Jeremy Bulloch, Boba Fett."
SANSWEET: Lots of people, over the years,
have worn the Boba Fett costume.
There were stunt guys
who did some of the work,
especially in Return of the Jedi.
RANDALL: This is what happens
to an old stunt man.
He needs this equipment in the morning.
Maybe what I'll do
is start with that wet suit.
It'll pick up enough slack
so it won't slip around.
MAN: Why don't you go up this ladder?
-MAN 1: Hey, buddy.
-LUCAS: What if he came up higher
and tighter so that you could get
the dunes behind him?
-Where is your hand go up?
-Up four, down...
MAN: The flexibility of the costume
is such that you could produce
virtually anything and justify it.
Let's shoot this.
Stand by to go.
It's a wonderful thing when that character
is performed by so many great people.
LUCAS: I always liked him,
and he was a good character.
And then I came and needed
another one, so I did Jango Fett.
(BLASTERS FIRING)
Boba Fett's father.
Temuera Morrison was hired
to play Jango Fett,
and Boba Fett is the sole clone
that was purely his DNA
without alteration.
My first introduction
to Boba Fett was, um...
Actually did a behind-the-scenes interview
for Attack of The Clones,
and they open up this book that
basically explains all the characters.
I remember I opened this book and I go...
Whoa! I even get the jetpacks.
(CHUCKLES)
I remember the guy behind the camera
probably thought,
"No, you're only
going to get a blue jumpsuit.
"But the original guy has all of this."
LUCAS: Acting-wise and everything,
it was very good to have Tem there
'cause he'd worked the character out,
and they were supposed to be
the same person more or less.
LOGAN: The first day I met him,
he said to me,
"I guess you're going
to be playing my son,
"and I'm going to be playing your dad.
"You call me dad and I'll call you son."
Dad, I think we're being tracked.
Hang on, son,
we'll move into the asteroid field,
and we'll have
a couple of surprises for them.
I remember being all of four-foot-nothing
and I look up at him
and I said, "All right, Dad."
And he just looked back down at me
with this big smile and he goes,
"All right, son."
(LIGHTSABER ACTIVATES)
Whose helmet is that anyway?
It belongs to a bounty hunter
I killed on Geonosis.
I was a fan of The Clone Wars,
and I really loved the cartoon,
and I was hoping to come back.
BOBA: You got a problem with that?
My name's Boba.
I was so thrilled to be able
to voice Boba Fett again
and to be able to fill in the gaps
after Attack of The Clones.
The greatest thing is I've been able
to show my son Attack of The Clones.
And I show him the little
Kamino Escape blue figure
and I would point out
and say, "Hey, who's this?"
He says, "Boba Fett."
SANSWEET: I've been
a collector all my life,
and when Star Wars came out,
that became the focus of my collection.
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
And when I moved up to Northern California
to go to work for Lucasfilm
in the marketing department,
I needed someplace to store my objects.
So I bought a house with chicken barns.
So what used to house 20,000 hens,
now houses Rancho Obi-Wan,
a Star Wars Memorabilia Museum,
which, according to
the Guinness Book of World Records,
is the world's largest collection
of Star Wars memorabilia,
including one or two Boba Fett items.
So here is a maquette
of the original Boba Fett costume.
The all-white costume.
And this is the original Boba Fett rifle.
When he was wearing the all-white costume
before production started.
I think that there are well over
1,000 Boba Fett items in the collection.
This is one of two Lego-authorized
Boba Fett figures that were sold
at FAO Schwarz.
In our cantina set,
we have Boba Fett guitars
from both Japan and the US.
And how many more than the 1,000
is really hard to say
because there are a lot of objects
that have Boba Fett as part
of a broader spectrum of characters.
This is a Japanese Boba Fett toy,
and it actually tap dances
to a couple of Star Wars melodies.
There are many strange Boba Fett things,
there are many fan-made Boba Fett objects.
But perhaps my favorite
because of what Rancho Obi-Wan used to be
is a painted Easter egg of Boba Fett.
The inside of the egg is long gone.
One of the reasons that Boba Fett
has become so popular among collectors
is because of the story of
the send-away Boba Fett action figure.
Here we have two versions
of the rocket-firing Boba Fett,
the one with a four-sided missile.
And this was an attempt to do
a locking mechanism
with an eight-sided rocket.
This is instead
what we all got in the mail.
Boba Fett in a plastic package
with a sonic-welded missile in it,
and a note to consumers...
"Sorry, the launcher has been removed
from the product for safety reasons.
"If you're unhappy,
we'll send you a different figure."
The handful that are out there
in the public among collectors
came from the ones that were tested
at Kenner Products in Cincinnati,
and when they go up at auctions,
they can go into the six figures now.
The Boba Fett figure was a big deal
because if you had that,
you had a capable villain
to do your adventures with.
And it invited creative thinking.
It invited stories to be told
about this character.
And now we play
with biggest toys there are.
And Boba Fett is still one of them.
He gets out of the Darth Vader carrying
case, and he's back in play. (LAUGHS)
(DEVICE BEEPING)
KENNEDY: How the fans would react to
Boba Fett reappearing in The Mandalorian.
We knew it would be big, I have to say.
I think this was
sort of a gasp rather than a scream.
MORRISON: All that time since the '80s,
when Boba disappeared...
and now it was like,
"Here he comes. The great comeback"
KENNEDY: To have Temuera Morrison back,
he's just remarkable in the part.
Big day today.
(WHOOSHING)
First reveal.
I've been tracking you, Mandalorian.
Boba, he's back.
MAN: Here we go. And... Action!
WEN: What happened to Boba Fett
after he was swallowed up by the Sarlacc?
That's a story in itself.
I'm here for the armor.
If you want my armor,
you'll have to peel it off my dead body.
Where's Boba been all this time?
I don't want your armor. I want my armor.
It belongs to me.
BURTT: I never imagined that Boba Fett
would be a character,
that we'd be talking about 40-plus years
after he was created.
A character if you see it,
and it enters your imagination
at the right age, it changes your DNA.
You sort of carry it along.
And there was
a whole generation of Star Wars kids,
I would call them, and young fans
that absorbed what was in the movies.
And it became a culture.
The world was ready
for this bounty hunter.
FILONI: Temuera and what he's brought
to the character,
Daniel, Jeremy, these people
that have been in the suit,
it becomes their legacy as well.
Fans have wanted this character
to come back in Star Wars for so long.
It's even more exciting to realize
that we have a whole series
on the way that features Boba Fett.
(CRACKLING)
The anticipation is remarkable.