Inspired by true events.
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
There are still student fraternitys in Germany today.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
They call themselves Landsmannschaften,
Burschenschaften, Turner and Corps
and their traditions go back for centuries.
Many of these student fraternities are still fencing.
It is a traditional rapier fight with sharpened weapons.
Fine, until someone bleeds.
My name is David von Scharrenberg, I'm a Corps Student,
and I'm about to go to my Mensur bout.
Up please.
Ready.
Let's go!
Be a student when the fencing lashes fall
in a sharp duel that you chose yourself.
In bloody clashes the courage builds you up for life.
Be a student if your only worries, whether you will stand firm and brave:
In your life, daring morning, Lord, never let times go by!
Alright.
Here we are, with the blues.
This is the Corps House. Blue Corps. Blue Corps? Yes.
They don't always have the best reputation.
The correctness principle.
But that's also an important principle
to consider in a professional career.
Yes, beautiful isn't it?
Look here, correctness principle. Correctness principle? Yes.
Well, you can say gray, but blue, blue circle.
We don't really need that. With us the color is white.
That means?
Principle of nobility.
But still 150 euros per month.
That is correct. That is very correct.
And for that you can't do it yourself.
Right.
So I'm ringing the doorbell now.
We can't go back now.
What should I say?
Don’t worry you’ll be fine.
They have a shortage off new members.
Correctness principle is always short.
Corps Teutonia. Here we come!
Doktor von Scharrenberg.
I welcome you.
Michael Brandt, I think we spoke on the phone.
Yes, Mr. Brandt.
Nice that you are here. How was the drive?
Wonderful. Smooth, but a little long.
Yes that's true. And this?
And this is my son.
Yes, that is definitely our future Fox David.
Would you like something to drink, coffee, cola, beer?
With pleasure.
Beer?
For me a coke, beer is a little early.
Yes, of course, is also much more reasonable than beer.
Who drinks beer so early in the day?
I do.
So! Would you like to sit down, maybe?
Mrs. Hofmeister.
Could we have a beer and a coke please.
Yes, a beer, a cola and?
Some tea, Mrs. Hofmeister.
Many Thanks. Thank-you.
Cheers. Cheers my dear. Your health.
Please don't get me wrong.
We are of course pleased that your son
has expressed his interest in becoming a member.
But I must be wondering why your son isn't joining your Corps.
Vandalia. White circle. Principle of nobility.
It's a good covenant.
You could say so. We closed!
I did not knew that. That is very unfortunate.
Yes, that is unfortunate.
How did you find us?
Dr. von Scharrenberg told me on the phone that, after checking the Corps Lists,
he found that one of David's ancestors was a founding father of Teutonia.
A founding father. Can this be true?
That is. A founding father.
What an honour.
Are you still fencing?
You definitely don't fight anymore, do you?
Of course we are still fencing!
But it's not dangerous.
Ah, there are our active students.
Good Day gentlemen. Karl Jankwitz. First in charge .
Dr. von Scharrenberg, it's a pleasure to meet you.
And to meet you.
Kröger. Consenior. .
David right? Hello my dear one.
Heard a lot about you.
You want to study law. That is a very good decision.
Kröger, not Wiener, but Richert and I, we all study law.
We can certainly help you.
Do you already have a registration form?
No, we just got here.
No problem. We have already picked up one for you
and filled it out.
All you have to do is sign it.
Wiener.
Sign right there.
Exactly. Right there.
Good. I would say gentlemen… See you shortly in the Kneipe.
Meanwhile, enjoy your cold beer.
See you then.
Wiener, take this to our old member Mr. Westend.
Yes will be done.
Shouldn't I take this myself?
The dean is a Corps Brother.
By the way, I'm Sören.
David.
So you want to become a member, yes?
Well, let's see, my father was also a Corps Student.
Gentlemen. The inaugural Kneipe won't be prepared by itself.
Well, we are the guests.
We don't need to do anything.
So now listen carefully, friends of the Corps Student idea.
I am Bernd Geier, your Fox Major.
And therefore responsible for you.
And from now on, you do exactly what I tell you.
Alright, the Senior is about to begin the Kneipe
and welcome all off us.
Then we shall sing a traditional student song.
You will then be called to the front & accepted into the Corps in the traditional manner.
This is a very special moment in the life of a Corps Student.
You answer with yes, understood?
Then we all toast!
Cheers, Cheerio. Your health.
Silencium.
Silencium in the Fox Hutch!
Silencium!
I hereby open the inaugural Kneipe in the summer semester 2020...
...and rub a thundering Pint Salamander with everyone present.
Ad exercitium Salamadris,
1,2,3,1, Cheers.
2,3,1,2,3,1,2,3!
I am delighted that so many Corps Brothers
have come to this inaugural Kneipe.
And it is an extraordinary pleasure for me to welcome Doctor von Scharrenberg,
representative of the Corps Vandalia, to our House.
Then on our left, Mr. Metzel, representative of the Corps Alemania.
My good friend Gustav Eisenstein,
Senior of the Corps Suevia.
And last but not least, it is a special honor for me to welcome
our honorary member, elder gentlemen AHEM Pfander!
Bravo. Pfander!
I could swear I know him from television.
That's our interior minister.
Silencium, Mr. Scharrenberg.
Dear senior, on behalf of the elder gentlemen man, I thank you very much for the invitation
and I am delighted to be able to have a long sip with everyone present.
Cheers! Cheerio.
It is also a great pleasure for me to announce
that three future Foxes have taken their seats at our Fox table.
They all applied to join our Corps.
Mr. David von Scharrenberg, Mr. Hain
and the son of our elder Gentlemen Mr. Hubertus,
Mr. Wolfgang Hubertus.
I warmly welcome you all to our midst, and I wish you a boozy time.
Right. We sing the very first song; Thoughts are free
to be found in the Songbook on page 173.
The active ones start singing.
Thoughts are free, who can guess them?
They fly by like nocturnal shadows.
No person can know them, no hunter can shoot them
and so it will always be: Thoughts are free!
Silencium.
We are now starting the ceremonial admission.
I now ask the three candidates to come forward.
Your appearance. Around the table once.
All of you have applied to join our Corps Teutonia.
I'll explain to you now what it means to be a Teuton.
The Corps Teutonia is a community of students from the university.
We maintain the traditions of the Corps
and also the academic fencing,
that connects young and old.
In the beginning you will be Foxes.
As a Fox you have to obey your older Corps Brothers.
We all live and study together on the Corps House.
After a trial period of two semesters
you will be accepted into the Corps after fencing the Mensur.
David von Scharrenberg, if you are willing to accept these rules,
then answer yes.
Yes.
Please free your sleeves.
Impressed by the atmosphere,
unable to realize the words or the meaning of the speech,
I just answered "yes".
I would never have uttered a "no" in this situation.
Which groom in front of the altar answers "No" when asked
whether he would like to spend his life with this woman?
That occurs only in movies.
Yes boys cheers. Drink.
Here drink, drink, drink.
I feel really sick.
I think I must puke.
But not here.
That will not do.
Wiener, show the fresh Fox our Pope!
Yes Sir, Fox Major.
I don't have to go to the Pope.
Yes, yes.
No, I'm evangelical.
Are you evangelical? Yes, I am a Protestant.
Hain you faggot, what's the matter with you?
Are you all right?
The Pope is a puke basin by us gentlemen.
Where we pope.
We bow to the Pope
and pay homage to the god of Porcelain.
Goethe is wrong.
Poping is derived from the Latin verb pabere, spit, spew, vomit.
I'm so sorry. I didn´t mean to...
Caution Wiener. Take care of your new Fox.
Otherwise you could lose him right away.
Everything under control, Mr. Metzel.
Come on. Come on Fox.
I just used the Pope for the first time.
Very good David, we drink to that.
We drink to that. Bottoms up!
Here.
What?
So that you have something to write next time.
So David, now that you are a Fox, you need a Mentor.
And at some point you need to decide if you would like me to become your Mentor.
We get along really well, don't we?
Yes, yes, great.
Richert, isn't it?
You know, I'm really happy about that ...
... that you put so much trust in me.
Then everything is clear.
Now you will be my Fox Student.
You know, I don't know the other corps brothers very well yet.
And then I thought that I, well,
So I actually wanted to get to know the others before I decide.
I need a little more time.
But it's really nice with you, to make that decision.
Can we do this after breakfast with the other brothers? I'm not fully awake yet.
As you wish, Fox Scharrenberg.
I didn't want to put you under pressure.
Take your time.
Scharrenberg.
Fencing, fencing, fencing!
Men get up. Fox Hubertus. Krause. Wake up!
Late comers, do push-ups.
Fencing hour. Get up.
Get up. Hey, wake up!
Inactive Corps Brother Brandt…
Yes sir.
Get me a Beer Boy.
Accepted.
Fill up.
With pleasure.
What are you doing there?
We are drinking our first Beer Boy of the day.
Beer Boy?
Accepted.
Here.
No thanks, but...
Honestly now what is a Beer Boy?
Beer Boy is both an invitation and the generic term
for an academic beer duel.
You call the other fraternity student to quickly down a beer.
To win, you need to finish the beer faster
and put the glass down first.
Cheers you whore. Drink!
Finished.
Obviously a draw.
No, come on, thank you, I think it's too early to drink, right?
I mean, I'm still totally hungover from yesterday.
Just leave it be.
Fox, when you said Beer Boy you officially challenged me.
And I accepted.
So I would say the mugs are filled up according to the rules.
All preluminaries are thus fulfilled.
Do you see it differently?
Do you need a referee?
Now become truthful and drink like a man.
Or are you not capable of giving satisfaction.
Satis...what?
Genugtuung is Latin for satisfaction.
It's about honour.
We Corps Students keep our word.
You want to be a Corps Student, right?
Then you have to stand by our principles.
The first command counts.
From the floor.
To the testicles.
From the floor to the testicles.
To the belly button.
To the trap.
Say cheers in the middle.
Cheers. Drink!
Finished.
Hey, hey.
Look at that. The Fox is capable.
He is quick with the Beer Boy.
You looked pretty old here mate.
Accepted.
Double.
Say Jankwitz. You have such awesome porn.
Give me one.
Fuck off.
Wiener. Get lost.
Get the fuck out off from my room.
Come on everyone out!
Disgusting, filthy dirt pack.
Hey Wiener, leave that shit.
Hello.
Folks, what´s going on?
Fencing is the order of the day.
Nope.
Are we a fencing fraternity here or what?
My dear Mr. Choral Society.
Ah, Brandt.
Did you wake up in the yellow circle again today?
Senior take a look at our Secretary.
She takes care of things that are none of her business.
Better take care of the Corps Treasury.
I was downstairs earlier and looked at the Corps Bill.
I would say pretty sloppy cash management.
It’s not my fault. What am I supposed to do if they don't pay?
Well, then you have to issue fines.
2 Euro, 5 Euro, 20 Euro. Man Richert, that's your job!
You want the Corps to be run tight, don't you?
So now listen up.
You are aware that our Corps account devours
18% overdraft interest when it is in the red.
I'll make an announcement now.
If the account is still in the red by the next Covent
I'll file a complaint!
What kind of mess is this here?
Hey! In 5 minutes there will be fencing practice.
What is this crap?
And what is this?
Well well Wiener, I always knew that you were a piglet, but this?
I need this now.
You will you get it back after fencing, when I'm done.
Forget it. I am freed from fencing for the whole semester.
Broke my wrist last semester.
No more fencing for me, okay?
Got a medical certificate from our old man, Meier the fourth.
Yes. True.
But good enough to beat the meat?
Granted.
So, now a nice hangover breakfast, okay?
Fox, where is your ribbon?
In my room.
Very wrong answer Fox Krause.
The ribbon is always on the man.
Uh, yeah, sorry, my apologies.
I did not know. I'll put it on right away.
Ah, it's not that easy.
Not until you extricate.
Oh Richert, Do I have to do it now?
Are you getting impudent with me Fox?
You drink that up now.
Come on. Extricate. Quickly!
Well, it works. Fox Krause.
Hopefully this will teach you a lesson.
Never leave your ribbon unguarded.
And now sing our color verse.
Teutonia I belong to you.
I swear by your colors.
On the red and gray ribbon.
Well well Fox Krausse. Maybe something will become of you after all.
Warm up men.
Geier, where is your guard?
Your quart has been better too.
Beer Boy.
Double.
Quadruple.
Fox Scharrenberg.
What are you doing?
When I say the lesson begins at 8 o'clock Cum Tempore.
Then it begins on time and not a second later.
Someone doesn’t know any Latin.
Waldorf student what?
But I had to.
You want to argue with me?
Go down. 10 pushups at once.
Get down Fox.
Get down.
Scharrenberg, it will never work like that.
And again we have to wait for you.
Come on, that's enough.
Up with you.
So men. This is the Basket blade.
The weapon of the Corps Students.
The Training Blade is 120 centimeters long.
And of course dull.
So you can't hurt yourself with it. Not yet!
The Mensur Blade, however. Razor sharp.
The front sharpened 35 centimeters.
And the back is sharpened 25 centimeters.
And the fencing gauntlet of course.
Scharrenberg. Repeat.
Yeah, um...
Yes! You have to listen.
Richert!
Geier, show us the target areas.
So guys.
We have three target areas.
Once prime.
Quart.
And the Terz.
OK?
All right? Come on men.
Centered. In the middle? Exactly in the center.
What's going on here? Fox. Arm up.
Too much of drinking yesterday?
Nice.
You are supposed to swing Fox Krause. No falderal.
And down. It doesn't work. Down. It's not working.
How's it going?
Well, he is doing well. Yes.
Krause. Get your arm up, proper up.
Feet position. Yes, this is better.
Up there, and then you turn off,
pull past you on the left. Here where I am now.
Swinging! Fox Krause! - Right past you, pull up and turn your wrist.
And then back here.
So Men. Sparring!
Richert. Bring me my fencing stuff.
Alright Buddy.
Distance yourself.
Pull backwards. Hold it with your left hand.
Height adjustment..
Down.
Come here. That’s enough.
Up.
Ready.
Go.
Your guard.
Relax.
Again.
Kröger.
Set. Go.
Yes.
Halt!
Go.
A bit faster Fox. Man.
Halt! That's enough.
Richert. Come here.
Well done buddy.
Now all stand in a circle.
So guys. You don't know about the chairs yet, do you?
Pick up chairs. The chair always stays above your head.
Did I say form a semicircle?
Hello !!!Scharre.!!! Yes. Please!
So now. Where is the circle?
Make a real circle. And now pass it on.
Look sharp Jankwitz. Where's the next chair?
Kröger you slow-poke. Yes sir.
Next. Yes, nice. And so on. Tempo. Now people. Keep it up.
Here we go. Nicely high. Okay Please. Onward. Next chair. That's how it has to work!
Tempo, Tempo. Exactly. Faster. Good.
Keep your shoulders and arms up.
Teutonia I belong to you.
I swear by your colors.
On the red-gray ribbon.
And pee against the wall.
That´s right Wiener.
Hey David, have you settled in well?
Hello!
Really great. It's a lot of fun with you here in the Corps.
Thanks Wiener.
What worries me a little is the university.
I haven't done anything for that yet.
Oh nonsense. Now is just the introductory week.
It really doesn't start until tomorrow.
We can go to the seminar together tomorrow.
Then I'll show you everything. Agreed?
That would be cool.
Yesterday Richert asked me if I would like to be his Mentor.
Really?
I refused.
I think he's really mad at me now.
Don't worry about it.
Take your time.
That’s your choice.
Such a relationship needs to be chosen well.
Well, it really took me a while
to figure out that I want Brandt as my ...
Swine... Mentor.
And I haven't regretted it until now.
How do I actually do it when have decided for a Mentor.
You have to drink.
You get two beers, go to the one and just ask.
Nobody will refuse. You do not do that.
Especially not with a smashing Fox like you are.
Very well then.
Jankwitz.
I would be very happy if you became my Mentor.
I'm really pleased old sport. Cheers.
Cheers student. Bottoms up! Drink.
Brandt.
Yes.
Would you be my Mentor?
Of course. Come here.
Turn around nicely. Turn around.
Here we have the sugar.
Thank you very much, Ms. Hoffmeister.
You are welcome.
That looks really good. Thanks.
Thank you Ms. Hoffmeister. Tastes glorious.
Yes fine. Brutus.
Nice sausage for breakfast.
That's the way it should be for a Corps Dog of your class.
Fox Student.
We saw you. Come here.
Where do you want to go?
I still have to go to university.
I have an important introductory lecture today.
I definitely don't want to miss it.
Give me something from the hooker shower.
Yes, and what about breakfast?
I wanted to have breakfast in the cafeteria.
Nonsense Fox.
You have breakfast here on the house with your Corps Brothers.
Nothing better can happen to you.
Then we will go for a wonderful walk with Brutus
and saunter through the spring.
Sit down Fellow Fox and eat.
You still have to get big and strong.
Yes, fine Brutus. Yes fine.
Yes Brutus.
Are we going out later?
Feed him.
5 euros in the piggy bank immediately.
Ten. Then I have another one free.
Wiener.
Do you want coffee? With pleasure.
From now on there was breakfast every day
or any other reason not to leave the house.
The university was becoming more and more distant.
But that didn't bother me much.
The Corps had an incredible pull on me.
Cheers to the middle is welcome. Extremely welcome.
Like a kind of maelstrom.
We ran a House.
A big House.
And that took up the whole man.
There was always something to do.
Going to university was frowned upon.
- Cold Iron.
Fox Education.
So what's that?
Do I see a TV in the house?
Hurray, we're becoming stupid.
That is absolutely unnecessary!
Turn it off immediately. The TV must go as soon as possible.
Wiener, you’re responsible for it.
Or you are taking off to...
To where?
Wiener, seriously now.
We are not an association here to which one can sue for membership.
This way you'll always stay a Silver Fox.
Hey, where's the remote?
Okay.
Fox Major.
Yes.
Can I be given leave of absence from the Fox Lesson?
I still have to study. I've an exam tomorrow.
Yeah, but now it's Fox Education.
You can study later.
So, now, finally.
I hereby open your second Fox Lesson.
Fill up your glasses, yes.
Beer again?
I still feel rotten from yesterday.
I'll have a coke.
Can I also drink non-alcoholic?
I have the important exam tomorrow.
I'm reporting beer sick.
You are Foxes.
You’re at the beginning of your studies. You can still afford that.
See, I finished my studies years ago.
Actually, I’ve been an old gentleman for a long time
and need to take care of my doctor’s office.
I'm drinking because of you guys.
I became active again because of you.
Now don't act like that. No shit.
You are Corps Students… You have to take a little hardship.
But actually.
But what, but what? There is no discussion here, Fox.
Hey, we all want to have some fun here, right?
Yes, well then!
Now you fill up the cups.
Hello Hubertus, are you going to fill your cup.
Exactly. Good Fox.
Don't worry. We don't want to get totally drunk here or anything. Right?
Just a small, cozy beer.
Ok, so cheers.
Cheers.
Cheers to you two.
So. First part done. Bugger me!
David. What is it like?
The colors of the fraternity houses?
From the Corp Houses. Tell me.
Teutonia.
Red grey.
Well. Super. Yes come on.
Colours?
This is taking too long for me now.
Hubertus. What about the circles?
What kind of circles do we have? Blue circle.
For example. Well start with the black circle.
The principle of fencing and the principle of thrift.
Good yes. Next circle. Blue circle.
Social Principle and Correctness Principle.
Correct.
Okay. Next would be the green circle.
Shabbiness principle and tolerance principle.
Well then we still have the white circle.
This is actually unimportant. But for the sake of completeness.
Principle of nobility.
Principle of nobility. Okay?
Super. Wonderful.
Do you now know the colors of Suevia? David.
Green.
OK. Well, we have Corps relationships too.
Wiener. You tell me. Who is our befriended Corps?
The Corps Suevia. These are the Swabians.
Yes and what kind of circle?
That's the green circle.
Krause?
No, it is circle-free.
Circle-free, exactly. And today we have an away game, a visit to the Suevia.
Look alive. We’re dressing up and paying them a visit.
Here we go.
Cheers. Cheers.
Open up. Home visit.
Open.
Open the door.
Jankwitz. Corps Teutonia. We are stopping by for a beer.
Huh? I have to ask the Senior first...
Ah, booze frats, booze.
Oh no you again. That is boring.
You have nothing better in mind.
That is very poor.
Fill up, you whore.
Your sayings were better.
Fags in the house. Home visit. Home visit.
Foxes. Come here.
You... You!
Gustav.
Man Foxes you have 5 seconds to come here!
Get some liquid. Fill up.
Faster you bastards.
Fill up. Finally fill up the cups.
Well Eisenstein. Shit isn´t it?
How are you doing?
As always, better than you!
Where did you find those four failures?
In the same brothel your mother works in.
Tell a story.
Shut up. Drink!
Hey! They're for the boat race.
Strengthen yourself dumb Fox and then fill up the cups.
Fill up you dumb Fox.
Yeah, fill up, you dumb Fox.
Shut up Scharri. Fox cigarette lighter.
Well Foxes, they're like that. Drink.
You are pretty overconfident, so can you do with the cup?
We'll see that in a moment, colleague.
What's your name?
Kirchow.
Ah, an East German beast.
Let me guess.
Your name is, ah, Mike?
Ronny.
Or Rene?
Enrico.
Enri, Enrico, on the fourth guess a hit.
Hey! You are drinking right now.
Come on. Drink!
Drink up, you son of an Eastern hooker!
Kröger no more mother insults.
For this we must both drink a pitcher.
Gladly, but not before I am finished with your East Fox here.
Silencium.
Shut up, you bastards!
Well, it's a tragedy that the Teutons
get lost in our House every now and then.
How often should we flush you out?
You never learn anything?
Hey, I'll give you a gastric lavage in a moment.
Silencium.
Wiener, I'll come to you.
So now we're drinking todays debut boat race as an overture.
Cheers.
Do you know what that means, you uneducated assholes?
Since you were here yesterday, you know the preluminaries.
Let's begin right away.
The right side counts.
Affirmative. One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven. Eight. Nine.
Ten. Teutonia comes to ten.
So, Suevia counts through.
One two Three.
Four. Five.
Six, seven.
We drink twice.
Decent. Then Suevia has fourteen.
You will have to catch up.
Gladly.
The four new Foxes each drink twice.
One. Two.
Two.
Four you pig.
Four.
Six.
Seven. Eight.
Ten.
Eleven.
No, Hain, you have to say twelve.
I cannot. I can not do it.
Teutonia no longer drinks. Teutonia no longer drinks.
Quiet. Silencium.
Don't chat. Count.
I take over.
Thirteen.
Fourteen. Teutonia has fourteen.
Teutonia also comes up with fourteen.
Jankwitz was your side showing signs of weakness? Incredible.
So, let's go.
Cheers my favorite frat.
Gulp.
Gulp. Faster.
Come on Scharrenberg.
Geier, Geier.
Brandt.
Down it.
Here we go.
Silencium. That was a classic draw.
A draw, are you crazy?
Look at your boys, they spilled half of the brew.
They bleed.
Silencium.
Jankwitz that also applies to you and to you Brandt.
This boat race is suspended for five beer minutes
until both parties have adequately refilled.
Silencium Ex.
Drink.
Do you see that looser?
Totally cut up.
Never let your guard down.
Then it works with women too.
Geier. Talking about fencing is bad style.
I've told you that a thousand times.
What kind of hooker price do I get with a face like that?
You fucking Foxes!
Just 3-days here and already big mouthing?!
Wait until you have to fence yourself.
Then you shit your pants.
Take that back.
Why should I?
Did you just call me a stupid boy?
It will be like that.
Herr Geier. I ask for satisfaction.
With pleasure.
I look forward to settle this matter with you
as a personal contract.
See you at the next ordinary determination day!
Beer Boy.
Double.
Quadruple.
Accepted.
Fill up Fox.
Yes, the Swabian has challenged Geier to a personal Contract.
That means he challenged him to a duel, so to speak.
We also call this an honorary quarrel.
And one who, yes, who is as appropriate as Geier of course accepts it.
For us, this is part of the comment.
Good manners.
So a personal contract...
...is an aggravated form of academic fencing.
45 rounds instead of 30. Six strikes instead of 5.
No breaks.
Oh shit.
Do not worry. Geier used to be a fencer ace, the best fencer in town.
In his active time, he slashed everybody.
I don't understand.
Why do they want to duel because of such a trivial little thing?
Well, it's about the principle. Honour. Satisfaction.
So you take care of who you talk to.
You can also get challenged, yes!
Eightfold.
Gottlob, can you still drink?
Eightfold. Sixteen times.
Thirty-two times.
Sixty-four times.
Accepted.
Drink you whore.
Just a moment. Fill up.
Fill up you...
Such visits and return visits were typical.
It happened all the time.
In our town there were 5 Corps and dozens of other fraternities.
Why did you steal the flag?
Are you going to wipe your ass with this?
Exactly, that is color disgrace, you don't do it like that.
Official Assignment.
Quiet the contrary Krause. We have a long tradition of stealing flags.
Listen, the Swabians have to come here now and recapture their flag.
It would only have been Color disgrace if we had destroyed the flag.
Recapture?
Everything we put on the flag they have to drink up.
And and we swear on them and we scream at them.
That's stupid.
I'm going to bed, I'm totally exhausted.
Weak Fox. Slow-poke.
Me too. Good night lads.
Dry shite.
Ditto. Wet dreams Corps Brothers.
Departure.
Wait and see, they don't even need to take off their clothes.
How come?
Well, because the Swabians will quickly notice that we have their flag.
And then they will come over.
Section 11 of the German Beer Comment.
Keep on drinking.
Someone came to visit almost every day.
And if they were too lazy to come over.
Then they got on the blower or demanded a videocall.
A marathon that never seemed to end.
Hey.
Wiener, he won't wake up.
We'll have to play the Russian game there.
Yes, it's okay. Please don't speak so loudly. My head is throbbing.
What are you going to do now?
Take a good look Scharrenberg. We're playing the Russian game now.
We're now playing the Russian game, the Russian game, the Russian game.
We're playing the Russian game now.
Russian game.
And who doesn't want to drink.
Who doesn´t want to drink, will get wet!
Wake up!
Russian game.
Hey, Fox Hubertus, get up. Come on!
Drink. Finally drink.
Up with you and finally drink Hubertus.
I have to sleep.
Sleep?
You get up now and drink or...
Stop it, he's totally exhausted, come on.
What? Shut up Fox! Go to the fencing hall and warm up.
Come on Hubertus. Just a beer or get up.
Drink now or...
Fuck.
Are you nuts?
Do you also want to rebel Fox?
Come on. We have fencing practice now.
Go to the fencing hall. Immediately!
Wiener. Come on. We have to go now.
I want to sleep through for twelve hours now - Without interruption.
At least.
Forget it Krause. Our drill instructor was just here.
Changed the schedule.
Morning exercise is the order of the day.
So Foxes. Listen carefully.
Fencing Master Metzel is coming today.
You can really learn something from him.
He has been training all of the fraternities in the area for 30 years.
So, a little respect.
I hate morning exercises.
Come on men. The early bird catches the worm.
Except Wiener, he only has bad breath.
Good morning, Gentlemen.
Man, already so hardworking.
Who is the Consenior here this semester?
That would be me, Master.
Man Kröger it is the possibility. Hilarious.
Well then, let's go.
All of you sit down.
Up. Ready.
Go.
Jeez!
Kröger.
That is a completely pointless what you are fabricating.
A little more technique. More elegance.
If I may ask.
Sorry Master.
Or do you want to cut off my arm?
Geier. You come up.
Show me how to waggle properly.
Go.
Stop. Man!
Geier. What's wrong with you?
No stamina?
Don't you have an appointment for a personal contract?
Even a fencer ace has to prep orderly otherwise it won't work.
Don't worry Master. I'll be back in top form in no time time.
You're totally drunk.
Sit down.
Oh boy!
Hubertus, Hubertus.
Very good. You will become a good fencer.
What's your name?
Wolfgang Hubertus.
The son of Jens Hubertus.
No wonder.
Thanks. Next.
Come over.
Quick.
I'm starting.
Ready. Go.
Fox. So what is that?
So if you go on Mensur like this
then there will be shredded food later.
Over. Done. End.
Sit down.
You are all totally done. Unacceptable.
Now listen up. Kröger, the next time I come,
you'll be sober. All off you!
Wiener bring me an apple spritzer.
Yes Master.
Do you already know the joke about the two gays who go canoeing?
I have another one.
Don't give up so easily.
I thought you'd like it here, with us in the Corps.
You are a son off a member. What should your father think?
Man, you are so naive.
You don't understand anything at all.
I don't want to jeopardize my studies.
I want to study biology and not binge drink every day.
You can still study.
I'm tired of being commanded by these idiots all the time.
It's not that bad.
It would be a shame to lose you as a Corps Brother.
You'd better not lose yourself.
All the best David.
Take care of yourself.
Don't be like them.
Master Metzel is over there.
What is he doing there?
On such fencing days, Metzel is always there.
He trained the Germanis in the low fencing style.
Low fencing?
This is the fencing style the two fraternities have agreed on.
A more dangerous version of the Mensur.
Watch carefully Scharrenberg.
We wanted to show you this so that you know what to expect.
Silencium in the fencing room.
I would like to ask you to close all doors and windows.
As well as quitting smoking and eating.
I would like to point out again that filming and photographing
is strictly forbidden during Mensur bout.
The second gentlemen have the floor.
Thank you high impartial.
I am hereby anouncing a tripartite Pro Patria.
Between my dear fraternity Germania
and a respectable fraternity Austria.
The rules of the low fencing style apply.
I am anouncing the first match of the Pro Patria.
Mr Meier, representative of the Germania fraternity, is fighting at my side.
This Mensur bout goes over 40 rounds of 5 strikes
including the first strike.
There is no blow of honour. I have nothing more to announce.
My brother Moeller is fencing on my side.
I still have a medically prescribed leather Scar-protection to report.
The long opening command is on my side. The final command with the others.
Thanks. Silencium for such a Mensur bout.
Finally we start.
Stance.
Ready.
Hit yourselves.
Halt!
Up please.
Ready.
Hit yourselves.
Halt.
Physician.
Continue.
Germania reports a small bloody hit at quart.
In position for the third round.
Ready.
Hit yourselves.
Continuation.
Oh God. Why don't the Austrians give up?
He's badly injured.
Yes, the frats let stand longer.
They don't give up as quickly as we do.
Hit yourselves.
Halt.
O ha, direct hit. That's it for the frat.
We stand.
That's very cool.
Stance.
Ready.
Hit yourselves.
Halt.
Withdrawel.
High Impartial. Austria Graz withdraws after loss of substance.
And thanks for the mensur bout.
Partie Ex. Silencium Ex.
Yes, but it was still worth it, wasn't it Geier?
There you can see, that you always have to keep your defense up, Scharrenberg.
Defense is for frats and cowards.
Come on.
Hey guys. Sunk again in the bar?
Hangs.
Cheers my dear Cheers.
Get that down there.
Hey how are you?
Crappy.
Yes, then we should have another beer right away.
Then you'll feel better.
Fox Student.
Tell me, is something wrong?
There is simply nothing right at all anymore.
I can't get anything done.
The Corps is taking up far too much time.
I don't go to university anymore.
I'm drunk again and It's not even twelve.
Oh David. It's always like this in the first Fox Semester.
Of course it's tough.
But we don't want to include everyone in our Corps either.
We select our people very specifically.
Do you understand.
And now you've got your first Fox Fuss and would like to throw it all away.
It has happened to all of us. You have to go through that now.
Or do you want to give up?
Just like that.
Like Hubertus.
Cheer up my dear. It will get better soon. Believe me.
Listen. Next Semester you will probably become a full member.
Then you're a Corps boy and get your own Foxes.
Your own Foxes, and they do the dirty work for you and you go to university.
That's how it has worked for over 200 years.
Tell me what's your really the problem?
I'm really scared of fencing.
I was just on one of these PPs from ...
From such a right wing fraternity. What's their name again?
Germanen?
Yes, exactly the Germans and such a totally disgusting Austrian fraternity.
The guys looked so ugly later. I don't want to end like this.
Moment. Did you see this PP?
Who took you there?
Well, Richert and Geier.
Oh yes, our Buxen. Yes everything is clear now.
No, Richert und Geier.
Exactly. These are the Buxen in our Corps.
Geier must have done that especially to scare you.
David, you don't have to worry about fencing at all.
Yes, take a look at our faces. Do you see a scar somewhere?
Everyone got through the Mensur cleanly, even Wiener.
Don't worry, we'll prepare you properly.
Nothing will happen to your handsome face.
David, I have something for you.
Here.
Wow.
What do you need the medal for?
This is a ribbon button. This holds the ribbon in place.
Come on, I'll show you.
What's the matter with your ribbon?
So, you put this in here and then it finally looks like something.
So my dear...
What's the program for tonight?
How about a lady visit?
We haven't had a lady visit for weeks.
Yes, relax.
I'm in.
Foxes. Fun. Yes.
How are things here?
Tidy up the House.
Fencing practice as usual. 6pm. On time.
Not a second later.
What kind of shitty mood is that?
Get me a Beer Boy David.
The Corps hosted an elegant cocktail party every semester.
A strict alcohol ban was issued by the Corps Convention.
So that we were able to serve the guests
and make a good impression on the student body.
Foxes, I need two Mai Tai here and hurry!
We don't want to let the ladies die of thirst.
Shit, what is in the Mai Tai?
Scharrenberg, where are the cocktails?
Stop talking. Start mixing.
Great, well done. Krause my Fox Student.
Thank god. Geier really is getting on my nerves.
Krause is no better, believe me.
Here, Relax. Calm down.
The alcohol ban?
Just don't drink so much and don't tell anyone.
Cheers my Fox Student. Cheers Mentor.
A Vodka-O please.
Vodka what?
O please.
Krause. A Vodka-O and quickly, yes.
Today if possible.
Are you new to this fraternity?
Yes, you can say so.
But you haven't picked the best one here in town.
Badly mixed drinks.
Bulky dancers.
And lousy DJ.
By the way, my name is Julia.
Fox Scharrenberg.
I mean David.
Thank you darling. I know that you are still a Fox.
Man, she is hot.
I'd like to bone her, you know.
Get lost Fox. Away with you, you stinky Fox.
Oh Jankwitz, did you see her?
Yes, but you better forget her right away.
She is not in your league. You can get her, but you can't keep her.
She goes out with the son of our old member Mr. Pfander.
Pfander. The Interior Minister?
Yes the interior minister.
Is the Pfander's son also a Corps Brother?
No that not. The father is enough.
So leave it. Believe me. She is trouble.
Brandt, why Geier is entertaining your girlfriend?
Come on. As long as I don't have to dance.
Another champagne please.
Tell me, do you have to work here all evening?
Actually yes.
It's a shame because I would love to dance.
Doesn't your boyfriend get jealous?
Which boyfriend?
I thought you were with Pfander's son.
Not any longer.
Wait!
Fuchs Scharrenberg. There you are. You may have nerve.
What are you doing out here?
Especially during one of our Corps Events. Hello.
That's what I call Ex-kneipen and you come in with us right now.
No, that's not possible Richert.
Let me pass.
Shut up Fox!
Come with me now, otherwise you can forget about the Corps right now.
I'll kick you out if you don't come with. Now!
Shit!
Shit, shit, shit, you screwed up!
That will have consequences, I guarantee you.
I'll bring that to the Corps Convent.
Asshole Richert. Asshole.
Nothing asshole.
Man man Scharrenberg. Why didn't you listen to me?
Now you've screwed up a lot.
Yeah man i'm sorry.
I could not think clearly. There was this girl.
I mean she totally turned my head. You know that.
Alright. Listen up.
If you do exactly what we tell you,
you'll come out of this reasonably clean.
You say that you left because of a girl ...
... but with any one. No way with this Julia, do you understand?
Yes? Yes.
And only answer when asked.
And by no means start arguing.
The best thing to do is to admit your guilt immediately
and assert that it will never happen again. That goes down well.
Can I get kicked out for something like that?
Well, it's not that bad. But we will have to punish you.
You stay here. We'll get you.
Hey Scharrenberg. What a horny goat are you.
Have you completely forgotten the career opportunities the Corps offers you?
A brothel is cheaper.
Cost benefit factor understood?
Krause. Shut up.
Scharrenberg. Come in.
Stand there Scharrenberg.
So gentlemen. I hereby open the second Corps Convent in the summer semester 2020.
We are negotiating the criminal complaint
that Corps Boy Richert brought up against Fox Scharrenberg.
Please Richert.
I hereby file a criminal complaint against Fox Scharrenberg.
Scharrenberg left the cocktail party without permission.
Not only did he leave an official Corps Event without excuse.
But he also abandoned his Corps Brothers who had to do his job.
Later, I found him in front of the house, drunk and with a girl.
Yes, with that, he not only left without excuse, but also stayed outside the Corp House,
as a Fox in our colors unaccompanied by a Corp Brother.
Last but not least, Scharrenberg disregarded the alcohol ban...
... and at first even refused to follow the instructions of a Corps Boy,
in present of foreign fraternity members...
And when I was about to get him to go back to the Corp House with me.
Thank you.
Well, Scharrenberg, these are serious accusations.
What do you have to say in your defense?
Should I say something now?
Yes please.
I am very sorry.
I don't know what got into me either.
Ah, so you admit it?
Yes.
Yes, I plead guilty on all counts and ...
... I'm really, really sorry.
Why did you have a drink despite the alcohol ban?
You knew that you were not allowed to drink alcohol.
I kind of forgot.
Forgot? You don't forget something like that, Fox!
Man Wiener, why are you picking on me now?
You're my Fellow Fox, you don´t tell me what i do.
Corps Boy Wiener. More respect Fox, if I may ask.
Slow down Wiener.
Do I need to remind you how often you've broken the alcohol ban?
Or how often I had to cram you out on other corp houses.
Brandt. That's not an argument.
When you defend your Grandson Fox, stay objective and don't attack others.
Excuse me Senior.
Back to the topic.
Scharrenberg, you still haven't told us the reason
why you just ran away like that.
Well.
It was because of a girl.
She really wanted me to go with her and ...
I couldn't say no.
Yes, and who was that girl?
I don't remember, I've forgotten her name.
Because you were so drunk?
The Fox runs around drunk with some chick in front of the house
and drags our colors to the dirt.
That's incredible, isn't it ?!
So you don´t show up for own Mensur when you're on a date?
You know that would be real problem.
In my capacity as Consenior, I would have take your place.
No of course not. The Corps has absolute priority!
I am really very sorry.
You see, he apologized.
But that's not enough.
Scharrenberg, you're not getting your studies done at all.
When was the last time you were in a lecture?
Do you have a lesson plan for example?
Yes.
You're right.
The Corps is taking too much of me.
That is not an excuse. Study always comes first!
Studies must never suffer from activity.
Am I right Wiener? Yes!
You know we have to pass exams, don't you?
I hope you know what that means.
We've already had to part with many dear Corps Brothers,
because they failed at their exams.
Life's not always all about fun.
Silentium Geier. Silentium.
That is not the subject of discussion now.
Thank you Scharrenberg. It is enough.
Culpability is given. You can see that yourself.
You can go now.
We will negotiate the sentence and then call you back inside.
Cheer up Scharrenberg.
Have a quick one. Then you'll feel better again.
Krause leave me alone. I don't drink any more.
Never again.
So Scharrenberg, taking into account that you haven't been with us that long
and that you are also understanding ...
... the Corps Convent has decided to suspend you for 2 weeks.
You will receive a work order from the Corps Convention.
You will clean up the beer cellar before the next convention.
And you'll take care of our Corp Dog Brutus
and walk the dog at least three times a day.
During the time you are suspended, you are not allowed to wear our colors,
or go to other fraternity houses.
Not even in the company of other Corps Brothers.
Nevertheless, you still have the duty to
attend all official Corps Events.
Do you accept this punishment?
Absolutely!
And I wanted to say again that I'm really, really sorry and ...
I will get better in the future. It never happens again.
Would be better for you.
You can understand this punishment as a yellow card.
One more thing and you out! I guarantee you that.
Well. I hereby close the Corps Convention at32 pm.
You can leave now.
Thank you dear Corps Brothers.
Oh Scharrenberg, one more thing. You have to give me your ribbon.
I will keep it for you and give it back after your sentence expires.
Yes, I hope you see this as an opportunity.
You have to get better.
Gentlemen.
Suddenly, the fun was over.
For the first time I noticed
how seriously everything had to be taken here.
Even when jokes were cracked.
They were right about their allegations and I decided to become better.
As a Corp Student and otherwise.
Fox. Phone.
Twenty one, twenty two. Twenty three.
Ah Scharrenberg. It's a beer.
Corps Teutonia, Fox Scharrenberg good evening.
Speaking.
Drink.
Wait a second.
See you later.
So friends.
Now you are learning how to drink properly as a Corps Student.
Let's see if you are any good as a Corp Student.
Gentlemen, let's do some straight talking here.
This is where the wheat is separated from the chaff.
A case of beer for everyone.
And you can't go to bed until the tub is full and the beer is empty.
Are we clear?
Say Wiener. You still know it goes, right?
Show your former Fellow Foxes how to drink properly.
Why me?
Richert can do it.
So.
Hey Wiener, haven't you heard
what your Consenior told you?
This is an order, is that clear?
Yes, high Consenior.
No chit-chat Wiener. Drink!
You know what... You are now doing the whole program.
That's how you do it.
Pull through. Yes sir.
Corps Brother Wiener demonstrated how it's done. Let's go. Hurry up.
Get rid of it. Put it away.
I give up. I've have enough.
I cannot.
We will make it.
Hey guys, I've been through this before.
Make some effort! Start drinking properly!
Keep going. No more dramatic pause.
Drink like men. We don't have all day.
Come on Hain. We're all going through the same, yeah.
Do not give up.
Come on, you whimper. Get to the beer front!
Richert, you bastard. Sadist! I can not anymore.
Leave me alone. I want to get out of here.
Shut up Fox. You're drinking this now.
You loser.
I just can't take it anymore. I want to get out of here.
I want to get out of here. I want to go home!
Pull yourself together Fox! Okay?
If you give up now, then you are no longer be one off us.
Kröger, leave him alone,
You can see he's screwed.
Hain, that's it. You are out.
And goodbye.
Hey, where do you want to go?
Don't touch me!
Do you want to get violent now or what?
This is my Fellow Fox!
He was your Fellow Fox. Forget him.
He wouldn't have been a good Corps Student anyway, okay?
Richert, you owe me 50 euros.
Yes, sure.
What are you staring at?
Did anyone tell you to stop drinking?
You don't stop until we say that, is that clear?
That's how it works here!
We drink on and on.
I felt nothing. I was completely exhausted.
I didn't care at all about Hain.
To be honest, I was just angry at him because we had to drink his remaining beers.
We never saw Hain again.
He left the Corps House early the next morning without comment.
Nobody wept a tear after him.
Here David. Your ribbon. The two weeks are up.
Make something of it.
You can count on me.
Elisabeth, you look lovely.
Many Thanks.
May I introduce you to our new Fox Scharrenberg.
Good day. I welcome you Madam.
But what is that? Please don't be so formal.
Howdy Fox.
Oh hello.
Give me my regards to your daughter.
Elisabeth is the wife of our old Member Mr. Raul.
Mr. Raul is the CEO of one of the largest industrial groups in Germany.
Revenue in the billions.
Selling ​​weapons to the entire world.
Tanks, assault rifles, submarines, the whole product line.
The main customer is the German Army.
And who is this?
I was just about to say.
This is our old member, Mr. Mueller the third.
He is the State Secretary in the Ministry of Defense.
Of course, he and Mr. Raul always have a lot to talk about.
It then comes down to budgets in the billions.
I am a Lieutenant and study in the Military University.
After graduation, I will work for the Department of Defense.
The gentleman back there is the Vice Chancellor and Minister of Economics of Austria.
Is he also a Corps Men?
No. He is a Religious Frat.
He's in a non-fencing catholic fraternity.
But they have been in power in Austria for decades.
I wonder how?
Fencing Duels are not tolerated by church.
But that is an excuse, if you ask me.
But you know, in the end it doesn't matter.
One and the same kind.
You got to be in a fraternity. We know our people.
Sick.
Do you see the little bitch sitting there?
This is the daughter of our old member Mr. Raul.
I banged her at the garden party last year in our beer basement.
She squealed like a stabbed piglet.
Contenance.
Richert.
Gentlemen.
Walter Pfander is sitting over there.
He is the interior minister's son.
Please take special care of him.
Try to make him a member.
Just put a ribbon on him before someone else does it.
I beg you.
Dear Corps Brothers, dear families, dear guests.
Our Corps is strong, demographically healthy
and is proud, like every semester ...
... about a large number of good, new Foxes.
And looking at our active ones, my inner feeling confirms...
... that we are on the right path with the alignment of our Corps.
I have the greatest respect for these young and older Corps Brothers.
Whom have decided to live by our values.
And defend the heritage of our covenant.
That at a time when values ​​and traditions are needed.
Since they threaten to disappear more and more from the consciousness of our people.
At this point, however, it should be said;
We don't see ourselves as an elite.
But when we are needed,
then we don't deny our responsibility!
Honor, loyalty, honesty, morality.
These are all values ​​that we stand by and are worth fighting for.
Because they are often denied and thus the cohesion of society is threatened.
Of course, standing for those values, doesn't mean we can´t have fun times in our fraternity life.
I like to remind you of our regular events and our spontaneous evening activities.
Which will certainly not be forgotten.
But I have to urge caution.
We are non-political.
There are still very severe deficits in the public perception of the Corps.
That also means that we have to set ourselves apart.
Of revanchism and revisionist ambitions.
Dear Corps Brothers and Friends,
even if patience is a virtue, and time heals all wounds.
We must move forward in healthy patriotism.
And must never leave the field to the right-wing extremists!
Splendid.
Anyone who wants to disrupt the social democratic system.
Everyone who spreads fake news and denies life-threatening climate change.
Deserves the social criticism in full force.
With that in mind, I would like to ask everyone...
... to rub a thundering salamander on an everlasting Vivat Crescat of our dear Teutonia.
Vivat, Vivat, Vivat.
David, David, Fox Scharrenberg, wake up.
It's time for your mensur bout.
What's wrong with you? Now you have to be wide awake.
Wake up you sleepyhead.
Don't listen, just focus on yourself.
This is where it’s at!
Hold on tight here Wiener. Yes I got it. OK.
Too tight?
Can't you make it so tight, please?
No, that's exactly right.
We don't want a blade getting lost near your carotid artery.
Here have a drink. You are way too nervous.
Don't be afraid. We have practiced this a thousand times.
I've trained you well.
You defense is tight. Everything's alright.
Nothing can happen to you my boy.
Besides, the other Fox is just as scared as you are.
Stay calm, concentrate on your strikes and then it's over in no time.
In 20 minutes you will laugh about it.
Swab here.
It´s not that bad, David. It's just a small cut.
Don't be scared now, yeah.
You go out there now and finish off the fucker!
Don't piss your pants.
Nothing happens in the Fox Mensur. Never.
So Scharrenberg, it's time.
We must. Come on. Let´s go.
Good luck in the fight. Knock him off.
Luck in the fight. Focus. Like in training.
You will do it. Good luck.
Luck and a sharp blade.
Listen up Scharrenberg. Now comes the honor round.
Your blades touch on top and then you take your arm down.
Concentrate now. Do not strike.
Otherwise the Mensur won´t count and you'll have to fence again next week.
Turn around.
Height adjustment.
I hereby open the first Ordinary Open Air Determination Day in the summer semester 2020.
I'm announcing a simple blade Mensur between my Corps Brother Scharrenberg on my left,
and on my right side the honorable representative of the Corps Suevia, Mr. Kehl.
The word is now with the seconds.
The beginning and ending command will be on our side.
The first strike will be on our side.
I have nothing more to anounce.
In position.
Up please for the honor round.
Ready.
Go.
So Scharrenberg, now it's getting serious.
You only hit primes at first, yes! No experiments.
And don't strike before the go. And always keep going.
In no case stop.
The round is not over before you hear the word halt.
Luck and a sharp blade my boy.
In position please.
Up, please, to the first sharp round.
Ready.
Go.
Halt.
Take it easy. You are doing great.
Everything is fine, just not so wild please.
Ok, easy. You don't necessarily want to hit him.
You just have to go the distance. Okay. Keep it up.
In position please.
Up, please, for the second sharp round.
Ready.
Go.
Halt.
After the first few rounds, my opponent and I had found our rhythm.
Of course, no one wanted to get hurt, no risky strikes.
I fought like a machine, executed my fencing routine.
Strike, turn, pull up, strike, turn away again.
Quart, prime, prime, quart, terz.
Practiced a thousand times. It was almost like riding a bike.
Then everything went very fast.
Listen, one final round, that´s it.
Understood? Alright, keep it up.
Up please for the final sharp round.
Ready. Go.
Halt!
Yes, you did it.
Fox Student. My dear Fox Student.
And then. Then everything was over.
So suddenly and quickly, as if the Mensur had never happened.
Cheers. Cheers.
You were better than me.
After my harmless Fox Mensur,
... Geier still had to fight his personal contrahage against the Swabian.
I had the honor, as a so-called Drag Fox, to hold Geier's arm during the breaks.
I hereby announce a personal contrahage between my Corps Brother Geier on my left,
and on my right side the Honorable Representative of the Corps Suevia, Mr. Kraftburg.
This contract goes over 45 rounds, five strikes, no honor round, no breaks.
The word is now with the seconds.
The beginning and ending commands are on my side.
First strike is on my side.
I have nothing else to announce.
Stance.
Up please.
Geier started out strong, as expected.
Ready.
Go.
Halt.
Geier, calm down. You still have 40 rounds ahead of you.
If you continue like this, you'll run out of breath.
Hogwosh. I will slash this jumping jack next round.
Okay.
In position.
Up please for the second round.
Ready. Go.
Halt.
Geier, watch your defense. Your arm must be higher. You are not protected!
Leave it. I know exactly what I am doing.
Alright.
In position please.
Up please.
Ready. Go.
Halt.
Why halt?
Teutonia reports one...
Down, down, head down.
I correct myself. Two bloody ones.
Physician.
Teutonia thanks for the Mensur, and quits because of hit.
Crap.
Silencium. Mensur Ex.
What's going on?
Silencium Scharrenberg. Fox Escape.
Fox Escape?
Fox Escape. Another Corps Student tradition.
Once a semester, the Foxes flee from their Corps Boys.
Imagine a scavenger hunt through the fraternity houses in Germany.
I would like to spare you more precise details.
Let's go Scharre,
What's the matter with you man?
You're totally drunk.
I failed to pass the exam for the second time.
Shit.
I'm really sorry for that.
Can you try again?
No chance. That´s it.
Game over!
But hey, David. Do not worry.
You surely will do better.
Michael. Please let's talk. Michael. Please wait. Wait.
Do something.
Somebody call a doctor.
Please bring me home. I can not stand it any longer.
Geier.
What do you want?
You know that yourself, I think much better.
Geier you are a disgusting piece of shit.
I do not know what you're talking about.
Say what you have to say. Loud and clear Fox or shut up!
I saw what you did.
What did you see?
You saw nothing at all.
You made out with Brandt's girlfriend.
Now he's dead.
So what? I took her.
She needed a real man.
Not an impotent loser like Brandt.
It is not my fault if this mimosa jumps to his death because of it.
I don't see any legal or moral connection there.
Disgusting rat.
Carefully Scharrenberg.
Be very careful with what you say.
I can only repeat it.
I am not to blame for Brandt jumping.
The man was incapable of living.
Did you know that he had failed the exam for the second time.
Maybe it's better for him that way.
Quiet Fox. Take it easy.
I could break your neck now.
Do what you want Fox.
But nobody will believe you. You're just a fucking Fox.
So, pull yourself together, or you'll be out faster than you think.
And shut up from now on.
You degenerate noble piece of shit.
Fuck off.
What's going on here?
Scharrenberg is becoming a problem.
How come that effects you?
I don't want to be with an alcoholi who will kill himself some day.
Either you break up with the Corps or it's over.
You're kidding me.
I can not.
It's not possible.
What does the Corps have to do with us?
Wait.
Take care.
Godawful.
The semester was coming to an end.
Jankwitz, Kröger and Geier were inactivated
and thus no longer had any duties on the Corps House.
Krause was made a full member.
That means he was given a Corps Boy status early on.
While I had to serve as a Silver Fox.
Richert became Senior and Consenior.
Wiener became Secretary.
And Krause took over the post of the Fox Major.
Good news. We have two new Foxes.
One of the new Foxes you already know. Walter.
This is Pfander's youngest son.
You know, this is the one whose girlfriend you stole.
Really now?
No worries. That's alright.
You look sad.
Listen. I'm telling you a secret now.
But you have to give me your word as a Corps Brother to keep that secret.
Well, Walter, that's not Pfander's real son at all.
Yes, he has a different father.
Pfander is always on the road with his duties and Walter has a lot to deal with.
That's why Walter sometimes seems to be a bit strange,
but he's actually a very nice guy.
Walter.
Walter. Scharre. Walter has just received the ribbon.
Say hello to your Fellow Fox.
Beer Boy.
Finished.
Done.
You know David, I don't blame you that you stole my girlfriend for a while.
So she could at least see what she got in me.
But now she's back. All well again and forgiven.
I beg your pardon?
Well, now that we're Corps Brothers, we should try to get along.
At least I'm not a drunk looser.
Tell me Walter, you don't look a lot like your father at all.
And so what?
Well, maybe the postman was there.
Sorry it was just a joke. Do you understand?
The Postman.
Come on, that's funny, isn't it?
Fox Scharrenberg. What kind of shit are you talking about here?
Can't you even keep your mouth shut?
Apologize right now. Immediately, or ...
Man Richert, that was just a joke.
It’s not my problem if he has no humor.
Ah, now you're arguing again.
You apologize now!
On who´s side are you?
We have been Corps Brothers way longer.
The Fox hasn't even fought.
No, he hasn't fought yet.
And yes, we are longer Corps Brothers. But not for long.
If you don't apologize right now.
Ok Scharrenberg. Forget it.
You are done.
Yes what's up? Yes fine. Yes fine.
Yes fine.
Yes drink. Drink.
Hey Fox Major. Yes. Look!
I got the gun from my father's weapons locker.
Don't tell, don't tell anybody.
Okay your father, have you already talked to him?
What about the job in the ministry of interior?
We're going out for dinner next week.
Then you can ask him yourself.
Yes who is fine. Yes who?
Drink up Brutus, drink up. Fine, drinking!
You stop that shit. This is cruelty to animals.
Hey what? What's wrong with you?
It's a Teutonic hound.
That's a real Teuton.
Not such a pussy.
He drinks it. He drinks it. Brutus.
Hey what's the point, why give the good brew to the Corps Dog?
Fuck, we have to sew this.
That’s definitely three stitches.
Scharrenberg, get the sewing kit we need to take care of this.
Shit.
Stop it. What are you doing? NO!!!
No, you Bastard!
Give me the gun. Calm down. Give me the gun!
Asshole!
Folks.
Richert, you call old member Pfander immediately.
Krause, you take the dog out and bury it immediately.
Can't be. This can't be.
Man, we can't afford that.
This is not possible here at all. That is not how it works.
Lord sacramento again.
Geier! This can't go public!!!
Shit pile.
Idiot.
What have you done now?
Pfander shot Brutus.
Geier and Richert are involved.
Yes, of course, Richert and Geier are also to blame.
Your problem is that you're constantly drunk.
It's always other peoples fault, right?
You are always the victim. The others are the bad guys.
Man, Geier banged Anja, that's why Brandt is now dead.
Shut the fuck up. Leave Brandt out of the game.
Were you there?
Who do you want to believe? Them?
It doens´t matter who I believe. No one will believe you.
You are really a great Corps Brother, you know that.
Not to mention what a body boy.
You'd better help me to report the two.
Did I warn you?
Yes I warned you
Yeah great, you were right again.
Are you proud of yourself now?
Okay, you have only one last chance.
You call Pfander and try to explain everything to him.
But be careful man. You can't go against them.
David... What?... Wait, Pfander is here.
Yes and?
Pfander is here.
Yes, and he said everything was okay.
Forget what he said.
Fact is that this guy doesn't attend the Corps Convention for pleasure.
You have to help me.
Scharrenberg, you're a very nice guy.
I really like you. But you have a problem.
In a desert could be one lonesome pitfall and you would fall for it.
So, then we would have concluded point three of the agenda and...
Sit down.
Hereby we move on to point four off the agenda.
Various.
First, we have a criminal complaint from old honorably Member Pfander against Fox Scharrenberg.
If you please come forward Mr. Pfander.
Thank you Richert.
Fox Scharrenberg, please get up.
I hereby file a criminal complaint against Fox Scharrenberg.
Sir Fox von Scharrenberg, if I may please.
Against Sir Fox Von Scharrenberg, because he repeatedly attracted negative attention.
He's out of control.
He is dragging our colors in the dirt and behaved repeatedly non Corps Student wise.
This is not the first trial against Sir Fox Von Scharrenberg.
What should I make of my Corps Brothers?
When one of our Foxes throws glasses at the wall and willfully destroys Corps Property.
Green virtues are celebrated in this house.
Shirts off Corps Brothers are torn a part.
Excessive and disgusting drinking.
Fist fighting.
My God. We're not wild animals!
We are Corps Students.
Furthermore, women have been harassed in a disgusting way.
That's not true.
Silencium Sir Fox Von Scharrenberg.
Who allowed you to speak?
Are you denying that you approached my son's girlfriend inappropriately.
In a way that I don't want to repeat here.
I ask the Corps Convent here and now
whether we can and want tolerate such people in our ranks?
I mean what kind of upbringing did you enjoy?
What kind of family do you come from?
These are questions I ask myself when I look at your behavior.
Sir von Scharrenberg.
With or without Sir.
For sure you are definitely not a Corp Student.
There is no place in our ranks for people like you.
So, Scharrenberg, would you like to comment?
So gentlemen.
It seems to me that I ...
...am played as a pawn sacrifice in this Corps Intrigue.
I just can't be bothered with this.
That my family is insulted here...
...makes it unbearable for me, and inevitably calls for satisfaction!
I hereby put down my ribbon.
I will keep my ribbon button, which my Mentor Jankwitz has given to me.
For your information.
My family has had Corps Students in all circles for generations.
Mainly in the white circle, of course.
My maternal ancestor was a founding father of your covenant in the year1820.
That is why I joined this inadequate covenant.
That's the only mistake I can blame myself for.
Mr. Pfander, I expect an apology from you!
As you choose to not apologize,
I hereby challenge you to a duell!
The choice of weapons is yours.
You will hear from my second.
Good day gentlemen.
Silencium, Silencium.
I hereby hand the floor to Mr. Pfander the third representative of the Corps Teutonia.
Dear representatives of the Seniors Convent.
I was given the great honor to be the voice of my ...
How can it be that someone is allowed to speak here who is not honoring satisfaction.
Silencium. Who are you that you are speaking here without being asked?
Scharrenberg the IV. Senior of the Corps Vandalia.
I take the liberty of speaking here because I consider it my duty ...
... to inform the council that the Pfander Family is not respecting the terms of an honor duell.
And that the council can't possibly tolerate letting such people of no honor speak for it.
How dare you?
That is an incredible insult.
Can you please substantiate your allegations.
With pleasure.
A year ago, I challenged Pfander the First to a personal contract over an honor dispute.
But instead of accepting the challenge, my letter came back with the note; "Address unknown"...
There is no doubt that Pfander the First disgracefully pulled himself out of the affair.
I'm here today to sort it out once and for all.
So far that's true.
The requested person is apparently not present.
Then Mr. Pfander, are you going to comment on these allegations for your father?
Gentlemen, I would like your brief attention.
Admittedly, Teutonia was aware of this honor dispute.
But we negated it at the time, because it was with a former Fox off our Corps.
Besides according to our rules, non fraternity members are not allowed to challenge Corps Students.
So I would suggest...
I knew you wanted to talk your way out of it.
But according to Article 23 of the Kösener Statute, this is permissible.
I quote.
In honor disputes, non fraternity members, are authorized to challenge Corps Students...
... if another fraternity grants them protection.
Quote end.
Can someone fact check this?
High Council, Metzel, Corps Alemania, Chairman of the Black Circle.
If you allow?
I insist.
Indeed, according to Article 23, non fraternity students are allowed to challenge Corps Students.
Kröger Teutonia, representative of the Blue Circle.
Completely irrelevant.
The challenge was issued one year ago and has expired.
Did Mr. Scharrenberg apply for protection when he had the non fraternity student status?
Silencium, silencium, from now on there will be a list of speakers.
I will not tolerate any further heckling.
From now on, all heckling will be punished with a fine of 100 euros.
We can do well with the money.
Honorable Councillor, I hereby declare that I have granted
Mr. von Scharrenberg protection retrospectively for my covenant.
That is unheard of. That's not possible, Herr Metzel.
Silencium, silencium.
Order, otherwise I'll have the room cleared here, yes.
So, first of all, a fine here for Mr. Richert.
So this is indeed an unusual case, for which, to my knowledge, there is no precedent case.
That's why I feel compelled to decide this case on an ad hoc basis.
For this reason we will vote on the admissibility of this honor dispute.
We are now voting according to circles. So now the vote.
Which circle votes for it?
The black circle votes for it.
The green circle votes yes.
All right and who is in dissent?
The Blue Circle votes against it and hereby protests against this attack-like vote.
Apply for a corresponding protocol note.
Yes, yes, everything is noted.
And how does the white circle decide?
Traditionally abstains from the vote.
It's unbelievable what's going on here.
Fine for the tall gentleman with his barrel hat.
Yes, so now order please. Silencium.
To me it now looks like we've found a vote.
Namely two votes in favor, one vote against and one abstention.
So for me this honor dispute is permissible.
So Mr. Pfander III, are you going to accept on behalf off your father?
I'm not trained at all.
But it shouldn't fail here.
That's enough, that's embarrassing!
I am providing goodwill and am accepting the challenge, so that it is clear!
Well then that would be clarified.
According to the rules, the challenged has the choice of the time, the place and the weapons.
Here and now. We fight with sabers.
Please what? With sabers?
Mr. Geier are you sure about that?
The last saber fight happened shortly before the second world war.
Saber!
Listen, Scharrenberg, a saber fight is different from a Mensur bout.
This is no longer fun, it is bitterly serious.
You can still think about it, you have achieved what you wanted.
I stand by my word.
It's an honour dispute, you do not quit.
Alright be careful, you don't have to prove anything to anyone.
Just see that you get out of the matter safely.
Keep calm and fight defensively. Anger makes you blind.
I am next to you and will protect you, understood?
Good. Now it’s about to begin.
Silencium.
I hereby open an honor dispute between Geier on my right side, Teutonia ...
... and Mr. von Scharrenberg the IV, Vandalia, on my left side.
The word is with the secondaries now.
Thank you high official.
I hereby announce a sabe rfight over 60 rounds each with 8 blows.
That´s all.
High official, Teutonia demands a break.
Break for Teutonia.
I ask you to consider the following.
Of course we're not going to back down.
As Teutons, we keep our word.
However, we are also committed to the Corps and other fencing fraternities.
Saber fights are prohibited by law.
If anyone dies in this saber fight, it would be an unparalleled scandal.
And it would be a disaster for the reputation of the Corps.
We should, yes we should find a face-saving solution.
I know what we are doing.
I'll negotiate with the other side that there will be only one honor round.
Thus the Fox has restored his honor and you faced the challenge.
That's the only solution for the Corps.
Mr. Richert, honorable Representative of Corps Teutonia,
may I draw your esteemed attention towards the violation off rules ...
...by contacting participants before such an honorary dispute.
My Corps has instructed me to inform you upon the fact
that our participant is constitutionally incapable of accepting the risk
of fatal injury during an honorary dispute.
So there is only one option.
There will only be an honorably round.
After that both parties discontinuate fighting.
As the honor dispute is not aware off any honorably round,
this arrangement will not be announced as such.
Mr. Metzel, Mr. Scharrenberg, are we in agreement?
Our side agrees.
Ok Geier, I'm sorry ...
... but the other side isn't willing to accept our offer.
I see only one option.
And what would that be?
You have to stand one single exchange of blows.
After that our side aborts due to technical reasons.
Is it Agreed?
Agreed.
Bandaging pause finished.
The word is now with the secondary.
The beginning and ending command will be on my side.
Silencium for such a honor dispute!
Stance.
Ready.
Go!
Halt.
Well
That's called a Kösener smile.
If this story would be movie, I would have been purified ...
... would have left the Corps and that part of my life in the past.
Maybe I would have sold my story as a whistleblower to the press.
But what was the story all about?
Fencing fraternities are a normality in German-language countries.
A secret elite society pulling the strings in the background.
Nobody dares to speak about them.
We all know they exist. But who cares?
And what about me? I want to have a career.
My new Corps Brother offered me a job in a first class consultancy.
I did not say no to that offer. Would you?
But there remains one question.
What would you join?
You want to make a film about Corps Students, yes?
We go to the Pfälzer, there we get a beer. Frats.
You fill up immediately.
You are shit. You are a frat.
What's happening here? Yes, would you please pan over.
Your reasons for beer are as follows.
Which would that be? One, two, three, four, six, seven
You don't think this is going to be boring.
There are a lot of people who find it really exciting.
Smashing Fox.
The whole thing's just a game.
There is full physical effort.
Torture yourself. Torture yourself.
We'll see each other again next semester.
With pleasure!