All right, this is the most handsome
of who we're fighting for, gentlemen.
Get down, get down, get down.
We like this house.
We think we're gonna take it.
Yes, sir.
See you in a bit.
Let us know if this thing changes.
Sir, there's a wall up here.
Copy that.
Why is there a wall?
It's two apartment.
Top of bottom block, two houses.
I understand.
Break it.
Redman zero six, propane five four.
Contact individual
headed north to your location.
Silly traffic east
and west of your structure.
I have a propane five, ten, five.
All stations this
net, all stations this net.
Clearance operations are complete.
All friendly units are RGB at this time.
Be advised you
have new friendly location.
Baker company has moved
north west of your location.
Two clicks.
Understand, copy all.
Sir, Baker company
we're here and not here.
Two kilometers in this position.
Copy that.
Manchu, stand by for sit rip.
Say when ready to copy, over.
Long man, send your traffic.
At zero, nine or seven, we observe people
probing our position from the east.
Section PAPO, one, zero, building 174.
East of root boiler.
At zero, nine, one, two,
we saw amassing at building 175.
North of root Spartan.
Break.
At zero, nine or one, six.
A blue dew with
mams north on root Lakers.
How copy, over.
Yeah, frog man, repeat everything
after blue dew, over.
Manchu, a blue dew
with military age males
traveling north on root Lakers.
Over.
Copy all.
Do you have any more
traffic from my station, over.
Negative, Manchu.
There's your signal.
It's good now, still intermittent.
Cool.
Got eyes on the
northwest corner of building four.
Is that white highlick still there?
No, highlick's pulled
out like five minutes ago,
but I got a male,
white shirt, dark tracksuit pants
looking at our position.
That sounds familiar?
Negative.
ID any weapons?
No weapons.
He's gone.
Is he going on the list?
Single man.
White shirt, dark tracksuit pants,
building four, northwest corner.
By the way, my blue Nike
hoodie went missing off the base.
If you see somebody out
there wearing it, let me know.
Don't shoot him either, I want it back.
Yeah, I'll try. Yeah, I'll try.
We should check that round of buildings
to the west again.
You can just step
right across with rooftops
if you want to, walk right to us, right?
How's it going, Doozer?
Fix six tracking, fix six out.
How's it going?
Going well.
Okay.
That's that new guy energy.
How's it done, man?
Cigarettes and tea, you want tea?
Yeah, I'll pass.
What do you got up here?
Peakers.
Where?
Corners of building four.
Oh, I got you.
I don't see any windows.
I can't see anything.
You know, he's back.
White T-shirt?
Mm-hmm.
Alpha two, this is one.
We might have guys
starting to move in our position.
Maybe because they heard you sludging
through the fucking wall, right?
We could hear every strike.
Why didn't you just charge?
I didn't want to make a noise.
I'm not sure that looked out for you.
Profane five four, this is Redman six.
Can you slew your sensor to the east
on my position on one zero zero meters?
I'm building per GRG.
Call contact.
Redman zero six, stand by.
Turning.
OX-855 track group one.
Profane five five, looking.
Contact, order I see for time.
Hey, we got an individual who was peeking
out of the
northwest corner of building four.
He's disappeared to the west.
Do you see anybody
hanging around that corner over?
Stand by, looking.
Five four, contacts.
Just be advised
you've been probing our position.
Do you see any
mass or suspicious activity
that can indicate a threat over?
Negative zero six, say you're open.
Roger that, profane.
Redman out.
You keep an eye on that for me?
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
Red scarf, red green jacket.
Peeking again, that's the
fourth fucking time he's done that.
It's a peeking and probing.
Peeking with Sirius and Ted to probe.
How many times you
gonna let this guy do this?
I don't know, related, I'd be too.
Hey, cowboy, give me a
heads up if you see this guy
come to your position.
Head scarf, red green jacket.
Copy, we're gonna
build up a big duty or two.
Got a pair of guys
in blue jeans, proven twice.
I have two mams, that
description just showed up here,
blue jeans, one red shirt.
Yep, that's all.
Oh, it looks like
they're getting their jihad on.
Alpha one, Bravo one, we're in a check.
We're getting rockets, small arms fired.
We're all good right
now, but we're pulling air
to our position.
Roger that, check in with BDA when able.
We'll go.
Alpha five, this is Bravo four.
Hey, I think we're gonna
need to pull profane or AO, over.
Roger that, Bravo four.
Redman zero six is
profane, we have been retest.
We have checked off station at this time.
Roger that, profane.
Hey, is there a reason
they're pulling air from us
and not sourcing it from somewhere else?
I'm on it.
What's up?
Just lost air support, pushing to Bravo.
Wild Eagle baseball, Eagle two four.
Profane five four
checked off station at this time.
Looking for any
available air assets, over.
That's not good.
Picture was in contact.
A firm, Wild Eagle base, standing by.
Hey cowboy, we're getting movement here.
Hi, the bono.
Very giant.
Yeah, the streets
are definitely clear now.
Yeah, I'm tracking.
Captain Eric?
It's no good.
They say they call
on all Muslims for jihad.
Jihad to come now, to
kill you, to kill Americans.
Yeah, that sucks.
Yeah, that does suck.
All right, go keep lower
deck lockdown, you understand?
Yeah, I know, and then there's a job.
Hey, downstairs, keep it fucking secure.
Okay, hella, that's it.
There's a job and I'm gonna talk to you.
I know.
You think they're gonna do it?
I think we're about to find out.
You been in there for a while?
Yeah, I live in there now.
All right, swap out, I'll relieve you.
Yes, sir.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Hey Frank, jump on this a second.
I'm out of dip and I gotta stretch, dude.
Here, I got you.
I got a blue opal,
moving east to west
towards OP-1 position, over.
Roger that, blue.
Blue opal is approaching building three.
Three mams, just exited vehicle.
Correction, make that four.
Biting into building three.
Fuck.
Cowboy, the fourth man at PKM.
Couldn't get the shot off, over.
Wake.
Here you go.
What happened?
I couldn't get
him, he ran inside too fast.
Wake.
Yeah, we have definite massing.
A six mams, just
exited building five in my sector.
I'm gonna see him,
I'm gonna see where we are.
Yeah, building three.
I'm gonna take a piss.
Oh fuck.
No!
Our position is under smaller fire.
Frank, Tommy!
Yeah? Tommy, Elliot, you good?
Move!
Move man, bulk in the head!
You hurt?
I'm good, I'm good, check on Elliot.
We got Gary Stone in there.
Put your arm up.
Okay.
How bad is it?
Yeah, we're gonna need a casser back.
All right, this is Frogman six,
Romeo, we are troops in contact
at our last known position.
More info to follow, stand by.
Wild Eagle baseball, Eagle two, four.
We are troops in contact,
requesting immediate air support, over.
Alpha two, this is one.
We've had grenades
thrown into our position.
Copy, one word, contact two.
Elliot is injured, are we coming to you
or are you coming to us?
Stand by.
Hey!
Downstairs, keep it fucking secure.
I'm shot.
Alpha one, we're moving.
You will let you know when we're inbound.
All right, all OPs are under attack.
This is what we're gonna do.
We're gonna collapse to the first deck,
Casa Vachelia, break it down,
let's get ready to move.
Collapse, collapse.
OP two, what's your status?
I gotta get the receiver.
Sir, sir, sir, sir,
sir, sir, what are you doing?
I gotta get the receiver.
We're in a check, all right.
Mack, not a good idea.
This is Frogman six, Romeo,
we need to Casa Vac at
our last known position, over.
Cover him, yeah.
Frogman confirmed,
sector and building number.
OP one location as
follows, Papa one, zero, building.
Five, eight, how copy, over.
Frogman, read back
as follows, Papa one, zero,
building five, eight.
Good read back.
Frogman, anti-amplifying remarks over.
Negative, no amplifying remarks,
just need to Casa
Vac, devise on ETA, over.
Copy that, stand by, over.
Yeah, I'm, guys,
my shit is still in there.
Where is it?
I don't fucking know,
dude, it's in there somewhere.
I have my shit's in there too.
All right, all right, I got it, I got it.
Alpha one, we're moving to you,
we'll let you know when we're inbound.
Copy.
Tommy, you see
where that gun fire came from?
I saw a guy, it shot through the window.
I can't find it.
It's in there, bro.
I can't fucking find it, man.
Frogman six, Romeo, Casa Vac is inbound.
Call sign, Bushmaster on
ID 755, ETA one zero mics, over.
Copy, Bushmaster 755, over.
Radley launched, ETA 10 minutes.
10 minutes. 10 minutes.
All right, stack
up, get ready to collapse,
we're moving down.
Yes, sir.
Sir, I still think
there's dudes on our roof.
Yeah, we're gonna
blow claymores as we move, Sam?
Yes, sir.
Alpha two, be advised,
we'll be blowing claymores.
Oh, fuck, I got a bunch of C4 in my bag,
I gotta get my shit.
Yeah, I'm gonna get it.
Sam, Tommy.
Let's go.
My shit's to the left.
His gear's in the corner.
Copy.
Gotcha.
I got Frank's shit right here.
Gosh.
How we doing?
Yeah, I'm up.
School.
Tommy, I'm me, all right.
All right. That's your kit.
My bag, thanks, Mac.
That's your kit.
We're good.
Larry, skimmer some hands.
Moving.
Clip him in?
Yes, sir.
Tommy.
Opie two, this is one.
We are breaking
down, getting ready to move.
Over.
Yo, somewhere took me in.
Yep.
Tommy, I'm me.
There's an M79 in that room there.
Oh, shit, it's mine.
Got it?
Sam, sledgehammers, in front of you.
Fuck me, I gotcha.
I gotcha.
Come with behind.
You got that?
Who's got that?
I'll see you right there.
Thank you. Yep.
All right.
Hook me up, hook me up.
Yep.
Frank, let me know when we're up on gear.
Sir.
I need my backpack.
Is there any more
gear in that room, Tommy?
Thank you.
How am I?
Right here, brother.
Fuck.
All right, we're all right.
We're up.
Copy.
Go, Mac.
Alpha-2, we're about to blow claymores.
Blow claymores, Sam.
Roger.
Find the hole.
Go!
Last man.
I got the window.
I have the door.
That Bushmaster,
your cap back is inbound.
We are at six
minutes from your position over.
Six minutes out.
Copy, Bushmaster.
Okay.
Alpha-2, we're preparing
to receive Castabak platform.
Are you guys broken down yet?
Get one, not yet.
Check.
All right, here's the breakout plan.
Mac, Laris, you're covering your family.
Yes, sir.
When the tank rolls up,
Frank, you're gonna pop smoke.
Check.
The scouts are gonna lead us out.
It's gonna be Tommy, Elliot, Sam,
and I'm bringing up the rear.
Ray, you're with me.
Once Elliot is in the tank,
we are all coming
back inside the building.
All right, do it.
You, me.
Tell them no sudden movements.
No talking.
I'll
keep their hands where these men can see them.
Rockman, this is Bushmaster.
Goodbye, we've got to receive you, over.
Bushmaster, we'll
be extracting two packs,
exiting out of Metal
Gate directly out of the pressure.
Bushmaster, mark by H-C, over.
Back right, Parker.
Copy, Rockman, two
packs, Metal Gate, H-C-A,
five minutes over.
Copy, Bushmaster.
Five minutes, sir.
All right.
Alpha-2, when the tank
rolls up, we're gonna breakout.
Once we get Elliot evacuated,
we're pulling back to our house.
Break.
You mean?
What, why?
Sir, why?
What is the plan?
We need to cover this door.
The thing we can do to
facilitate your movement to us.
Just don't fucking
do this when we roll up.
You cover this door?
Why, sir?
Just do it, okay?
She's in.
Hey.
Mack, are we good in there?
Yeah, we're good.
We're a few minutes out here.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Hey, find out from me
whether the tank is gonna be left side
or right side.
Yes, sir.
Bushmaster, this is Frogman 6 Romeo.
What side of the gate
will you be landing, over?
How you doing?
Left hand side, left hand side, over.
Left hand side, sir.
Copy.
Yeah, that fucking
Claymore rocked me, dude.
Fuck, I'm ringing my bell.
Do me a favor.
Check on Tommy.
He's pretty close to that grenade.
Elliot, you good?
Good.
I'm good.
You okay?
Yeah, let me see.
You're good.
Ah, fuck.
We are 10 minutes behind.
I'm able to break out.
Roger that.
Captain made a wear
right here, Steve wanted.
Three mics out, your position.
Copy, Bushmaster.
Three mics out.
All right.
If it's only--
Actually, Mrs.
Manny, actually we are Captain.
Stop it.
What's going on?
You are holding security.
Yes.
We are gonna bust
out, go to the Bradley's.
I'm gonna get into Bradley's.
You guys are gonna
come back to the house.
Just like before, everything is okay.
All right?
Rockman, Rockman, we are two mics over.
Copy that.
Two minutes.
Two mics out, pass.
Back, back, Frank.
Two minutes.
Two people.
Two people, I collect.
Tom?
Hey.
God.
Good.
Frank, I hear it, prep the smoke.
Smoke's prepped.
Rockman, sick fromia,
help approaching your OP now.
One minute out.
One minute.
Tom?
Yeah.
Yes sir.
All right, Frank, smoke out.
Smoke out.
Rockman, we I.T. hear smoke, 36.
Hey, stay in the
stack, stay in the stack.
Wrap it down, wrap it down, wrap it down.
We're gonna go.
Break out, break out, break out.
Go, go, hold up.
Go.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh my God.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Hey, get air.
Sir.
Well, beautiful base.
Well, beautiful two six, one platform.
It's available, pushing my paws.
Five zone ETA one.
This is Bushmaster.
We are troops in contact.
We just experienced a large IED.
We have the RTV at this time.
How copy?
Bushmaster, this is Manshew.
Solid copy, our troops in contact.
What you sit around for?
Yeah, upon arrival,
OV1, we were ramped down
on the course of progress.
In there.
We had a massive IED break.
We moved our gunners to some frags.
We're gonna have to our Navy to the cash.
Hey, what on me?
We're gonna need
assistance off loading our casualties.
Over.
Solid copy, our long Bushmaster.
Tommy, what the fuck are you doing?
I need you to help me.
Get the fuck out of here.
We deal with a lot of threats.
Hey, can we get some guns up here?
Frogman six, this is five.
Radio jack, face the fire up there.
Stand by.
I'll be sending some guns up, chief.
I'll grab you, Master Web,
let it out before I'll step right to you.
Me, uh, Bushmaster, copy.
You know, are you
gonna hand me the new one,
Frogman over?
Is that the situation over there?
Uh-huh, I think I'll push back.
Hey, sir, what's that thing over here?
Check, check, check.
We're gonna have to have a better life.
What's going on?
Stand, understand, break free.
All one, get yourself a new radio jack.
Frogman, this is Bushmaster.
Frogman six, Frogman
five, pass me on the fire.
Let me check my car.
Radio jack, how do you read, Master?
Radio jack, follow over.
Prepare to break down.
Now, I need you to break down.
I need you to push, Master.
Negative on comms
with all of the elements.
We are coming to you now.
No attempt continues, Lea.
Frogman six, this is five.
I advise that you
attempt it on your end, over.
Status.
Stand by, prior to breaking out,
we either gonna blow those claim words
or we gotta switch them up.
Alpha two, this is one.
We have taken massive casualties.
We're anticipating
a coordinated enemy attack
at our position at any moment.
We need you to collapse to us, time now.
Jake, this is one, collapse to us, now.
Dragon, but where are you guys?
We're bu--
We're built on.
Look for the blood
and the smoke, we're there.
Tell the ropes, Jake!
What was that?
Fuck.
Tell the ropes, Jake!
No, no, don't tell the ropes.
Jake, what's your update?
Alpha one, this is Alpha two.
We're experiencing a
fire from across the street.
We're looking to
try to break out of there
once it gets solved.
Damn right.
Copy that, just fucking hurry.
Yeah, we'll go.
Hey, I gotta do blood swing.
Okay, all right, all right.
All right, hell, right here, right here.
Just hang in
there, you're not alone, man.
You're okay, I'm going to blow you off.
Okay, all right, all right, all right.
You're good, all right?
You're good.
All right, I'm gonna go the first one.
But I'm gonna give it over
your boot right now, all right?
All right, just hold on, just hold on.
Oh man, that's not gonna work, okay?
All right?
Yes sir, yeah, all right, perfect.
Bring this down.
Menchie 6X Ray, this is Frogman 6 Romeo.
Oh shit, fuck.
We have two severely wounded.
We need another cast
effect as soon as possible.
Be advised that IED
caused the injuries, over.
You want me to do it?
Okay, all right, okay.
Your legs are stretching me.
Frogman, you are not readable, say again.
Menchie 6X Ray, this is Frogman 6 Romeo.
We have two severely wounded.
We need another cast effect, over.
Who's the severely wounded?
It's me.
No, it's not you.
Menchie 6X, who is it?
Menchie 6X.
Who is it?
Hey, hey, we got air back.
We can't do gun runs because the bad guys
are running top of
us, but we can't coordinate
a show of force.
Do you want me to do it?
Do it.
Profane 5X, wild
eagle 2-4, we need an immediate
show of force over our
position, over our position.
OP-1, from south
to north, how copy, over.
Affirm, wild eagle 2-4, show of force,
south to north, inbound 30 seconds.
Sweetie, through.
Guys, I need more gas.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Hey, hey, Fletcher, hey, Fletcher.
What the fuck is Frank doing?
Frank, Frank.
Lock the fucking
stairwell down, this guy's up there.
Hey, bro, I need you
to take over comms from me,
you got it?
Got you.
Wild eagle base, wild
eagle 2-6, request you relay
to Manchu X-ray,
we're receiving small arms,
fire, grenades, we
have two severely wounded,
we need air support over.
Just stop, just stop, just stop.
Please, please, please.
Stop, please, exactly.
We gotta put a tourniquet on you.
All right.
Alpha 1, this is Alpha
2, what's your Z-rep over there?
We're treating Ellie and Sam right now.
We advise possible
multiple mams on our rooftop.
Roger that, we're taking effective fire
from across the street,
we're 200 meters to your east.
Stand by for a DTA and our side.
Roger that.
Come on.
Hey, I'm gonna do
something that's gonna hurt.
I can't put the tourniquet on,
I need to apply pressure another way.
Okay, okay, okay.
I need morphine, I need morphine.
There's no morphine.
Jake, where are you guys?
We're gonna walk out.
Alpha 1, this is Alpha
2, we're broken out over there.
Guys.
We're now 100 meters
to your location to the east.
Now we're still on
rock hamper, be advised.
I don't know.
We're about two minutes out.
We're looking at a coordinated attack.
Give it to him.
Okay, I don't know where the morphine is.
It's in my bag, it's in
my bag, it's in the medic bag.
What, is it in the medic bag?
It's in the pocket.
Okay, I've gotta get,
I've gotta get, I've gotta get.
Hey, Ray, I need
morphine too, you gotta give me some.
Ray, give it to me.
You got it, I got it,
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Give it to me straight.
Ah, shoot, shoot, shoot.
Sir, hey, you fucked up?
I did it upside down, I
did it in my, in my own thumb.
You all right though, you good?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Bro, bro, bro, bro,
you gotta get another one,
there's more in there.
Right.
Get another one out.
Oh, fuck.
I'm pushing your whole mission up,
I'm going to gain
five-by-the-voltage of the fuck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, it's coming, it's coming.
I'm just trying to.
Elliot, he's in your
arm right now, all right?
This is your arm,
the more feet in your arm,
it's going to kick, you're so good.
I need more and more feet, man.
You can't have more.
Please, not enough, I'm
telling you it's not enough.
I'm telling you, you're good.
You're not even the
one we're worried about, okay?
Wild Eagle Base, Profane 5-6, we,
Flight A-2, we're
overhead, we are contact,
the friendlies, the
frogmen moving from south to north,
and tally the
individuals, they are taking contact
from the north,
taking contact from the north.
Profane 5-6 is
contact several individuals,
they are using
rooftops along Frogmen's position,
they are using the
rooftops going from east to west.
We are contact the friendlies,
they are moving
from east to west as well,
and looks like we are
picking up the second element
of Frogmen to the west side of that same
same street,
Profane 5-7, keep your sensors
to the north in vicinity of OP-1.
We are contact the friendlies linking up
on that street right now.
And Profane 5-6 is
tally several individuals
that are just to the
north of the Frogmen position.
Just to the north
of the Frogmen position,
we have several
individuals setting up in the prone,
they are just
initially setting up an ambush
for the Frogmen position.
And we are also contact
several enemies to their east
using the rooftops in
vicinity of their position.
Just to--
Profane 5-6, this is--
This is the H-X!
Let's move!
Drive way!
Move!
Go, go, go!
One, this is two, we're coming to you,
we have eyes on you.
We're coming to you.
On the gate!
Let's move!
Move along the road!
Keep your gun!
Hold this position!
They're coming to us!
Move!
Change it!
Go, go, go, go!
Move, move, move!
Hey, hey, over there!
Contact, quick, top!
One, this is two, we're
coming, we're fucking coming.
I'm leading!
Run, man, safe, run, man, fight.
Perfect smoke!
Go, go!
I got him!
Go, go, go!
Keep your gun!
Ready, go!
We gotta move, we gotta move!
Right now, let's go, come on!
Stand by.
I'm moving, we're moving!
Move, move, move!
Hey, hey, over there!
ringed enemies
Oh, get it.
All youSSians!
I got no blood on my hand right now.
Shit.
All right, check it out.
We got multiple leg injuries here.
I need morphine.
Gaws.
It's whatever you guys got.
We got windows in every--
Hold your--
Got windows in every inch of this house.
We got dudes on our roof.
We need to get these
guys the fuck out of here now.
Have you called for Casa back?
I can't punch out from here.
Go, get up there.
Zowie, go.
Can you make arms?
Yes, sir.
Sir, has anyone
looked at you, checked you out?
Hey, take a knee.
Take a knee.
Has anyone looked at you?
Let me do a blood sweep.
Manchu X-ray, this is Frog Map 5.
Romeo, be advised.
OP-2 have consolidated on OP-1 position.
How copy?
Over.
Is it Casa back
platform coming back here?
How calls have been made?
Dude, I'm fucked up.
I'm gonna need you to run point.
What's going on up there?
All right, we got
grenades stolen in this room over here.
We probably got--
probably got dudes on our roof still.
Okay.
This is the external
door straight ahead, all right?
Yeah.
Help me.
Hey, Sabam, with you.
All right, I'll get it to you.
Let's go.
Hitting both of his
legs is-- hitting his arm.
He's got abable wounds in
him, and he's lost a lot of blood.
Okay.
And there's
something burning inside of him.
Yeah, that's
phosphorus. It's all over its side.
All right.
Can you breathe?
Hey.
Yeah.
Oh, hey.
You're good.
Did you guys hear me with that morphine?
Yeah, I gave you the morphine.
I gave you the morphine, man.
A few minutes ago,
right before you got here.
You just do it in my arm,
because I got
shaved blood return in my leg.
Yeah, in your arm, man.
I did it right in your arm.
Move, move, move, move!
Let's go, boys!
Let's fucking do this!
Hey!
I know we're moving fast.
We don't step on anyone's fucking legs.
All right, Sammy, let's go.
Relax, man.
My man, let's do this! Come on!
Fuck with him!
All right, guys, listen up.
Everybody shut the fuck up.
Eyes on me.
Start doing a re-org.
Prepare for breakout.
We're gonna get these guys cast back.
Yes, sir!
Damn.
Go, Brock.
Yo, what's up, Frank?
You got ammo for the gunners upstairs?
Yeah, outside pocket.
I want four brothers over here.
Two for a cast back, two for extraction.
I want the cast backs on
either side of the front gate.
Brad one will be right.
Brad two left.
Yes, sir.
Hey, lock down the windows.
Thank you.
This is Frogman 5, Romeo.
We need a cast evac
from OP1 building for Bradley's.
Two for cast evac
of two severely wounded.
Break.
Stay in there, Rode.
You're good.
Relax.
Hey, it's fucking good, man.
It's a fucking paper cut.
You're a fucking frog man, Sam.
You're a fucking frog man.
Let's go.
Fuckin' man.
Frogman, Badger.
You are denied
Bradley cast evac due to IED,
small arm start in the AO.
I'll copy. Over.
Solid copy. Stand by.
Sir?
We're waiting on brigade approval.
What the fuck?
He's the last tanks.
They're fucked up.
So they won't send the cast evac.
Unless the CO gives the thumbs up.
We gotta get him out of here, sir.
You've gotta be the CO.
Sir, stay back.
Radio them right now.
Say you're the CO.
Give them the order
to send the fucking brats.
Roger that.
Hey, Tommy, lock it down.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
What happened?
Oh, no.
It was an IED, what?
Don't fucking know, huh?
Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah.
Manchu X-ray, this is Manchu 6.
I authorize Bushmaster.
I'll copy. Over.
Hey, firm.
Manchu 6, break.
Broad man, five room.
You'll be ready to
receive Bushmaster on 7-5-5.
I'll copy. Over.
Wilco, Bushmaster 7-5-5.
Bushmaster has
approved a maneuver to her position.
Mikey, Brian, give
me an update on the roof.
Take the effect you better be firing.
Multiple backyards at the rooftops.
Bushmaster has approved.
I'll give you a shot. You okay?
Let me know.
You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
You got a rug in there?
Mm-hmm.
Here, kid.
Right here.
Got it.
Are you all up on gear?
Hey, James, get out there.
There's gear in the street.
Join with me.
Get away!
Fuck! Relax! Relax!
Relax! Relax!
Relax!
Fuck!
Get away!
Broadway's are four minutes out.
You got four bikes.
Yeah.
Hey, push me! Get out of there!
We got it off! It's fucking rooftop!
Get away!
Get back! Get back!
Ah, motherfucker!
What's going on?
Catch the big inbound. I need a 5W.
Had to suck back,
unable to hold position.
We got multiple bad guys
trying to get to our position.
Sir?
Sir, I'm calling in to show a force.
Profane 565-7, wide range.
When the Bradley's get here,
Mac, Aaron, Tommy, you grab Elliott.
You guys are going to go out first.
You're going to go
into Brad 1, right hand side.
Right hand side, check.
Brake, grab Sam, Brad 2, left side.
Got it.
Three minutes out!
Three minutes!
Hey, hey, I got his legs, I got his arms.
Yeah, let's get him ready.
All right, let's get the shit straight.
Get that leg.
All right, we're
getting the fuck out of here.
Come on, give me your hand, brother.
All right, watch this.
We're going to get
the fuck out of here, okay?
All right, come on.
Right here, right here.
Right here.
Okay, okay, okay.
Tommy, let's fold him, okay?
Tommy, on you.
We're going to fold him your way.
Oh, my God.
You guys, you're going to need me.
You got to be in there real fast.
Yeah, we will.
All right.
Hold on.
All my count.
All right.
All right, all three.
One, two, three.
Okay, come on, come on.
You good?
You ready?
Set him down.
All right.
You good?
Other side, we got this.
All right.
One, two, three.
Two minutes out!
Two minutes! Two minutes!
Two minutes!
All right.
M-I-3, two, one.
Bro, you're doing great.
You hear that?
Those are in my fucking arm.
Don't worry, bro.
Your arm is still attached.
It's right here.
I got it.
Two minutes out!
Two minutes!
Hey, you got to get ready, man.
This is going to hurt.
No, no, no.
No other way, man.
There's no other way we got to do it.
BTF up, bro!
Which side are we getting Elliot out of?
Elliot?
Inbound!
Elliot, right
side, same on the west side.
Elliot, right.
Roger.
One minute out!
One minute!
All right.
Tommy, Frank, you
two are breaking us out.
Yes, sir.
Gunners, you'll set up
security out on the street.
Frank, you straight?
Good.
I'm going to button hook right.
I'll copy that.
I'm taking the right breath.
Hello, man.
This is Bushmaster.
We are approaching only one at this time.
Frank, Tommy, you good?
Bro! You got me?
Break out of here.
Eyes on me and only me.
All right. We're good.
We're good.
Riley, they're here.
All right.
Let's get them on three.
Three, two, one.
Wrap
down, wrap down, wrap down.
Break down.
Break out, break out.
I'm stuck.
My brother's moved.
One, two, three.
Up, up, up.
Move, bro. Move, go, go, go.
Move!
All right, Riley.
One, two, three.
Come on, brother.
We got you.
Let's go.
Move, move.
Come on.
Take me.
Move.
One more.
Get the fuck out of here.
Fucking crap.
Put your fire.
Man, I'm getting you.
Move, move, move, move.
Wake up, wake up.
Get the hell out of here.
Fuck.
You all right? Yeah.
I thought you were hit.
I was just hit.
Let's go, let's go.
Yes, man, yes, man.
Hey, come on, man. Get it up.
I didn't make it out.
I'm stuck in the Bradley, over.
Profane says the
guys are moving to our booth.
They're telling us to get
the guys off the roof right now.
Do we still have guys up there?
Who asked guys up
there? They're right on us.
Zowie, you hold
security and lock it down.
Check.
Listen up.
I'm gonna have the Brawleys take
off the second floor of this building.
Gunners, you're holding
security out on the street for extract.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Mack, I want to show a
force for when that happens.
Yes, sir. Sergeant. Yeah.
First semester, one-one.
We need you to fire at
the top deck of our building.
We have enemy on our
building and all surrounding buildings.
Say again, fire at the door building.
Got a full head count.
Fire into our building. Top deck.
Zowie, get the fuck down here.
Negative. Fire may not yet do that.
The top deck is
fucking clear. Fire into it.
Here's your... I'll give you...
I'll give you... I'll give you...
Roger that. Stand by.
Go on out. Fuck it, fuck off!
Let's go! Let's go!
Get down, get down, get down!
Come on, boys!
Watch out, dude!
Look at the... Break it out, Isaac!
Let's move! Let her's up!
Front man, bush
master, shifting fire. Go to hot.
Why? It's a vessel left in the fifth.
It's a Hazar. Why?
I'll give it to you. Why?
I'll give it to you. Inbound, inbound!
Stand by!
Break out, break out!
One, two...
Get in there! Three...
Back man! Move in!
Let's go!
Go!
The fucking ramp up!
Let's go see them.
I didn't think you were going to make it.
I lost so much.