Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
♪ Are you ready to fall in love
this Christmas? ♪
♪ Under the mistletoe ♪
♪ There’s a kiss
on the top of your wish list ♪
♪ Well I know a girl
you should know ♪
♪ She is sugar and spice
naughty and nice ♪
♪ Waiting
under that evergreen ♪
♪ If you’re ready to
fall in love this Christmas ♪
♪ Fall in love with me ♪
♪ If you’re ready to
fall in love this Christmas ♪
♪ Don’t wait
for Christmas Eve ♪
♪ Take a chance on romance
’cause this is ♪
♪ The time to trust your heart
and believe ♪
♪ There’s no mystery
it’s chemistry... ♪
I had a feeling you’d be here.
It was an uneventful
Thanksgiving in Santa Barbara,
that’s for sure.
You mean your mom didn’t
beg you to stay
and go shopping with her
at 5 a. m.
for the Black Friday sales?
Oh, she did, I just couldn’t
bear the thought
of listening to her decide
between rose gold
or a shiny champagne
wrapping paper.
But let’s be honest,
there is a distinction
between a shiny rose gold
and a sparkly, shiny champagne.
An hour‐long distinction?
The answer is always rose gold.
Unless the champagne is dusty.
Like mother, like daughter.
No. I am finally committing.
How’s this for a delicately
stacked holiday dessert spread?
Nice. Five sketches in,
you finally figured it out.
‐Good for you, Ame.
‐Don’t tease.
Do you really like it?
Of course. It’s great.
They all were.
Anyway, you had the cat in
the bag with these arrangements.
I know, I just think
a client literally named
after the holiday, we couldn’t
go light on the florals.
Amy, you’re the only event
designer in the entire city
who could love Christmas
as much as Tiffany Christmas
is gonna love
what you’ve created
for her family’s reunion.
Well, we don’t have the job yet.
Come Monday morning, we will.
Well, what if Frankie
pushes for Greta instead?
Her idea seemed to really
pique his interest, too.
Look, yours were clearly
way better.
You can’t just assume Frankie
will have it out for you.
Plus, Tiffany’s gonna
wanna see options,
so really
it’s up to her, anyway.
I don’t know, Kayleigh.
After Frankie’s aunt
promoted him,
I kinda feel like he does.
Well, if that’s the case, it’s
only because you’re amazing
and he is threatened
by all your amazingness.
‐You think he’s threatened?
‐Hello.
He wishes he could design
like you. You’re like Christmas.
Warm apple cider and holiday
cookies, and he’s more like,
I don’t know,
the worst of Halloween,
a tasty piece of candy
with a razor in it.
His aesthetic
is the worst. Seriously.
Well, he’s running
the show now, so...
So you just need to prove to
Tiffany you have what it takes.
This year’s ten‐year Christmas
family reunion, it’s all yours.
You know what? You’re right.
Frankie Diaz liking my stuff
or not, it is my time to shine.
That a girl.
I think you’re done.
Amy, can I see you
in my office, please?
I gotta say,
these are even better
than your initial sketches.
Really did an amazing job here.
Really? Thank you.
Do you think it’s gonna be
enough for Tiffany to hire us?
Well, I only spoke
with her manager once,
but she did say she loved
your original sketches
and said she might be leaning
towards us, so we’ll see.
Really? That’s so exciting!
But look, Ames, I’ve also gotta
be totally transparent with you.
You know you’re
an incredible event designer
and we will use your designs,
but I think I’m gonna be
taking on the majority
of the legwork here myself.
I’m sorry, wait.
Why would you implement
my designs instead of me?
Because this is a massive gig
for us, Ames.
Tiffany Christmas
is an exploding pop star,
and I simply have
more client experience than you.
Or are you just
threatened by me?
What? No, that’s not it at all.
What do you even mean
threatened?
Oh, come on, ever since
your aunt promoted you,
you’ve had it out for me.
She loves my designs.
And you don’t like that, do you?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Amy.
My auntie
totally trusts my judgment
and she loves my designs.
That’s why she promoted me,
clearly.
But I’m on the line now.
I’m only doing what’s best.
Or maybe you got promoted
because you threw a fit
to your mom.
Ames, the only one who seems to
be throwing a fit here is you.
I’m throwing a fit?
Ha‐ha‐ha... No.
This is throwing a fit. I quit.
‐Ames, don’t be brash.
‐And I will have...
All of my stuff out by the end
of the day, and that includes
Kayleigh,
if she’ll come with me.
What are you gonna do?
Start your own business?
‐Maybe I will.
‐Okay.
Well, we still own
your designs, you know?
‐You made them on our clock.
‐Uh‐huh. Wrong.
You don’t pay me overtime,
so, technically,
I made them off the clock.
Merry Christmas, Mr. Diaz,
and a very happy New Year.
‐Ames!
‐And don’t call me Ames!
You know I hate that name.
You’re gonna be
all right?
I think so. I’m gonna miss
this work table, though.
We’ll get an all new work table.
Thanks, and thank you
for joining me
on the fun‐employment
front lines.
You know what we need?
‐A spa day.
‐A spa day?
I don’t think
that’s the wisest investment
considering it’s the holidays
and we have no income.
I think it depends
on where you go.
Well, you were certainly right.
Always go with the rose gold.
Aw, it looks so cute.
I love it.
Let me see yours.
I went with, um,
snowflake sparkle.
Although I don’t feel
very sparkly right now.
Oh, you will, though. Just wait.
What are you talking about?
‐Thank you.
And here’s our reason
to celebrate.
What are you talking about?
Wait, is that...
That’s your shot right there.
Go.
‐Excuse me.
‐Yeah.
‐Hi.
Sorry,
are you Tiffany Christmas?
Yes, I’m Tiffany. And you are?
Amy. Amy Kessler.
I would shake your hand, but‐‐
Oh, my gosh,
that is so cute!
‐What color is that?
‐Snowflake sparkle.
Oh. Aw, I already had my heart
set on Rudolph Red.
But I’m gonna remember that
for next time.
Oh. Well, Rudolph Red
is an excellent color.
And a perfect color for,
I don’t know,
a, um, upcoming family reunion?
Um, you’re not some, like,
crazy stalker fan, are you?
’Cause I really can’t deal
with that right now.
No, actually, I was the one
who created your designs
for Diaz Events Design,
you know, the one
with the snowflake‐falling
photo booth?
Yes! I absolutely loved
all of your designs.
But wait, I thought Frankie
said that you weren’t available.
He, he said that he was just
gonna do it himself, I thought.
‐Well, I actually am.
‐Oh! Okay, well, perfect!
I’ll just let Frankie know
that I prefer you instead.
Okay, well, um‐‐
Yup. We most certainly
are available.
‐I’m Kayleigh, Amy’s assistant.
‐Hi.
We’re such fans
of your new holiday album.
It’s so nice to meet you,
we were listening to it
the whole time we were
designing, and I mean, like,
Amy refused to turn it off.
Aww, that’s so sweet. Thank you.
Well, and actually we were
thinking it would be great
if you sang Love Me Like
Christmas at the reunion.
I was thinking of putting,
like, a little stage
in front of the tree.
What do you think?
Yes! I love that idea!
Okay, I’m excited now.
Um, can we meet tomorrow?
Tomorrow? Uh, yeah.
That sounds good. Yeah.
Okay, so I’ll pick
a time and place.
Here, put your number
in my phone.
‐Okay.
‐Yay.
Don’t worry.
I’ll take care of Frankie.
Just go with it.
Your time to shine, remember?
‐Okay.
‐Mm‐hmm.
‐Here.
‐Okay. Perfect.
Um, well, cheers, ladies.
‐Cheers to...
‐A Christmas family reunion.
‐Yes! Cheers.
‐
Thank you.
Uh! I have got to get the name
of this window display designer.
Okay.
Oh, hi. Sorry, I’ve actually
already taken this table.
Uh, so you can
reserve tables here?
‐I didn’t see any little signs.
‐Uh, n‐no.
It’s just, well,
I‐I saw this table on the way in
and I was gonna put
my purse down, but...
You know, it’s a little
too close to the door.
So you just stacked some, like,
mental claim on this table?
Correct.
I don’t think
that really counts.
We both sat simultaneously.
Well, I think I need this table
for a very important meeting.
for a pretty important
meeting, too.
Well, can you find
another great table
for your less important meeting?
Wait. Why is mine
less important?
Uh, you said pretty important.
I said very important.
Fine. I need this table for
a very important meeting, too.
Well, can you take
your very important meeting
and find a equally great table?
Like, like that one over there.
Um, can’t see the holiday
display or the beautiful view.
Okay, can you just be
a gentleman
since it’s the holidays
and, I don’t know,
let a recently unemployed woman
just have her way?
I really need to make
a big impression here today.
You must be Amy Kessler.
Wait. How did you know my name?
I’m Tiffany’s cousin.
Housemate, bestie. You name it.
Tiffany’s cousin?
Wait, where’s Tiffany?
‐
‐Oh. There she goes.
"Hi, Amy, I’m so sorry
I couldn’t make it.
I got caught
at the recording studio.
My cousin Calvin
will be meeting you.
He’s amazing. You’ll love him."
Okay, well, I guess we got off
on the wrong foot then.
You think?
Uh, Amy Kessler, event designer.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Christmas.
It’s nice to meet you, too.
So are you a photographer or...
That’s right, I take
all of Tiffany’s photos,
social medias and otherwise.
She won’t let anyone shoot,
except for me,
so I thought I’d take photos
for the reunion as well.
Great.
I guess you’re hired then.
I also loved
your photo booth idea, too.
‐I thought it would be fun.
‐Oh, thank you.
I’m glad you liked it.
Tiffany and I also thought
maybe you could use
my assistance, you know,
with a little bit help.
She’s so busy with the album
release these days and, you know
especially since our moms
combined can be a bit of a lot.
I also have an amazing eye
for visuals, so I don’t mind
giving you any direction
there, too, if needed.
‐Direction, hm?
‐Yeah.
Well, we were just checking out
this holiday window display,
so I assume
you must have great taste.
And with that in mind,
I would love to show you
some venue possibilities
I came up with.
‐Uh...
‐What?
Did you guys
already pick a place, too?
Actually, my mother
and my Aunt Mona
both wanna have it
at each of their places.
My mother feels
it needs to be at her place,
but Aunt Mona thinks
it’s not as homey or cozy enough
and wants it at her place.
Between you and me, I don’t
think either can compromise.
Okay, well, have you hosted it
at either of their places
before?
No, we always had it
at Grandma Gladys’ place.
But now since she’s gone,
Aunt Alma lives there,
and it doesn’t seem like
much of an option now.
And also because Aunt Alma’s
not the one to fight for it.
So what is the solution then?
Tiffany and I was thinking
maybe we could host, say,
a pre‐union gathering
at our place this weekend.
You can come and meet everyone
as a pro,
and then if they agreed, and
leave it up to you to decide.
Okay. I suppose
I could do that.
Plus, I wanted to talk to you
more about your ideas.
I loved everything
Tiffany showed me,
but I thought it would be cute,
you know,
you can incorporate
some family traditions into it.
Family traditions. Okay. Got it.
That is, of course, provided
if you’re okay with that
and up for a challenge.
Always.
‐Always?
‐Mm‐hmm.
Well, I really hope
you mean that
because this reunion,
it’s not gonna be no easy task.
Well, I’m not worried because
I am going to make it perfect.
‐Perfect?
‐Mm‐hmm.
This is gonna be
a total disaster.
Oh, come on,
it can’t be that bad.
If I have to deal with him
the whole time, it will be.
And they even live together, so
if I wanna meet up with Tiffany,
he’s probably
gonna be there, too.
We’ve had worse clients,
come on.
Remember Bob the banker
who watched
every penny of our budget?
We had to have
every line item approved,
he even counted
the white tealights
to make sure we didn’t take any.
But this guy was just smug.
Does the hot gene
run in the family?
What does that mean?
I mean, is he as hot
as Tiffany is?
‐
‐Mm‐hmm!
So he is hot. I knew it.
Kayleigh, pass me the dumplings.
Anyway,
we have bigger fish to fry.
Tiffany says her family’s
filled with matriarchs
and each one of them
wanna have it their way.
So we figure out
which one signs the check.
‐That’s who we listen to.
‐Nope.
Because I think Tiffany
is paying for the entire thing,
so we have to figure out
who’s really in charge
now that they’re all competing.
And that’s who we really
have to win over.
Finally taking charge
of her life.
You know what, Amy Kessler,
that last dumpling in there,
it’s all yours.
You are officially my hero.
Don’t mind if I do.
‐Those look so good. Oh!
‐They do.
Mommy, come here,
I wanna introduce you
to our Christmas
family reunion planners.
‐Oh? Cool.
‐
‐This is Amy.
‐Hey.
And her assistant Kayleigh.
‐Ladies, this is my mother Mona.
‐Hello.
Mona, it is so nice to meet you.
Oh. Gosh, I love your dress.
‐Oh, this? Hey!
‐Oh, oh, oh, oh!
No, Tiffany bought it for me,
she spent way too much money
on it. But, uh,
I do look good in it, don’t I?
You certainly do.
Love the style.
Oh, thank you!
Well, look at you two ladies.
You know, initially
I thought you guys were
some of Tiffany’s model friends.
‐Oh.
‐Got it going on.
Thank you, but we are only here
to make sure
that you have
the best holiday reunion ever.
Oh? Well, thank you.
And I accept all of that
because,
guess what, the reunion’s
gonna be at my house. Right?
‐You told them that, right?
‐Mom.
‐What?
‐That hasn’t been decided.
And we still have
a lot to discuss.
Well, we have a lot
to discuss about
how it’s going to be
at our house. Right, baby?
Um, and, ladies,
this is my dad Terrence.
Terrence,
these are our party planners.
‐Hey.
‐Nice to meet you, ladies.
I tell you,
this food is something else.
You know, it’s like
Tiffany gave you a‐a‐a list
of my favorite finger foods.
Actually, Mr. Christmas,
she did.
Did you try the little
fig‐glazed chicken fritters?
Say what?
Uh... Why’d you do that?
Now these need to be
entree sized!
Oh, gosh. Right.
No, they don’t.
We’ll be right back.
Okay, Terrence, take it easy.
Take it... You gotta take it...
‐Right.
‐You know, of course, darling.
Oh, Aunt Eve is here.
Come on, I want you to meet her.
Hey, uh, can you head out
and grab the swag bags?
‐Are you sure you’re good?
‐Yeah. I’ll take it from here.
‐Okay. Thanks.
‐Okay.
‐Tiffany! Hi, baby girl! Mwah!
‐Hi, Aunt Eve! Hey!
Aunt Eve, I want you to meet
Amy, our reunion planner.
‐Amy, this is my Aunt Eve.
‐You must be Calvin’s mom.
I can certainly see
the resemblance.
Well, of course.
Amy, nice to meet you.
And what a lovely idea
this little pre‐reunion dinner
you’ve put together.
Calvin says you’re very good.
Don’t know if I said that
just yet.
But you did good, Amy.
Real good.
Well, it was a ton of fun
and a tiny taste
of what’s to come, I suppose?
‐We shall see.
‐Mm...
We generally tend to go
a bit more traditional
with the holiday decor,
but this is cute.
Thank you, uh, we just
wanted to do something fresher
for Tiffany’s casita look.
You know, the space,
it’s, it’s very modern space.
Yeah. Yes.
As is, as is my home.
And yet I’ve still managed
to instill a homey
and warm feeling, anyway. Well,
you’ll have to come see it.
I mean, after all,
we’re hoping to host the reunion
there this year, right, son?
I’m sorry, that’s
what you are hoping to do,
not what we are hoping to do.
Amy, please forgive
my poor sister‐in‐law.
You know, she really thinks
she’s the boss of this family
ever since Terrence lost
his poor dear mother, okay?
‐The boss, really?
‐Yes, the takeover spirit.
No, more like
the well‐organized one
who keeps
the whole family together.
Mother...
Takeover spirit. I mean‐‐
Please!
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
‐What?
‐You guys, please!
I barely just hired her.
Please don’t scare her away.
We still have three weeks
until the reunion.
Tiffany, I am your mother
and you will never silence me
like that in public.
‐What is wrong‐‐
‐Can I?
‐Baby, please.
‐Wow.
So everyone just wants
to team up on me today.
Oh, uh, mama, mom,
I‐I think Aunt Alma’s here.
Will you please go help her
on the stairs?
‐
‐I love you.
Look forward to seeing
all the things
you’re gonna do, okay?
‐I can’t wait to show you.
‐All right.
Always the extra parts.
My sister‐in‐law just showed up
with my baby nephew. Uh...
‐I‐is everything okay?
‐Hey, hey.
Don’t worry about it.
Everything’s under control.
‐Okay. Thank you.
‐Okay. Go.
Calvin, would you go and get me
a Shirley Temple
with extra cherries?
‐Sure. Uh‐huh.
‐Thank you.
‐So, Amy, is it?
‐Yes, ma’am.
When you have a moment, I would
love to sit and talk with you
about our family reunion.
I think once you see my place,
you will agree that it is
the perfect spot for the event.
Okay. And when would you like
to talk about it?
‐How about right now?
‐Right.
Uh, well, I guess you wanna know
what kind of ideas I cooked up.
Yes, absolutely, I mean,
we could always use
some improvement, right?
Look at you, my little man.
You’ve grown nearly an inch
since I last saw you.
No, that isn’t true.
Letty just hasn’t cut his hair
all year.
‐Now, mom, be sweet.
‐What? I am sweet.
‐Thank you.
‐
I suppose I should go say hello.
‐Hello, my dear!
‐Hi!
Uncle Leon and Aunt Alma.
Sit. Aunt Alma is
Grandma Gladys’ younger sister.
Ah, yes.
And their last name is Turner?
Oh, I see
someone’s been boning up
on the Christmas family
guest list.
Oh, I am very good at names.
Uh, well,
if you’re good with names
as you are standing your ground,
my mother really wants to have
the reunion at her place.
And if you let her boss you,
Amy, she will.
Oh, looks like
the apple didn’t fall far
from the caramel‐candy tree.
What is that supposed to mean?
So your mom is passionate
about a family reunion venue.
It’s a little more relevant
than being, uh, territorial
over a cafe table
I won’t mention.
But, hey, we came
to a common ground, didn’t we?
Yeah, because we were forced to.
Good evening,
good evening, everyone!
I just wanted to thank everyone
for being here tonight
and also thank everyone
who downloaded my album.
‐
Now then, we are so very excited
about our big upcoming family
reunion, and we just wanted
to invite a few of you locals
out here tonight
to look over my most up‐to‐date
email tree and make sure
that we have everyone’s
correct information, okay?
Um, we also are going to discuss
venue options.
So tonight here with us
we have Ms. Amy Kessler,
who we have hired
to help us with the event.
So any questions, concerns,
requests, food allergies,
anything like that, all goes to
her, and she is ready for you.
Yes. Well, thank you so much
for having me.
I cannot wait to meet
your big, beautiful family.
If you guys have any questions,
I’m so happy to help
with flights, accommodations,
anything that you guys need.
Mm. Thank you.
Okay, now...
So we’re gonna bring out
some more hors d’oeuvres.
Everyone go freshen up
on your cocktails
and don’t forget to save
the date for December 23rd
for our ten‐year
Christmas family reunion!
‐Christmas family tradition!
‐Christmas!
Aah! Here we go. Whoo‐hoo!
Uh, there, you know, okay?
You know the doctor said
you can’t have that, baby.
‐And, mom?
‐What?
You know how you get after two.
‐Ah, Tiffany.
‐I’m just sayin’.
‐Tiffany.
‐Yes?
Would you believe,
on our way over here
your Uncle Leon
saw a girl on a billboard
and she looked
exactly like you!
I tell you,
it was a spitting image.
It was really something else,
Tiffy.
Aunt Alma, Uncle Leon,
that was me.
Well, heavens! Are you serious?
What the heck you doin’ up
on that billboard, sweetheart?
Mm, oh, I think I know
what I’m getting you guys
for Christmas now.
‐
‐Can’t believe it.
‐That was me.
Can’t believe it.
So, Letty,
when are you expecting Eli
back from the service?
Hopefully before Christmas.
Uh, we’re cutting it
kinda close, right?
He was already
supposed to be back.
‐Mm.
‐Uh, Jonah.
What did I say earlier?
But, mom,
I only hate half the apple.
No, you ate off all the caramel
and half the apple.
‐Okay.
‐But I’m still hungry.
So eat something else.
Grab a chicken fritter, hm?
Seriously, though, there is
so much caramel on those apples,
you could feed a whole army
of Santa’s elves with ’em.
Grandma Gladys’ apples
were so good.
I miss her so much,
I don’t know why Aunt Alma
won’t just follow that recipe.
Jonah, what did I say?
Oh.
Remember those days.
Okay, so if I put
a snowflake projector
in front of the stage,
with the tree,
will that be a problem
for your lighting?
No. Not at all.
‐Tiff.
‐Hm?
Um, had Calvin met Amy
before this evening?
Oh, yeah, you know,
Calvin’s been really helpful
with all the planning.
‐Is that right?
‐Mm‐hmm.
Mm...
It actually looks great.
It could even be a Rocky
Mountain snowcapped mountain
like where Grandma Gladys
grew up.
That is a fantastic idea.
Look at us, finally agreeing on
something for once, Amy Kessler.
At first I was getting
a little bit more concerned.
Well, the only thing
you should be concerned about
is how to admit what
a fantastic job I do in the end.
Well, if it’s anything like
what you did tonight,
I may stand corrected,
but I still think
you have your work
cut out for you, Amy.
‐...about you and your home.
‐Well, it’s not all about me.
‐Let’s talk to Amy. Amy!
‐Amy!
‐Incoming.
‐Hi, honey.
‐Hi, dear.
‐We’ve come to a bit of a truce.
‐Just a bit of one.
‐Okay, of course.
And, um, how is Monday,
this Monday,
to come by my home,
see where Calvin grew up?
I have a lovely koi pond
and a fantastic garden
you just can’t miss.
I can definitely be there.
‐For sure. Yeah.
‐Great.
Okay, well,
how is Thursday for you
to come by my house
and see where Tiffany grew up?
I mean,
our home is just as good.
We don’t have a koi pond.
Fish smell fishy.
All right, but we do have
a baby grand piano
that is just itching
to be played.
‐I can be there, too.
‐Oh! Fantastic!
Well, those days don’t work
for me because I have
a signing on Monday
and a morning show on Thursday.
Why did you even say Thursday
anyways, mom?
Because I need time
to get the house ready.
Okay, look, you can’t just
reschedule it, honey?
Oh, yes, that’s right,
that’s what she’s gonna do.
She’s gonna reschedule
her whole PR tour for you.
Yes, it’s called
production,
and that’s what they do.
They make adjustments.
Not for the mother
of the artist.
Honey, the stage mother they do.
No, mom,
I, I really can’t do that.
Ladies, it’s okay,
I can bring Amy out. I’m free.
I just have a few, you know,
couple greeting‐card shoots,
but no one’s asking
for any headshots
in this point in the year,
so I can bring Amy.
Perfect. That works out perfect.
‐Very convenient. Thank you.
‐Yup.
‐No problem.
‐Good. Good, Good.
Okay, and then
that way we can all decide
whose home
we will have the reunion at.
Uh, actually, Amy will decide
where we’re having
the reunion, right?
Because that’s what
we all agreed on, right?
Did everyone get a chance
to try my candy apples?
‐Yes.
‐Yes, we did.
I almost went
to a diabetic coma,
but they were delicious,
they were delicious.
They are delicious,
aren’t they?
So now, Amy, is it?
Was that right?
Yes, ma’am.
It is so nice to meet you.
Oh, it’s nice to meet you, dear.
So if we are going to talk
about having the reunion
at my place on the 23rd,
we’ve got a lot
to talk about, right?
Yes, Christmas
is just around the corner,
so we have to make
some big decisions very soon.
When did Aunt Alma’s house get
in the running? Wait a minute.
‐
Is this where you grew up?
A Ventura County kinda Christmas
since I was a little kid.
Are you an only child?
‐My mom said I was a surprise.
‐Oh.
Dad said,
only a surprise to her.
But that even in her heart
she knew I was meant
to come and rescue her.
Rescue her from what?
Well, my dad passed away
ten years ago
right after
I graduated from college,
not too long after our last
Christmas reunion, actually.
‐Hm.
‐Oh, Calvin.
I’m sorry to hear it.
It’s fine.
Stan died a happy, happy man.
And we all got to say goodbye.
It was bittersweet.
But he’s still here, you know?
Still feel him every day.
Well, um, you ready to meet mom?
‐Yeah.
‐All right.
Wow! This arrangement and that
garland are all very impressive.
Yeah, my mom loves to redo
the holiday decor
every couple of years.
She has a strong opinion
about decor.
A person with strong opinions
does a strong leader make.
Amy, hi again.
Hi, Mrs. Christmas.
‐Please call me Eve.
‐Eve Christmas.
Yes, but please don’t
write it down.
It seems to always come out
backwards.
‐
‐Hey, mom.
Hi, darling.
‐Good to see you.
Wow! Eve, I just love
these poinsettia arrangements.
They look like
they just walked off
of some Rodeo Drive
window display.
You have to tell me
who the designer is.
You’re looking at her.
‐You are?
‐I am.
I was just launching
into interior design
when my sweet little Calvin
came along.
I ruined her dreams of becoming
the first black Martha Stewart.
Oh, shush! Don’t say that.
You were my angel,
my miracle baby come true.
And I wouldn’t have it
any other way.
You just had
really bad timing is all.
Now, that man couldn’t get
anywhere on time
even if he tried.
But it just so happens
that you two have come along
at the perfect time.
‐Oh.
‐Uh‐oh. I know what that means.
‐She’s putting us to work.
‐That’s right. Follow me.
Great.
So what is all this?
Told you
she’s putting us to work.
These are Santa’s Stockings
From Stan.
Now say that three times fast
and let’s get to stuffing.
Wait. Did you say
Santa’s Stockings From Stan?
Isn’t that your father’s name?
It’s an old Christmas family
tradition my husband started
when he was a little boy.
When he found out that there
were kids who didn’t get toys
or gifts for Christmas, he asked
his mama Gladys and his papa Joe
to give his toys
to the kids in need.
So after he passed,
Calvin and I decided
to continue that tradition
in his name.
The whole Christmas family
participates.
‐So no family gifts at all?
‐No.
We haven’t exchanged gifts
in the past ten years.
My goodness.
That is so incredible.
I think I know exactly
what I’m gonna ask my parents
for next Christmas.
And where are your parents, Amy?
Oh, they’re here.
Up in Santa Barbara.
Oh. Fancy living, huh?
Yeah, you know,
they, they still do nice things
like donate money to charities.
But this,
this just feels...
warmer, more personal.
I love it.
Hm. And I see
you’re not married.
‐Huh?
‐Mother.
What? It’s just
a friendly conversation.
It’s fine. Um, I was
in a serious relationship.
And I thought
we were gonna get married,
but, no.
I am still single.
Hm...
So what’s next?
‐Get to stuffin’.
‐Okay.
Okay.
We stuffed
three dozen of stockings.
I’d say we cleaned up.
‐Well done!
‐What now?
Now we take these down
to First Presbyterian Church.
They have a distribution list
of all the families in need.
Then we surprise the families by
leaving them on their doorstep
on Christmas Eve.
‐Aww! I love it.
‐
Oh, can we go see the koi pond?
‐Wow. They’re so beautiful!
‐That they are.
You know,
you look a lot like your dad.
‐Thank you.
‐You guys have the same smile.
He was a good‐looking dude.
Come on,
let me show you the rest.
Okay.
Oh! These lampposts
are incredible.
Yeah. My dad put these put up
when I was small.
He and my mom knew
I was notorious for sneaking
out the house,
especially around the holidays.
Why especially
the holidays?
Well, I thought Santa and I
had a special deal
where I used to bring cookies
out to my favorite play spot.
And I was sure if I came out at
night, I’d eventually see him.
Hm.
Of course, I thought
Santa was eating the cookies.
Now I’m pretty sure it was just
a squirrel or the birds.
Aww...
A pinecone tree! How adorable!
Yeah, my mom
always loved pinecones,
so we all built this together
one year for Santa.
We used to put the cookies
right on this small stump
sitting next to the tree.
Memories.
‐Think I could get a photo?
‐Sure.
You know,
I think I have some already
in my phone where I can send.
‐Great. Thanks.
‐Yeah.
‐You wanna know what I think?
‐What’s that?
How do you know it wasn’t really
Santa who was eating the cookies
you left out?
With these lampposts to guide
him, would’ve been pretty easy
for him to find it
on his sleigh, don’t you think?
‐Yeah.
‐
So what do you think
of our place?
Perfect spot
for the reunion, yes?
I think it’s definitely
a strong contender.
‐You sold it very well.
‐Well...
Obviously, not well enough
if you haven’t
made a decision yet.
Well, it’s just that
I promised everyone
that I would check out
all the places first, so...
My mom is just teasing you.
She knows we have to be fair
about this, right?
Yes. Of course I do.
But because
Amy clearly has good taste,
I’m convinced
that you’ll decide what’s fair
is having it right here.
Is she gonna hate me
if we decide
to have it somewhere else?
Nah, she might pretend
you don’t exist
when she sees you next, but
definitely wouldn’t hate you.
‐Uh...
‐I’m teasing you.
‐Totally teasing.
‐Thanks.
Aah! There he is!
There’s my favorite nephew!
I thought
Bryson was your favorite.
Oh, Bryson is my favorite
during soccer season
and when he’s playing.
‐Hey! Hi, baby.
‐Hi.
Mona, it’s so good
to see you again.
It’s so good to see you.
And you know what?
I’m excited you’re here
because you’re just in time
to help me put up the
Christmas lights on the porch.
‐Hey, you ready to get to work?
‐Uh‐huh.
Ah, it’s a Christmas
family tradition, I guess.
You visit family,
they put you to work.
‐
‐No complaints from me.
Oh, exactly,
because who doesn’t like
putting up Christmas lights?
Especially on a porch like this.
Mona, this house is spectacular.
Oh! Well, I am so glad
you approve, darling.
Come on in, I’m gonna
give you the full tour.
‐Okay.
‐Oh.
‐
Ah.
This is so precious.
Oh, Tiff and I,
we started that collection
when she was just a kid.
No wonder
Tiffany loves Christmas so much.
It really shows
in her new holiday album.
‐I know, right?
‐Mm‐hmm.
‐My baby is so talented!
‐
‐Come on! This way.
‐Okay.
This stuff is vintage,
isn’t it?
Yes! I am
a vintage Christmas connoisseur.
Well, it definitely shows.
Hey, can we get some photos
of all of us?
‐Oh. No problem, I got you.
‐Great.
Oh, Calvin,
make sure you get your auntie.
‐Yes, auntie.
‐Okay.
And look at baby Jesus.
Isn’t he cute?
‐He’s so cute.
‐Uh‐uh. Don’t touch it.
‐Oh, sorry. Okay.
‐Don’t touch it. All right.
A little higher
to the right here, baby.
Oh. Amy.
So, I take it you went out
to see Eve’s place on Monday?
Yes. And her place
is beautiful, too.
Oh, for sure, but, you know,
we both have very different
decorating styles,
even though I do appreciate
her decorating expertise.
Absolutely, but you both have
excellent decorating skills.
Ooh, so I guess it’s safe to say
that I am still in the running?
‐Oh, Mona.
‐What?
Doesn’t matter
where we have this reunion.
You’ll still have all eyes
on you. You always do.
Aww. You hear that, Calvin?
See, that is how you get
the girl of your dreams.
He still knows how to woo me
after 32 years.
‐What’s next?
‐You’ll see.
Hm.
Wow.
This must be Tiffany’s old room.
Yeah, I used to get stuck
sleeping there
right on the floor as a kid
when mom and dad brought us
for a visit.
Aww, little Calvin
on a sleeping bag
in a sea of pink.
I could see it now.
Oh. You got jokes now?
‐Mm‐hmm. Mm.
‐Mm.
Come on, let’s go.
‐We finally arrived.
‐Uh‐huh.
Wow, do you think your
Aunt Mona would let us borrow
some of this stuff
for the reunion?
Oh, yeah,
it’s not a problem at all.
‐Except cool Santa here.
‐Oh.
He stays and protects all her
stuff. Get a photo with him.
It’s the least
we can ask of him, anyway.
‐Chic.
‐Chic. Okay.
Well, these are chic. Come here.
‐Let me put them on you.
‐All right.
‐It’s somethin’ else.
‐It looks adorable.
‐Hm, let’s go.
‐Okay.
‐One, two, three. Say "Money!"
‐All right, Santa.
Money!
All right. Light it up.
Light it up, baby!
Ah, ah!
Never ceases to amaze me.
No, you never cease to amaze me,
Mr. Christmas.
‐
‐Ooh.
Tiffany Anne,
what are you doing here?
I thought
you had the morning show!
‐What are you doing?
‐Hey, baby.
Mom, it was a morning show!
‐It’s night. I’m done.
‐Oh, I’m sorry.
Plus, I couldn’t miss
the beautiful
house‐lighting ceremony.
Aww!
Tiffany,
I’m so glad you made it!
‐I’m so happy to see you.
‐
And, girl, I may have plugged
you on the morning show.
‐What?
‐Yes.
I mean, just how amazing you are
in getting
our family reunion set up.
‐Thank you. That is so sweet.
‐Of course.
My little girl
moving back home yet?
‐Mm‐hmm. You wish, daddy.
‐
‐Oh, this is so beautiful!
‐Isn’t it gorgeous?
It looks so good, as always.
I say we just have the reunion
here and call it a night.
‐Yeah, uh, okay!
‐Okay!
‐
‐Uh, you think about it.
‐I’ll think about it.
‐
So, have you heard
anything more as to when,
you know, Eli will be home?
Letty said maybe Christmas,
but we just don’t know.
I mean, he’s still active duty
on the Air Force,
so I have no clue.
Hm, well, I sure hope
he makes it in time
for, you know,
little Jonah’s sake.
Tsk. Don’t we all?
This old piano is incredible.
Guess now I know where
your musical talents came from.
‐
‐All right.
All right! Get over here. Okay.
I think it’s time for a little
Christmas family tradition
because I don’t think
Ms. Amy is quite sold
on having the family reunion
here yet.
So you’re gonna get a treat
that you can only get
at Ms. Mona’s house.
Christmas carols and cocoa.
‐
‐Oh...
Go, Tiffany.
Show ’em what you got, babe.
‐Okay. All right.
‐Shall we?
‐Calvin.
‐We shall.
‐All right.
‐All right!
‐You’re gonna love this.
‐Okay.
Okay. I hear you, oh, baby.
I know, baby.
♪ Hark
the herald angels sing ♪
♪ Glory to the newborn King ♪
♪ Peace on Earth
and mercy mild ♪
♪ God and sinners reconciled ♪
♪ Joyful all ye nations rise ♪
♪ Join the triumph
of the skies ♪
♪ With angelic host proclaim ♪
♪ Christ is born in Bethlehem ♪
♪ Hark
the herald angels sing ♪
♪ Glory to ♪
♪ The newborn King ♪
Every year you just get
better and better.
‐Better, baby!
‐Thank you.
‐Ooh, that’s my baby!
‐That’s a good man, over there.
Just like my brother Stan was.
Hey, this doesn’t
all look like the stuff
from your original sketches.
Well, I kinda decided to go
in a new direction, I think.
You? Go in a new direction?
Since when?
This isn’t rose gold
and champagne
we’re talking about here.
Exactly, it’s a family reunion,
so we should treat it like one.
‐Oh. Thank you.
‐You’re welcome.
Right this way.
Oh, this is...
Like something
out of a fairytale.
An old romantic
Christmas fairytale.
Welcome to Casa de Christmas.
Ah.
Is this...
‐Is this handmade?
‐Yup.
‐By my great‐grandmother Ethel.
‐Ah!
This wreath
has magical Christmas powers.
‐I can just feel it.
‐Well, I sure hope so.
It’s a Christmas family
original.
Welcome.
Wow.
Indeed.
Lots of this stuff
has been passed down.
My guess is
my mom and Aunt Mona
are gonna have to fight
to see who gets it some day.
‐Hey, family.
‐Uncle Cal!
Hi.
‐Hi.
‐Hey, buddy.
He likes to call me his uncle
even though
he’s technically my cousin.
You know me better than that.
I don’t live on technicalities.
‐Whatever that is.
‐
So you’re Calvin’s girlfriend,
yes?
Aunt Alma, no, she’s his friend
and our reunion planner,
remember?
Yeah, you met her
at me and Tiffany’s place
just a week or so ago.
‐Oh, right!
‐Mm.
‐Oh, I’m so sorry, hon.
‐It’s fine.
Well, maybe she should be your
girlfriend. She sure is pretty.
Ah, Jonah.
Excuse me, little man.
Can I get you guys
some pumpkin nog?
I made some fresh from
the pumpkin just this morning.
‐It’s really good.
‐Pumpkin! Yes, please.
Yeah.
Okay.
Look, Uncle Cal,
we’re making our yearly
annual gingerbread houses
for the dining‐room table.
You mean yearly or annual?
You know it means
the same thing, little bud.
‐I knew that. I was testing you.
‐Mm‐hmm.
What are you doing?
Well, I assume
we’re getting put to work, no?
Looks like another Christmas
family tradition to me.
Now, I like this one.
She’s got the right idea.
Now you go over there
and wash your hands.
But, you know,
I’m really bad at making
gingerbread houses,
though, all right?
He’s not lying, last year
his gingerbread house caved in
and my dad had to come in
last second
for major
construction reinforcements.
That’s right, he had to make
little candy‐cane beams
to hold ’em together.
And those were Gladys’
famous homemade candy canes.
It was a waste of tasty
holiday treats, if you ask me.
Hm.
Yeah, I agree.
Which is why
I should just take photos
and be a nice spectator today.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
If I’m building a house,
you’re building a house, too.
‐Oh, really?
‐Mm‐hmm.
Oops.
That looks so good. Hm.
‐What do you think?
‐What?
Hm, this is really good.
You think so?
Oh, I was, uh, talking about
the eggnog.
But your house,
it’s, it’s not bad. Really.
I don’t know
if I’d call it good.
Okay, okay,
let’s call in Uncle Leon.
‐Yeah, maybe he can‐‐
‐Uncle Leon.
What’s all this yelling about?
We need you to judge our houses.
You’re the only one with a bias.
Without a bias.
Another test.
Good thing you passed.
Hm, all right, let me see, uh...
Mm‐hmm.
Mm‐hmm. Mm‐hmm.
Mm?
Mm! Mm...
‐Uh, you built this house?
‐Mm‐hmm, yup.
Well, did a hurricane
come through there?
Uh, the roof
looks all
‐You know what? It’s fine.
‐What?
‐Yeah, there you go.
‐Oops.
Jonah’s house
is clearly the winner.
‐Yay!
Now, uh, can I go back out
and get my work done?
I still gotta feed the chickens.
‐The chickens?
‐Saving the best for last.
Ah!
This is where the reunion was
ten years ago.
Last time dad was here.
‐It’s perfect.
‐Great.
Tiffany and I also agree.
Why didn’t you guys
say something?
We needed
a professional opinion.
‐
‐Really good.
That was fun.
All of our trips
have been a lot of fun.
You know, I wish
my parents had a fraction
of the Christmas spirit
that yours does.
Why? Your family doesn’t like
the holidays?
No, they do, it’s just...
My dad,
he loves food and sports.
And my mom loves shopping
and buying gifts
for extended family.
And don’t get me wrong,
I love my family.
It’s just,
I do spend my Christmases
cooking with the maid
and watching Christmas movies.
Mm! Christmas movies, huh?
What? I get a ton of inspiration
from them.
No judgment here. I could dig
some Christmas movies.
But the viewings
are meant to be shared.
Well, then maybe I’ll ask Santa
and see if he can extend
his visit next time.
Or if Santa is too busy,
which I know he will be,
I could join you.
Uh, I’ll ask Santa
and see what he says.
I don’t loathe the idea.
I just need a view
with the best seat, that’s all.
Oh!
‐To be discussed, seat‐stealer.
‐Mm.
Um...
Okay. Um...
I guess we should get going.
Can you swing by Sunday at noon?
Yeah, Sunday at noon, mm‐hmm.
Yeah, um, I just have to
reconfigure a couple of things.
Oh, no, no, no, this won’t be
about event stuff.
This is so we can tell our moms
where we’re having the event.
‐We?
‐Oh! We.
Christmas, no pun intended,
just calm down.
Everyone! All right. Everyone.
After much deliberation we have
finally come to a decision
on the reunion and where
we’ll have it this year.
It was a hard decision for us
to make as a fellow family,
and that is why we objectively
left it to Amy.
Though we support
that decision.
Now, then, uh, Amy,
you can tell them.
Well, after much thought,
I decided the theme
for this year’s family reunion
is Christmas tradition.
And not the holiday Christmas.
What I mean
is the Christmas family
and your traditions.
‐That’s cute.
‐Okay.
But all of our houses have
Christmas family traditions.
Right. And so many
wonderful ones, too.
But with that in mind,
I think the best place
for a reunion
filled with lots of traditions
is where it all started.
‐Alma and Leon’s place.
‐Yay!
Ah. Whatever!
Listen, I‐I can’t believe we
have left our family tradition
up to this little party‐planner.
She doesn’t even have any skin
in the game.
Exactly why we left it to her
at the end, mom.
‐Amy knows what she’s doing.
‐Really?
‐I think we can trust her.
‐Yeah.
‐Does she?
‐Mm!
Or maybe Amy should take
another trip
down to the ranch house.
Amy, do you like
deep‐fried turkey?
’Cause, you know, Terrence,
he makes the best,
and I’m sure that he would love
to make some for you.
‐Mom.
‐I mean, what?
You cannot bribe her!
You cannot bribe her,
you guys, we don’t have time
to keep going back and forth
about this.
We have two weeks left
for the reunion now.
The flights have already
been booked and the invitations
have to go out by Monday,
all right?
Listen,
I knew that it was a mistake
to leave this reunion
up to you kids.
We are the parents,
and we still know what is best.
‐For this family.
‐Speak for yourself, dear.
If you know what’s best,
mom, maybe
you and Aunt Mona might agree
on something for once.
How dare you speak to me
in that tone, Calvin!
Everyone, please,
may I just say...
If you all trust me
and give me a chance
to bring this reunion to life
the way I know I can,
I promise,
I will not let you down.
You sure you don’t want
to come back to the ranch house?
‐Mom!
‐What?
I make a mean margarita, girl.
You do. Aunt Alma.
Aunt Alma, is there anything
else that you would like to add?
‐A‐about what?
‐About us...
Having the family reunion
at your place now.
Well, wasn’t it always
gonna be here?
‐Oh, my God!
‐Okay, you know what, see?
‐We made the right decision.
‐Absolutely.
Amy, this is incredible. Really.
‐Really? You like it?
‐It’s perfect.
And the pinecone tree,
nice touch, Ms. Kessler.
Oh, well, I just figured,
since you took my table,
you wouldn’t mind me
stealing your tree.
All right, uh...
What’s next on the agenda?
I think it’s time to decorate.
‐Let’s go.
‐Let’s do it.
♪ It’s freezin’ outside
but warm in my heart ♪
♪ The holiday cheers
they wake up the dark ♪
♪ A walk in the crowd
a song in my step ♪
♪ Gonna buy you something ♪
♪ That you’ll never forget ♪
♪ The best loved time of year
fillin’ up with... ♪
Hey, let me grab a photo
of you guys all together.
♪ Of oohs and ahs ♪
♪ Then the hugs
that follow along ♪
♪ My eyes light up
at Christmas ♪
♪ I wanna make your eyes
light up too ♪
♪ There’s a magical scene
what I wanna see ♪
♪ Is your eyes light up ♪
♪ Your eyes light up
at Christmas ♪
♪ Oh‐oh oh‐oh ♪
♪ Spring summer and fall ♪
♪ I listen so close ♪
♪ Hear every word
what you’re wantin’ the most ♪
♪ I’ve waited a day
till the one in December ♪
♪ You’ll be surprised ♪
♪ And always remember ♪
♪ The best loved time of year
fillin’ up with... ♪
Okay, who’s ready to try
my special take
on Gladys’ recipe?
Oh, yes.
‐Thank you.
‐Thank you so much.
Can’t wait to try
this new recipe.
Yum.
‐
I think they’re a little strong.
Only a, only a little.
‐Like, just a little bit.
‐You know what?
Some people love strong mint.
O‐or, you know,
maybe just for the reunion,
it would be nice if we stuck
to Grandma Gladys’ recipe.
‐To honor her.
‐Mm.
‐Grandma’s recipe. I like that.
‐Yeah.
Okay, you might be right,
I think I’ll stick
to the original recipe.
Good idea.
Ah. Ah.
Go on, get out of here,
go on your bug swipe holidate.
‐You know, I think he’s the one.
‐Hm.
You sure you don’t need
any more help?
I think we’re okay.
Mm! Mm‐hm.
Hm. Shall we?
‐We shall.
‐Yeah.
Ah...
So beautiful.
What’s on your jacket?
Oh! Must’ve gotten some dirt
from the photo booth.
Yeah. You mind
if you let me see?
‐Sure?
‐Yeah.
Okay.
‐Thank you.
‐There.
She’s all better.
Grandma Gladys,
she seems to be the glue
that held the family together,
huh?
Oh, yeah, she’s the woman
that could work and play
and check on everyone
all in the same day.
And your mom and Aunt Mona, they
seem to really look up to her.
Yeah, I feel like both of them
marrying her two sons,
they competed for her attention.
And that’s where all this
venue drama stems from.
Well, I can only imagine
how difficult it must be
being someone’s daughter‐in‐law,
I mean,
trying to do the same job
with your kids
as they did with theirs.
Right. My dad, he made my mother
much sweeter.
Better.
He’s a lot like Grandma Gladys,
actually.
I think you’re a lot like them,
too.
Oh, yeah? Table‐taker,
you’re calling me sweet?
Well, I didn’t wanna admit that.
But it’s kinda hard not to.
I mean, here you are,
helping me with my jacket.
You’re not that bad yourself,
actually.
A lot like my mom,
talk a big talk,
but you’re sweet down beneath
all of this polishedness.
‐Oh.
‐Uh‐huh.
You really poured your heart out
into this
Christmas family reunion.
Seems to me that the holiday
spirit is kinda your thing.
Your boss must be grateful
to have you.
My boss...
Yeah, it’s,
it’s a little complicated.
Look, I’ve been, I’ve been
meaning to tell you something.
‐There you are.
‐Hi.
What are you two doing
out here in the cold?
Uh... Mom!
‐What are you doin’ here?
‐I came to check on things.
And see how the decorations
were going.
And actually Uncle Leon
is bringing in some groceries
that I brought over and I’m sure
he could use your help, Calvin.
Yeah, for sure. You good, Amy?
Oh, yeah, I’m‐I’m great.
Uh, thank you for helping me
with my jacket.
No problem. I’ll see you
tomorrow to do the gift bags.
Yup. Bright and early.
‐Right. Goodnight.
‐Goodnight.
‐I’ll see you inside, mom.
‐Sounds good.
All right.
‐So...
‐It is a work in progress.
‐Clearly.
It seems like there’s a lot
still left to do in just a week.
Right, and I do have
a couple of assistants
coming in next week
to help with the stuff
that we don’t want weathered
right before the reunion.
Mm.
And, uh, the Santa set‐up?
I think you’re gonna love it.
Well, I hope so.
‐So much good stuff.
‐Merry Christmas!
‐Look at these swag bags!
‐Hey. Hey.
Good morning, look at all
these brands I got to sponsor
our swag bags for free.
‐Oh, Tiffany, that is amazing!
‐Yes.
Well, you guys, let’s get going.
They’re not gonna
stuff themselves.
‐Right.
‐Let’s get to stuffing them.
Oh, you guys, it’s my manager,
I gotta take this.
‐One second. Hey, Ricky.
‐Oh. Okay.
‐She’s not coming back, is she?
‐Definitely not.
I guess it’s just us, huh?
I guess so.
Can you go first?
I’m scared to.
‐Okay.
‐
"You will find
the true path to love."
‐Mm‐hmm.
‐I could get with that.
‐I think you have mine. Give me!
‐Absolutely not!
‐
‐Here.
‐This is yours.
‐All right, let’s see.
"You will catch
a shooting star."
Oh, maybe you did get mine.
Give, give.
‐Nope.
‐Nope?
‐Okay.
‐I did get you something though.
‐You did?
‐Follow me.
Okay.
‐What is this?
‐Just a little gift.
Just to say thank you for making
our family reunion a great one.
Yeah, a film fanatic gift bag
for all your
Christmas binge‐watching.
Calvin, this is so sweet.
I mean, you’re gonna share it
with me, right,
when I come over
to binge‐watch with you?
But you’re welcome.
Oh, my God, you guys,
I’m so sorry, I just had to take
like, a hundred calls,
and I really hope
you saved me some food.
Okay, w‐w‐what’s goin’ on here?
Did... What did I miss?
‐Uh, nothing. Mn‐mn.
‐Nothing at all. Mn‐mn.
Okay, um, anyways,
how would you two
like to come with me
to Ms. Pia Perna’s
rockin’ holiday party
tomorrow night?
Wait! You mean the Pia Perna?
‐Like, the music producer?
‐Yeah.
Like, the one who produced
my entire album. Hello!
Amy, you actually met her
the same day you met me
at the salon, remember?
‐Oh, wait. She was so young.
‐She is.
Which means that this party
is gonna be fun, right?
‐Definitely.
Okay, so t‐this is gonna be
a thing now.
You guys are just gonna
start talking together?
‐No.
‐Uh, no. Mn‐mn.
None of these look great.
I’m going to a gorgeously famous
producer’s party
with an equally
gorgeously famous singer.
You are equally as gorgeous,
okay?
And you looked great
in all of those.
‐Really?
‐Um, yeah.
I think the real question is
who are you trying
to look amazing for.
And if we’re talking
about Calvin,
that one.
This one? Okay.
Tiffany, when are Mona
and your dad getting here?
They’re not coming, they said
Jonah’s Secret Santa exchange
at school ran late, so...
Ugh, so Mona’s leaving me here
with all these young people?
‐I’m gonna need a drink.
‐But you don’t drink.
I’ll make it a virgin.
So, what did you think
of the album?
Well, I‐I told Tiffany
I thought it was amazing.
I mean, the album covers
and the singles are perfect.
December Dreams deserves
all the attention it’s getting.
Aww. Thank you. And that one
was totally my baby, too.
‐Oh, yeah? You did a great job.
‐Oh, stop. Seriously.
But not really.
Now, if we can just get
Frostbitten to become a hit,
right, we’ll definitely get
a new record deal.
One hundred percent. Done.
♪ Fa‐la la‐la‐la la‐la‐la‐la ♪
♪ Strike the harp
and join the chorus ♪
♪ Fa‐la la‐la‐la la‐la‐la‐la ♪
♪ Follow me in merry measures ♪
♪ Fa‐la‐la la‐la‐la la‐la‐la ♪
♪ While I tell
of Yuletide treasure ♪
♪ Fa‐la la‐la‐la la‐la‐la‐la ♪
Hm.
Wow! She actually came.
You look...
I mean...
I have nothin’.
I will take that
as a compliment.
Yeah. I’m speechless.
Well, I will say this, I didn’t
go shopping for this dress.
I just happened to have it
and I threw it on.
This was definitely
the right choice.
Amy!
You made it! Yay!
I’m so happy you came.
And that dress
looks great on you.
It sure does.
I think I’m gonna get a drink.
You want one?
‐Please, a double.
‐Okay.
Hi, can I get a Cosmo, please?
Oh, did you want another?
Yeah, uh, Shirley Temple,
please.
‐Thank you.
‐Of course.
So did you see
that Amy outside?
The family reunion
event‐planner.
Oh, right, yeah, uh,
she’s out back
with your son swooning over her.
‐Oh.
‐Pia!
‐Frankie. Hi. Merry Christmas.
‐Hello. Merry Christmas.
‐Thanks so much for having me.
‐Thank you for coming.
Oh, Frankie, this is Eve.
Eve is Tiff’s aunt.
‐Eve, Frankie Diaz.
‐Hello.
Hey there, very nice
to meet you. Happy holidays.
Well, Merry Christmas
to you, too.
‐Thank you.
‐So how do you know our Tiffany?
Oh, right.
Well, Pia and I go way back.
I heard Tiffany was looking
for an event designer,
and I tried to get the gig,
but didn’t work out.
But aren’t you
with Diaz Designs?
Well, I am Diaz Designs.
‐My family owns it.
‐Oh!
But we did hire you.
Your event planner, Amy.
So I was gonna ask you.
I know you have the reunion
on the eve of Christmas Eve
and then Christmas
with your parents.
Me and, me and my mom.
But I don’t have
any Christmas Eve plans.
So if you don’t either,
I was thinking,
you and I could watch
Christmas movies if you want.
‐I would actually love that.
‐Yeah?
‐Uh, but...
‐Let me guess.
You already have a New Year’s
event plan for work, huh?
No, no, it’s not that,
it’s just...
‐What is it?
‐The‐the truth is...
‐Yeah?
‐My job‐‐
What job, dear?
’Cause as far as I can tell,
you don’t have a job now.
Frankie?
What are you doing here?
‐Frankie, hi.
‐Tiffany, hi. How are you?
I’m good. How are you?
‐Merry Christmas.
Let me tell you,
your girl here is killing it.
Oh, no, not really killing it,
because she quit,
and took his gig.
Well, that’s not entirely true.
Oh, really, Amy?
Well, then what is true?
Because Frankie said
you took his job
that our family was considering
his company for.
Or did you just
not realize that?
Tiffany, look,
I was meaning to tell you.
‐I did work for Frankie‐‐
‐Before you took my client.
I mean, what else is there
to explain, Amy?
That maybe
you stole my ideas, too?
You worked for me.
Your ideas were mine.
Or did you not read
your contract
you signed upon your hire?
Tiffany,
I was meaning to tell you this,
but‐‐
She was hoping to wait
until she got final payment.
‐I’m fairly sure.
‐Okay.
Could you guys take this
out front?
This is really not a good look
for Tiffany.
Well, don’t you worry
about that.
‐Calvin, I’m ready to go.
‐No problem, mom.
Uh...
I’ll see you later.
We should talk about this
another day.
I will just see myself out.
And you’ll surely be hearing
from my lawyer.
Merry Christmas, Ames.
‐Just have a misunderstanding.
‐Right.
And we spoke most of the time
and she told me‐‐
Calvin!
I’ll meet you at the car.
I’m sorry.
I‐I meant to tell you.
‐I tried to tell you.
‐Yeah, but you didn’t.
I gotta go, Amy.
‐Oh, thanks, sweetheart.
‐Here.
Oh, that’ll be Amy
with the last of the drop‐offs.
‐Would you grab that, hon?
‐Certainly.
Kayleigh, hi! Where’s Amy?
Uh, Amy’s actually
not feeling great,
so I’ll be taking over for
the remainder of the project.
Um, she’ll be issuing
a full refund
for the inconvenience, but...
‐May I come in?
‐Well, sure, come on.
Look at that, candy‐cane lane.
‐Told you.
‐What’d you tell me?
What exactly did you tell me?
Aunt Alma.
Auntie?
Kayleigh.
I didn’t know you were
stopping by, I was just,
uh, heading out.
Amy is not here today?
Yeah, um, she asked me
to cover the rest of the event,
given the circumstances.
But I’m actually glad
you’re here
because I wanted to tell you
it’s my fault, the way
that everything went down.
What’s your fault?
Amy did wanna tell Tiffany
that we left Frankie’s company.
But I said that I would take
care of it and then I just
didn’t take care of it.
I was just so mad at Frankie
for trying to take this gig
away from Amy
and use the designs himself.
He was a terrible boss to her.
She was up for a big promotion,
and he used his
family connections to take it.
Then he was going to literally
take the ideas
that Tiffany loved, use them,
and not let Amy
design her own work.
Wow. That’s pretty insane.
‐I didn’t know.
‐You know...
After hearing all this
and actually meeting that man,
I’m not surprised.
Yeah, well, we really are sorry
for the way
that everything went down.
And if you wanna bring someone
else in to work the event...
‐We understand.
‐Hm.
Either way, Amy said
it’s probably not a good idea
for her to come, so...
Unless you feel otherwise,
I’ll be here Saturday
for the event alone.
‐Yeah.
‐Hm.
Hey, where’d these come from?
Amy didn’t mention these.
Yeah, uh...
They are a special gift
from Amy for the whole family
since you guys
never exchange gifts.
Don’t worry,
it’s outside the budget.
Just something she wanted to do.
I guess you kinda
liked that girl, didn’t you?
Yeah, I kinda did, actually.
How did you know?
I know what you look like
when you’re smitten.
Hm.
Your father used to look at me
that way.
And I guess
I was kind of
a complicated woman as well.
You still are, mother.
‐And you like that.
‐
‐This is sweet.
‐It is.
‐Tiffany? Hey.
‐Hi.
Eve. Hi.
‐May we come in?
‐Of course. Yeah.
This is quite tasteful.
Thank you. That means a lot
coming from you.
I got all of your voicemails.
All five of them.
As well as three emails.
Right, a‐and I wanted
to apologize
to you in person, but I‐‐
But you’ve already done that
eight times.
Which is more than enough.
Look, the reason why we’re here
is because we wanted to say
thank you.
I stopped by Aunt Alma’s
this morning,
and the reunion you put together
is simply amazing.
Well, I‐I’m really glad
you guys are happy.
And Aunt Eve here told me
about everything else
as well, so...
‐Everything else?
‐Yeah.
About Frankie
being a total jerk,
him trying
to take this gig from you
and just being a crappy human,
period.
Right.
So we’re sorry
that that happened.
But it still doesn’t take back
the fact that
what you did was inexcusable.
That’s right,
and so we feel the only way
that you could truly
make it up to us
is for you to attend
our family reunion,
to ensure
that nothing else goes wrong.
Wait. Seriously?
Plus, I mean, it already feels
like you’re part of the family,
so it would be a real shame
if you missed it.
I know
my son would feel that way.
You did break his heart.
And the least you could do
is come back,
so you could give him
his only Christmas wish.
Which is?
You, my dear.
I’ll admit
I was a little bit resistant
at first.
But I could see
the minute you walked
into the room with Calvin
that the two of you
were feelin’ each other.
I’m just a protective
mama‐bear type is all.
I thought you didn’t like me
because,
I don’t know, I said something
off‐putting or‐‐
Amy, if you ever said anything
off‐putting,
I wouldn’t be afraid
to talk to you about it, okay?
‐Trust me. Right.
‐Nor would I. Okay?
Well, thank you. A‐and your
family means so much to me.
Especially Calvin.
I just wanna make sure
that I’m listening.
You are.
Just took me a minute
to get used to the idea
and really see who you are.
So, do you wanna come
to our family reunion?
We’d still love to have you.
‐I would love to.
‐Yay!
Okay, good. Phew! Ah...
‐Cheers.
Santa, Uncle Leon.
♪ See the old man
on the sleigh ♪
♪ Place some presents
by the tree ♪
♪ Hope there’s one for me ♪
♪ All the little
girls and boys ♪
♪ See their faces
lit with joy ♪
♪ Christmas lights
they’re all aglow ♪
♪ Glistening in the snow ♪
♪ Bells ringing
choirs singing ♪
♪ Spreading laughter
and cheer ♪
‐Hey. How we doin’?
‐Hey.
How you doin’, Aunt Alma?
You’re not overwhelmed, are you?
Are you kidding me?
I live for this!
‐
‐I know you do.
I only wish
that Gladys was here to see it.
‐Aw...
‐Ah, don’t we all, Auntie Alma?
Yeah.
She sure could throw a party.
But, Tiffany,
what you did here, thank you.
It’s amazing
what you did for the family.
Thank you.
Anything for the family, right?
I mean, that’s what
Christmas is all about
and what the Christmas family
is all about.
‐That’s right.
‐Oh, wow!
Look at you,
little handsome man.
Aunt Tiffany,
you sure look pretty, too.
‐Almost as pretty as my mom.
‐Thank you. Ah!
‐Ah!
‐My little man.
And my biggest fan.
Well, one of them.
And speaking of fans...
Attention, everyone!
But, uh, I think we have
a special guest here tonight.
There we go. There’s
my little man of the house!
Oh, my goodness!
Oh, my God!
I tried, but mom keeps
bossing me around instead.
I thought you weren’t coming
till the 27th!
Well, I couldn’t miss
the Christmas family reunion.
‐Now, could I?
‐Well, you know what?
I know you better get over here
and give your mother a big hug.
‐Oh, my, look at you!
‐Of course. Hey, mama.
‐Look at you. Good to see you.
‐Oh!
‐Are you eatin’ okay?
‐I’m‐I’m a military man.
‐I have to be in shape.
‐I know, baby.
‐All right?
‐You in shape. Look at my...
Auntie, you’re lookin’ gorgeous
over there.
‐Look at your cousin. Hi.
‐Right.
‐So good to have him back.
‐Yeah.
‐
Good to see you.
This is turning into
the most fabulous Christmas,
after all.
Yeah, sure is, huh?
Aunt Alma even made
some decent candy canes.
‐Okay, got that right finally.
‐All right.
Thank you. Thank you.
She’s finally following
your Grandma Gladys’ recipe.
‐Yeah, she is.
‐My goodness. Mm.
And, honey, thanks in good part
to you and all that you’ve done,
we have nearly raised
over $10,000
from family donations
for Stan’s Stockings.
‐We did?
‐We did.
‐Wow.
‐Oh, honey.
You are such a marvelous man,
you know that?
‐I’m very proud of you.
‐Thank you.
And you know your dad is here.
He’s here with us. And I know
he’s proud of you, too.
‐Merry Christmas, baby.
‐Merry Christmas, mama.
‐Love you.
‐Love you, baby.
All right, now go and say hi
to the person
who got this thing all together.
Ma, Amy’s not here.
Mm. She is, though.
Over there.
Surprise.
So Christmas miracles
do come true.
Go.
Well, aren’t you gonna thank me?
‐For what?
‐For saving your money.
On a reunion photographer,
of course.
Oh!
‐Thank you.
‐And thank you.
You did an amazing job
on this reunion, Amy.
You didn’t even know my family
just a few weeks ago.
Now it’s like
you’ve known us forever.
What can I say?
My family is not really
in the Christmas spirit
and... yours just
inspired me.
Well, maybe your family
could come around.
We’ll be happy to have ’em
at the next reunion.
You know, get them
into the holiday spirit.
‐I think they’d like that. Yeah.
‐Yeah?
How about you, Amy?
‐Would you like that?
‐What?
To be at the next reunion.
’Cause I’d really like
to have you at all of ’em.
‐Oh.
‐If I had it my way, actually.
Well, you know
I like to be put to work.
All right,
you come to the reunions
and I promise to share the table
with the best view with you.
Ah.
‐Deal.
All right, everyone!
And now it is time for another
annual Christmas family tradition.
We do this at my mom’s house.
Christmas caroling and hot coca.
‐
‐Cue the music.
♪ This time ♪
♪ I won’t let you go ♪
♪ I want you to know ♪
♪ You’re mine ♪
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ Be my gift forever
on Christmas Day ♪
♪ This time ♪
♪ We won’t be apart ♪
♪ I’m giving you my heart ♪
♪ You’re mine ♪
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ And be here forever
on Christmas Day ♪
♪ I’m sorry baby
that I left you in tears ♪
♪ Broken‐hearted
with no Christmas cheer ♪
♪ I know I made you feel
so so blue ♪
♪ But all I want for Christmas
is you ♪
♪ ’Cause last Christmas
you gave me your heart ♪
♪ And this year
I’ll fall apart ♪
♪ Please baby
please don’t tell me no ♪
♪ Kiss me under the mistletoe ♪
♪ This time ♪
♪ I won’t let you go ♪
♪ I want you to know ♪
♪ You’re mine ♪
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ Be my gift forever
on Christmas Day ♪
♪ This time ♪
♪ We won’t be apart ♪
♪ I’m giving you my heart ♪
♪ You’re mine ♪
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ And be my gift forever
on Christmas Day ♪
♪ Baby baby
take me by the hand ♪
♪ Hold me close
in this winter wonderland ♪
♪ While we... ♪
What is that?
My fortune said I was supposed
to catch a shooting star.
It lied.
Well, at least
one of our fortunes came true.
♪ You next to me ♪
What do you mean?
♪ Present this year ♪
A true path to love?
I just needed
a couple lampposts to get there.
♪ I won’t let you go ♪
Just a few.
♪ I want you to know ♪
♪ You’re mine ♪
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ Be my gift forever
on Christmas Day ♪
♪ This time ♪
♪ We won’t be apart ♪
♪ I’m giving you my heart ♪
♪ You’re mine ♪
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ And be here forever
on Christmas Day ♪
♪ Deck the halls
with boughs of holly ♪
♪ Fa‐la la‐la‐la la‐la‐la‐la ♪
♪ ’Tis the season to be jolly ♪
♪ Don now our gay apparel ♪
♪ Fa‐la‐la la‐la‐la la‐la‐la ♪
♪ Troll the ancient
Yuletide carol ♪
♪ Fa‐la la‐la‐la la‐la‐la‐la ♪
♪ See the blazing yule
before us ♪
♪ Fa‐la la‐la‐la la‐la‐la‐la ♪
♪ Strike the harp
and join the chorus ♪
♪ Fa‐la la‐la‐la la‐la‐la‐la ♪
♪ Follow me in merry measures ♪
♪ Fa‐la‐la la‐la‐la la‐la‐la ♪
♪ While I tell
of Yuletide treasure ♪