Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
- Daddy! Can I go to the pool?
- Yes, but be careful.
Tell me, did she have
previous concussions?
- No.
- I don’t know.
- Allergic reactions to
medications?
- No.
- Well... We can do
a CT scan... if you want.
Whiskey?
Want to tell?
- One patient, a girl.
Her CT is the same as...
- Will you be able to help her?
- The second shot was normal.
Hmmm... that's it.
How are you?
- My affairs?
Nobody asks the bartender
about his business.
They tell him theirs.
- Cheers.
- Kolya, hey!... I told you!
Hey... what’s this!...
- What’s going on?
This is a mess!
- You... come in ... Sorry!
Come on, pick it up!
Well, we have taps.
- Well, and who pays?
It’s from your salary.
- What have I got to do with it?
I'm just stuck, that's all.
- You can! Come on! Hey!...
- Ok.
- Anton!
- Sorry, we are closed.
Ah, it’s you.
- I need a drink.
- Can I offer you
something special?
Thirty years of whiskey,
cures everything.
Soft, fragrant.
You’ll like it!
At the expense of the
institution.
- Will you give me ice?
- This one is just clean.
Bad day?
- Can I have more?
- Come on, come on. Come in.
Come on, be careful.
- Enough, enough,
enough, enough!
Get ready for reanimation!
- No, no, you can't come here.
Wait, please, there.
- They will take care of her,
ma'am.
Try to calm down.
Everything will be fine.
One, two!... Three!...
- How are you?
- Some water?
- No!
You can't go there!
- She has a cardiac arrest.
- Prepare a defibrillator.
- Calm down!
Warning! Discharge!
- The heart did not start.
- Let's do one more time.
Warning! Discharge!
How much time has passed?
- Thirty seconds.
- Raise it.
- Ok.
Discharge!
- We lose her.
You can't come here!
Who are you?
Listen, we are...
- Attention! The heart started!
Get parents out of here.
- Prepare oxygen!
Please take off your hands...
- Come on, come on!...
- Attention! Attention!
- Where is the oxygen mask?
- Get away!
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Where's the mask?
- Give me the mask, faster!
- The mask!
- Here you go.
- All right. It works!
- Now I am free, Mommy.
- Forgive me.
- I love you.
- I love you, too, my baby.
I miss you so much.