Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[ominous music]
[tense pounding music]
[music reaches climax
then stops]
-[door clicks]
-[gasps]
Nice run?
Yeah, thanks.
-She up yet?
-What do you think?
-[Hailey] Sienna.
-Hmm?
Come on.
We got packing to do.
Go away.
Three days. That's it,
and then you'll feel better.
Sienna.
I've invested too much time
in your recovery
for you mess things up again,
okay?
-Get up.
-Ah.
Five minutes.
[brooding music]
[pulsating music]
[somber music]
[Josh] So this is it?
This is the place you learned
to be--
[Hailey] ...a medic.
We used to spend weeks up here
trekking through this forest.
I hated it.
[Josh] And you wanted
to come back. Why?
I strangely missed it.
The air, the nature,
secludedness.
It's nice.
I'm not sure Sienna
would ever like it.
Yeah, well, she's nearly
over the hill.
These next few days
will be rough for her, so...
-We have to make an effort.
-Yes, Sarge.
It's Captain to you.
Permission to ask
a question, Captain?
Hmm. What is it?
[birds chirping]
You know that...
what we talked about?
I think I'm ready
to start trying.
[soft sentimental tune]
Maybe even right now.
[giggles] My sister
is right there.
She's not gonna hear.
[giggles] But seriously
there's never perfect time
or a place...
when there's a perfect person
-Hmm?
-[giggles]
Did you just rehearse that?
No...
Come on.
[soft music playing]
[birds chirping]
[tree leaves crackle]
[foreboding music]
Guys, guys.
You have to see this.
-Oh, God.
-[Hailey] Sienna.
Guys, come on.
This better be good.
[Josh] Hailey!
What could possibly--
Wait.
[intriguing music]
Oh, my God.
I have to call Lyssa.
-Is that what I think it is?
-I think so.
It's beautiful.
Let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
We don't know if it's friendly.
I don't see the Army anywhere.
What if it just got here?
If they were here
to take over the world
they would have done it
already.
[suspenseful music]
Wooh, wooh, wait, wait.
Sienna?
Sienna.
[radio crackling]
[phone crackles]
[man screams on the phone]
[signal lost]
[eerie music crescendo]
[loud hissing noise]
[groans and growls]
[gasps]
[groans]
[eerie music]
[high-pitched tone]
[groans and gasps]
[sound fades down]
[morose music]
Josh, Josh?
You okay?
Baby, wake up.
What happened?
I don't know.
I guess they are not friendly.
No, not at all.
Oh, my phone's not working.
How long were we are for?
I don't know, it's night.
Few hours?
We need to go to the car.
We need to check the car radio.
Yeah, good idea.
Let's just hope it still works.
Come on.
[brooding music]
Let's get packed up.
Get the stuff to the car.
[distant blast]
[closer blast]
[loud whizz]
[explosions]
[gasps]
-We have to go now.
-Go?
[blast]
But where?
We're staying.
We're staying, it's safer.
-Okay.
-What?
We can't go back.
What's the point?
I'm going to sort out
the wood for the fire.
Go to the car, check the radio.
See if you can find out
what's going on.
I need you to go to the car.
I need you to grab
the lighter fluid.
Can you do that?
[sobs]
The walk will do you good.
It'll keep you warm.
Josh, look after her.
You'll be fine.
I'll be fine.
Okay
[breathes heavily]
Come on.
You okay.
[gasps]
[white noise]
[soft ominous music]
Is the radio working, then?
No, it's dead.
Can you not just start the car?
There's no point.
What do you want from cars
that got computers.
So whatever that was...
would have fried everything...
along with our phones.
Yes.
Okay, let's head back to camp.
[whizzing noise]
[suspenseful music]
Let's go.
[campfire sizzles]
The car is dead.
Managed to get it going?
You got any food?
I have some marshmallows...
some bread...
some cheese, some soup.
You got any water?
[animal-like sound in distance]
[Sienna] Guys,
there's something out there.
[scare chord]
Guys, there's something there.
[Josh] Who is there?
[Josh shouts] Stop.
Stop!
Stop.
-Stop.
-[growls]
Stay back, stay back.
Stop!
[thud]
Is she okay?
Is she...
Check her pulse.
[growls]
[dramatic music]
[high-pitched roar]
[animal growls in distance]
There's more of them.
We need to go.
Give me the bag.
Pack the tents up.
Pack up the tent.
Be careful.
Come on.
-Your hand.
-Don't worry about.
Let's pack up the tent
and let's just go.
Sienna, pack up the tent.
[sinister tone]
-Okay.
-[Hailey] We need to keep going.
Your sister's not going
to go any further.
Look, the further we are away
the safer we'll be.
Come on.
Hailey, I'm tired,
I'm hungry
and we haven't seen
one of those things in a while.
We're staying here.
Are we staying or going?
It's broken
We need to keep moving.
We can't just walk in the dark.
[indistinct]
I'm not leaving her.
If we carry on walking
she'll follow us.
Come on.
You need to pick
her up and get out of here.
Who are you?
Those things are everywhere.
What are they?
I don't know, mate.
But they don't stop.
So you shouldn't either.
Stay quiet
and find a place to hide.
Where are you hiding?
I've been in my holiday home.
Is it far?
All right. You three look
like you need a hand.
Stay quiet. Stay out of sight.
[soft intriguing music]
[foreboding music]
[dramatic chord]
[Liam] Run faster, please.
[Hailey]
We're faster than them.
[Liam] You don't get it.
They don't stop.
[gasps]
Wait, wait, wait.
This trail.
If we follow this trail
we can make it to the coast
in about three or four days.
Three or four days?
If we keep up the pace,
we can stay ahead
of those creatures.
Ad you even trust this man?
He seems
to know where he's going
so I'm gonna take my chances
-Hailey?
-She's right, Josh. Come on.
Josh, come on.
Come on love.
[gasps and groans]
[alien growling]
They are coming.
[screams]
[pained whimper]
You owe me one.
Why have they stopped her?
They're outnumbered.
[roars]
[Liam] Okay, we're clear.
Josh, keep a lookout.
-Map.
-Yeah.
[breathes with difficulty]
[grizzles]
[Liam and Josh
indistinct chat]
-[indistinct chat continues]
-[breathes heavily]
All right?
[whines]
[birds chirping]
[sobs]
I'm sorry I brought you here.
-I did it for you.
-I can't...
I can't do this anymore.
I need you to do
something to make it.
I need to dig deep
because we need to get
the hell out of here.
You can, you can.
Have I ever lied to you?
Have I?
I promise you.
I'm not going to let
anything happen to you.
I swear.
Okay?
It's okay.
[dramatic musical buildup]
-You've got this.
-[sobs]
[brooding music]
[Liam]
Right, it's just up here.
-We call it Emerald Ridge.
-[Hailey] Who is we?
Me and my business associates.
We need to discuss terms
before we get there.
-Terms?
-Yeah, terms.
So what do you want?
My house, my rules.
So you do as I say
when I say it.
Secondly, we're splitting
these supplies
and thirdly,
you stay out of my tent.
Specially her.
[suspenseful music]
Fine.
Lead the way.
[helicopter whirring]
Hailey, give me some lights.
Give me the flares,
give me the flares.
[indistinct]
Where is he going?
To find the key ring.
[indistinct]
Don't just leave me here.
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music crescendo]
[flare hissing]
[Josh grunts]
[grunts] Liam!
What are you doing,
you stupid prick?
Get off me.
[both grunt]
[sting]
[Hailey] Josh.
Get off him.
Josh, you're gonna kill him.
[roars]
[chokes]
[coughs]
[Hailey] Stop it. Stop it.
You two, stop.
Everyone knows where we are now.
You're on your own.
What the hell
are you playing at?
It wasn't me.
I wasn't in control.
You just say the word
and I walk away, I promise.
We stick together.
Let's go
before he steals our stuff.
Guys.
[ominous music]
[branches crackling]
[footfalls]
-Where are you going?
-Over there.
He's going to get us all killed.
You can't just leave us here
with no food.
Watch me.
He was just trying to help.
Please.
[pulsing music]
I think it's
an old Army compound
but a landslide blocked
the only route in
except one.
[suspenseful music]
Welcome to Paradise.
Right, you lot set up out here.
[music fades down]
[lamp clicks]
[brooding music builds up]
[campfire sizzles]
Josh, your hands.
Sienna.
-Sienna, come--
-Calm down.
What happened to his hand
since last night?
It'll get better tomorrow.
Hailey, he's turning
into one of them.
Be quiet, please.
If that stuff in his hand
changes him
we'll deal with it, okay?
I promise.
Do you really want
to be stuck with Liam?
Haily,
you can't hide this forever.
-And if Liam sees it...
-He won't find out.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Everything all right out here
in Paradise?
I found this old radio.
Get it fixed.
See if we can find out
anything useful.
Care to give us a house tour?
This ain't
the Four Seasons, mate.
Stay out.
What kind of a person
needs a hideout?
The kind that survives.
[eerie music builds up]
[eerie music]
You do realize that's
an old short wave radio.
We're going to need
a battery and antenna.
-We'll get more luck--
-Look, I'm just trying to help.
I'm sorry.
What's up?
What strange is that is
in the middle of the forest
and it only has a short wave,
a few miles max?
So whoever originally
put that in that tent
...was in range
of a bigger base.
Exactly.
So why don't we lead them out?
I have to figure out
what it is first.
I'll get some supplies.
You can tell Sienna.
She'll be more
compliant with you.
And Liam?
I can try.
You really think we can
tear him away from Paradise.
[birds chirping]
[footfall]
I like you better
than your man cave.
When was the last time
you ate something?
What do you care?
Let's just say I've seen
what going cold turkey
can do to a person.
Where did you get those?
Lets' say
there's a good reason
why you need
to stay out of my tent.
We might as well
have some fun, hadn't we
Before they kill us...
or worse.
[eerie music builds up]
[birds chirping]
[brooding music]
[music fades down]
[birds chirping]
[tree branches crackle]
[water running]
[water bubbles]
[distant swish]
[water running]
[birds chirping]
Is someone enjoying herself?
Sienna.
[silence]
[birds chirping]
Don't mind me.
Just trying to keep us going.
Sienna.
Hailey, Hailey.
Look at me.
Ow.
Liam.
What?
What did you give her?
Look, I've seen
withdrawal before.
Now isn't the time for her
to go cold turkey.
You seem to think
of Sienna better than I do.
You expect me to believe
you did that
for any other reason
than to take advantage of her?
You dose my sister again--
And you'll what?
Is there anything else in there
you're hiding from us?
More food, drugs...
weapons?
Any secrets you've got
you should be worried about.
The water is contaminated.
Thought you should know.
Just wait for the rain.
Yeah, what if it doesn't rain?
Yeah, you seem to know it all.
Know of any other freshwater
we could use?
It's a bit of a trek.
I'm going to need a hand.
If you don't think
you could do it by yourself
then let's go.
You two can go.
We're staying here
considering
she can't go anywhere.
Josh, can I have a word?
[Hailey] Josh.
Lads night out
[Hailey] Listen.
Listen.
[distant bangs in tunnel]
Look.
It's not safe out there.
So, be careful.
Be careful of him.
Hey.
Please.
[bottle crushes]
[metal bang]
[ominous music builds up]
[forest silence]
Right. I found some things
that can carry water.
We'll line your back with these.
I found this.
You best hang onto this as well.
Come on, partner.
[birds chirping]
Sienna.
[sobs]
Give me the bottle.
No
-Sienna, give me the bottle.
-No.
-Sienna.
[inhales deeply]
[Sienna growls]
[shouts]
What are you doing?
[thud]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[both grunt]
Hailey said she heard some
of those things earlier.
When?
I don't know.
A few hours.
We better get to move on.
We are in the middle
of the forest.
What could those things want?
I dunno mate.
If I were a betting man
I'd say
they're looking for us two.
Do you think we'll make it
back to camp?
We can try.
Come on.
[brooding music]
[clicks and clunks]
[Sienna whispers]
What did you do to me?
I can't keep doing this.
I'm tired.
It'll pass.
It always does.
You killed me.
Are you joking?
Sienna, you're killing yourself.
We only have each other, Sienna.
And you keep doing
shit like this.
You're not only gonna get
yourself killed
but me too.
What a shame that would be.
[brooding music]
[Josh]
So you know the forest well?
[Liam] Not bad for a druggie.
[Josh] I never called you that.
But you did drug Sienna.
I didn't force her, mate.
You took advantage.
You knew she was vulnerable.
What are you going to do?
Report me?
I'm not trying to start a fight.
You sure about that?
If you was in my position
would you not try to do
the same thing?
I'm just trying to get Sienna
and Hailey to safety.
Safety?
I've taken you three to safety
and now I'm taking you to water.
So I'm doing a much better job
than you, mate.
That's for Sienna.
Liam, stop.
You two abandoned her.
I'm just asking you to do
one thing, just one thing.
If something happens to me...
then you're going to be
what they only have.
Let's get the water
and get out of here.
[grunts]
Finally.
Come on.
[water running]
[giggles] It's clear.
I think you're
understanding, mate.
That's going to be
a lot tougher getting back
especially carrying
these water bottles.
-It's your--
-Sh, sh, sh.
[ominous music]
She's looking the house.
She will live?
Something is not right.
Be careful.
[sinister tone]
She's been shot.
[sting]
There's no blood.
Just get the water and go.
[Josh screams in pain]
You have to [indistinct]
Let's have a look.
I'm fine.
You're not good
with a swollen arm.
Stay off. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Whatever you say, mate.
Go.
[ominous music]
[panting]
Oh, you, Josh.
[ominous music crescendo]
[scare chord]
[groans]
Josh!
Josh.
Jooosh!
[dramatic music builds up]
[distorted voice] Liam.
Liam!
Liam.
Help me.
[dramatic music crescendo]
[whines]
[breathes heavily]
[thud]
[dramatic music]
[pounding music]
[music slows down]
[both panting]
[distorted voices]
Josh.
[Liam] Josh.
[suspenseful music]
[Liam grunts]
Here, the gun.
[blast]
[high-pitched noise]
[distorted voices]
[musical climax then silence]
[campfire sizzles]
Where is Josh?
Liam.
What the hell
happened out there?
Liam knows.
-Huh?
-He knows.
Oh, shit.
What happened to your face?
I don't take it personally.
I need to see if it was.
I cannot control myself.
We need to get out of here.
Yeah.
Yeah, we do.
I guess we all have
to thank you for all of this.
Sorry.
You're just after another fix.
So you want?
It's your choice.
Like you said
[indistinct]
[Josh mumbles]
Okay. Okay.
[indistinct]
[delusional murmur]
[water running]
[metallic clunk]
[dramatic music]
Where is Josh?
We didn't hear about.
Get out.
Something happened to his tent.
So?
So we're going to go find him.
Oh, shit.
Josh?
[shouting] Josh.
[suspenseful music]
Josh.
Josh, can you hear me?
Hailey.
Josh, I will take you back.
Okay?
This way. Come on.
Liam.
[Josh mumbles]
Hailey. Someone helps.
He's too far.
He needs to go now.
Just go and call Hailey.
[Liam] You need to let him
rest in peace.
[Sienna] Hailey.
[Liam]
Stop calling your sister.
[Liam indistinct
distorted voice]
[distorted voice] Sienna,
you have to let me go.
[indistinct distorted voices]
[Josh pants]
[distorted voice] Josh?
Josh.
[Liam] Hailey.
Josh, wake up.
Hailey.
Josh.
What the hell happened to him?
-He's gone into the tunnel.
-He's turning, Hailey.
We need to get him in your tent.
He needs somewhere warm.
He is not going in my tent.
Liam, he's going in your tent.
Please, dont' be stupid,
just help me.
Liam, please, come on.
Christ.
Move the bed.
Stay with me.
We need to keep him awake.
Every time he falls asleep
he gets worse.
Do you have any stimulant
or anything?
Yes.
Hey, baby. Stay awake.
Look at me.
Please, stay awake.
Baby, come on.
Stay with me.
Come on.
Haley.
Haley!
[gasps] What the hell
are you doing?
He's too far gone.
It's not like you said.
He still has time.
You don't get it, Hailey.
I've seen this before.
Liam, please.
Liam, wait.
Just let her say goodbye.
It's too dangerous.
Tie him up, just--
Just give me this.
Please.
One hour.
One hour and then I'm doing it.
[eerie music]
[Liam] It's time.
All is changing
if you like it or not.
We need to adapt and learn.
[Liam] Haley.
Come on, Hailey. It's time.
Get off Josh, please.
Last chance.
I can make it painless.
I've seen those things
rip my friends apart.
You have no idea
how dangerous he is.
This is the best thing for him
and the best thing for us.
Please, may I?
[Hailey screams]
Put your hands
behind your back.
[whispers] Put your hands
[water running]
[sighs]
When it's near the end
I'll give him some [indistinct]
Quick and painless.
You can say goodbye.
[scare chord]
[Liam] Don't worry.
I won't abandon you.
She can check on him.
[thumps]
[groans]
Hailey.
Help me.
[brooding music]
[screams]
[music fades down]
[sobs]
[gasps]
[eerie music]
Help me.
Come on, Sienna.
We have to go.
We can't stay here.
Sienna.
I've got a better idea.
Please.
What are you doing?
Bend on your knees.
Liam, just let her go.
[suspenseful music crescendo]
[low-pitched growl]
[blast]
[sobs]
[suspenseful music]
[punding suspensful music]
Liam. No!
She's done nothing for you.
She was going to run away
with that thing
take all of our supplies
and leave us here to run.
He's lying, it was for you.
I swear, I promise, Sienna.
Bullshit.
Sienna.
Make another move,
and I put one in your leg.
To [indistinct] this world.
[indistinct] survive.
And that's-- [growls]
Hailey.
[Sienna] Run, run.
[whirling noise]
[growls loudly]
[screams]
[scream fades in distance]
[silence]
[birds chirping]
[footfalls]
Sienna, come on.
We have to go.
-Please, get up.
-No.
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
He was giving lot of shit
helping you.
But you won't be here
if you run.
I'm not going anywhere.
If you're staying, I'm staying.
If you're done, I'm done.
Sorry about Josh.
Me too.
[birds chirping]
[dramatic chord]
[dramatic pounding music]
[both gasp and groan]
[slow violin tune]
[slow sentimental music]
[pulsating dramatic music]
[thud]
[music fades down]
[distorted voice] Sienna?
Sienna.
[sentimental music]
[distorted voice] I'm sorry.
[sobs]
[melancholic violin]
[musical transition]
[music becomes uplifting]
[uplifting music]
[helicopters whirring]
[music continues playing]