Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Mr. Heathcliff?
I'm Lockwood, your
new tenant, sir,
at Thrushcross Grange.
I'll do myself the honor of
calling as soon as possible.
I hope I've not inconvenienced
you in my arrival.
I should not allow
anyone to inconvenience me
if I could hinder it.
I do wonder why you
should select the thick
of a storm to ramble about in.
From Thy bounty, through
Christ our Lord, amen.
I don't think
it possible for me
to get home without a guide.
Perhaps you could
spare one of your lads.
No, I could not.
I don't keep accommodations
for strangers.
I shall sleep in a chair.
A stranger is a stranger.
If you wish to stay,
you can share a bed
with either Hareton or Joseph.
Let this be a lesson
for you, Mr. Lockwood,
to not go on any more
ramblings on the moors.
I can go with him
as far as the park.
It would be hell.
Follow me.
Mind the candle, and
don't make a noise.
My master has an odd
notion about this room.
Have a good night, sir.
I'm so alone.
Cathy?
You, out now.
Don't leave.
Come back to me.
Come back.
This whole house is swarming
with ghosts and goblins.
If that little fiend
would have gotten in,
she would have strangled
me, snatched my soul away.
I'm not a fanciful man,
ma'am, nor a dishonest one.
I saw her with my own eyes,
and felt her with
my very own hands.
Who was she?
You have lived in
this neighborhood
a considerable
time, have you not?
All my life, sir.
First here, and
then at the grange,
when my mistress was married.
The master retained
me for his housekeeper
till he passed away.
Followed my second
mistress here.
Indeed, then you have seen
a good many alterations.
Aye, and a lot
of troubles too.
You knew her?
This, Cathy.
And Mr. Heathcliff,
he knew her as well?
He loved her, dare I say.
He is a rather churlish man.
He must have led
a tumultuous life
to make him such a rough fellow.
Do you know anything
of his history?
I know all about
it, Mr. Lockwood,
save for the
circumstances of his birth
and how he got his fortune.
It would be a
charitable deed to tell me
something of my
neighbors, Miss Dean.
It's not a joyous tale.
There's not room for
smiles and laughter
so much, just tears and remorse.
I should like
to hear it still.
30 years ago, when I took
over my mother's position
as housekeeper at
Wuthering Heights,
Mr. Earnshaw, Cathy's father,
was to return from
Liverpool that evening.
We all eagerly
awaited his arrival
because he was to bring
a present for all of us.
A riding whip for Cathy, a
fiddle for brother Hindley.
Your brother is studying.
And some
apples and pears for me.
Papa, Papa.
Papa, we're so
glad you came home.
I can see that.
Oh.
Catherine, give
your father a rest.
He's had a long journey.
Oh, oh oh oh.
Come.
I brought you something.
What
did you bring me?
See here.
Oh, what is it?
A gift from God.
A gift from the
devil, more like it.
Quiet, girl.
I found him starving in
the streets of Liverpool.
It was the Christian thing
to do to bring him home.
How can you fashion
to bring this gypsy brat
into our home when we
have our own children
to feed and care for?
I couldn't let him starve.
Why not? Tends to
be what his kind do.
What's so special about
this dodgy foundling?
He's not my blood any
more than he is yours,
but he will be our son and
Hindley and Cathy's brother.
An easy
conversion, no doubt.
Cathy.
Do you want to know
what I brought for you?
Yes.
I brought you Heathcliff.
Heathcliff? Heathcliff?
You've named this
after our brother?
It is a befitting name.
You hardly knew your brother,
and Cathy was only a twinkle
in my eye when he passed.
Nelly, wash him and
find him some clothes.
The rest of us, will go to bed.
Come on.
Dear God, thank
you for your mercy,
and thank you for this bounty
we are about to receive.
And dear God, thank you for
the gift of Heathcliff, amen.
Amen.
Here.
It'll make you strong.
Eat it up.
Here, put this in your lap.
Neat and tidy, huh?
From
the very beginning
Heathcliff bred bad
feelings in the house.
Two years later,
Mrs. Earnshaw died,
without ever seeing
Heathcliff as anything
but her husband's
ill-begotten bastard.
After the mistress' death,
Hindley began to view his father
as an oppressor
rather than a friend,
and Heathcliff as an usurper
of his father's affections.
That's right, keep
that nice and clean.
Otherwise, the
powder will ignite.
Very good. Now, see if you
can put that back down.
That's it.
That's right, now
hold this up here.
All right, pull this out.
Go ahead and pull that out.
And ram it down inside that.
Heathcliff and
Cathy became inseparable.
There wasn't a
place where one went
where the other didn't follow.
You're a dirty
gypsy, Heathcliff.
I hate you.
Finally, Arcure
advised Mr. Earnshaw
to send Hindley to college.
Mr. Earnshaw agreed, but
he never thought Hindley
would thrive, no matter
where he wandered.
I never believed.
I was the only one who
truly cared for Hindley.
Until the night
of his departure,
it seemed I would
be the only one
who would regret his absence.
Cathy?
Why can't you always
be a good lass?
be a good man, Father?
Father?
Time for bed.
Nelly!
Day for your prayers, Mister.
Mr. Earnshaw.
Mr. Earnshaw?
Cathy.
Heathcliff, take Cathy
to bed. Back to bed.
Fetch Dr. Kenneth.
You'll always be
Catherine Heathcliff.
Forever.
Tell me, Heathcliff,
where did you come from?
I don't remember.
I don't remember
anything before you.
I think you're a
prince in disguise.
Your father was the
emperor of China,
and your mother was
an Indian queen.
And you were kidnapped
by wicked sailors
and brought to England.
You're worried
everything will change
once Hindley
returns, aren't you?
Well, with Father dead,
he does own the Heights.
I won't have much to
protect me but my own wits.
I shall protect you.
My brother won't touch a
single black hair on your head.
No one dare try to
take you away from me.
Nor you from me.
Hurry.
No parson in the
world ever pictured heaven
so beautifully as they did.
And I could not help wishing
we were all there safe together.
After his schooling,
Mr. Hindley came home
and set the neighbors
gossiping, right, left.
He brought a wife with him.
Heathcliff.
What she was
and where she was born...
The horses.
He never informed us.
She had neither money nor
name to recommend her,
or he would scarcely have kept
that union from his father.
Young Earnshaw was
altered considerably
in the years of his absence.
Hello, Catherine. This
is my wife, Frances.
Isn't this charming?
This is my sister Catherine,
our housekeeper Nelly,
and that was Joseph.
Welcome to Wuthering
Heights, ma'am.
Cathy, Hindley's told
me so much about you.
I've always wanted a
sister of my very own,
and now I have one.
Oh, why don't you
show me around?
From now on,
Nelly, you and Joseph are
to stay in the servants'
quarters, where you belong.
Of course, master.
And as for you, Heathcliff,
no more curate, and
stay in the stables.
My wife and I want the
house to ourselves.
Hindley
became tyrannical,
evincing a dislike
to Heathcliff.
He drove him from their
company to the servants',
deprived him of education,
and insisted that he
should labor out of doors.
It's horrible what
Hindley's done to you.
Things will get better.
It'll be all right.
You do trust me, don't you?
Of course.
Good. Well then.
I'm going to read to you.
Where we were?
Heathcliff
bore his degradation
fairly well at first,
because Cathy taught
him what she learnt
and worked or played
with him in the fields.
They both promised fair to
grow up as unruly savages.
The young master being
entirely negligent
how they behaved
and what they did,
so they kept clear of him.
It was one of their chief
amusements to run away
to the moors in the morning
and remain there all day.
They forgot everything the
minute they were together again.
To seek revenge,
but leave a place
for divine retribution.
Never pay back evil for evil.
Let your ills be such as
all men kept honorable.
If possible, live at
peace with all men.
What? Done already?
I think
that's enough for today.
When Father was
alive, we were permitted
to play on Sundays.
I don't give a
damn what Father did.
This is my house
now. I am master.
Hindley, let them be.
If they want to run around
like savages, let them.
Fine, off with you then.
Here, look.
It's beautiful, Heathcliff.
That evening,
Hindley, in a passion,
told us to bolt the doors
and swore nobody should
let them in that night.
The household went to
bed, but I was determined
to admit them in spite
of the prohibition,
once they returned.
Heathcliff, look.
There's marigold at the grange.
I wonder how the Lintons
pass their Sunday evenings.
Standing around
shivering in corners
while the help burn their
eyes out by the fire.
Cathy.
Thrushcross Grange.
Your new home, Mr. Lockwood,
was once home to the Lintons,
a proud family of landed gentry.
Old Mr. Linton had
long since passed,
but he left two spirited
children, Isabella and Edgar.
They had all the grange
entirely to themselves.
Shouldn't they have been happy?
We should have thought
ourselves in heaven.
And now, guess what those
good children were doing.
Livelier,
Isabella, livelier.
Livelier.
Don't you wish you had
been adopted by the Lintons?
Livelier, live...
I am playing it lively. You
sit down and play it then.
There's
somebody out there.
They haven't seen us.
Men!
Heathcliff!
Heathcliff, bring her in here.
You can lay her right there.
I have sent one of my
men for Dr. Kenneth.
He will be here within the hour.
Miss, where does it hurt?
Don't don't, don't
touch her. Please, please.
Sir.
No no, no no. Don't
touch her please.
Please.
Sir.
Get away.
Sir, if you cannot
behave civilized,
then I will have to
ask you to leave.
If you're not
sure, we'll wait for the doctor.
Fine.
But I can't leave Cathy here.
Let me tend to her.
Please, no, please. Please.
Seamus.
Your presence,
sire, is no longer required.
Do not worry.
She will be well taken care of.
She will be well cared for.
Look
at the state of her.
I need to have.
My word.
I shall have to talk
to Hindley Earnshaw
about his gypsy brother.
Perhaps she would benefit
from staying here for a while.
Cathy stayed at
Thrushcross Grange five weeks.
By that time, her ankle
was thoroughly cured
and her manners much improved.
Mr. Linton commenced a
plan of reform by raising
her self-respect with
fine clothes and flattery,
which she readily took.
Remember, Heathcliff,
if I am to allow you
to stay here at the Heights,
you are not to speak to Cathy.
Not unless it
involves her horse.
Brother.
So that, instead of
a wild hapless little sage,
there lighted a very
dignified person.
Oh, Heathcliff,
you may come forward
and wish Miss Cathy welcome.
Heathcliff.
Have you forgotten all about me?
Shake hands with
her, Heathcliff.
Surely that's permitted.
Heathcliff,
what have you been
doing with yourself?
I won't stand
to be laughed at.
I didn't mean to laugh.
I couldn't handle myself.
Look how dirty you are.
You look lovely, Cath.
And on that note,
let's go in, shall we?
May I present a toast
to our guests the Lintons.
Edgar, Isabella, I bid you
welcome to Wuthering Heights.
Why thank you, Hindley.
Happy to be here.
It's marvelous pears
this year, quite a yield.
Nelly?
Can you
make me decent?
High time time, Heathcliff.
You know, proud
people often breed
sad sorrows for themselves.
I believe a few of Mr.
Earnshaw's old clothes
are in the attic.
As soon as I can steal
time, I'll help you.
Edgar Linton will look
like a dog compared to you.
What are you doing in here?
This is a place for civilized
ladies and gentlemen,
not for dirty gypsies.
Wait!
Till I take hold of those
elegant locks of yours,
see if I can't pull them
out a little longer.
I think they're long enough.
Look's like a colt's
mane.
Oh!
No, Heathcliff!
Back to the stables.
Excuse us.
Fight!
I told you to fight back!
Now you must!
You were no more
his son than I was.
Joseph, I have to go give my
father's coat another brushing.
Next time, Edgar, take
the law to your fists.
It will give you an appetite.
Now then, who's up
for a round of bridge?
Heathcliff, it's for
God to punish the wicked.
We must learn to forgive.
On that morning, my
first bonny little nursling
and the last of the ancient
Earnshaw stock was born.
How's the babe?
Nearly ready to
run about, Nelly.
And Frances?
She'll be perfectly well
by this time next week.
But Dr. Kenneth...
Damn him!
Damn the doctor.
I'll go and see to her.
Where's Cathy?
With Mr. Linton.
He's so big.
I'm going to name him Hareton.
Hindley had an
ancestor named Hareton.
It is a good family name.
Happy mum.
Hareton Earnshaw, promise me
you'll look after him, Nelly.
You'll love him like your own.
Oh, it was
such a grand bairn.
The finest lad
that ever breathed.
And, Frances, she'd been in
consumption for many months.
She had nothing to keep her.
The other side.
You going somewhere?
No.
What do you got that
silly frock on for then?
Edgar Linton's supposed
to call here this afternoon.
Edgar Linton.
Catherine and he
were constant companions,
still, at his seasons
of respite from labor.
That's six weeks in a
row you've turned me out
for that pitiful
friend of yours again.
What have you got there?
Oh, that's very foolish.
As if I were to take notice.
Where's the sense in that?
To show you that
I take notice.
Here, look. Look here.
But he ceased
to express his fondness
for her in words, and
recoiled with angry suspicion
from her girlish caresses.
Every mark here
is a mark that you
have spent with Linton.
These marks are days with me.
Must I always
be simple to you?
You might be dumb for anything
you say to amuse me.
As if conscious, there
could be no gratification
in lavishing such marks
of affection on him.
Never knew that
I talked too little
that you disliked
my company, Cathy.
There's no company at all
when people know nothing.
Say nothing.
Heathcliff!
Where is my son?
Sh.
He's right here, Mr. Hindley.
Well then, let me hold him.
You're too drunk.
I'm his father. I'm
not going to hurt him.
You're a drunkard and a
poor excuse for a father.
It's all right, Heathcliff.
You can take a moment before
you return to the stables.
Just remember to brush
them before you turn in.
One more thing, don't
tell Mr. Hindley.
Nelly.
Your tongue has grown
rather sharp of late, Nelly.
Get your hands off of me.
I never noticed
what a woman you are.
Now's not the
time to take notice.
I could kill you for
speaking back to me.
Don't listen then. I
have to know my place.
Catherine, our time
together has been,
well, just lovely.
And, I feel we should
spend more time together.
I guess what I'm
trying to say is...
there's nothing that
would make me happier
than if you'd take
my hand of marriage.
Are you alone, Nelly?
Yes, Miss.
Will you keep a secret for me?
Is it worth keeping?
Today, Edgar Linton
asked me to marry him.
And I accepted.
Do you love Mr. Edgar?
Of course I do.
Who could help it?
Why do you love him?
Because he's handsome
and pleasant to be with.
Bad.
Because he's
young and cheerful.
Bad still.
Because he shall be rich.
And I shall be the greatest
woman in the neighborhood.
Worst of all.
You're making jest of it!
I'm very far from making
jest of it, Miss Cathy.
It doesn't matter what
you say. I shall marry him.
Very well. Your
brother will be pleased.
You will escape a
disorderly coupleless home
in favor of a wealthy
respectable one.
If you love Edgar,
and Edgar loves you,
all will be smooth and easy.
Where's your obstacle?
Here, near my heart,
near my soul.
I'm convinced I'm doing wrong.
Nelly, have you ever
had bad dreams at night?
Now and then.
I dreamt I was in heaven once,
and I was miserable there.
And I broke my
heart with weeping.
And the angels were so angry
that they thrust me out
right into the, right on
top of Wuthering Heights.
And I woke up sobbing for joy.
Don't you see, Nelly?
I have no more right
to marry Edgar Linton
than I have to be in heaven?
And if Hindley had not
brought Heathcliff so low,
I would have never
thought to marry Edgar.
But to marry Heathcliff
now would degrade me.
So he shall never know
how much I love him,
and my great misery
seeing his world diminish.
I have watched him run him off.
And my great thought
in living exists.
My love for Edgar is like
the foliage in the forest.
Time will change it, as
winter changes the trees.
My love for Heathcliff is like
the eternal rocks beneath.
A source of little visible
pleasure but vital.
I am Heathcliff, Nelly.
He is always, always in my mind.
But not as a pleasure to
myself but as my own being.
Miss Cathy, Heathcliff
might have been listening.
He left when you said it would
do you disgrace to marry him.
No!
- Miss Cathy!
- Heathcliff!
It was a very
dark evening for summer.
A storm came rattling over
the Heights, full of fury.
Catherine would not be
persuaded into tranquility.
She kept wandering to and fro,
heedless of the growing thunder,
and the great drops that
began to splash around her.
She remained,
calling at intervals,
and then listening, and
then crying outright.
She cried for
Heathcliff all night,
till she was greeted by the
warmth of the rising sun.
Where the hell have you been?
Outside.
Were you with Heathcliff?
I never saw him.
Well.
When he comes back,
I'll throw him out.
I've had enough of
that gypsy bastard.
You won't get
your opportunity.
He's gone.
I lost him.
I've lost him.
I've lost him! I've lost him!
I've lost him!
I don't have to go.
They have plenty of
maids at the Grange
to take care of Miss Cathy.
I can stay here with
you and Hareton.
There's no use for you here.
I want no women in this house.
But Hareton needs
a mother, sir.
He had a mother. She left him.
She left me.
Frances loved you, sir.
I'm sure it would break her
heart to see you like this.
Goodbye, Angel.
Edgar Linton
believed himself
the happiest man alive
on the day he led
Miss Cathy to Gimmerton Chapel.
He offered me magnificent wages,
and so I had but
one choice left,
to do as I was ordered.
And since then Hareton
has been a stranger.
Come on, fella, come on.
Hindley had mortgaged
every yard of land he owned
for cash to supply his
mania for gaming, drinking,
becoming something less than
a man, let alone a father.
I got Miss Catherine and
myself to Thrushcross Grange,
and to my agreeable
disappointment,
she behaved infinitely
better than I dared expect.
She seemed almost
overfond of Mr. Linton,
and even to his sister she
showed plenty of affection.
I believe I may assert that
they were really in possession
of deep and growing happiness.
But on a mellow evening
in September, it ended.
His cheeks were covered,
his brows lowered.
I remembered the eyes.
Excuse me, sir.
Yes.
A person from Gimmerton
wishes to see you, ma'am.
What do they want?
I didn't question him.
It's not one of
Hindley's creditors, is it?
No, someone the
mistress doesn't expect.
Shall I continue?
Please.
Heathcliff.
I thought I've
never been alive
since the last I saw your face.
Forgive me.
I struggled only for you.
Edgar, Edgar!
Heathcliff's come back!
Try to be glad
without being absurd
in front of the whole household.
Ah, Mr. Heathcliff.
Please, sit down.
Mrs. Linton would have me
give you a cordial reception.
Of course I am gratified with
anything that pleases her.
As am I, especially
when it is anything
in which I have a part.
Thank you, Nelly.
Well, tell us, where have
you been the last few years?
Abroad?
Yes.
Soldiering perhaps?
I shall
think it a dream tomorrow,
to have seen and touched
and spoken to you.
Yet, cruel Heathcliff, you
don't deserve this welcome.
To be absent and
silent for three years
and to never think of me.
A little more than
you thought of me.
I heard of your marriage.
Where are you
staying, Gimmerton?
No.
At Wuthering Heights.
Hindley Earnshaw invited you
to stay at Wuthering Heights?
No, it is I who have
invited him to stay.
Seems Hindley
mortgaged the property
to pay for his gambling debts.
I managed to help my
brother with his finances.
I am the owner of
Wuthering Heights now.
Well, hm, I'm eager to see
what you do with the place.
Cathy, do you think I
could maybe speak to you?
Isabella, can you leave us?
We've both been
through so much.
Please, please, we can
undo what was done.
And now I have
come back for you.
Mm.
Where do you expect to
take us, Heathcliff?
Away from here.
Away from all this.
I've seen the world now,
Cathy, and it is beautiful.
Come with me.
Heathcliff, I can't.
I'm having, I'm
having Edgar's child.
How can you do
this to me, Cathy?
How can I do it? You're
a fine one to talk.
You weren't there.
You don't know. Don't
talk to me anymore.
Cathy, please. Please.
Heathcliff.
You aren't a very nice person
to come here and
communicate this way.
Get your hands out
of your pockets.
Okay, then,
it's all right, it's all right.
There's still time.
It doesn't matter.
We can all leave.
Me, you and the child,
we can all leave.
Please, Cathy.
Cathy, Cathy.
No, no, you are too late.
You are my life.
Heathcliff.
Stay with me, please.
I can't, I can't, okay.
Mr. Heathcliff.
Cathy was cruel
to you yesterday.
As her friend, I feel the need
to apologize for her conduct.
You needn't apologize. I'm
well aware of Cathy's nature.
Oh, stop sighing, Isabella.
You are harsh and cruel to me.
It's jealousy that
makes her strike out.
Jealousy?
Oh yes, she is quite jealous.
You told me to
ramble where I pleased
while you sauntered on
with Mr. Heathcliff.
You wished me away because you
knew I wanted to be with him.
You desire no one to
be loved but yourself.
Cathy can only put on a silk
costume and play the part,
but you, Miss Linton,
are truly a lady.
Heathcliff is an
untamed creature,
and it is your powerful
ignorance of his character,
Isabella, and nothing else,
that makes you love him.
A beautiful lady.
Oh, Heathcliff.
We've been quarreling
like cats about you.
Catherine, no.
Mind us, this love I have
is nothing like the love
she entertains for you.
Oh no you don't.
Oh go on then.
Sweet Judas.
Who is it, Nelly?
You weren't telling
the truth, were you?
Oh please.
I like her too well to let
you seek to win her over.
And I like her too
little to attempt it.
Then again, she is her
brother's heir, is she not?
Now.
Not much longer.
Wait, no, I...
Heathcliff.
I told you to
leave Isabella alone.
What's it to you?
I have every right to
kiss her, if she chooses,
and you have no right to object.
I am not your husband.
If you love Isabella,
then you shall marry her.
But tell me the
truth, Heathcliff,
do you love her?
Thank you for telling me
your sister's little secret.
This way, I'll make
the most of it.
Have you been listening
at the door, Edgar?
I was not ignorant
to your miserable,
degraded character,
Mr. Heathcliff,
but foolishly I acquiesced
to my wife's desire
to keep your acquaintance.
Hereafter, you are no longer
welcome in this household.
I require your
immediate departure.
Nelly, fetch the men.
Cathy, this lamb of yours
threatens like a bull.
By God, Linton, I
am mortally sorry
you are not worth the
trouble of knocking down.
Heathcliff.
I wish you the joy of
this perfect coward, Cathy.
And I compliment you.
Catherine, remain
where you are.
After today's events, do
you intend on continuing
your intimacies
with Mr. Heathcliff?
Leave me alone.
Your cold blood cannot
be worked into a fever.
Your veins are
full of ice water.
Will you be with Heathcliff,
or will you be with me?
You cannot be his
friend and my wife.
I require you to choose.
Oh!
I require to be left alone, oh!
Catherine.
I'm going to die,
aren't I, Nelly?
You're not gonna die.
Heathcliff then,
he doesn't love me.
He never missed me.
I'm afraid of being alone.
You're not alone.
Oh, I need him not to wait
and to come straight
down off the moor.
Oh, let me have just one breath.
I will not.
No.
Why am I so changed?
In an instant, I was
converted into Miss Linton,
the lady of Thrushcross Grange.
I am
an exile, an outcast
from my world.
I wish I were our dogs.
I wish I were a girl again.
Savage and hardy.
Laughing at miseries.
Not maddening under them.
I should be myself if I
were among the heather.
Nelly, let me feel the wind!
No, ma'am, I will not let
you catch your death of cold.
No!
Look, there's my room,
with a candle in the window.
Heathcliff is waiting for me.
Heathcliff.
I dare you now.
Will you venture?
I shall not rest
until you are with me.
I never will.
He's considering.
He'd rather
I come to him.
Nelly, are you
mad? Shut the window.
Catherine.
Edgar, you are one of
those that is ever found
when you're least
wanted.
Am I nothing to you anymore?
Do you love that
wretch Heathcliff?
What you touch at
present, you may have,
but my soul will be that hilltop
before you lay your
hands on me again.
What you had of me is gone.
Her mind wanders, sir.
She's been talking
nonsense all night.
Send for Dr. Kenneth.
We must take precautions so
she doesn't harm herself.
Or the baby.
Isabella?
Sir?
It's from Miss Isabella.
Oh.
So what shall we do?
She left of her own accord.
Who the hell are you?
I was Isabella Linton.
We've met before, sir.
I've just married Heathcliff,
and he brought me here.
Heathcliff married you?
From now on, she is
my sister only by name.
Not because I disown her.
She has disowned me.
Where shall I sleep?
Heathcliff's bedroom
is up the stairs,
second door on the right.
Make sure to bolt the
door, Mrs. Heathcliff.
Why?
It's a great tempter to
a desperate man, is it not?
Every night, I try
to open his door.
If once I find it
unlocked, he's done for.
When the time comes,
all the angels in heaven
will not save him.
I'll warn him.
I don't give a damn if you do.
Wuthering Heights will be
mine, his gold will be mine,
and then his blood.
Hell can have your soul.
Nelly, how are
you this afternoon?
I've come to
see Miss Isabella.
Have you a letter for me?
I have nothing.
My master sends his love,
but he refuses to communicate
with this household ever again.
Sorry.
And how is Cathy?
Mrs. Linton gave birth to
a little girl last night.
She'll never be like she was.
Her life was spared.
What will he call her?
Catherine.
This young lady
looks sadly worse
for her change of condition.
Someone's love falls far
short in her case, obviously.
I should guess her own.
Under delusion, she pictured
me a hero of romance
and expected
unlimited indulgences
from my chivalrous devotion.
It was a marvelous
effort on her part
to discover that I
did not love her.
I've never in all my life met
with such an abject
thing as she.
She even disgraces
the name of Linton.
Take care, Nelly.
He means to provoke
Edgar past desperation.
I'll die first.
To your pleasure, I can imagine.
Or to see him dead.
Enough with the
providence. Out of my sight!
Nelly, I must see her.
I cannot allow that.
Cathy's delirious.
She slips in and
out of consciousness
and remembers very little.
She must call for me.
You know she has
not forgotten me.
For every thought
she spends on Linton,
she spends a thousand on me.
Nelly, am I to fight my way
through Edgar and
all his footmen?
Will you please be the friend
you always have
and let me see her?
Please.
Cathy.
How can I bear it?
You've broken my heart,
and now you come to me
as if you are the
one to be pitied.
I shall not pity you.
You killed me.
You tell me, how
many years do you
plan on living after I'm gone?
While you're
possessed of the devil
and speak to me in the
manner while you are dying,
you know those words
will be bred in my memory
while you are at peace.
I shall not be at peace!
I don't wish to torment you.
Come to me, Heathcliff.
Why did you betray
your own heart, Cathy?
You've killed yourself.
You.
You loved me.
Then what right had
you to leave me?
For the poor fancy
you felt for Linton?
This degradation and
misery and death,
nothing God or Satan could
inflict could part us.
You...
You of your own will did.
I have not broken
your heart, Cathy.
You have broken it.
And in breaking it
you have broken mine.
If I've done wrong,
I'm dying for it.
You left me too.
I forgive you.
Forgive me.
I love my murderer.
But yours, how can I?
I wish I'd told you.
But I cannot.
My master has
returned. You must leave.
Cathy, I must go.
No, no, you mustn't.
I must.
No, not for a minute.
No, no, don't leave me.
No, don't leave me.
Heathcliff, if
you stay it will be
your most diabolical deed.
What in God's name?
Unless you be a fiend,
you'll help her first.
Then you shall speak with me.
No!
Heathcliff!
What have you done to her?
Catherine!
She's dead. I've not
waited for you to learn that.
Don't you snivel
before me, damn you.
She wants none of your tears.
She is at peace now.
Did she die like a saint?
You poor wretch, your
pride can't blind God.
How did she die?
Her senses never
returned after you left.
She sank into a sleep.
Her life closed
in a gentle dream.
May she wake as kindly
in the next world.
May she wake in torment.
I pray one prayer,
and I'll repeat it
until my tongue stiffens.
Catherine Earnshaw, may you not
rest as long as I am living.
You say I killed
you. Haunt me then!
Be with me always! Take
any form, drive me mad!
As long as you don't leave me
in this abyss where
I cannot find you.
I cannot live without my life.
I cannot live without my soul!
I cannot live without
my soul.
I cannot live without my life.
Cathy!
No!
Do you believe such people
are happy in the other
world, Miss Dean?
Retracing the course
of Catherine Linton,
I fear we have no right
to believe she is.
But we'll leave that
to her and her maker.
To the surprise of
the whole parish,
Catherine's burial was neither
under the carved monuments
of the Lintons nor by the
tombs of her relations outside.
It was down on a green slope,
in a corner of the churchyard,
where the walls are so
low that the heather
climbs over from the
moors and buries it.
You and I have a great
debt to settle with him.
If neither of us were
cowards, we could combine.
He's leaving me...
Are you as soft
as your brother?
Are you willing to
endure to the last
and not attempt repayment?
I'm weary of enduring.
He will be my ruin, and
you and your child's death,
not unless we get him first!
No, you mustn't hurt him.
No, Heathcliff, stop!
No, get off him. You
might kill him, stop it!
I couldn't kill him
Heathcliff, stop!
Let him go. Stop it!
I believe our
father gave me this.
If God gave me the
strength to strangle you,
I'd go to hell with joy.
Isn't it enough you've
already murdered his sister?
Everybody knows she'd still be
living if it weren't for you.
So why don't you go
lay over her grave
like an old, faithful dog?
Surely the world isn't
worth living in now, is it?
Heathcliff.
Here you are.
Drink up.
Your brother
barely knew her too.
You clean him up.
Isabella, what
has happened to you?
Hindley is dead.
He fought Heathcliff true
to form, drunk as a lord,
and Heathcliff fought back.
I cannot live another
day with that villain.
I'm leaving for London,
and I've just come by
to see you and the
baby before I depart.
If my brother asks,
I permit you to tell
him where I've gone.
But do not tell Mr.
Heathcliff, will you promise?
I promise.
Give my love to my brother.
I'll write to you.
Godspeed.
Now, my bonny lad,
let's see if one tree
won't grow as crooked as another
with the same wind to twist it.
Hareton, who should
now be the first gentleman
in the neighborhood,
was reduced to a state
of complete dependence on
his father's inveterate enemy
and lives in his own
house as a servant.
The next 15 years, following
that dismal period,
were the happiest of my life.
Little Catherine
grew like a larch.
She was light and
fair like the Lintons,
but with the handsome
eyes of her mother.
Good morning, Papa.
Good morning,
Catherine, Nelly.
Morning, sir.
She had not been
beyond the grange by herself.
Wuthering Heights, and
Heathcliff, did not exist for her.
Oh.
Something wrong,
Miss Catherine?
Oh, no, I've just
a slight headache.
Would you like some tea?
Oh no, no. I'll just rest.
Catherine?
Sir?
Sir.
I'm afraid I'm quite lost.
Do you know where Thrushcross
Grange is from here?
You're Edgar Linton's
daughter, aren't you?
Yes, I am. Do
you know my father?
So to speak.
My name is Catherine.
What's yours?
Hareton.
I'm pleased to make
your acquaintance.
I'm afraid it's going to rain.
Do you live far from here?
Miss Catherine?
If your father had any notion
of you being at this house,
you'd be glad enough to get out.
It's your father's,
isn't it, Hareton?
No.
I thought you had
been the owner's son.
Are you a servant?
I'll see you damned
before I'd be your servant.
You'll see me what?
Damned.
How dare you speak
to me that way?
I'll tell my father
what you said.
Miss Catherine here knows
nothing about being civil.
Although Hareton's not your
master's son, he's your cousin.
My cousin?
Mm-hm.
Nelly, you must be mistaken.
My father has just gone to
fetch my cousin from London.
A gentleman's son.
People can have many
cousins of all sorts
without being the worse for it.
Miss Catherine.
Promise me you'll
look after him, Nelly.
You'll love him like your own.
Hareton.
We'll not
tell your father
that you went to
Wuthering Heights.
I cannot
understand why not.
Before your father departed,
did he or did he not
tell you to mind me?
Well, since you've deceived me
in your counterfeit sickness
to break your father's one
rule, perhaps you could repay me
by not telling him I
failed as your guardian.
I shan't whisper a word.
A letter
announced the day
of my master Edgar
Linton's return.
Catherine.
Papa.
Now, Catherine, your
cousin Linton is not
as strong or as
merry as you are.
He's just recently
lost his mother.
Isabella was dead.
Just don't expect him to
play and run about just yet.
And he
wrote to bid me get
mourning for his daughter.
Linton.
This is your cousin Catherine.
She's very fond of you already.
And arrange a room
and other accommodations
for his youthful nephew.
May I go to bed, Uncle.
A pale,
delicate, effeminate boy.
Nelly.
Good evening, Heathcliff.
What business brings
you here tonight?
I am here to see my son.
Master Linton has gone to bed
along with the rest
of the household.
And unless you have
something particular to say,
you may entrust
your message to me.
Who is it, Nelly?
I
have come for my son.
He may be your son,
but his mother desires
him to remain in my care.
His mother is dead.
How did you come to know that?
How I know is of no matter.
Surely as a magistrate
you will not keep a father
from caring for his only child.
Nelly will accompany Linton
to Wuthering Heights
in the morning.
He has just come
from a long journey,
and his health is
very precarious.
If you care for him at all,
which, with much regret
I doubt you do, you'll let
him sleep through the night.
Very well.
I look forward to seeing
you in the morning, Nelly.
Good evening.
Mr. Linton
commissioned me
to take the boy home early.
He was very reluctant
to be roused
from his bed at five o'clock,
and astonished to be informed
that he must prepare
for further traveling.
But I softened up the matter
by stating that he was going
to spend some time with
his father, Mr. Heathcliff,
who wished to see him very much.
It is truly worse
than I expected.
You are your mother's son.
Do you know me?
No.
You've heard of
me, I dare say.
No.
Hm, your mother was wicked
to leave you in ignorance
of the sort of
father you possessed.
I hope you'll be kind
to your son, Heathcliff.
He's the only kin in the
world you'll ever know.
Remember that.
I will be very kind to
him, Nelly, you needn't fear.
After all, my son is
the prospective owner
of Thrushcross Grange.
I shall not wish him
to die until I was
certain of being his successor.
That is the sole consideration
which I can endear, wealth.
Brought this for young Linton.
He won't need that.
Hm, the dainty chap
says he cannot eat it.
His mother was just the
same, just as hard to please.
Don't mention his
mother to me again,
and get him
something he can eat.
See, Nelly, all is fine.
Have a good afternoon.
On a beautiful
spring day, my young lady asked
to have a ramble on
the moor with me.
She was off like
a young greyhound.
Young lady.
And as I
toiled to follow,
she came upon Mr. Heathcliff.
I hope it's still my father's.
And who is your father?
Edgar Linton, owner
of Thrushcross Grange.
Do you know him?
Very well.
Miss Catherine?
Miss Catherine.
Is he your son?
No, but I do have one.
And you've met him before.
My house is just over the hill.
Perhaps you would
like to come to tea.
Catherine, you are to
come with me at once.
I will not.
This man has just
invited me to tea
and said that I know his son.
I'm sure he's mistaken,
but what an adventure.
Heathcliff, my master
will hate me if he found out
I allowed her to
enter your house.
I will be blamed for your
devious design and discharged.
My design is as
honest as possible.
I wish for the two cousins
to fall in love and marry.
And you needn't worry about
your job at the Grange.
There's always a position
for you at Wuthering Heights.
Oh, it's so lovely.
Now, do you know who that is?
Your son?
Linton, it's Linton!
Oh, you have very much changed.
And you must be my uncle then!
Why don't you come and visit
us at the Grange with Linton?
To think, all these years
such close neighbors
and to never visit us.
I visited once or twice
before you were born.
But your father and I quarreled
at one time in our lives.
Why did you quarrel?
He felt me too poor
to marry your sister,
and was grieved to learn
that I had won her.
His pride was hurt, and
he had never forgiven it.
Well Linton and I have
no share in your quarrel.
If Papa will not
let me come here,
then Linton must
come to the Grange.
To walk four
miles would kill me.
Please, come here,
Miss Catherine.
Not every morning but
once or twice a week.
Linton, have you nothing
to show your cousin?
Take her to the garden.
Oh, that sounds lovely.
Wouldn't you rather sit here?
If
that's what you prefer.
I'll take you to the garden.
Very well.
Behave like a
gentleman, mind you.
And take your hands
out of your pockets.
Get up, you interloper.
Now you've got a rival for
your cousin's affections.
What does that name mean?
Some damnable writing.
I can't read it.
I can read.
I want to know why it's there.
He does not know
his letters.
Could you believe in the existence
of such a colossal dunce?
Has anyone attempted
to teach him?
Or is he simple?
Please, there is nothing
the matter but laziness.
Is there, Earnshaw?
My cousin fancies you,
an idiot, Earnshaw.
If you weren't more
a lass than a lad,
I'd fell you this minute.
Nelly, you recollect
me at this age.
Did I ever look so stupid?
Worse, because you
were more sullen.
I would have
loved the lad had he been
someone else's, but I am sure
he is safe from her love.
Hindley would have been proud
of his son, wouldn't he?
Almost as proud as I am of mine.
Oh, Papa, I saw
Linton the other day,
at Wuthering Heights.
I met my uncle, too.
Why didn't you tell me
that Linton was nearby?
Catherine, you know why I kept
Linton's residence from you.
Is it because you
dislike Mr. Heathcliff?
No, not because I
dislike Mr. Heathcliff.
It's because Mr.
Heathcliff dislikes me.
Catherine, you
must listen to me.
He is the most diabolical
man, looking to wrong and ruin
those he hates given the
slightest opportunity.
I knew that you could not
keep acquaintance with Linton
without coming into contact
with Mr. Heathcliff.
But Mr. Heathcliff
was very cordial, Papa.
He didn't object to Linton
and I seeing each other.
But I do object, Catherine.
My reasons you would
not understand.
You mother may still be
alive if it were not for him.
I will not see the
last person I love
in this world
suffer at his hand.
You are to stay away
from Wuthering Heights.
Dearest Catherine,
ever since I last
looked on to your face,
I have been able to
think of little else.
I would gladly think
of nothing else.
However, my memory
cannot compare
to your true form.
I am still not well enough to
make the trek to the Grange.
To understand this
world, to keep one's faith
in its deep meaning, to
reconcile the existence
of God to the existence of evil.
How should we picture heaven?
You
must find a way to defy
Uncle Edgar and see me
here, at the Heights.
How long have you been going
to Wuthering Heights,
Miss Catherine?
In a rustling green tree,
with bright white clouds,
and birds of all sorts
pouring music in at all sides.
Only a little while.
And it's only because Linton
is too ill to travel here.
You should not
be risking so much
to simply visit
with your cousin.
Nelly, I love him.
How should you picture heaven?
This, warm by
the fire, with you.
You've seen Linton but a
handful of times in your life.
He has the worst bit of
sickly slip that ever
struggled into his teens,
and I'm glad you have
no chance of having
him for a husband.
I will see him again.
If I had my
father's permission,
I'd spend half of
my time with you.
After Papa, I love you
better than anyone.
You'd love me better than him
and all the world,
if you were my wife.
What are you laughing at?
People often hate their wives.
You are false.
Your father hated his wife.
Why do you say such a thing?
Your mother hated your
father, and loved his.
You liar!
You cruel-hearted fiend.
I will not remain another
moment in your company.
No, no.
Catherine, please don't leave.
You will come back, won't you?
Only if he's not here.
Your father's getting
worse by the day.
If he knew about your trysts,
it probably would kill him.
Stop this for his sake,
if not for your own.
With all my love, Linton.
Oh, Linton, I'm so sorry it
took me so long to get here.
I had to read my
father to sleep.
Good evening, Catherine.
It's been so long
since you've graced
my house with your presence.
My father is very ill.
The rumor goes he
is on his deathbed.
Is that an exaggeration?
I'm afraid not.
Well perhaps I can
console you with a gift.
I give you what I have.
It is hardly worth accepting,
but all that I have
to give you is my son.
What?
Father wants us to be married.
He knows Uncle Edgar
will not approve,
but he is wary of my dying.
Thus, we have to be
married in the morning,
and you can return to the
Grange in the morning.
I'm not afraid of you.
Give me the key.
Oh, you're not afraid of me.
Your courage is well disguised.
I'm afraid now,
because if I stay here
my father will be miserable.
Please, let me go home.
I promise to marry your son
tomorrow if you let me go now.
I'll make sure you'll
keep your promise.
You will not leave this
house till I am your father.
The only father that you
will have in a few days.
At least send word to let
my father know I'm safe.
His happiest days were
over when yours began.
He cursed the day you
came into this world.
I did at least.
Heathcliff, you
are a cruel man,
but you are not a fiend.
If Father were to die
before I returned,
how could I bear to
live with myself?
I'm going to kneel here
until you look at me.
Please.
Have you never loved anybody
in all your life, Uncle?
Ever?
Get your fingers off of me.
I detest you.
Hareton, please, tell
my father where I am.
Please?
Father.
Catherine.
Where have you been?
Out on the moors.
But I'm here now.
I'm here.
Well I can go to her now.
I love you.
I've come to fetch you home
to Wuthering Heights now.
Her father just died.
Is there no end to your cruelty?
I am seeking a tenant
now for this house,
and I want my children about me.
I can give you till morning.
Heathcliff, no.
I'll go, Nelly.
Linton is all I have to
love in the world now.
I know he has a simple nature,
but I know he loves me, and
for that reason I love him.
Mr. Heathcliff, you
have nobody to love you,
and however miserable you make
us, we will have the revenge
of knowing that cruelty
arises from your great misery.
Heathcliff.
Linton is dead.
How do you feel?
He's safe, and I'm free.
I should feel glad, but you
have left me so long to struggle
against death alone, now
I feel and see only death.
Here is Linton's will.
As you can see, he has
bequeathed all that was his
and all that had
been yours to me.
The Grange is mine.
Catherine stayed
in bed a fortnight.
When Mr. Heathcliff was
unsuccessful at finding a tenant
for the Grange, I offered my
services at Wuthering Heights.
Not even that would stir
my mistress from her bed.
And that brings us to now.
It is a remarkable tale.
I shall never forget it.
Now get some sleep, sir.
Quite all right.
I must collect my thoughts.
Oh, it is morning.
We've talked all
through the night.
I'll be going back
to the Grange now.
I must rid myself
of this awful place.
Thank you, Miss Dean, for the
accommodation and the insight.
I do wish there was more.
It's good to see
you, Miss Catherine.
Are you feeling any better?
I suppose.
I found some of
your mother's books.
Would you like to
read one to us?
I am well aware that some
people now begin to doubt
about witchcraft or, at
any rate, feign to do so.
How dare you touch
me? Get away from me!
I despise you.
I would have given my
life for one kind word
when you were my jailer,
but you kept off.
I asked Mr. Heathcliff...
Be silent!
I would rather be anywhere
than hear your detestable
voice in my ear.
Continual, continuous streef.
Str, strife, strife.
No, no.
Stay out of that room.
Strife.
He's just like the cart
horse, isn't he, Nelly?
He does his work,
he eats his food,
and sleeps eternally.
Do you ever dream, Hareton?
Hareton, can you hear me?
Go to the devil,
and let me be.
I have found that I want
and am glad to be your cousin.
Well I shall have
nothing to do with you
and your mucky pride
and damn mocking tricks.
I'll go to hell, body and soul,
before I look
sideways at you again.
You should be friends
with your cousin.
- Friends?
- Mm-hm.
When she hates me and thinks
me not fit to wipe her boots?
It is not I who hates
you. It is you who hates me.
You hate me as much as
Mr. Heathcliff does.
You're a damn liar.
Why have I made him angry then
by taking your part 100 times?
I didn't know
you took my part.
I was miserable and
bitter at everyone, but
now I thank you.
And ask you to forgive me.
Catherine.
What should I
have done, Nelly?
He wouldn't shake my hand,
and he wouldn't look.
Nelly, since Hareton
won't speak to me,
can you tell him that,
if he takes this book,
I'll teach him to read it?
And if he refuses
it, I'll go upstairs
and never tease him again.
Hareton.
You'll be ashamed of me
every day of your life,
and more ashamed the
more you know me.
So you won't be my friend?
I thought I had cured
you of your laughing.
It was me.
Mr. Heathcliff, might I
plant a small flower garden
on the north side of the house?
No.
She already has.
What is your
grievance, Joseph?
Her and Hareton, they pulled
up three of my fine firs.
She's bewitched the lad with
bold eyes and forward ways.
Pull the flowers up.
How can you begrudge
me a few yards of earth
when you have taken all my land?
Your land? You insolent slut.
You never had any.
And my money.
Enough.
And Hareton's land and money.
If you strike me,
Hareton will strike you,
so you might as well sit down.
Don't intend to
rouse him against me.
You should avoid putting
me into a passion.
Take her out of my sight.
Why don't you eat, Papa?
Go.
I don't know how you can
stand to be away from her.
Go, please.
Please.
Leave me.
Heathcliff.
It is a poor conclusion,
is it not, Nelly?
My old enemies
have not beaten me,
and now is the precise time
to revenge myself
on their children.
I could do it, and no
one could hinder me.
Where's the use?
I have lost the sense
of their destruction.
Want a cup of tea?
There is a strange
change, Nelly.
In every tree, in every cloud,
filling the air at night
and caught by glimpses
in every object by day.
I am surrounded by her image.
The most ordinary faces
mock me with resemblance.
The entire world is
a dreadful memorandum
that she did exist
and I have lost her.
I cannot continue in
this condition, Cathy.
I have a single wish,
and my entire being is
yearning to attain it.
I have yearned for so
long and so unwaveringly
that I am convinced
it must be reached
because it has
devoured my existence.
It has been long flight,
and I wish it were over.
Heathcliff.
Whereas the
contrary brings bliss
and is a pattern
of celestial peace.
To you, I've made myself
worse than the devil.
Morning, Heathcliff.
Heathcliff?
Joseph.
Joseph!
Hareton!
And still, I don't like
being by myself in this house.
I cannot help it.
I should be glad
when they leave it
and shift over to the Grange.
Hareton and Catherine are
going to the Grange then?
Aye, as soon as they're
married on New Year's Day.
Since you're
vacating the Grange,
there's no use for you
staying in this dreary house.
Who would live here then?
Joseph will take
care of the house,
but the rest of it
will be shut up.
For the use of such ghosts
that choose to inhabit it.
Nay.
I believe the dead
are at last at peace.
They are afraid of nothing.
Together, they would brave
Satan and all his legion.
I wonder how anyone can
imagine unquiet slumbers
for the sleepers in
that quiet earth.