Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
NETFLIX PRESENTS
HERE WE ARE READY FOR ANOTHER YEAR
SILVER FOREVER
EMANUELA MACCARINI
THREE MONTHS EARLIER
BERGAMO
TWO DAYS LATER
THAT'S ENOUGH
Prosecutor Ruggeri!
NSD
NOT ONLY DANCE
PARMA
R.I.S. CENTRAL HEADQUARTERS
ROME, A YEAR LATER
FORENSIC POLICE CENTRAL HEADQUARTERS
GORNO (BERGAMO)
A YEAR AND FOUR MONTHS AFTER FINDING YARA
REST IN PEACE
BERGAMO, APRIL 2013
ONE MONTH TO THE CASE FILING
BEAUTY SALON TANNING SHOP
JULY 2015
FOUR YEARS AND EIGHT MONTHS
AFTER YARA'S DISAPPEARANCE
JUNE 2016
LAST DAYS OF HEARING
WE ARE ALL EQUAL BEFORE THE LAW
July 17th, 2017, the Court of Appeal
confirms the guilty verdict.
October 12th, 2018,
the Supreme Court confirms
Massimo Bossetti's guilty verdict.
Despite the rulings, Massimo Bossetti
never ceased to proclaim his innocence.
November 2019, Bossetti's defense
requests access to the findings
for new evaluations,
but the motion is rejected.
January 11th, 2021, the Supreme Court
orders the Assize Court of Bergamo
to schedule a hearing
to analyze the findings.
June 3rd, 2021,
the Assize Court of Bergamo
rejects Bossetti's defense request
to access the findings.
Subtitle translation by: Angelica Lacetera