You think young people
between 16 and 20 years
They convert automatically
In criminals
After making a couple of mistakes.
You agree with that.
No, I agree
With what the law says.
Do you know there are 300 parasites
What do they live in our body?
Prisoners of 10 or 20 years ...
-All will you help discipline?
- At least let me piss!
Sodchimeg namsrai,
One year and four months in prison
for repeated cases
of human beings,
get others to prostitute themselves,
Mortgage and harassment execution.
Menen Khangai,
arrested several times
for their repeated
robbery cases,
He entered voluntarily
In the workfield
For a year.
TSENGEL SERGELENBAATAR,
inmate number 1037,
born in Ulán Bator in 1998,
25 years,
full secondary education,
abandoned the 8th grade.
Unemployed,
Computer engineer by profession.
Involved in drug cases,
bets, etc.,
specialized in online crimes,
has signed to be rehabilitated
For 1 year
In the workfield
at your own request.
Namuun and Namulan Batdoj.
Have been sent to the field
for a year and a half
For murders, assaults,
crimes with violence
and group aggressions.
Tsegts Narantuya,
inmate number 1025,
born in Ulán Bator in 1998,
male, 25 years,
full secondary education,
single,
unemployed, psychologist,
He even worked like
military psychologist
Repeatedly associated with the
Alcohol, tried to commit suicide.
A bad example for society,
and has also signed
For a year of correctional service
In our field.
Hopefully they do it.
Uyanga Gunsambuu ...
Careful!
And his brother, Ibra.
They were born in 1998 and
1999 in Ulán Bator.
Secondary education ended
In Mongolia
and they attended higher studies
abroad.
Your higher education includes
Master in Fraud
and deception at a higher level.
These brothers
They are professional scammers.
Have signed for their own will
A rehabilitation program
one year in our field.
Hello, everyone.
Good morning, sir.
Step to expose internal policy
To all newcomers.
First of all,
The fights
and any other physical contact
Among the inmates will be
strictly prohibited.
In second place,
They will only leave the job
after having obtained
permission to do so.
Third,
They must follow and attend all
organized activities
With no excuse.
Fourth,
They will not abandon the facilities
After the curfew.
Fifth,
The inmates
They can't ask questions.
Sixth,
They must fulfill all orders.
Inmate 1025,
Iza the flag ...
I didn't sign this shit.
I will raise it.
I can do it, I'll raise it.
- I can do it.
- Raise.
I can do it.
Field 3 policy,
Any task given
For the officers
It will be executed promptly.
Or, they will take strict
disciplinary measures.
Take it, three days of cell.
Eh, let me down!
Lift me! Hey!
Any questions?
Serve the dinner and put them to work.
Attention!
Right!
And underway.
Finish.
Above.
I wanted you to eat,
Not that you will play music.
It seems that you are not hungry, right?
Guards, sit down.
The others were and put yourself in a row.
If you can't eat as humans,
You will do it as dogs.
What stupidity.
Return to your position 1030,
Or do you want ...
Life here?
A warning.
Who violates the rules twice,
You will receive two warnings.
From the third,
The arrest period
It will extend a month.
With each warning,
The disciplinary arrests
They will be at the same time.
Is it clear?
Well...
You can eat.
Good puppy.
Finish.
Above!
The men on the left,
The women to the right.
Good. Under way.
It's cold.
Have enough firewood.
Understood.
Watch those who have been challenging
this afternoon.
Do not let them cause problems.
The authorities
They are mired in chaos.
This girl can be the cause.
Retire yourself.
Good.
Wake up!
Fuck!
Where is?
High!
Attention. In row.
Enjoying the outdoors?
Standing.
Come on.
Damn Imbécil.
You have ruined my bet.
We have three fugitives the first day.
It is a good start.
Take it to the outer cell.
I think you've already seen
That there are no fences.
If you think you can escape,
Try it.
The inmate Z103
has broken internal policy
for the failed attempt to escape.
Therefore,
You will all be punished.
For their actions you will all assume
responsibility.
There will be no dinner tonight.
Do you agree?
Attentive.
To the right.
And underway.
One...
Two...
Why do you tremble?
Triangle...
Sun...
car...
12.
Good job.
I'm sick?
Am I going to die?
By no means.
You are here to save many lives.
Take.
We will do some tests,
that's all.
Are you OK?
Our tortolites have returned
of your honeymoon.
You look good.
Discipline feels good to you.
Inmate 1025,
Iza the flag.
Good puppy.
Ibra?
- That?
- What is Tsengel doing?
I guess you have decided
get along with tairdas.
- Good...
- OK.
Liars,
thieves, frauds,
drug addicts, suicides,
prostitutes,
mafia.
Congratulations to all young people
with talent
that were skilled in their trades
And I wish you much success
In his brilliant future.
Have you finished?
Yeah.
You no longer have anything to hide
to each other.
So,
I give you 30 minutes of rest.
You can relax,
Go to the bathroom,
Smoking a cigarette.
Foolishness.
Who tries to hide anything?
Everyone has a dark past.
You can't escape him.
Let's smoke while we have
The opportunity.
Hey...
Everything will go well.
Inga Look.
Listen.
Whatever happens,
We must remain alive.
If we do it well ...
It's not that.
Whatever happens,
We have to face it.
- Do you remember?
- Yes of course.
What do we do?
Whenever
They can catch us.
We will leave everyone behind.
It doesn't matter, whoever is.
Well, be strong.
Hey.
Do you want to get out of here?
We go inside.
Wouldn't it be better to observe
For a few days?
Hey,
I don't want to stay here for more days,
Even hours are unbearable.
If we are brave
We can get out of here.
We have to do it now.
The longer we stay here
more we will be under your control,
physically and emotionally.
That's how it is.
We have to escape as soon as possible.
We will be weaker over time.
If you don't join us,
Do not set in trouble.
It will be better to leave tomorrow.
Inga will not last long here.
Have you not won yourself yet?
Do you know what happens ...
At the end of the game?
It doesn't matter...
If he is king
or pawn,
If you have won or lost,
All the pieces go to the same box.
A pawn ...
can become queen,
But never in king.
Compare yourself.
Open.
Seems...
that you have forgotten who you have been
And thanks to who you are here.
Compare yourself!
Son of a bitch.
Go away.
The prisoners are not them.
Eh, what are you doing?
There are two men in a car,
They have entered the basement
With the supervisor.
Who cares?
Duémete.
It separates that.
Who are they?
I don't know, Lord.
They have passed with identifications
of the Secret Service.
Tairdas comes.
Tairdas, tairdas.
Get up and dress.
Hurry up.
Ibra.
What will you do with him?
I'm not sure.
Is the mammon selling us?
Let's escape now.
Leave. Fuck.
I already have enough torture.
We should not have explained
Our plans
To that son of a bitch.
Come on, come on, come on!
Fast brings together
and continue fire immediately.
Come on.
Come, come!
Fast!
Shit, shit!
In the truck.
The key is in the truck.
Come on, come on, come on!
Come, here. Come on.
Runs!
Fuck.
No!
What pussy is happening?
No idea.
- What is all this?
- Silence!
- Alright?
- I think so.
Eh, guys, look!
Is it a truck?
I think so.
Come on.
Okay, well, wait here.
We will check it.
Well, come on.
Wait.
Hurry up!
Run, run ...
To the camp.
Hurry up. Enter.
Callad.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Go ahead.
For.
Good puppy.
Get up.
What have you done?
I have broken the key of the truck.
Hey.
Go for strings.
What pussy is happening here?
What are those things?
I don't know much either.
He will know.
Bastard!
It was an emergency level 5.
What is a level 5 emergency?
I don't know very well either.
In that basement, they do experiments.
But something has changed,
Now all those people ...
It appears frequently.
They brought a girl,
And this has happened.
Zombies ...
That...?
Zombies, were zombies,
Don't you understand?
I understand,
But it is difficult to process.
You have seen it.
Yes, that's why I tell you they were zombies.
Very good, listen,
Now we have to rest.
Where?
Enter there.
Bastard.
You took Tsengel to the basement.
Let's make shifts to monitor.
I will start.
Rest.
You are the next.
Hey, don't lose sight of him.
Tomorrow we will go to the arms warehouse.
You know how to use them, right?
It will be better that you
Forget your weapons.
The supervisor kept the bullets
In its safe.
We should check the basement.
Something happens there.
I don't know anymore.
I'm going to bed.
Well, be careful.
It is the worst day of my life.
Shouldn't you sleep?
I'm not well.
I can't believe ...
What is happening.
Me neither.
It's just a virus, right?
That means
That there should be an antidote.
Don't you think?
Don't know.
But we have to stay alive.
Can I ask you something?
Clear.
Are you kind to me
To be able to escape from here?
Have we escaped?
Don't take everything so seriously.
Well, if you're not tired, I'm leaving.
Hurry up.
Silence, silence, silence.
- Namule, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
We thought you had died.
Are you OK?
Are you injured?
We finally leave the forest.
Are you OK?
Are you okay?
Those ... things ...
- were...
- Zombies.
Well, let's see.
We don't know how long
We can stay here.
So we have to go
immediately.
Yeah.
Those cars may work.
Hey!
Huh, wake up.
Do they work?
It seems not.
But there is a car elsewhere.
Is there another camp?
How far?
Where?
First give me water.
There are several camps.
There is one close.
Now it's your turn.
Bold,
The other truck is on the road,
TRUE?
The key has been broken.
Oh Shit...
Will it start manually?
Ought.
Should, right?
Hey. Do you know where to go?
I also had blindfolds
When I arrived.
I am not sure of the way.
Oh...
Only you know the exit,
You will have to come with us, right?
Do you have more options?
Or you can stay here and die.
I will not go with him.
It is better to die.
Whatever you want...
Fuck,
He has not bitten me.
Let me see.
It has scratched you.
Fuck!
Shit...
And now what do we do?
- Bad luck.
- Eh, h.
- For, uncle.
- Get out!
Undone of him.
There is no other way.
Or get rid of you.
Hey, this time he is right.
- You have to do it.
- No, for, uncle. Let's wait a little.
What do you want to do?
Hey! What do you want to do?
The more time I stay,
More dangerous will be for us.
Fuck.
I don't know. Come on.
Let them and sit down.
If we don't go,
We will all die here.
- Where to?
- To the truck.
Listen to me.
Do not stop, if they catch one,
Do not try to save it.
Understood? Come, come on.
Fuck,
I had to go to piss.
Where are we going?
Fast. Over there.
Come on.
- Forget about him. Let him leave.
- Come on!
Come on, hurry up.
Come on.
Look at me.
You? What are you doing?
You have no right,
The girl is the only vaccine that
exists. Don't you understand?
What a shit.
- Namuun! No!
- Leave it. Come on.
Careful.
Inga, take the steering wheel.
Ibra!
Do what we have said.
Don't be silly, I can help you.
Over it, Ibra!
Ibra!
Hey!
- Brother...!
- Go back and look for me.
Ibra!
I have done it.
Fumas?
No, thanks.
I don't feel like smoking.
What happened to you?
There was zombies in the truck ...
And we separate.
We have lost Namuun ...
also.
And now ... where are we going?
Don't know.
We do not know the way.
It is already obscuring.
What if we go to the camp?
Inga took the car.
That?
Because?
Need to save
Your own ass, right?
Do you realize?
It was obvious,
The brothers planned something.
A woman can become
In pure evil.
I am cold and hungry.
Well ... come on.
Yeah.
Depart.
Field calls
- Who is it?
- Open the door.
Open.
Do you have water?
Sit.
Have you found it?
That...?
The map,
You have found it.
There are several places like this.
What are you talking about?
What places?
Follow me.
I want to show you something.
This experiment
It started two years ago.
At first nobody knew
The purpose of the experiment,
It was just a deadly disease.
Some time ago,
Several scientists discovered
The virus when they were investigating
a certain parasite in
The human body,
And how those parasites
are capable of affecting
The behavior
human and the brain.
Then they performed
A broad experiment
To create an antidote
Against the virus.
Finally achieved it,
They created the first vaccine.
They keep the experiment
In our facilities.
The first vaccine trial
It was a success in Enkhjin.
They planned to experiment
The vaccine in you,
But they lost control of the virus.
It is a disease.
What kind?
It is not, they are zombies.
Be a zombie or not,
We lost control.
Enkhjin is the first
and only vaccine we had.
But that tairdas bastard
He has taken it.
Does it know everything
From the beginning?
I didn't tell you that I knew it, right?
He was even one of
The key people
in charge of all this,
He and the supervisor.
I have nothing to do with this.
Believe me.
We can't let ...
Have the girl.
Well, come on.
Where to?
To field number 2.
Tairdas must be there.
I stay here.
I will not go.
There is no guarantee
to stay alive if we leave.
But please
Call someone and bring help.
I beg you.
Be careful.
Field number 2.
Oh...
What change.
Inga is one of those women
They are pure evil.
At least I am not
evil like her.
Well,
How are you, guys?
I hope you are so generous
As to feed him
To an old friend.
Eat ...
We will follow our path.
And the girl?
He stays with me.
She take her.
Because?
Do you want to stay like a hero?
It will come with me.
Or none will leave here.
What field?
To field number 1?
Or to field number 7?
Oh.
That?
Do you want to go without me?
Bastor!
Brother...
Wasn't you who left us behind?
Sit.
It seems that you have some grudge
Towards me, little brother.
What's happening?
You are alive, right?
Me too.
It is good that you brought it.
Okay. Alright.
I let you go this time.
If you don't want, you can rot here.
Enter. Fast.
Where is Tsegts?
Tsegts?
Leave it. Think of you.
- Be still.
- What are you saying?
Am I human or not?
When I came for the first time,
Aunt yours said she would save lives.
So why do we leave them behind?
I want to save people.
If I'm not human,
Please let me out here.
I'm tired.
Inga!
We can save at least
A person please.
If we survive this,
What do we differentiate
of our past?
Are you sure?
I am.
Damn zombies.
Take the steering wheel.
I let the zombies out
And I gave your friend.
And now what?
What are you going to do about it?
Have you ever killed someone?
Can you do it?
Shoot!
They are your zombies, take care of yourself.
Tsegts,
You should not trust anyone.
Trust yourself.
Idiot.
To the car, come on, climb to the car.
Come on, go up.
Run, come on.
Leave it, leave it.
Look for us again.
Namulan! Namulen, no!
Namulen, no!
What a shit day!
Comes back...
and find us!
- Who are you?
- It's me, it's me.
Relax.
You are alive.
Yes, I try to survive.
Well, let's try to survive together.